Nice
(South France)
Barbara, how would you like a Moscow Mule?
Thank you, Michael.
Fritz, I've brought you some juice
Fritz, say thank you to your dad.
Thanks, Mister.
Fritz!
It can't be helped.
He'll gradually warm up to me,
just like how I'll have to get
used to this new art business.
It's all just so sudden for me...
Being able to live in this wonderful mansion,
having such a kind husband
to make me delicious cocktails...
Hey, do you feel anything?
Huh?
From the neighbor's house.
It feels like we were being watched from
the second-floor window over there.
You know that there's no one living there.
I know, but...
To tell the truth, I heard from Mrs. d'Autrey...
About what?
The neighbors, the husband and wife,
were killed twenty years ago.
Ever since then, ghosts appear in that house.
What's wrong, Michael?
Don't tell me you believe that crazy story!
N-No way!
Are you going out?
Yes.
I'll get the car.
Don't worry about it.
I want us to go out, just as
a family, every once in a while.
We don't need a bodyguard.
I see. That way, Fritz will
warm up to you faster.
Yep. That's what I'm aiming for.
Good luck, Mr. Dad.
Shall we go?
Happy Holidays
What are the results of your investigation, Detective?
I'll start with Dr. Tenma.
The police are after him because he's a suspect
for the murder of a married couple,
but there hasn't been any trace of him.
When he was called back by the
police, this is what Tenma said:
A boy whose life he saved ten years ago
killed three people and escaped.
The victims included the director
of Eisler Memorial Hospital.
The boy's name was Johan.
The boy appeared in front of him as an adult
and committed another murder right before his eyes.
Next, I'll tell you about Nina Fortner.
She is the daughter of the murdered couple.
Her whereabouts are currently unknown.
This is Mr. Messner.
He made it all the way to Frankfurt, as ordered.
Where is he now?
He's dead.
He was recklessly stabbed two months ago.
He was involved in a drug deal that went bad.
Back when I was in the force,
Messner was my partner.
I see.
He was dismissed on drug charges.
The man who saved him after
that incident was "The Baby."
He was an influential man in an extremist group.
What happened?
There was an incident in Frankfurt where
fire was set to the Turkish quarters.
The rumor is that the man behind it was "The Baby."
They say that a certain Asian
man put out the flames.
The name of that man was Tenma.
Could it be that... it was our Dr. Tenma?
It is said that the arson that
"The Baby" was involved with
was a ceremony to welcome a certain man whom they
were trying to make their organization's leader.
A certain man?
What was the name of the boy that Dr. Tenma saved?
Johan.
The name of the man whom "The Baby" was
trying to get as their leader... was Johan.
So that's where you're going to move.
Roberto... My life is just like that pawn.
What's wrong? Is something on your mind?
Until I got that one phone call, everything
in my life was a failure.
My partner Messner and I had gotten our
hands dirty selling confiscated drugs.
The person on the phone knew everything.
If I wanted him to keep quiet, I
had to kill that married couple.
The Fortners in Heidelberg...
We'd be safe if we killed them.
There was another person in the house that night.
He was a newspaper reporter or something.
Messner and I killed all three of them.
After that, we received a lot of money.
I was picked up by a syndicate
after I quit the force.
I was immediately placed in a good position.
The money I made was easily laundered.
Then you met your wife and washed
your hands clean of that business.
I wonder why I was able to
leave the syndicate that easily.
Who was on the phone that one time?
When we received all that money,
who was controlling my life?
Roberto, I'm grateful to you.
You've always protected me.
Then could you take back that last move?
Huh?
I can't do that!
You're strict!
I'll be back, dear.
Right. Take care.
Buy me toys!
Say goodbye to your dad.
It's useless. He's only thinking
about toys right now.
I'll be back, Dad.
Goodbye!
Roberto, has the detective called?
He should be here by now.
Roberto.
Roberto, the detective's been hurt!
Come quick!
Roberto!
Who are you?
I'm the daughter of the couple
you killed, Nina Fortner.
Did you kill him?
Roberto!
The one who killed him was
your bodyguard, Roberto!
Roberto did it?
I saw it from the house next door.
That can't be. Roberto is my
friend. I can trust him.
You... you've come to get your revenge on me!
Roberto... Roberto!
I'm taking this bag.
If you want to stay here, go ahead.
A person like you has no one to trust.
What's wrong, Mr. Mueller?
Mr. Mueller?
Start the car.
Hurry!
You've been watching me from that
house for quite a while now.
What do you want from me?
I hate you from the bottom of my heart.
I hate you enough to kill you!
I... I was blackmailed.
If I didn't kill your parents, they would
have found out that I was selling drugs.
Messner and I didn't have a choice.
We had no choice!
You didn't have a choice?
You didn't...  have a choice?
Stop!
Stop the car!
They were wonderful people.
Truly wonderful...
My mother and father loved
me with all their hearts.
W-Wait!
I wasn't even their real daughter!
But Mom and Dad truly... truly...
Stop! Please, don't!
Despite all of that, they were
killed by scum like you!
Barbara...
Fritz...
Barbara... Fritz...
What? What are you saying?
What's wrong with you?
This is what it feels like...
to be killed...
Fritz... He called me "Dad" for the first time.
I don't want to lose it.
I've found something I don't want to lose.
Barbara... Fritz...
Düsseldorf... Every day at 8:30 at that café.
I was ordered there every day after
I joined the organization.
I was ordered to look very
clean-cut, just like a salaryman.
Every day, a mother and her child would pass by.
That was my only contact with everyday life.
H-Hi there. Good morning.
Good morning.
What did you hire that detective for?
To find you, Tenma, and my partner
from when I was a police officer...
but Messner is dead.
I heard he was killed.
I was having a more detailed search done.
I got a call from the detective last night.
I have something unusual for you.
Something unusual?
Yes.
Messner was a heavy junkie who was in no condition
to get involved with some syndicate.
The killer wasn't from the Frankfurt syndicate.
He's from Düsseldorf.
Düsseldorf?
I'll give you the details when I see you.
Here it is.
It's scribbled on a piece of scrap paper.
"Messner's case."
"The perpetrator."
"Who is Roberto?"
Do you know what this means?
Hello.
I want the bag back.
R-Roberto!
Your wife and Fritz are relaxing right next to me.
Wh-What did you say?
Let my wife go!
You should come back soon... to your "Happy Home."
Your gun.
Could you lend me your gun?
You can only use it at close range,
and it only has four bullets.
It's good enough.
I was a police officer.
Be careful.
You want me to be careful so that I'll go
confess to the police after this, right?
That's right. You'd better not die.
I'll cover you from the house next door.
Dad!
Fritz?
Look, Dad! It's a fishing rod.
That kid! He's not going to rest until
he gets you to take him fishing.
Barbara.
Where's Roberto?
Oh, yeah.
Some of his friends from the security company
are here. It looks like something happened.
Friends?
Don't worry.
There wasn't any damage.
Roberto, Michael is back.
Don't worry. There's just one broken window.
It must have been some
kids in the neighborhood.
There's nothing to worry about.
Wh-Where's the body...?
The body of the detective that was here...
There never was anything here.
Roberto... Who are you?
The madam and Fritz will be here.
Now don't cause a fuss.
Here.
Good.
In truth, nothing happened.
Today was a peaceful day,
and it will be from now on.
Nina!
Nina...
She was a beautiful girl.
What did you do with Nina?
We're treating her with courtesy.
She's quite special to a certain someone.
A certain someone?
That boy's name was Johan.
Johan, Johan, Johan! What's with this Johan?
Who are you people?
We want you to live happily with
the madam and Fritz.
Let's just leave it at that.
Just like that.
Thank you for your patronage.
I'll be leaving now.
What are you going to do to Nina?
Are you going to kill her?
Live happily.
Dad, when are you going to take me fishing?
Hmm...?
Tomorrow, if it's sunny.
Hooray!
I don't see ghosts anymore.
You have nice eyes. You and
Johan look very much alike.
When can I see Johan?
I came peacefully because you
said you'd let me meet Johan.
He wants to see you, too.
Where is he?
He lives happily in Munich.
Munich...?
You have really nice eyes.
Such a shame...
Well, take care of the rest.
Dr. Tenma?
Why...?
Why did you come here?
I told you. I used to be a police officer.
We'll be at your house soon.
I promised Fritz I'd take
him fishing tomorrow.
I see.
I hope it'll be sunny.
It'll definitely be sunny.
Lunge's Trap