You look well.
I am.
How's work?
Is it going well?
Yes.
That's good to hear.
Is Rosemary doing well?
She is.
She has lots of friends.
I see. That's great.
That's great.
So she's getting used to school.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but I have to be going now.
I've brought a picture of Rosemary.
Can I see her?
How about it? We'll meet right here.
I've stopped drinking, and I'm getting my
life straightened out to how it was before.
No, this might be the first time in
my life that I've been this stable.
I understand the importance of
the things I've lost.
I'll let her decide whether or
not she'll see you.
Oh. Well, sure...
Then, if you'll excuse me...
Okay.
Yes?
More coffee, please.
Proof
Doctor, what do you think of this man?
Hey now, Richard.
Yes?
What exactly do you think
you came here for?
You came here to receive my counseling.
I told you, I'm not a fortune teller.
It's the years of experience
with clients, right?
So who is this boy?
He's the one who discovered the body.
He was the first to find Fahren's body.
He's just a friend.
Hey, Richard.
You shouldn't be such a workaholic. You need
to relax some of the time too, you know.
I am relaxed.
That's good then.
Actually, Doctor...
What?
I might be able to see my daughter!
Oh, you must be excited!
Yes.
However...
even if you see her,
you can't take back what you've lost.
You should keep that in mind.
No matter what happens, do not drink!
Got it?!
Don't worry.
So are you going back to work?
Yes.
Well, soon you'll have to tackle the case that got you
fired from the police. Are you ready for that?
Yes, of course I am.
He was 16 and a serial murderer.
I shot and killed him...
while I was on duty and drunk.
That's good.
You can't run away from that.
You cannot erase the truth.
But what's important is...
Moving forward from there, right?
Good.
You're a good student.
Do I get 100%?
Don't be ridiculous. I don't hand
out 100%s so easily.
People who get 100%s are boring, anyway.
No way!
Karl Neuman.
A management studies major in the business
department at Munich University...
Just like Fahren, he claimed to be
the son of Mr. Schubert.
I cannot yet determine whether
this is true or not,
but this young man definitely has
something to do with the case.
Hello?
Richard, I'm done with the cleaning,
so I'd like to excuse myself.
Thanks for all of your hard work.
It's no problem at all!
I can't believe a man living by himself
keeps his place so clean.
It was pretty horrible before, though.
There's a new picture of your
daughter now, isn't there?
Yes, soon I'll be able to see her.
That's great! She'll be so happy.
Do you think so?
Of course! There's not a girl in the world who
wouldn't be happy to see her parents.
Munich University
Friedrich Emmanuel Hall
That's good.
So have you finished your report?
Karl Neuman.
Why haven't you told Mr. Schubert
that you're his son?
Are you a swindler... or are
you the real thing?
If you really are his son,
a parent would like to see
his child any time he could.
I'm sorry. She said she didn't
want to see you.
I guess that will have to do.
I'm sorry. I don't have much time either.
Oh, I see.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Bye.
Okay.
Yes?
What would you like?
Whiskey.
All right.
Here you go.
Huh?
Excuse me...
I'm going to see Dad.
Not now.
If you want to see him,
go when you're grown up.
But you mustn't want anything from him.
You must not hate him if
he treats you coldly,
because I don't hate him.
Take this.
Your father gave you this when you were born.
"With no one to admire it,
the Lares daffodil bloomed."
"With no one to admire them,
the Pierias trees rustled."
"Ah, you follow in the tracks of those of the
same blood before you, nameless ones."
Wonderful.
Neuman, you've become wonderful at reading.
Thank you very much.
I'm very impressed that you've become so
good at reading Latin in such a short time.
The truth is that I've been taking lessons.
He must be an excellent teacher.
Who is it?
Johann... Johann Liebert.
So it was Johann? He's perfect.
Yes.
Not just in Latin...
In law and business. No, he's complete
in many forms of study.
He's even been blessed with a handsome face.
Um, Mr. Schubert.
If a young man like him... if a young man like him
were your real son, what would you think?
He smiled.
He actually smiled.
It seems that you'd be the perfect son,
according to him.
To be honest, I was jealous.
Even though it's obvious that you're
better than me.
After doing that, I kind of felt
disgusted with myself.
Why don't you tell him?
Huh?
Why don't you tell him that
you're his real son?
Stop that!
I've told you that I don't have
any intention of doing that.
Even if I did tell him, he wouldn't believe me.
He'd just think that I was a
hyena after his fortune.
I absolutely don't want that.
He doesn't know my mother lived and died.
He doesn't know how I've felt.
I don't want him to think of me that
way without knowing those things.
That's exactly why you should tell him.
Make him understand everything.
He won't believe anything.
There's got to be something that
will make him believe you...
Something that will make him
know you're his real son...
No, there isn't.
Remember. There has to be something.
I told you, there isn't anything! I
have no intention of telling him.
Then why are you learning Latin from me?
Because you want him to be proud of you?
Because you want him to like you?
I think I'm going to quit.
My job, reading to him...
I'm going to quit.
Thanks for your concern.
It's okay now.
Johann.
I'll tell this just to you.
The truth is that I do have
proof that I'm his son.
What is it?
But I don't have any intention of showing
it to him and claiming to be his son.
My foster parents are coming
to see me next week.
I've made up my mind.
When they come, I'm going to...
I see.
So you won't go back on your decision... Maybe
you should leave that evidence with me.
You look well. I'm relieved.
Isn't that right, Mom?
Yes. I was worried about how
you were eating.
I've been eating out so much, I'm
worried that I'm getting fat.
Mom's cooking will make you fat, too.
Because it's so good.
How's school going?
Have you made any friends?
Yes, great friends that
I can ask anything of.
I see. That's great.
I can tell by looking at your face
that everything is going well.
I'm so thankful that you've allowed
me to come and study here.
What is it now?
I've had so many foster parents up until
now, and you've truly treated me well.
It's because you're such a wonderful child.
That's right, Karl.
Thank you, Mr. Lindner.
Could you stop calling me Mr. Lindner?
Have you accepted our proposal
to be our real adopted child?
We've waited all this time that you've been in college,
but we were thinking that you've had
enough time to make your decision.
We believe in you.
Can you believe in us?
Of course.
Your real parents might be
alive somewhere.
We might never be able to
replace them, but...
That's not true at all.
You are my true parents.
Honey.
This calls for a toast.
We'll order some special, expensive wine.
Okay.
Excuse me. Could we see the wine menu?
Today is a special day!
Hello?
Is that you, Neuman? It's me.
Mr. Schubert?
I've heard that you're going
to quit your job.
Yes.
It's a shame.
Forgive me.
You've worked so hard to
become good at Latin.
Thank you.
It really is a shame. It saddens me.
If you wouldn't mind,
could you read to me one last time?
Yes, I'd be happy to do so.
Is Chapter Three from
"From Aeolis to Lemnos" okay?
Yes, that would be great.
"That deep sea of mystery..."
"Wasn't it wishing for the death of Phoebus?"
"Doesn't Cerberus have anything else to look forward
to other than the death of our sons and daughters?"
"Now, 'Go forth,' says Zeus. 'Go forth. Go forth."'
"Dance at the temple of the gods."
"Gods of Juno, who live in the earth,
the sea, and the heavens."
"From the summit of the Parthenon, steal
the forbidden apple of Campania."
"Bring it all here. Seek out... my heart."
"My heart..."
Mr. Schubert.
That phone call...
That was splendid.
That was the most heartfelt reading
I've ever heard.
Why did you hide this from me?
That...
It's the same rabbit foot that I gave
to your mother, Margot.
It was a lucky charm to bring you good
fortune when you were born.
This is yours, Karl.
I'm sorry I've caused you such pain.
Father!
My son.
It's thanks to him.
He told me.
He's going to be working for
me as a secretary.
A young man I can trust...
Just One Case