Do we have a guest list for the reception?
Yes, I have it.
We have an idea of who was there at the time.
He was after the governor, wasn't he?
All the attendees were important people.
Most of them probably have enemies.
Well, see if you can find any connections to the culprit.
The Frankfurt police station sure is in a large
uproar over this convention center shooting.
They sure are. Even though they know the identity
of the culprit, they don't know who he was after.
They know his identity?
Yes. He's a dentist in the redevelopment area.
A dentist? Oh, man.
What's wrong?
The first place I planned on going
to after I retire was a dentist.
I've been so busy every day that I haven't been able to go.
Count me out if there are dangerous dentists out there.
Inspector, right here.
I'm Inspector Weissbach, Northrhein-Westphalia Police.
Reinhard Dinger.
Age: 42.
Occupation: Taxi driver.
Suspected of killing a passenger in Gunter Forest Park.
He was also suspected in the Bilker Investment Bank employee murder case in '97,
the Hofgarten murder in '96,
and a murder on the bank of the Rhine River in '95.
He is wanted as a suspect for all these
murders in the Dusseldorf area.
By signing here, I request that the suspect
be transferred to Northrhein-Westphalia.
Are the arrangements ready?
Yes.
Get out.
All right. Let's go.
Unrelated Murders
Do you want anything to drink?
No.
There's no smoking here.
The passenger cars are all non-smoking.
If only you had lived your life strictly to that moral code.
How many people have you killed with those hands?
Counting irreplaceable lives on your fingers...
would even make the stomach of one of your murder victims turn.
This is my last assignment.
I retire tomorrow.
I had a rather simple career as a
police officer, but it wasn't bad.
From now on, all I have to do is live happily
with my wife, tend my garden and such.
That's what life is about.
I want you to regret the fact that you've
destroyed other people's modest lives.
Even a man who spat at me?
A customer, who I picked up on Addler Street, spat at me as he was getting out.
Don't tell me that's why you killed him...
People who spit at other people are filth.
A couple who got on at Gerensheim Station were even worse.
They started having sex in the back seat of my car.
In my back seat!
That's why I killed them.
A young alcoholic with a dirty mouth.
A prostitute that tried to pay her fare with her body.
A old hag smeared with make-up
that insulted everyone she saw.
A lot of people have gotten in my taxi.
They're all scum.
That's why I killed them.
Then I'll ask you one thing.
What about the Bilker Investment Bank employee?
How was he scum?
He was hard-working and sincere.
That bank worker loved his family.
Because you killed him,
a financial corruption scandal that he was going to blow the whistle on remains a mystery.
The aftertaste from that one was pretty bad.
Look.
You talk as if you're delivering heaven's judgment,
but you're really just trying to justify yourself.
I didn't have a choice.
Did someone ask you to kill him?
I won't tell you.
I told you there was no smoking.
If you try to smoke in front of me again, I'll kill you.
What made you this way?
I've always had the right answers.
I just got that extra push on the back that day.
That day, there was a man walking his dog in the park.
The man kicked it just because it pooped.
The dog, which was getting kicked, was frightened.
All it did was poop.
I stopped him.
When I came to, I was being taken away by the police.
There was a boy there.
The boy said this to the police officer.
"It's not that man's fault."
"The man with the dog hit him first."
Because of him, I wasn't arrested.
To thank him, I told him I'd take him home in my car.
He said he didn't have a home to go back to.
On top of that, his little sister was with him.
They were twins.
I didn't know what to do, so I brought
them to my apartment.
It was weird. After they took off their jackets
all they were wearing was pajamas.
It was like they ran away from a hospital.
Now that I think of it the boy had
a bandage around his head.
After we ate that night, I watched the news.
I started to talk to myself like always. I began to curse.
"This stupid world,"
"filled with stupid people,"
"all the scum should die!"
What do you think the boy said?
He said, "You re right."
And then he said this...
People like that are worthless.
That is when he unleashed me.
Get serious!
Are you saying that is when you started killing people?
Thank you for your hard work, Inspector.
No prob.
You got through your last assignment safely.
Yep. All that's left is to clean out my desk.
Thank you for your dedication over the years.
I'm kind of disappointed.
I guess I do have one unsolved case.
What's wrong, Inspector?
His little sister was with him.
They were twins.
All they were wearing was pajamas.
It was like they ran away from a hospital.
Do you remember anything from that night?
Anything is fine.
Anything that you can remember is fine.
Your name is Anna. Anna Liebert. Isn't that right?
Now that I think of it, the boy had
a bandage around his head.
The twins. They've completely disappeared.
Inspector!
Huh? When did I meet them?
Let me think. Maybe 11 years ago.
What did they look like?
They had beautiful faces and were blond.
How is this possible?!
The twins that disappeared back then.
The twins that were the key to Dr. Tenma's case.
Geez.
Only 30 hours until I retire.
A vampire, huh?
Isenburg Prison
(Frankfurt)
I see.
13 people...
You can't keep on living unless you drink their blood.
They have to be virgins.
I see.
Let me ask you something.
The incident 3 months ago... The daughter
of the general store owner in Frankfurt,
Frieder Schelling.
Did you drink her blood?
As you said, all your victims until
recently have been young girls.
You've even done background checks
on them before pursuing them.
I understand that you need virgin blood.
But this Frieder Schelling...
She's 21 years old,
although she looks like she's in her teens.
But that's not the problem.
She has worked at a cafe on Seiler Street in Frankfurt since she was 16.
It was close to a famous gymnasium.
The boys there treated her like the Madonna.
But, she had a baby when she was 17.
The rumor was that the father was one of the students from the gymnasium.
Her parents opened a general store after the baby was born.
The parents of the student who impregnated her were rich,
and they opened the shop with the money they received from them.
Did you know that?
You knew so much about the other girls.
Do you drink the blood of non-virgins?
The aftertaste from that one was pretty bad.
Why did you target her?
I met the real thing.
The real thing?
I knew it when I met him.
I was still just a bat pretending to be a vampire.
He was the real thing.
Did he tell you to kill her?
Who was it?
Where did you meet him?
In a suburb of Frankfurt.
Griesheim.
There's a park there just like any other park.
He wrote a girl's name in the sand
in the sandbox with a stick.
I just carried it out.
Who was it?
I told you. A real vampire.
Pinneburg Prison
(Hamburg)
I can't wrap my head around it.
Your murder of Erich Klemperer, 4 months ago.
All your other missions were in Niedersachsen.
Why just this one in Frankfurt?
Was this another message from the aliens?
Did the aliens all of a sudden change their minds
and make you kill people in Frankfurt?
Or did you have a different reason?
Klemperer did have a villainous past.
He escaped from East Berlin during the Cold War.
For a few years, he managed to make a
good living trading foodstuffs here.
But there were rumors that he was involved in the
placement of adopted children from the East to the West.
In other words, he sold children from the East to rich people without children in the West.
It wasn't a message. I had a face-to-face meeting with them.
I was ecstatic.
There really was an alien standing in front of me.
Where did the UFO land?
A park in Griesheim.
He spoke in an alien language.
So he made it easy for me and wrote
the words in the sandbox.
I was so ecstatic. I wish I could let you taste it as well.
Dusseldorf Police Station
Thanks for your hard work, Inspector Weissbach.
We're counting the seconds until your retirement.
You're that eager to get rid of me, huh?
That's right! Let's have a drink tonight to celebrate
us getting rid of such a hassle like you.
That doesn't sound like a good drink to me.
Who's that man?
That's Dr. Gillen.
I hear he's a criminal psychologist.
He's here to interview the taxi driver serial killer, Dinger.
Did someone ask for him?
No. He said he's here for a research paper.
I hear he's an authority in that field, so he was
able to get permission from the big shots.
So you ran over the man who spat at you as he was leaving your cab.
I've said this in interviews over and over again. The people I've killed were worthless people.
You people just don't understand the truth.
Truth?
Do you mind if I ask you a question?
You're always talkative during interviews,
but you don't like discussing the murder
of the Bilker Bank employee, Fritz Overt.
In your previously documented testimony,
you claim that you had legitimate reasons
for killing the people that you killed.
But, you have never given a clear reason
why you murdered Mr. Overt.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
How did it go, Dr. Gillen?
I'm Inspector Weissbach.
Was there anything academically interesting
that you heard from Dinger?
No.
He didn't say anything he hasn't said before.
I'll see you.
The truth is I have something I
desperately wanted to ask him.
I'm facing retirement today.
I don't think I'll ever be able to rest if I don't ask him.
What do you think of this academically?
There was a child who was like a monster.
After he had grown up, he came to visit a man
who took care of him when he was a child.
A child who was like a monster?
This is such an absurd story.
Please tell me everything you know about it!
Why are you two here?
I told you I don't want to talk to that man.
I'm still a detective, at least for today.
This is an interrogation.
You told me about the twins yesterday.
You said that he unleashed you.
If he came back to visit you after he'd
grown up and asked you for a favor,
would you listen to him?
Hmm? I don't know.
The murder of the Bilker Bank employee, Fritz Overt...
Did someone ask you to do it?
A hard-working man. A sincere man.
That's the kind of man Mr. Overt was.
Not the kind of scum that you always talk about.
He was going to expose a financial corruption scandal.
If you call him scum, the righteousness of
your crimes will be completely destroyed.
It wasn't a request.
There's no need for words between him and I.
Him?
That bank employee was scum to him.
That's what I believe.
Why?
Because he is correct!
Who is "he?"
Is it that twin?
When did you meet him?
Griesheim. A park in that city.
A suburb of Frankfurt, Griesheim.
A park in Griesheim.
He wrote a name in the sand in the sandbox.
He didn't say anything.
But I knew.
I must kill the man with this name.
There's no need for words.
We all understood.
These people are worthless.
What do you mean?
Are you saying that the three people that you interviewed
were all ordered by the same person to kill their targets?
By using three unrelated serial killers, the meaning
of the three murders becomes harder to spot.
The meaning of the three murders?
What do you mean? Tell me!
Tenma and Nina are coming to Frankfurt.
Johan!
They're trying to start something in Frankfurt.
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Baby's Depression