Don't worry. Hang in there.
Shoot me.
Kill.
I'll save you.
Are you going to shoot me like you did back then?
Yes.
I'll end it all.
End?
What is the end?
The end...
The end... The end...
The end.
I've seen the end many times.
What is the end?
I'm ending it!
You will die and so will I.
You've seen it.
What did you see?!
You don't know anything.
I'll tell you...
a truly frightening tale.
I'm home.
I'm Back
This truly frightening tale you speak of...
don't you mean the things I saw?
The things I told you about?
The things I saw?
The place I was put into after I was taken from the Three Frogs was a pitch black room with no walls.
No matter where I touched in that room, I couldn't
get a sense of what was up, down, left, or right.
But, I knew someone was observing me.
It was a room without sound.
No.
I could occasionally hear screams.
Meals were provided for me from somewhere.
I counted how many they gave me.
5, 6, 7...
11, 12, 13...
21, 23...
Some time after I lost count,
that man appeared.
Listen up.
People can become anything.
Huh?
Is this an appropriate place for a little kid like you to be wandering around?
No, that's the kid.
Oh, this child?!
Ah, how cute!
So this is the kid.
Amazing. What a beautiful child!
Look! This is the kid!
So this is the kid!
So this is the result.
This kid is....
We... the result... we, the chosen ones
I can only remember parts of the speech.
toast to the future of our country.
Cheers!
The first person collapsed.
The people around him rushed over.
The people who rushed over began to
fall on top of him one after another.
The moans, the screams, the shouts.
Fear filled the room.
42 people died in that room.
Only Franz Bonaparta was left.
I ran.
In order to get out of there, I ran.
I didn't even notice that the rose thorns had cut my arm.
I ran.
You met me when I arrived at the Three Frogs.
I told it all to you.
The things that happened to me every day.
Everything I experienced.
You're wrong.
You're wrong!
Nina.
Can you hear me, Nina?
Calm down.
Nina.
It's me. It's Tenma.
You understand?
It's me.
Yes. Yes. Calm down.
All right. Good girl.
It's okay. It's okay now.
You're wrong!
You're wrong! You're wrong!
It wasn't me.
I wasn't the one who said, "Welcome home."
The one who said, "Welcome home"...
I...
I said...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Johan is mistaken.
Johan only heard what I told him.
The one who was taken to the Red Rose Mansion...
was me!
The one who was dragged down
the stairs of the Three Frogs,
the one who was in that pitch black room with no walls,
the one who counted the meals,
the one who stood in that room full of dead bodies...
was me!
It was me!
I'm scared.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Tell me everything.
Let me tell you...
I told him.
About every day...
It's okay.
I told him about all my experiences.
Johan took my experiences...
It's okay.
and made them his own.
It's my fault that Johan...
It's okay!
I told him everything.
Back then, Johan...
Johan listened to me and looked
like he was about to smile,
but, he also looked like he was about to cry.
I-I've never seen anyone make a face like that.
I didn't shoot.
But I'm sure that...
he will destroy himself.
Just like me.
Don't think that way.
Just like I'll destroy myself!
Don't!
If you died...
If something happened to you...
what would I do?
If you died, where would I go?
Please live.
I'm begging you.
No matter what happens...
Yes, it's me.
You found a car near the mansion?
Yeah, it fell down a cliff.
Edward was killed inside the car.
The one who killed him is probably...
Johan is most likely...
off to kill Franz Bonaparta.
His son is in Prague.
I told Johan that.
However, I don't know if it will end there.
I don't know if that will be the limit of his destruction.
The sister's memory...
What memory is she still missing?
There's one more thing inside Johan.
What was that memory...
the thing that we were trying to create, Franz?
Franz Bonaparta...
Please live.
I'm sure that...
the place you're supposed to go to...
the place we're supposed to go to...
exists...
Hey, there.
I'm glad you could make it.
I never thought you'd be the one to contact me.
Well, come in.
I was just about to have some tea.
I wanted you to taste my famous tea.
Well?
How do you like it? It's my special herb tea.
Since you came here, this must be pretty important.
Ask me anything.
I'll get prepared immediately.
Who are we going to kill next?
Huh? Stop it with the stupid jokes.
Stop!
I've awakened...
from my dream.
Are you tired?
What about your plan?
I've awakened.
Hold on.
Then why did I get all that money from you?
I've awakened from my dream.
Why did I kill all those people?
I've seen the end many times,
but, now I see something different.
The scenery of the true end.
In a memory that only I have.
The place where we are supposed to go...
Huh?
Ruhenheim.
This is it.
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
Ruhenheim