It looks like another scorcher today.
Hey, it's summer,
yet you're all bundled up.
Aren't you hot?
What's that?
That paper's three days old.
They say this time a middle-aged couple
in Verden was killed.
I hear the Killer is a doctor...
Oh, yeah... You said you're going
to Verden, didn't you?
You know someone there?
Yeah... I don't know if I can
meet up with him or not, but...
I have to go there...
The Girl and the Seasoned Soldier
Giessen Police Station
(Germany)
You got your start
in the French Foreign Legion.
After going off on your own, you joined
the fighting in Nicaragua in 1979.
From 1981 to 1984 you aided
the Afghan rebel guerillas...
In 1987, you played a central role
in the Mossad's secret operation
to assassinate Islamic extremists.
What a brilliant fighting record,
Hugo Bernhardt...
Since a mercenary such as you
is sponsoring this seminar,
I'm sure you must have some
outstanding students graduating...
It might be a good idea to send
our young ones to attend your lectures
and have you whip them into shape.
Yes, well...
Incidentally...
Was this man outstanding?
I believe he showed up
at your training grounds
about five months ago.
He is brilliant with a scalpel...
but did he show an aptitude
with a pistol?
I have no wish to speak
about my students...
I see.
Five Months Ago
Have you ever learned
to shoot a gun?
No...
So you're self-taught...
I've never shot a gun before...
Not once?
No... I know I'm asking
for the impossible, but...
I have no choice
but to ask you for help.
Anyway, anyone
who comes here is asked
to forget all he's learned about guns.
But...
I've never had anyone
who'd never shot a gun before.
Jump rope...
Regardless of your experience,
this is where everyone starts.
Just like that child...
Don't just stand there!
Get busy!
Y-Yes, sir!
Faster.
Faster!
Watch your balance! Your balance!
I just can't do it as well as you do...
Do you always keep an eye
on the trainees for the trainer?
Okay, okay, you needn't glare at me
that way. I'll do it.
I must do it.
Oh, a brambling...
I wonder if it's looking for food
for its chicks.
Are you so exhausted that
you've lost your appetite?
Huh? Yes...
Eating is part of your training.
Yes, sir...
Is she your child... or, your grandchild?
No...
That child's mother
was shot and killed by me.
Right before her eyes... in Myanmar...
When I ran into a hut in the jungles
for shelter, they were there.
The mother was holding a gun
If I'd been a fraction
of a second slower,
I'd have been shot dead.
And that's why
I brought that child here.
Since she began living with me,
that child has never smiled.
She'll probably die hating me...
When you have a gun,
that sort of thing happens.
If you don't like it, you're better off
never picking up a gun.
What's that?
Something smells nice...
It smells like daphne blossoms...
Thanks...
That's enough.
Huh? Then...?
It's time for some running.
Oh, I see...
When you're done running,
come to the low ground in the back.
Huh?
Low ground...?
The firing range.
Firing range...
Remember, twice...
Whenever you shoot your gun,
pull the trigger twice.
By pulling the trigger twice,
you raise the probability
that you'll get your target.
If you can't do that,
consider yourself dead.
What is this?
You're always preparing meals for me,
so today I decided to make you
some Japanese food.
This is called "nikujaga.”
I hope you'll like it.
Those are chopsticks.
They're carved out of wood.
I thought they would enhance
the Japanese feel of the dish.
You're good...
You use those chopsticks well.
Once more!
Aim!
Do it again!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's a brambling chick.
I guess it fell out of its nest.
Oh... no, no!
You have to return it to its nest!
That chick is going to die!
It's very difficult to raise it
away from its nest.
It's rare that you
can do it successfully.
Let's return it to its nest...
to its mother.
Three seconds!
Everything is determined
in three seconds!
If there's even an instant of hesitation,
the one killed will be you.
So...
How was his performance record
when he finished the course?
Technically, he had a perfect score,
and his physical condition also improved.
His concentration
was phenomenal. However...
However?
Being able to shoot a person
is another issue altogether.
Oh?
Whether he's able to shoot
his first person will determine
whether he will or won't be able to
use his gun.
I see... I wonder which way he'll go...
Well, never mind about that.
Do you have any idea where he went?
I'd like you to tell me if you do know...
Thank you for everything,
these five months...
Enclosed is the rest of my tuition.
And please help yourself
to the nikujaga.
You have my sincere thanks.
Jeez...
Damn...
She laughed...
How about it? You do know where
he went, don't you?
I can't tell you that.
That's fine... You may leave.
This way.
A Past Erased