I've never seen you before.
If you want to do business,
get permission from the state.
Unlicensed prostitutes are a nuisance.
I can't make much money
if I do it legitimately.
Get out of here.
I just have to get permission
from him, don't I?
Let me meet him.
Him? What are you talking about?
I'll keep coming until you
let me meet him...
The man known as “The Baby.”
Be My Baby
You can't catch it with your hands.
You're not the goalkeeper.
I don't care about the rules!
Where did he go?
He?
Tenma, Tenma!
He told me to stay with you until
he found the man he was looking for.
Me?!
He wants me to look after you?!
No way!
I hate kids!
Tenma, that bastard...
He doesn't give me any warning
and picks up some strange kid...
What happened to making money
as an unlicensed doctor?
Get a real job.
Pass!
Nice header!
Why you...
What do you think
you're doing, you brat?!
Hey...
I told you that you can't hold the ball
with your hands. That's a yellow card.
Shut up! You can't get through life
being worried about that!
If you say things like that,
you'll get a red card.
Shut up!
Frankfurt Central Station
You're late... Quickly!
Give me the goods...
Give them to me now!
It's been a while, Detective Mesner.
D-Doctor Tenma...
That's right. That's what you
called me then.
It was the first time we met.
You hadn't even asked
what my occupation was.
But, right now, I'm an ex-doctor.
Come to think of it,
you're an ex-detective.
Detective dismissed on
suspicion of narcotics use.”
I was surprised when I found
this six-month-old article.
You'd better not stand up.
I'm pointing a gun at you
from under my coat.
W-What do you want—?
I want to know what you did
ten months ago in Heidelberg...
And who hired you to do that.
I-I don't know...
You took the lives of
the Fortners and Maurer!
I didn't do it! I was just a lookout!
My partner, Muller, did it.
Detective Muller also
quit the police immediately after
the incident, didn't he?
Y-Yeah...
It seems that he took his money
and is doing quite well...
And you, on the other hand,
used up all of your money on drugs
and ended up like this?
He took the request. He did the killing.
He got the larger portion
of the reward!
Someone even tried to kill me
to keep me silent...
I'm surprised you're still alive.
I was saved by a certain organization.
A certain organization?”
That's enough, isn't it? Forgive me.
I've already spoken too much before.
Before? To whom?
Leave me alone already!
I don't have the time for that now!
Withdrawal symptoms, huh?
Drug dealers probably won't
approach you while I'm sitting here.
W-Well...
The Baby” saved me!
The Baby"?
Go to the pub called Candy.
You can meet him there.
Who is “The Baby"?
He's a big name right-wing extremist.
He's an executive of
two right-wing political parties...
After the Wall fell,
The Baby went to Dresden,
on the east side,
and tried to make a town
of only pure German people.
But he failed and he's come back.
Why did that man save you?
The darkness.
When the Berlin Wall fell...
A great darkness was born...
A monster... was born...
A monster?
Go already! I told the rest to that girl!
That girl?
She came for revenge
and pointed a gun at me!
She's the daughter of
the couple we killed!
Anna...
Nina, Nina Fortner came to you?!
I-I was told by “The Baby”...
that I was to send that girl to him
if she appeared!
He said that she's important bait...
Important... bait?
You again?
You appear every night.
I'll buy you for a good price...
You're the one that said that
I'd get in trouble
if I did business without permission
from The Baby.
What did you say?! Why you...
What's with that look?
Is that the girl that wants to
meet The Baby?
Oh.. yes.
Right this way.
Please wait right there.
Huh?
Please wait on that symbol.
Oh. No, no... Right on there.
That's right.
Do you know this song?
Its pleasant rhythm will
carry you away, Miss Nina Fortner.
The Baby said...
This country will be all right
when the second Hitler is born...”
That woman is the bait.
Nina!
How do you know about me?
I know everything.
Your other name is Anna Liebert...
But neither is your real name.
Names don't really matter.
After all, I'm called “The Baby.”
Come on, dance, dance!
I heard that you know
where my brother is.
Ah, Johan, huh? That's a good name.
You know, don't you?!
You went as far as to dress like that,
so what do you plan to do
once you do meet him?
I have to kill him.
Don't wave that
dangerous thing around.
It's all right.
Johan will come to meet you.
I lived in this area when I was a kid,
so I know all of the back alleys.
There's an antique dealer
further down.
I'm going to trade
this rug in for money.
What? You don't have
any money, Mr. Heckel?
Shut up. I'm trying to do something
to pay for your dinner... Be thankful...
Huh—?
Huh??
Huh?
Whoa...
What's wrong?
This whole area's become
a Turkish district...
This is a fake.
Wha?! What are you talking about?
This design, this feel...
No matter how you look at it,
this is hand woven silk.
This is synthetic.
Well, I feel sorry for you,
so I'll take it for 100 marks.
Aww.. That's what I hate!
The previous German store owner
would have given me 10,000 marks.
Then take it with you.
You're going to beg me for it
when you realize it's real.
This is what you would call a real one.
Huh?
It's a 100 percent silk Hereke rug.
Take a close look.
No corners have been cut.
Not even the fine patterns...
It's 150,000 marks.
I-It's probably a fake!
You can't even see that
this rug is real.
Let's go, Dieter.
Say, I'm hungry...
It's real...
Huh?!
It's a genuine high quality rug.
150,000 marks, he says?
At the right place,
it can go for 800,000 marks.
Say, let's get something to eat.
Shut up!
If I get that, you can eat all you want!
Get it? How?
Just leave that to me.
What's with that look?
Thief!
Whoa, you idiot.
K-Keep your voice down, you brat.
Hold on, what are you planning to do?
Sorry, but try someone else
if you want a customer.
That's not what I meant.
An Asian like you might be killed
if you waltzed in there.
That store's a nest of right-wingers!
You're Turkish, aren't you?
Is it all right to be
doing business here?
Don't be stupid!
I wouldn't think of doing business
in a dump like this!
Those guys took a friend of mine.
It seems like she found out
a secret of theirs...
A secret?
I don't know what it is.
But I have to save her quickly.
Who knows what
she's facing right now...
A woman I know is also in there.
What's she like?
Could it be the longhaired blond girl?
Who knows...? Who knows what
hairstyle she has right now...
They just took her away by car.
Where did they go?!
I don't know.
But The Baby was with them,
so they probably
went to his mansion...
The Baby!
What kind of car was it?!
What color was it?!
Uhh... It was a red Mercedes.
All right... I've got to find that car
and go after it.
Hey! Save my friend, tool
Please.
She has a small child!
Please!
Well, well, you didn't die!
Right this way.
Before that, I'll take your gun.
Go right ahead.
Sit wherever you like...
Are you the girl that
The Baby brought?
Let me see your face.
Oh...? You're a beautiful girl.
It's as I expected of Johan's sister.
I am Professor Geidlitz.
The man in the picture
with Johan is General Wolf.
There are two others...
Together, the four of us
created this organization.
Would you like some fruit?
Let me meet my brother...Johan.
You'll meet him... He'll show up
once he knows that you're here.
He needs you.
You don't know where
Johan is either, do you?
We need him...
In order to lead us.
Do you know why Hitler
had so much power?
He was an intelligent businessman.
He knew the three essentials.
Control the banks,
stimulate the munitions industry,
and seize the military.
Right now, Johan is secretly
gaining power in one of those...
Do you think that
my reasoning is correct?
What do you plan to do with Johan?
However, Hitler achieved what he did
through his charisma.
Hitler failed
his art school examination.
Even in the military, he only made it
as far as corporal...
He became charismatic
once he passed his thirties...
But what about Johan?
He's had a monstrous charisma
since he was a child.
It's as if he were Jesus Christ.
But you mustn't forget
the three wise men from the east
and John the Baptist;
the four amazing people
who first realized Christ's talents.
We four have been paying attention to
Johan's talents since he was a child.
Isn't it wonderful?
What should I do?
We want you to stay here
for a while...
Until Johan comes to meet you...
Don't try to run away.
You've already gone too far.
There's no need to worry.
I wanted to come here...
I'll wait here for Johan!
That's fine...
Now, have some fruit...
It seems like you've
regained consciousness.
There's no need to worry.
We won't break any of your bones...
What were you doing around here,
Doctor Tenma?
H-How do you know who I am?
I'm asking the questions.
You just have to answer them.
What are you planning to do?
What do you plan to do
once you find Johan?
Where is Nina?
I said that I'm asking the questions!
What do you plan to do with Nina?
I thought I told you
not to ask questions!
Nina is an important guest.
Not trash like you.
Then... she's safe, right?
For now...
But she's very dangerous...
She has such a cute face,
but is trying to kill Johan...
We'll eventually have to
deal with people like that...
So Nina is just a tool
in order to call Johan?!
Who are you? What do you plan to...
Another question. Foreigners like you
have no right to question us!
The whole district is going to burn
because of your impudent attitude.
T-The whole district?
That's right... Tomorrow night,
the night sky will be beautiful...
I can meet Johan if I stay here...
Help...
W-Who are you?
H-Help...
Where are you?
Third floor...
You speak in broken German.
What country are you from?
Turkey...
I'm... going to be killed...
I've got to escape...
You've been confined
by the people here, haven't you?
Help...
But... I've got to stay here...
Please, help.
If I don't let everyone know soon,
my baby will die, as well...
Tomorrow night we'll have a party
to welcome Johan.
Only superior people, like us,
should survive in this world.
All the rest should burn.
I heard them talking...
They're going to set a fire
tomorrow night...
They plan on burning
the Turkish district!
Help!
Wolf's Confession