He has already gone to heaven.
All that remains here is
Richard Braun's body.
His soul will live on forever.
Let us swear on his soul...
that we will continue on living... in hope.
Let us turn to the Bible, Psalm 23.
This is quite unbearable, isn't it?
What a depressing funeral...
Even though he was a skilled detective,
not a single person from the
police department came.
While he was part of the force,
he had a drinking problem.
In the end, he drank and fell to his death.
That's what the police said, right?
On the day he died,
Richard had apparently promised his
daughter to see her the next day.
I...
What did I ever do for him?
Dr. Reichwein...
I just sat in my chair,
listened to his story,
and told him that he had regained his old self.
What did I ever do for him?
Dr. Tenma...
If we could find him, it's possible
that everything would be solved.
Dr. Tenma...
Don't you think it's strange, doctor?
This was no accident!
This was not a suicide either!
Mr. Richard spoke to his daughter on the
phone just a few hours before his death,
saying they'd meet the next day.
Doctor,
you did everything that you could have done,
and Mr. Richard did regain his old self.
Please don't blame yourself.
Decision
And then...
Hear me out, doctor.
My husband will not talk to me...
ever since I found out about his affair.
Every day, he washes the car and
then mows the lawn.
He won't even look me in the face!
Well, that's better than his not coming home,
but if this continues, I think I'll go crazy!
Are you listening, doctor?
Uh... yes...
Please continue.
And so, I stormed over to his mistress's house,
and what do you think happened then, doctor?
The possibility of a homicide?
No way.
That was just an accident.
That night, Richard Braun went up to the the roof
of Building 12 at the University of Munich,
drank a bottle of whiskey, and then
fell off after getting drunk.
Did you investigate the bottle closely?
Of course!
Richard's fingerprints were on it.
Can you show me that bottle?
Well, I suppose I could,
but it's shattered.
Richard...
Don't you think it's strange?
Mr. Richard spoke to his daughter on the
phone just a few hours before his death,
saying they'd meet the next day.
Yes,
this person came here that night.
He came alone?
Well, I don't remember...
So you remember his coming here, but you don't
remember if he came with someone else?
Well, I remembered him because
he ordered coffee.
Coffee?
It's unusual for a customer to come in that
late at night and not order alcohol.
That night,
was he with this young man?
I'm not sure.
Please try to remember.
I don't know!
Lots of customers come in here...
But it's true that he bought a
bottle of whiskey to go.
It's right there on the receipt.
Was it really Richard who bought it?
I told you, I don't remember!
The receipt only has "one bottle of Racke" on it.
What did you just say?
One bottle of Racke.
Why didn't I realize it when I saw the
bottle label at the police station?
Huh?
You drank again?
No... Well...
Just a little bit.
What did you have to drink?
Whiskey!
I only drink whiskey.
Hmph! Stinking up the room
with the smell of Racke!
Racke?
Are you kidding me?!
I would never drink that domestic stuff.
When I drink I drink the
real stuff, Scotch Whiskey!
That's a given!
The person who bought the
whiskey was not Richard.
Johann...
Was it him, after all?
Huh?
W-Wait!
Hey, wait up!
Hey!
W-What?
Why did you try to push me off?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you saying? Don't play dumb!
Yo, Gramps.
You got some business with my friend?
Bastard!
Stupid old man!
Who...
Who hired you?
Think about your age, old man!
A grandpa should just look after his grandkids.
W-Wait, you punks!
Wait!
I've trained with the border patrol.
Why did you try to push me off?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Don't underestimate a former police surgeon.
I... I was hired to...
By whom?
A big man!
A big man?
A big man that I passed in the subway
passage gave me money!
He told me to push you off...!
I got it for you, Richard.
It's real Scotch Whiskey.
You wanted to drink it, right?
It's fine now.
Drink all you want now...
Richard,
leave it to me...
I'll definitely figure it out...
His...
Johann's...
real identity.
And then, doctor, I told my husband,
"Your infidelity is like a disease,"
and, "You're the only one who should
be getting a doctor's counseling!"
Doctor, are you listening to me?
Uh...
Yes, of course, Mrs. Hesse...
What do you think?
If my husband stays that way,
my depression will get worse.
Well,
you're not really suffering
from depression, ma'am.
Huh?
I'm more worried about your quiet husband, who
washes his car and mows the lawn every day.
You think so, too?
It's weird, no matter how you look at it.
Doctor, I'm begging you.
Please see him.
That's fine.
Let's see...
I'm free the day after tomorrow at 5 PM.
I'll try asking my husband.
Please straighten out that cheating oaf!
Doctor, you have no more patients today.
Okay. That's all for today, Ms. Merez.
I'll leave first, then.
Oh, Ms. Merez...
Yesterday, you forgot to lock
the back door again.
No! Really?
I was about to forget today, too!
Oh! I did it again!
Thanks for your hard work.
Hello, is this Dr. Gillen?
It's Reichwein.
I read the newspaper...
Uh, that ad that you put out...
"Let's discuss our memories of
cheating. From Rudi."
Will Dr. Tenma really contact you
because of this one sentence?
Yes.
If Tenma sees that, he will
definitely contact me.
Well, it's a story that only
the two of us know.
I see.
Doctor, please don't do anything
rash until he appears.
I understand.
There is one thing I would like
to investigate, though.
What is it?
The prostitute named Margot Langer.
Richard said...
When Fahren, who committed suicide,
went to see that woman,
there was a youth with him.
A beautiful, blonde young man.
Please be careful, doctor.
I understand, doctor...
For the sake of exposing the truth, I will
be more cautious from now on,
for Richard's sake as well.
Well then, I'll contact you again.
Ms. Merez, you forgot to close
the window today.
Margot Langer?
I don't know her.
Well,
her current nickname should be
Sophie something or another.
Oh, that fat hag?
Mister, are you into those types of girls?
No, it's nothing like that.
You shouldn't be embarrassed at your age.
Two streets down, around the corner.
Second floor of the old building.
Thank you.
She's not there now, though.
I haven't seen her lately.
She probably found a better place.
A better... place?
Jeez, why are the fat ugly ones so popular?
I heard that a really rich guy came
to see her the other day.
Where did she go?
Hey! How about me, mister?
I can definitely entertain you better
than that fat hag!
You don't know where she went?
I don't know.
She must have gone somewhere
with that new guy.
New guy?
Yeah, I can't believe that old hag fell
in love with that big man at her age.
He was a big man.
A big man...?
He looked like he was big down there, too...
Um, doctor...
Could I take the rest of the day off?
Oh, that's right!
You're working until five today.
All I have left is an appointment with
that unfaithful husband, so go ahead.
You have a date, right, Ms. Merez?
Please, doctor!
Please remember the door.
If I show this photo to that prostitute Sophie,
who pretended to be Margot Langer,
and got her to testify that the one who
was with Fahren was this boy, Johann,
I'd be one step closer to the truth.
Yes?
I'm Hesse. My wife made an
appointment for me.
Oh, I see.
Please come up.
I guess I'll try questioning that
woman again tonight.
Nice to meet you, Dr. Reichwein.
Welcome, Mr. Hesse.
It's nice to meet you.
Please, come in.
This is my first time at a counseling session so...
There's nothing to be nervous about.
This is a place where you can relax
and tell me anything you want.
What you say here is strictly confidential,
so please don't worry.
Even from my wife?
Of course!
How have you been lately?
Is there anything bothering you?
Bothering me?
Yes...
My wife...
She found out about my affair.
I see.
Even in my own house, I don't feel at home,
so I mow the lawn and wash the car.
I do that every day.
And does that make you feel any better?
Not really...
I don't even talk to my wife at all.
There isn't an opportunity to talk
even when you want to, huh?
Well, I'm not sure if that's it...
What about her?
Huh?
What about the woman you
had an affair with?
Oh...
I killed her.
Huh?
I mean,
I dreamt that I'd killed her.
Do you often have those kinds of dream?
Often...?
Well... not lately, I haven't.
I was lonely.
And that's why you had an affair.
No, it was after I met him...
Him?
He's a beautiful boy...
with blonde hair.
No matter how many people I killed,
or even if the country was destroyed,
everything inside of me felt like a dream.
After I met him, though, things changed...
Everything began to seem real...
and I was no longer lonely.
Would...
Would you like some tea?
No, I'm fine, thanks.
I'm a bit thirsty.
Could you wait a moment?
My secretary went home, you see.
Apparently, she has a date.
She makes good tea.
I'm sorry I can't give you some.
Doctor?
W-What is it?
In a job like yours, many different
things must occur.
After all, you do learn about people's dreams.
Nothing good can result from learning about
dreams that you shouldn't know about.
Especially...
learning that I'm a murderer...
I-In any case,
if you intend to start over
as husband and wife,
you should talk things over.
I hope that you didn't close
the back door, Ms. Merez.
Y-You're...
Hurry and run!
Doctor... Tenma...
I've been watching over you for a while.
You're being targeted.
Run!
Hurry!
In Broad Daylight