Your mommy abandoned you!
You were thrown away like trash
along with your drunk dad!
Don't come out of
the trash dump again!
Chapter 70
"The Town of Slaughter"
I'm sorry, but I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
If you want to drink,
do it after you pay your tab.
If it's money...
Here. This is for today.
We don't have drinks to be bought
with money earned by children.
What?
Get out.
He's suspicious.
You mean what happened
to Mr. Conrad?
Mrs. Hillman's dog, too.
Could it be?
He doesn't have the guts
to shoot a gun.
That's right.
He's just a drunk coward.
Honestly...
We're supposed to
be searching, but...
Hey Merkel, let's call it a day!
Hey, Merkel!
I found him ! I found him!
Merkel ! Mer–
Merkel...
This is Laufer!
Please respond!
Someone !
Someone answer!
I'm gonna have to
take your gun.
He doesn't have the guts
to shoot a gun.
That's right.
He's just a drunk coward.
The entire town,
it's full of corpses.
It's like a battlefield.
Wim...
What's wrong, Wim?
It's all right.
Calm down. It's me.
I-I... I...
Calm down.
Now let go of the gun.
I don't really remember.
I shot them, didn't I?
They were teasing me...
so I...
Wim, you...
It's all right. Calm down. It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Calm down. Try to remember.
Who did you get this gun from?
Get a hold of yourself!
Laufer, I'm surprised you
got this far on that leg!
C-Call the station.
The telephone doesn't work.
M-My gun was taken away.
By someone in this town?
I don't know. He was an outsider
I've never seen before.
Anyway, apply first aid.
Is he one of your friends?
What are you talking about?
How many of you
have come to this town?
What are you trying to say?
You've scattered quite
a few guns around.
You've even given
this child a gun.
Wim!
A gun? Did you...
"You're not trash."
"Don't bother with them."
"You were born for a reason."
You told him those things
to encourage him.
He didn't shoot the gun.
All the bullets are still in it.
Wim did just what
you taught him to.
I'm so proud of you, Wim.
It's all right.
It's all right, Wim.
By the way,
this town is filled with corpses.
How many guns did you
hand out in this town?
How many people
got guns from you?!
Don't make me any angrier!
Terrible things happen
if you make me angry.
He looked just like
our grandson.
What?
He looked just like
our dead grandson.
He?
He knew us well.
It was as if he was
our real grandson.
Who is he?
You were writing a letter
to your dead grandson.
You were sending
him information.
Who is he?!
He's probably after me.
I'm what he's after.
Yes.
That's right, Mr. Poppe.
No. Franz...Bonaparta...
The heavy rain that continues
to fall in southern Germany
has caused many casualties
along the rivers in Bavaria.
Hey, you smoke too much.
It's all right. I've quit drinking.
You should quit smoking, too.
Dieter, what have you
been drawing all this time?
What do you think?
Does it look like him?
Look like whom?
Like Tenma.
I'm going to give that
to the police.
They don't believe you
at the crucial moments.
So I'll tell them...
"I'm talking about this man."
"This man has gone off
to hunt monsters by himself."
Tenma's going to
come back, right?
Now, a report on the damage.
Due to the Elgar River
flooding,
roads have been
closed in several areas.
Both outbound and inbound railways
have been shut down.
Also, it's become
difficult to get calls through
to areas that have
experienced power failures.
This is an e-mail that
came three days ago.
After talking to Dr. Gillen, we decided
that we should show it to you.
Please show me.
"To Nina..."
"I'll be waiting for you
in Ruhenheim."
Johan...
You think so too, huh?
You described what Johan is trying
to do right now as "a perfect suicide."
You said that lots of innocent people
are going to die.
Ruhenheim...
There is a rural village with
that name in southern Germany.
There's a possibility that
Tenma has headed there.
I've got to go there.
Let me go there.
It really is an odd feeling.
At first, you were someone who
existed in a certain man's delusions.
Yes. You were like a character
in one of your books.
For many years,
I've carried out my investigation
by compiling objective data.
But this time, I ignored all my data
and followed that man's delusions.
As I tugged at the loose ends,
partially for fun,
I met a young man
in the Czech Republic
who visited Red Rose Mansion
very often.
It was your son.
This is a handwritten postcard
that was sent to him.
It's signed K. P. for Klaus Poppe,
your real name.
Even though I've arrived at this place
and you're right before my eyes,
it still feels odd.
It's as if a character from
a picture book has sprung out.
But this is reality.
The list of Czech refugees in
the late 80s that I looked up
included the name
Klaus Poppe.
You fled here after
the fall of the Berlin Wall.
What were you
trying to run from?
People like me?
511 Kinderheim was established
because of your plan.
I was created there.
Were you trying to run
from people like me?
I know what he. ..what the man
named Johan is trying to do.
And it's happening in
this town right now.
Another gunshot!
There were lots of dead people
on the way to this hotel.
What's happened
to this town?!
Hey! Get me out of
here already!
I can't right now.
All transportation has been cut off.
Jeez. What are you doing?!
You go out and come back and
take a shower each time you do.
The town smells of gunpowder
and blood. It's sickening.
Now calm down. I've ordered
hot tea from the front desk.
It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Everything is going to disappear
when the rain stops.
"Disappear"? What will?
All the memories.
I will let you go
on two conditions.
You must go with Dr. Gillen...
And you cannot bring a gun.
I don't need a gun.
I'll get ready to go.
And. ..do what I told you
to do immediately.
Dieter, Eva, you Dr. Reichwein,
Mr. Schuwald, Karl and Lotte...
Everyone that knows Johan
must go into hiding.
Johan is trying to erase
all his memories.
Come on.
Try not to let Dieter see you.
My memories with Dieter...
My memories with you
Dr. Reichwein...
My memories with
Lotte and Karl...
the Fortners...
My memories with
Tenma...
I have memories
I don't want to forget.
Even if I have memories
I want to erase...
Johan is. ..
Johan's memories...
...shouldn't be erased.
A police officer...
His gun's been taken.
Don't move from that spot!
Save this town...
Who shot you?
There have been gunfights
all over town.
First...several armed men
came in.
Before I knew it, the townspeople had
guns and were shooting at each other.
I've got to go and call for help.
I've got to at least
save the children.
Help.
Johan...
The first time I heard
that name was in 1995,
in the statement of
a certain neurosurgeon.
Dr. Tenma.
You admit that your deduction
is now incorrect?
No.
He's still a key witness to me.
To me, Johan is still just a fabrication.
"Fabrication"... I was obsessed by
this term throughout my vacation.
What does a person who actually
exists have to do to become a fabrication?
The answer is simple.
Erase everyone who knows him and
everyone who knows about his past.
In the end, Mr. Bonaparta, it'll be just
like the ending of your picture book.
"At last he had
found a name"'
"but there was no longer anyone
around to call him by it."
"And Johan was such
a wonderful name."
If that's what's going to
happen to this town.
That's what I'd do if I were Johan.
I'm also a fabrication.
I'm not Newmeyer, the man
whose name is written in the ledger,
nor am I Wolfgang Grimmer.
I am nobody.
I'll disappear with the person who
took my memories and my name.
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting here
for my verdict.
I'm not afraid to die. But I don't
know how to make amends.
But I will accept everything that
happens to me.
You've been waiting?
You're not afraid to die?
Do you know how terrible
the things you did were?!
Do you know what it means to destroy
the root of good and evil in a person?!
Do you know what happens when
you awaken the monster within people?!
People... People should think
that meals taste good.
They should look forward
to picnics on weekends.
They should think that a beer
after work tastes good.
People should...
feel sad from the bottom of
their hearts if their child dies.
I won't let you die.
I'm going to get you
out of this town safely
and have you make
everything public.
You're going to
reveal to the world
the identity of the monster
that you awakened.
Until then, I'll protect you.
Where is Johan?
I-I don't know.
Someone's behind this massacre.
Where is he?
I-I don't know.
Another gunshot...
Is someone here?
Can you see me?
Look. I'm not holding anything.
It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I've come to help you. Relax.
It's dangerous here, got it?
Get out of town.
Don't cry! I'll take you to
the path through the woods.
You can run, can't you?!
Th-There's a man giving orders
from the Hotel Bergbach.
I see.
Even so,
this is my only gun.
These two were outside.
Sorry.
This all happened because
I won the lottery.
If only we had informed the police
earlier that we found Conrad's body...
Before the town
went mad...
You bought these?
I-I haven't fired a single shot!
Honest!
Let me borrow this one
and this one.
You protect this hotel.
What about you?
Even ordinary citizens
are carrying guns.
I'm a detective.
I can tell the difference.
Oh yeah. Mr. Grimmer...
Let me buy you a beer
when this job is over.
Yes, please...a good beer.
Now!
Run!
Please, live!
Make it Home - Fujiko Hemming
Kuniaki Haishima
Yes.
Gazing at what is now known in this world.
Make it Home - Fujiko Hemming
Kuniaki Haishima
Yes. Your eyes believe in kindness...
Make it Home - Fujiko Hemming
Kuniaki Haishima
Make it home. To your land of harmony...
Make it Home - Fujiko Hemming
Kuniaki Haishima
Make it home. To your land of purity...
Chapter 71
"The Wrath of the Magnificent Steiner"