You're gonna find her!
Tell me where Papa is.
What's going on with him, tell me?
I'm going to take a picture of you.
about much information on the East German government and its party.
The Liebertheus family and their two children look very happy.
They're very happy to be in West Germany where they're very well kept.
The family will first stay in Dusseldorf
and live in an apartment that's been given to them by the authorities.
That's what they've set.
l feel as though l never slept at all.
Don't even think about it. You have to get up, my dear.
The news is about you.
The operation was performed in the Eisler Memorial Clinic in Düsseldorf.
Clinic director Heinemann has just given a press conference.
The diagnosis of Mr. Rosenbach is subarachnoidal bleeding
due to a burst brain artery.
The operation went well and the aneurysm could be clamped down.
Mr. Rosenbach has a lot of fans around the world.
Will he be able to sing again?
We're doing everything in our power to get his voice back.
Dr. Heinemann and his team have already performed
numerous complicated operations.
With this complicated and successful operation,
he has once again established his reputation in medical circles.
I'm proud of you, Kenzo.
The news is not about me. It's about your father.
You're right about that.
But thanks to your excellent work in your father's team,
you contributed a lot to it last night.
My father will be very grateful to you,
because you are the one who helps his clinic to its good reputation.
No, I'm the one who should be grateful
that your father allows me, a Japanese,
to work in a German clinic.
Go on, Kenzo.
Stick to my father, then everything is possible.
It's just a matter of time
before my father becomes the head of the clinic.
And then you'll be the head of surgery.
And one day you'll be the head of the clinic.
And I'll be the head of the clinic's wife.
I need a strong and successful man by my side.
Are we going for a walk or are we staying here?
Blood pressure 128 to 64.
Skeleton splinter.
I'm mauzing down the pyramids.
As always this was great work, Dr. Tenma.
I thank you.
But you seem to be talented at the operating theater.
So young and already about to be the head of the clinic.
The hospital and the head of surgery appreciate you very much.
And they have even conquered the first-name of the hospital director's daughter.
W-What do you want to tell me, Dr. Beker?
Well. Pardon me, I'm not assaulting you.
But politics is just running in a hospital.
You're aware that the head of the hospital has once used you, aren't you?
The success of the surgery on the opera singer....
was, in itself, considerly. And the press says so proudly about it.
If he uses you in this way it means you are really capable.
Please remember me when you get up.
I'll invite you soon for a drink.
So?
I want him back!
Give me back my man!
THE DOWNWIND
Is this the address?
It's the emergency call from the neighborhood.
Well?
Oh.
That's nasty.
What in the world?
Oh!
There's somebody!
There is a survivor, a girl.
Two dead bodies, a man and a woman.
A young man is critically ill.
I repeat, a young man is critically ill.
The Freelancer
I have to go to the clinic!
Headshot?
He's the onlyונder wounded?
Yes, his parents dying.
It looks like a robbery.
Right, I'll go super-fast.
Have you already told your parents in Japan when you two will get married?
Yes, I have.
But it is not yet certain whether my father will come.
As you know, he runs a small practice all by himself.
That would be a wonderful opportunity for him to take a nice trip abroad.
I see that too. Your family is warmly invited.
Thank you very much.
You have already done so much for me, Mr. Director Heinemann.
When you came to Germany back then, I thought you were a top student.
And now you are actually the number one at the Eisler Memorial Clinic.
By the way, Kenzo.
You are currently dealing with the subject of
dangerous contractions after a subarachnoid bleeding.
Yes, I am creating a model for a subarachnoid bleeding in dogs.
I have to tell you that you will cancel your research.
Cancel?
I have long promised to give a lecture at the upcoming European Congress on Emergency Medicine.
And you should write me a draft for it.
But I worked hard for it.
I'm almost done with my research.
Maybe, but this afternoon there was an accident.
What happened today, dad?
A dubious organization has marched in front of the clinic.
They make us hot as hell because of the operation of this opera singer.
They accuse us of letting a Turkish patient wait in front of it while it was delivered.
There is a big mistake.
The Turkish person was operated first and everything else was a lie.
No doubt, our approach was completely faultless.
Or was it not?
Yes, of course.
These lunatics seem to believe we doctors work out of pure available love.
Of course we save people's lives but on the surface we are scientists.
Anyway. You will write the script for my profession.
I count on you, C Took, my son-in-law.
Thank you very much, Dr Hainemann.
D!
What on earth is he doing up there?
Oh shit!
Where is he?
He has just been brought in.
I acted on instructions from the clinic director and operated on the opera singer.
It wasn't in my hands.
Of course.
Some lives are worth more than others.
Give my husband back to me.
If you had operated on him, he would still be alive.
Give him back to me. I want him back.
Why? Why? Why?
Why?
What's wrong with you, Dr. Tenma?
Wait for me.
Another operation is waiting for me.
Wait, Dr. Tenma.
This is an instruction from the director.
We now have the CT of the mayor.
Please come with me. You have to see this.
Yes, right away.
Wait, Dr. Tenma.
Dr. Tenma.
Everything will be fine. Hang in there.
I'll save you.
Kill him.
I love you.