Embark
Blood pressure 120 to 80
Pulse 92
Thats good
I'll remove the bullet from the carrier
That ball is outside.
The ball has been successfully removed.
Yes, but it's too early to breathe.
Now we need to take care of the damaged
vessel doors!
Of course!
Tie up the problemrats!
Immediately!
I need some sleep.
The death of the Liebert couple...
in the comfort of a local disc quarters...
has left people on the ground.
There is sign of the house has been searched.
They don't know whether it's a crime...
by political nature...
but an investigation continues.
The Lieberts' twins have survived.
The young man suffered a headshot,
but is capable of surgery.
But he's not fully conscious yet...
killed
In other words.
The Eisler Memorial has secured its place as the leading medical
institution in our country
You, being such esteemed colleagues,
have foretold it with the excellent skill
for which I would like to thank you.
Regrettably, the mayor failed to arrive
at our clinic yesterday.
But, as usual, we did everything
that was in our power to do so.
The public won't appreciate
this incident,
so I would now like to ask Doctor Beuer and Dr Eisen
for their appropriate applause for doing everything
to save the mayor's life.
Ahaha, I was reading your article last week.
Very good!
Please continue your research, my boy.
Right?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
an operation is not a single performance but teamwork with only combined forces
we are able to save the lives of people
we
have
You're right. You're an idiot.
Eva!
Good evening Dr. Norden. What a nice suit?
Nothing against your radiant beauty, Miss Eva.
THE FALL OF THE DREAM
Strange story, isn't it?
I read Heinemann's article as a coincidence...
...and so I came to Germany.
I wanted to be trained to be a director.
Dr. Greenblatt can't save lives.
Some lives are worth more than others.
Nonsense. Every life is equally valuable.
I didn't do anything wrong,
and I was supposed to be problematic?
Then what are you?
A doctor?
A devil with money ировать out of Hell?
People like you...
deserve to die.
However, what your name is you are already aware of, am I right?
Your name is Anna Liebert, remember?
that both parents have lost and are now completely on their own.
That obviously stirs people to tears.
As long as no one pays for the immense treatment costs,
you are nothing more than annoying patients for the clinic.
But gentlemen, this kind of press is exactly what we need.
Huh?
This is a free advertising campaign for our clinic.
That alone makes the children of considerable value to us.
Or do you see it differently?
Yes, no, of course.
We have to use it for our purposes.
Release a joint photo of the twins to be published in the press.
Of course.
Requests of this kind have already come several times from the press itself.
What are you waiting for?
A photo that shows the two of them together in the loving care of our clinic
how they bravely fight back in their lives.
But the treating doctor says it's too early for a meeting of the two siblings.
Who is this doctor?
This is Dr. Tenma.
Take him away.
What?
This man should not have a position in which he stands in the limelight.
Dr. Tenma will be dismissed.
Yes, sir.
A heart-warming gift from the citizens.
Would you like some, too?
Yes, thank you very much.
How are you today, Mrs. Hankel?
I'm very well, Dr. Tenma.
I don't even know how to thank you.
I think we can pull the strings soon.
Then you can finally go home again.
Can I really go home again?
Yes, but you have to, as I have explained to you, absolutely.
Of course, I will do that.
prescribe Mrs. Hankel an antiepileptic and a blood pressure-lowering agent.
Please hold on.
What happened?
Dr. Tenma.
We brought her to her brother's room.
Then she started screaming terribly and then ...
Brought to her brother?
Dr. Tenma.
Bring Anna to her room.
Yes, sir.
Dr. Beuer, what does this circus mean?
What's the camera for?
Well, we wanted to capture the twins' moving reunion
photographically for the press.
With whose permission did you do that?
The treating doctor, that's me.
You know that.
That was once.
You were dismissed from the case.
I'll take care of it for you.
And in my opinion, it is completely unthinkable to bring the two together.
How can you ...
How can you put the children on display like that?
An instruction from the director of the clinic.
And I do not advise you to make the same mistake again.
I was the one who saved the boy.
And I have the duty to protect him until he is healthy again.
How interesting.
Look at the boy.
He hardly saw his sister.
Already he stretched out his hand and began to cry.
He regained consciousness and showed a completely normal reaction.
The operation was a complete success.
You did a good job, but that's it.
And now make sure you get out of here, Dr. Tenma.
Damn shit.
Is this supposed to be a joke?
I think you want to make fun of me, don't you?
Instructions from the director that I don't laugh.
These fuckers all think about money and career.
Money and career.
Damn shit.
I...
I didn't do anything wrong.
Hello, I'm back, Dad.
Hello, I'm back, Papa!
Where are you, Papa, are you in your room?
Excuse me, ship, are you still in a meeting this late?
Huh?
Are you listening, dad?
Is it your alarm clock?
I'm coming inside.
People like that deserve to be killed...
I thought we had all died!
Such people
deserve to be death.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah