METEOR BLAST
DOOR TAPPING
Please help.
Police. I am sorry to bother you so early morning.
Are you Dr. Tennemann?
Text & language by MirceaAngelici
Could you not hear me?
There is no one in this shop but the police.
There is no way in. We have to go to our patient.
You still unfairly don't understand.
We absolutely have to keep calm now. How is the emergency response going?
It's pure chaos. Today we have more emergencies than usual.
Two patients urgently need to be operated on.
I understand. I'll take care of it right away.
One patient has a head wound in a traffic accident.
First show me the X-rays. What about the other one?
The other patient had a stroke.
Ah, Doctor. We have a few important questions to clarify.
This is not the right time.
I know, I know, but I'm just doing my job here.
Do you know if the three gentlemen had a fight or had enemies?
Were there any quarrels?
The route you've chosen, your career, you built it yourself.
Now tell me what happened and work it out.
No. Nothing happened.
Doctor Tenma, terrible show! The two children, the refugees!
The children'sivos, they're missing!
what amazing things have he achieved during his life.
Live in peace, Dr. Heinemann.
Rest in peace.
Amen.
Eva, Eva!
It's terrible, but you must be strong!
Leave me alone!
Give me my father back!
In the course of the abduction, a poison that contains salpetic acid was detected.
Salpetic acid, you say?
A muscle relaxant?
Yes, of course.
As a doctor, you know your way around.
Yes, but how did you get the poison?
Over bonbons.
Bonbons?
That's right.
In addition to all three bodies, we were able to find the same bonbon paper.
And the court medicine found bonbon remains in all three stomachs.
Do you happen to know how the three gentlemen got this sweet, but also deadly treat?
No, I'm afraid I have to disappoint you.
How do you intend to proceed with the search for the siblings?
Since we have taken over the case from the BKA from the state police, it will proceed faster from now on.
So don't worry.
If you look at this case from a distance, it would also be conceivable that it is related to the murder of the parents, the Lieber.
Three murdered doctors from the clinic that took in the children of GDR refugees.
Their parents were murdered by someone.
A political background would also be worth considering here.
Most likely, the children play a decisive role in this case.
Please do.
Please do everything to find them.
We'll do our best.
Goodbye.
Shortly before the murder, the clinic director unplugged his family and his daughter's engagement.
A strange coincidence.
But the man had an alibi.
He was at the time in a bar drinking something.
And the witnesses confirmed this.
I would like to ask you a question.
What are you doing with your hand?
Hm?
Ah, that!
I'm guessing that!
I'm tired.
Just very tired.
The healing is going extraordinarily well, Mr. Buchner.
I am very grateful to you, Dr. Tenma.
Then I will be able to work again, yes?
But yes, of course.
If I'm not in the store, it won't take long and I'll be broke.
But please, don't overdo it.
After your discharge, I'll come by for a drink with you to check it out.
Dr. Tenma?
Yes?
There is a rumor that you stop here.
Is that true, Doctor?
I beg you, stay here.
You won't find a doctor like you anywhere.
Please tell me it's just a rumor.
Please don't go.
It is so, Mr. Buchner.
Dr. Tenma, the board would like to speak to you immediately.
There is an urgent need to discuss personnel issues.
Many posts are associated with the era of the former director.
Therefore, there should be some changes.
Dr. Eckner will, as I have heard,
switch to a clinic in Bavaria in the spring.
I understand.
Listen to me, Dr. Tenma.
No matter what the board will say to you, stay strong.
We are all behind you, you should know that.
Please stay with us in the clinic.
I'll say it again.
Your performance is all that matters to me, Dr. Tenma.
I appoint you head of surgery.
Life is insane.
I refuse orders from the Head of Surgery and he disfires me.
Eva is getting divorced,
and when I've aligned myself
with a routine doctor...
You are my family.
My daughter...
Kenzo!
Please wait!
Yes, I made a mistake!
Please forgive me!
Kenzo!
The patient with the spinal tumor has been waiting for a long time.
The suture seems to be very advanced.
I understand.
Then I should operate on him.
That's good news. Thanks a lot, boss!
Prepare everything for surgery.
Yes, sir!
My goodness. This crisp water has to be reissoned sometime in the future.
When the Berlin Wall fell six years ago from them, I hoped that
things would turn out to be better in this world.
But how ...?
Everything is gushing from the European Union,
but no help comes from there either.
From now on we take care of the investigations of the Panzers%,
I see..
Oh ye.. I do not have a hand for that.
I've never let a dragon climb, you have to know.
It was all good for the first time.
Tell me, how was your appointment the evening?
My appointment? Well, she was very nice.
She was very nice?拜拜
I beg you, that was the daughter of a chairman.
Well, not after the meal you just went home right?
Well, unfortunately I received an emergency call while eating food, and I had to return to the hospital immediately.
Are you serious?
Wouldn't you quit putting your work above everything else!
At some point you'll ever be forgiven for theporaphy,
and you'll regret it bitterly.
Hey!ז
Have a little bit of patience, boss.
A dragon.
Good morning, Dr. Tenma.
So, you are Carl, right?
My grandfather gave me him as a present.
But he just didn't quite have the will to fly.
Maybe you just lost your focused.
Do you know anything about it and would you perhaps help us?
In Japan I often let Ken ride dragons.
Hold it high up in the air. As high as possible.
Is that enough?
Yes, exactly.
Let's see whether it works.
And go!
Fly!
Very good
Er fliegt.
Und wie?
Du meine Güte.
Ich an seiner Stelle würde mir 5 Geliebte so zu legen.
Das wäre eine Leichtigkeit für ihn.
Dieser Kerl.
Sie sind der beste, Dr. Tenma!
Bald bist du wieder gesund.
Dann kannst du ihn allein hochsteigen lassen, Carl.
Ja.
We will now remove a minignon near the hypothesis.
We'll choose a paterio-nal entrance on my right
Roger that!
Observe very closely.
The chief surgery physician is operating on me today.
What a fancy attack! Never Danny injured any brain tissues.
It's incredible!
He really is a genius.
You as local pain specialist always have to take care of the brain most of all.
Becareful!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
How do you feel today, Mr. Junkers?
Good day, Mr. Junkers. Do you recognize me?
How many fingers do I show?
How many? Can you answer?
Yes?
Monster is coming. Monster.
Excuse me? Mr. Junkers?
The monster is coming.
Coming? What do you mean, what's coming?
The monster?