What do you mean, Mr. Junkers?
The monster is coming.
Coming? What do you mean, what's coming?
The monster?
The monster is coming.
Every living being is equally important.
And to save lives is my duty as a doctor.
Thank you, Doctor.
I think it will never be too late to start over.
Excuse me. I am looking for a working watch...
Wait a moment, what the fuck is going on here?!
Your date is waiting. We have to go.
It seems to me that it is never too late to start all over again.
I want to make a statement, would it be possible, Dr. Tenma, to call in?
Hm?
Mr. Watchtower?
Hello, Mr. Watchtower?
I need to get a hold of you people.
You little shreds.
You livestead of running through this poor flood right here.
I have been here for a much longer time, thank you!
Pray, dear God, so many people have passed through here today.
This is pre-meditated.
Pray well.
Oh!
Hey, what happened?
I'm gonna get help.
He's dead.
Trampolines!
Mr. Junkers!
Hurry up, Luke!
...
Wait, Mr. Junckers,
this is just like back then.
Toxicated bonbons and a missing patient.
The same as nine years ago!
Junkas!
Stay right there, Junkas!
I was already killed!
Just before my friend Fritz died, he said,
we worked for a cruel monster!
Killing a human has no meaning to them!
Run!
Otherwise he'll kill you too!
Run away, Dr. Thelma!
You talk too much, Junker.
No, I don't!
Don't do that, Johan.
What does Junker know about you?
Nothing at all.
On the other hand, I know everything about you.
I was your doctor.
Your name is Johan Liebert
and you have a twin sister.
Your father's name was Michael Liebert,
an East German government employee.
He fled to the West in 1986
together with his wife and two children.
You have no chance of hiding.
Your identity is known.
Stop it. Be reasonable, Johan.
Johan, you say?
Yes, that's what I used to be called.
But I haven't been called that for a very, very long time.
What? What does that mean?
Nobody knows my past.
Neither the four spouses,
nor the Lieberts.
But with them, it's different.
They saved my life.
And I'll never forget that.
You're like a father to me.
Like a... like a father?
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be standing here right now.
Please don't!
You can't kill him!
Why not?
Well, because...
What does a human life mean to you?
Don't you know that a life is precious?
When I saved you,
I found my calling as a doctor again.
This one surgery nine years ago
made it clear to me
that the life of every human being is equally valuable.
Nobody has the right to kill another.
And this principle
has been firmly rooted in my heart for many years.
What's so funny about that?
Doctor, as far as I know,
you were promoted after the accident.
That made me very happy.
You as head surgeon of neurosurgery.
What does all this mean?
The director, the head of surgery,
and the head of the station died back then.
Good for you, isn't it?
I think it's wonderful.
Was that you?
But that's exactly what you said.
That's what you wanted.
I could hear you clearly
when I came to my senses again.
You wanted the death of these three men.
I didn't do anything wrong.
People like that,
people like that
deserve to die.
If you're honest,
I've done you a favor.
Doctor, I'm scared.
Dr. Tenma, help me.
I don't want to die.
Dr. Tenma!
You know,
I should have died back then.
But you brought me back to life.
I don't want to die, please!
I don't want to die!
Doctor, I don't want to die!
This damn rain.
I hate rain.
I'll tell you why.
It ruins Every trace of a crime.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you