was actually an accident.
A key feature for murder was the warrant which was not given anywhere else.
Thus, a sentence of 15 years was imprisoned.
Now then.
You may have your seat, Nina Faulkner.
Thank you, Professor.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
OK, it's raining outside.
Thank you, Nina. You saved us the trouble.
It would fit for a carnival move.
You should be glad to have such a beautiful woman.
I'm here again, Dad.
Yes, right, about the carnival move.
Just now I saw kids who dressed up.
That was probably
because of the carnival move to San afterward.
Oh, you know, I would like to have dressed up as a child.
The three of them were really cute.
Would you like to?
Yeah, but Nena, you did that too.
Or maybe not, Dad.
Dressed up?
Yes, of course.
Let's see, where is the picture?
Ah, there it is.
You see?
Ah.
Oh.
Are you sure?
That was just a tiny breeze back home.
You remember?
Huh? Yeah, but was it really?
And so I have to wait. Wait for a spring that never comes.
Hanna.
Oh, Hanna, you're burying yourself again in your love sorrow.
Hanna!
Abort you with the most beautiful flowers,
On my own to satisfy this desire and I was born.
How lovely. Of whom this may be...
Almost fell for it Peter.
How do you feel today Nina?
Very good and this is thanks to your one and only help doctor Gai Gteg.
I'm all right.
Do you find it difficult to understand my question?
No. I...
The motive behind this murder
was in the testimony.
The testimony.
What?
Oh, Nina Fortner now knows better than this.
The time before I was ten years old.
Where are the memories from my childhood?
There.
Yes, that was a good husband and a good person.
Terrible that they had to die this way.
What?
Obxy children?
Yes, when I think about it, there was a point.
I think his name was Michael. He lived with them for two years.
A boy, you say? I don't know if you had a boy.
Yes, there was. His name was Michael. He must have been around 14.
A boy? Michael? Now I have to say it, maybe.
You're from the police, aren't you?
Yes, Michael Reichmann. He was in my class, a student of mine, but I have to admit ...
Well, yes. It would be impossible for me to describe him.
It's a little embarrassing, but I can hardly remember him.
Not even whether he had friends or not.
And there are no more textbooks from that time.
Six years ago, everything was destroyed in a big fire.
Six years ago he lived here in Cologne.
So a boy named Michael.
But his real name is ...
Johan, you say?
Yes, that's what I used to be called.
What's that? Who are you?
But what good is it to me if I know that?
What I know is that you have a twin sister.
That you kill people.
I don't have to know more.
What am I actually doing here?
Twins. That's it.
That's with his sister.
I'll pick you up soon.
Who is that?
Who writes that he will pick me up soon?
What does that mean?
A child?
Yes, they had one.
Seven, eight years ago.
Exactly, the Heiners who were murdered back then adopted a boy.
How was he, the boy?
How he was, you ask?
Well, that's quite a long time ago.
Besides, he lived with the Heinau family for at most a year.
I can't remember anything that would help you.
Was there also a boy, maybe a girl here?
No, just this boy.
In any case, I would like to forget the terrible murder of the couple.
It was all so terrible for us that we almost moved.
Yes.
I knew the boy pretty well.
Huh?
Come up. I'm making tea right now.
Sit down.
Gladly. Thank you very much.
It doesn't take long.
You should sit down.
Sit down.
Have a drink.
The tea is ready.
Thank you.
You're a doctor, aren't you?
I know as the lad.
You're Doctor Thenma, am I right?
Yes.
He writes to you. He picks you up.
Who is he?
I don't know.
The emails I get don't have an altman.
Well, you're getting Melissa's treat.
You must believe a beautiful prince
will have to hang around on a cabbage patch.
Oh, I'm going out, I'll be right back.
Hey!
But the professor doesn't seem to notice him at all.
That's exactly what I mean. And you know what?
He's staring at you all the time, Nina.
Huh?
That must be him!
What? Who?
Well, who else?
Of course, your prince charming.
I can tell you that the boy was extremely grateful to you, Dr. Tenma.
He said you saved his life and were more than a father to him.
Can you tell me what the boy's name was?
Franz. But that wasn't his real name, he said.
He must have trusted him very much, otherwise he certainly wouldn't have talked about it.
This boy suddenly appeared out of nowhere.
The Heilaus across the street were childless. They had adopted him.
He lived with them for about a year.
Well, to be precise, 14 months.
From March 1987 to April 1988.
Then one day he disappeared without a trace.
He was very intelligent and knew how to behave.
Quite unusual for a twelve-year-old boy.
At least you wouldn't expect it.
Did he come here to your apartment?
Yes, every day.
I've been living alone for a long time and have liked to receive him very much.
He was always sitting in this chair and was diligent.
Even had fashionable learning.
I taught him English and French,
and he learned extraordinarily fast.
When one day he disappeared,
He mastered both languages almost perfectly.
At only twelve years.
Tell me, what else do you remember?
Was there anything else?
He listened very patiently to me when I told him something.
Especially on one topic.
The boat stopped, it went quaking,
and we were scared to death.
It took a total of 38 hours
until we escaped from this hell.
Children love stories like this,
but my son wasn't like this.
It felt like he was possessed.
What fascinated him most was fear.
Yes, the fear of death.
He was curious about how people interacted with death.
He wanted to know everything.
He enjoyed fear.
scared him to death.
What impression did he leave on you when he heard this story?
Well, his eyes were holding up, and he was smiling...
probably.
Probably?
I couldn't see it. I'm blind.
He always said.
Where is she?
She is in Heidelberg.
See you later.
See you later and please drive carefully, yes?
Sure.
I have to go. See you later, dad.
Good. Take care of yourself.
See you later.
Soon it's time.
I don't know.
That's how we decided.
When she turns 20, she should find out that she is not our biological daughter.
Hey, wait, please. I can't do this alone.
But you wanted to meet him.
We told him that you would meet here today.
Good luck with your dream prince on the white mold.
See you later.
Clara! Beate!
Thank you for your support.
Look, there he is.
Now it's getting exciting.
Hello, Nina Fortner?
Yes, that's me.
I am... My name is Otto Rubermann.
Hello.
Who?
Who is that?
I know you.
But where?
Who are you?
Who?
Nina!
Nina?
What's going on?
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Nina!
What's going on?
Open your eyes!
Nina?
What happened?
Nina!