Mr. Maurer, could it be that you haven't showered again?
It can't go on like this.
You promised to take a shower at least every two days.
Do you remember?
That's good. Take care of yourself.
A visitor is waiting for you at the reception.
I'm going home now.
So you have to take care of him yourself, Mr. Maurer.
A visitor? Now at this time?
He hasn't showered in a long time either.
At least he smells just as uncomfortable as you do.
What you don't say.
Well, let's see.
There are good reasons why I don't have time to shower.
Without me, this lousy place would no longer exist.
It is unique and alone to thank the dear Maurer.
But that doesn't interest anyone.
As always.
Good evening. What gives me the honor?
Good evening. My name is Tenma.
I'm here because I need your help.
My goodness. You really look taken in.
So, so. So you're a doctor.
Difficult to imagine.
Whatever, doctor.
Let me summarize your story again.
You are of the opinion that there will be more victims in this murder series.
And here in Heidelberg, at least you suspect that.
A middle-aged couple who has an adoptive daughter
When the girl turns 20, the perpetrator comes and gets her.
And on this occasion, he will kill the parents.
You don't know the adoptive parents or the girl.
And you don't have an address either.
If you ask me, that's pure paranoia, doctor.
That's not funny. You have to believe me. Please.
That's nonsense.
A story like this is not even worthy of a Drip-Class 덮 기본 sweetie.
I didn't come here to deliver a story to you.
The twins left the clinic at the time.
But until they finally showed up again,
endless six months had passed.
And what do you conclude?
Well, I guess sooner or later it swallowed them both up.
To Heidelberg.
As you say it yourself. You suspect it.
And I suspect you were adopted by the couple
where the sister lives today.
the boy will probably lead the couple away again after a short time
In fact, he even admitted that he hasn't emailed you any of those enchanting emails.
Oh yes?
The trigger for your inability was a young man you saw at their back?
Yes...
Please describe this man.
I find it hard to describe... I sålo saw him for a short time...
What about his first impression? How did you sense him?
I felt a great longing deep inside.
Ah.
But, well, no, I don't know how to call it, but...
But?
Like...
Calm down Nina.
Don't overdo it.
The real evil!
I can't quite put it into words but...
The most important thing is not to force yourself, but to look ahead calmly.
Yes…
Do not worry.
Do sports, then your worries and anxieties about sweating will pass.
Mr. Maurer, did you stay again at this time?
Yes…
Have you interredted this worker in the archive and let him work?
This man in the archive?
He said, after you visited him and asked him what he was going to do about it,
he'd have let you do it.
That idiot is still here?
Damn it.
Hey, listen. It's lighten...
Hello.
Are you alright?
Hey.
Yes, the sweater is finally ready.
Do you remember how cute and small her sweaters were back then?
Do you really want to tell our Nina?
Tell her that she is not our biological daughter?
We can leave it as it is.
You are right.
It is not necessary to tell her.
Nina is and remains our daughter.
I'm home!
Hello darling.
Ahh… am I hungry?!
There is no problem with just looking forward.
Yes. I will do this. Dr. Geidel is right.
Tomorrow, on your birthday I'll meet you at 7 o'clock at Heidelberg Castle.
Tomorrow at Heidelberg Castle!
Rhéa really has enough to do and I've been foraging through this mountain of rubbish with
all of you for 2 days.
You should finally give up.
Listen, Doctor.
Agreed, only accepted.
I would actually try to get my wife back.
Do you really think he'd come back?
Yeah, if you quit smoking.
Huh?
The devil himself was on the scene here.
If the offender were to walk over the path here one day,
I'd kill him without refraining any fear.
Neckarstrasse 16.
That's the place.
Good evening, excuse the late intervention.
I must say I met some...
How do you call these people though?
Turkeys, chickens, and loincloths.
These are architectural terms.
They recognize magic,
Bunuvaras,
above an upsidedown không defendândôrâuis,
and that means
The woman had a cake standing in the hallway. A birthday cake.
Huh?
Nine years ago, you took a twin as hostage!
The girl is still living with you, right?
Please go!
We have raised Nina as our legitimate daughter!
Please don't destroy our peaceful life!
Get out of here!
Leave us alone!
About nine years ago, you took these twins hostage.
The boy had a surgical scar on his head
and the girl lost her memory.
That's right, right?
Listen, Mr. Fordner, we've got to notify the police immediately.
Your daughter's life is in danger. Do you copy?
But, Mr. Morlow...
H-How can I help you?
We need to speak to your daughter immediately.
No, that won't do. She's not home right now.
delicious. Not home. Where is she?
Probably at Heidelberg castle.
She said she's meeting a friend there today.
Lend me your cart, please.
One moment. First, we have to give the police some respect.
We don't have time to explain-
Quick, my keys!
I understand. Go and I'll explain to the police.
Thank you, sir.
One more thing, Doc.
Britney, watch your head.
As I said, he is an ice cold target.
Just look after yourself!
Yes, Mr Mauer!
Try to come back alive,
and then I'll stop smoking
how I think a quack hospician has.
Your wife will be happy then.
So, how am I just supposed to tell the police that?
Is our daughter really in danger? What's going on?
Please, tell me what happened.
Do not worry, I need your phone quickly.
Did Nina poop something?
What do you know? Please explain it to us.
Calm down.
That's not possible.
The line's dead.
ANAMNESIS
I hope you´re alright, Anna.
He should have been here ages ago. It´s already seven.
So this was all just a prank, and I fell for it.
I´ll get to work.
No! You won't.
You'll wait here.
You're not going anywhere.
Who are you?
I was hired.
You're Nina Fortner, am I right?
Do you remember me?
I'm Dr. Tenma, the doctor.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Anna...
Dr. Tenma...
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Are you...
the prince on the white mold?
What do you want here?
You're bothering me.
You shouldn't be here.
Only she should wait here.
That's what he said.
The girl stays here.
Otherwise...
I won't get any money!
He said no one would come!
Damn it!
Are you hurt?
No, just a little surprised.
Do you have anything to cut?
Anything?
Yes.
Who asked you to do this?
I don't know!
And when did this guy want to be here?
No idea. He didn't say that.
He just said he had something important to do.
Oh my god.
At your place?
Let's go home.
We have to go home as soon as possible.
But why?
I'll tell you later.
Now we have to go.
Quick, Anna!
Anna?
Hurry!
Damn it!
The rope is too tight!
Now you tell me right now
who you are and what you want?!
Besides, my name is not Anna,
it's Nina.
No.
When you came to the hospital nine years ago,
your name was Anna.
And your.
And your brother,
your brother was called John.
My brother.
I told you.
I want his brother.
And his sister,
his wife,
and his grandson.
I want them.