No.
They're gonna explain, who they really are and what they want.
Besides, my name's not Anna!
My name is Nina!
No.
The name was Anna,
when you was into the hospital from nine years...
And your if your brother's...
Your brother's was Joan.
My brother?
John! Anna!
I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's
a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
l dare speak to you.
Mr. Maurer, hear me!
Mr. Fortner, Mrs. Fortner, l'm Stenma.
l brought Anna, l mean Nina, home with me,
hello Mr. Maurer!
Drive and l'll contact the police.
The police were obviously not here.
Oh my god.
Come on, breathe, you must breath blev.
Breathe.
Come on.
You have to breathe.
Come back.
Come back, please.
Mr Maucher...
Here's one of your favorite cigarettes.
Kate grunting
Back then...
I killed him, didn't I?
Kill him,kedl
I killed...
I killed him...
I've killed him.
Nina.
That's impossible. I killed my brother back then.
And I...
I brought him back to life.
Come on.
The power line is still dead.
We need to get out of here,
before he gets back to get you.
Dear Lord!
Is this...
Is this man supposed to be...
I... I can't tell...
...what You're thinking...
Listen!
A road check.
We're saved.
Good evening. We are on the on the lookout for a fugitive runner.
Uh... sorry!
Oh come on!
Those are the gentlemen commissions Messner and Mueller
That's right. Good evening!
I assume you're on your way to the directive officecharges?
Hey, a brand new service car
Wh....what does that mean?
In a very short time, he looks like a pig again
We have no dolls for cars
Uh, excuse me
Would it be possible to get a gist of the situation
I think she's in pretty bad shape
What?
Yeah, but of course
Tell me, did the two of them perhaps do something?
The two of them did something? No, not at all.
What does that mean?
Are these two men real police officers?
But where does the blood come from?
And who put off the emergency call?
And the blue light?
What am I supposed to do?
Everything all right, Dr. Ten Ma?
How?
How do you know that?
I've given you my name, but you didn't mention once that I am a doctor.
Where do you get this information from?
I understand that you don't have an appetite, but you have to drink something.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I don't know what I'm talking about
The man and the woman encouraged us to do so.
Then my brother said,
I have a good plan.
And a little later,
a little later, the man and the woman were dead.
All these people who were good to us,
they all had to die.
But on that day I finally understood why they had to die.
Then I finally understood.
Is that the day when the Lieberts were killed?
My brother killed them.
He killed them both and all the others too.
He killed them all.
My brother killed them all.
I didn't know what to do and took the gun.
And then I aimed at my own brother.
He just laughed and said,
said to me very calmly,
Don't forget to throw the gun out of the window when you've shot.
You have to shoot me right in the head.
I shot him in the head.
I aimed and yet you,
you saved him.
If you hadn't saved him then,
then dad and mom would still be alive.
Why did you save him? Why?
You wait here for me.
I'm going to the police.
If the men were real police officers last night,
we have to assume that Johan has connections to the police.
I absolutely have to know that.
Listen to me well, Nina.
Your brother will definitely be looking for you.
You have to be careful and hide.
Eat something, drink hot coffee and sleep a little.
Then you will definitely feel better soon.
You are alive and that's all that counts.
You have a future and you live.
Try to look ahead.
Do you already know anything about the perpetrator?
Is there a connection to other murders of spouses?
I assure you that we are doing everything we can to solve the case.
But at the moment I can't give any details yet.
As far as we know, the Fortners had an adult daughter who still lived with them.
Is anything known about their whereabouts?
The search for the daughter is on the rise.
What about the dead journalist Maurer?
Why was he at the Fortners' house?
And who is the Japanese with whom Maurer worked together?
A Japanese? Oh, that sounds very suspicious.
Yesterday evening there was another murder at Heidelberg Castle at about the same time.
Is there a connection?
At Heidelberg Castle?
So he was also killed.
As always, we will inform you as soon as we know more about it.
Excuse me, please let me through.
Hello, listen!
Ah, if these are not our esteemed colleagues from Mannheim,
thank you for making an effort to come here.
The Commissars Messner and Müller.
But of course, we help where we can.
Please tell us how.
How is the state of the investigation?
It's best if we go in to talk in peace.
How are you conducting yourself?
Are you kidding me?
You are real though.
The two Commissars are real.
No!
What should I do?
Hello, this is the Heidelberg Post.
What ? I can not understand you.
Hell is going on here in the editorial staff!
What are you saying?
Who are you?
What's happening on corridor?
who says it?
Nina please don't scare me it's just me it's me
Nina
you don't have to go hiding Angeles
she
Is she...
Nina!
Where is she?
Nina...
Did he take her with him?
I shouldn't have left her alone like that.
Hm.
Dr. Tenma...
You're not at fault.
You've done all the things you did on your duty as a doctor.
It is not their fault.
Please eat the rolls, and if they can,
they can sleep a bit.
Life goes on.
And they will save so many of our people's lives.
Nina Fortner.
I'm begging you.
Nina, tell me, what's your plan?
You wanna kill him again?
I brought him back in life.
that I have brought this monster back to life.
I love you.