but it doens´t matter...
Nina, I ask myself what is your plan ?
Do you plan to kill him a second time ?
I got him back to life!
I got this monster...
...back to life!
I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's
a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
because you are the one who brings glory to his own clinic.
No, I am the one who has to thank you
that your father allowed me to work at a German hospital
that entered Japan.
Back off, Kenso.
My father is the one allowing you to do anything.
It's just a matter of time until my father's preached in the young story.
Then you'll be head of surgery.
And just when the director is...
And I will be the director's wife.
I need a strong and successful husband on my side.
Are we going for a walk or are we staying here?
I will know.
Listen, the gentle lady is taking aower.
She' s no nasty.
It won't take long, I'll be back.
But that's just impossible.
You have to go on a job sometime
and come back sometime else.
And stop all the noise outside.
But there is a man from the police.
Police?
Long time no see, Mrs. Eva Heinemann.
And who are you, please?
I investigated your father's murder case nine years ago.
My name is Runge from the BKA.
Runge.
I understand.
You can go back, Robert.
Oh, yes.
I remember you well.
You are the one who failed to solve the case.
I wonder what you want from me after so long.
Very remarkable.
I would not have thought that you could hold this property after your father's death.
And not only that.
It seems to me that you could even increase your luxurious standard of living.
Have you come to check what I have made of my inheritance
and the findings from my divorces?
Sit down and don't be shy.
If you like something, you can take it home with you.
As long as I have enough to drink, I am satisfied.
Listen, I would like to show you something.
This tie of yours.
A tie?
Do you recognize it?
Well, probably not.
It's been a while.
It has a simple pattern, but if you look closely,
you can see that it is extremely finely woven.
Best quality.
And what about it?
It was not easy to find out that this tie is nine years old.
But the tie comes from a business that made this model
in a limited number for a tribe of well-read customers.
And on the list of those customers, your name appears.
And what exactly do you want to tell me with it?
Mrs. Heinemann, do you remember whether you bought this tie
or gave it to someone?
Possibly it is the key to finding out about another murder.
A murder?
Oh, you know, I have given gifts to a lot of men
and I don't remember every single one.
In addition, all the men who talk to me
have only looked at my money.
Please try to remember.
As I said, I don't know.
In the end, they all just want my money.
There is no one who loves me from the bottom of his heart.
That is the sad truth.
In return, I have scrubbed some of them as well as I could
in three divorces.
Haha! They lost some!
Do you want something of me?
Do you want something?
Just say it.
But it may be very expensive to you.
We'll see you later and
if something comes to your mind, please notify.
Next time you come by,
bring a bottle, alright?
Goodbye.
He's been hospitalized.
They want him to sleep there.
Eva?
Eva, please tell your father l didn't do anything wrong.
I only operated the patient who was in the line.
As everyone would have done regardless.
Eufa, please.
But this is...
your engagement ring, isn´t it?
Vater is right, you are an idiot.
Eva!
Good evening, Dr. Norton. What slender suit you've chosen!
You have nothing against your brilliant beauty, Ms. Eva.
Robert! Go get the cart ready!
Dr RED!
Yeah, sir!
But thanks to you, Doctor, I can...
You also fought very bravely.
Thanks to your genius, I will not only be able to experience my daughter's wedding, but also the wedding of my grandchildren.
You are the best doctor I know.
Please stay with us at this clinic for a long time.
Excuse me, Dr. Tenma. There is a visitor for you.
I have a visitor now. Please tell him that I have something to do and send him away.
But...
Eva!
It's been a while, Kenzo.
It is.
Good.
A lot has happened since then.
Can you hear me, Papa? Are you already asleep at this time?
I'm coming in now.
Dad!
Yes!
Eva, Eva!
This is horrible, but you need to be strong now.
Leave me alone!
Give me back my father!
Give me my father back!
Kenso?
Please hold on.
I made a mistake.
Kenso?
Kenso!
Kenzo.
You lost a bit of weight, didn't you?
Kenso.
I want to make things right.
I've used three failed marriages and divorces to understand
that there was only one guy that ever loved me.
Kenso, it was you.
I have to go.
Kenso!
Just do what you want.
I'll tell the police it was your tie.
I'll tell them everything.
That you murdered my father and the others 9 years ago.
That it was your work.
What's he doing?
Look at her.
Take her back to Dr. Tenner
and make her a witness immediately.
But in a похожsofW flavor but will make her t
erroristic by the.
Lately, I've been hearing some peculiar rumors.
Not that I'll listen to anything of them.
Think about it for a minute.
Wait! Wait!
Dr. Tinma!
Hello, what is it?
What? The police?
Doctor Tenma was a suspected murderer.
Close all passages in that compartment
and don't forget the small memes.
Roger!
All right.
Wait, Dr. Tenma.
It's all going to be all right.
Hold on.
I will save you.
I didn't do anything wrong,
and I was supposed to be problematic?
What the Are You Then?
A hellish yellow demon drover?
These people...
deserve death!
I don't want to die.
Dr. Tenma!
You should have seen me die.
But you kept me alive.
Get out of here!
It's got to be bloody hot.