I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's
a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
You were with the French Foreign Legion.
After that, in 1979, you fought as a soldier in the war in Nicaragua.
From 1981 to 1984, you supported the government-enemy guerrillas in Afghanistan.
In 1987, you were in Mossad's fight against radical Islamists,
although you played a decisive role.
You have a lot of war experience, that's for sure, am I right, Hugo Bernhard?
You have a lot of war experience, that's for sure, aren't I right, Hugo Bernhard?
And anyone who performs any training with you will certainly fight very well.
As a combat-hungry veteran, you are indeed highly sought after as a teacher.
I would really appreciate it if our new members could enjoy such a training.
give my employees any information.
I understand.
Actually, anyone who comes to me has to learn to shoot from scratch.
But I've never had anyone who's ever made one shot land.
Start!
Don't fall asleep!
Let's go, start!
Yes, yes!
You need to walk a little faster!
Faster!
Hold the tension, man.
Put your hand to mine.
I said hurry up.
Hah!
I really have to say, you jump much better than me!
You're still lazy, Hunchback.
A mountaineer.
He's probably looking for food for his sheep.
THE LAST MISSION
Not hungry from all the hard training you had?
Uh...
But...
Money is education.
Yes of course.
To hate them all their lives.
That's something that happens if you deal with guns.
If you don't like that, you better cut them.
What's that?
Smells nice!
What's this?
It smells so good.
This must be real rope.
Da...
Thank you.
You may now cease.
What does that…
It is time to learn how to walk.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Very well then.
When you're done then you come to the amazing Madex rock behind the house
What .. to the amazing Madex Rock?
There's the shooting range
The shooting range
So, two shots
If shoot you REALLY have to press twice in a row
It increases the chance that they also really kill target
If they don't do it
Then you could pay with your life.
Shit shit shit shit shi-
What is that?
Super!
You are quite skillful in that.
Now, now, now.
And again.
Into position.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What happened?
There was a mountain giraffe.
Wait, it needs to get back in its nest.
Or the cub is dead.
It needs to go back to its mother.
You can just't bring it outside of the nest.
Come on, Jan.
We'll welcome it back.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
can be shot at a human is another question, as soon as he meets his
opposite, he will find out whether he knows how to deal with a weapon or
whether he cannot Hoping himself, I understand what it might empty things for you in the end
are ok mr bronat and you don't happen to know where he is right now
And again, thank you very much for everything
Again
Oh, crap!
You're laughing, aren't you?
Come on.
You know exactly when he just wants to stop.
I can help you.
Alright, you're free to go now.
This way, gentlemen.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you