Huh?
That's my lucky charm. You got that?
You wanted to know something about the murder in this villa, didn't you?
Well, yes. Coincidentally, I saw the perpetrator.
What are you saying?
You saw him?
Do you want to know?
What did the perpetrator look like? Was it a blond man around 20? Come on, tell me.
How do you know that?
That's not important. Tell me something about the perpetrator.
When we become partners, I'll tell you everything.
This is where the guy lives, on the second floor.
I'd be interested in how you know.
I scoped the villa fee of this person all month.
When I was finally ready to get started, this guy showed up.
I looked through the window and saw the two corpses lying on the ground.
I thought I could poison him and make some money, so I followed him.
Well, your innocence has been proven in this case.
I guess we can call the police or whatever you want.
and that's basically where I handled all unnecessary risks.
Hello.
It's pretty hot again today, isn't it?
Listen, I'm looking for someone.
Hey, Doctor, are you in there?
Hello, Doctor?
What did I say? He has a gun.
As a child, I often went for a walk with my mother.
We ran through sunflower fields on beautiful summer days like this.
But that's no longer possible. My mother has been dead for a while now.
Could it be that you were commissioned by someone to commit murder with this weapon?
Was it perhaps a man?
What? A man? A man, yes. One day he approached me in a bar.
Was the man blond and about 20 years old?
Oh, yes. And he had a beautiful smile.
His name was Erich.
This time he called himself Erich.
Erich and I often met and became good friends.
He invited me to his house, to the house ...
the villa of the deputy Springer.
So he lived in this villa?
Yes, he said you had picked him up about a year ago and treated him like your own son.
Wait a minute, I've been watching the villa for a month. I haven't seen such a guy.
You have been very nice people.
In the photo, I am seen with the spouse Springer.
But one thing I could not forgive him.
Huh?
Right in front of your property was a bed with sunflowers.
And he just destroyed them, just so they could build the driveway to the house.
And I told him that this was a very bad thing to do.
And Erich was of my opinion.
And that's why you killed her? Because of sunflowers?
Besides, Erich told me that Springer had a lover.
An affair.
He literally said to me,
I no longer want to be part of the Springer family.
Not a single day.
You have become a stranger to me. I no longer belong to you.
Then he asked me for a favor.
He asked me to eliminate the spouse Springer.
Having a lover is a sin.
My mother was also in love with someone.
That was bad for me.
I'm sorry. This has a different meaning.
Maybe you know where the safe is?
Sure, it's in the office.
Alright.
Doctor, I'll try to moisturizing there.
Did you know that you can erase your past?
If you do not like it, you can simply drag it out.
That's my story.
If I may ask you to leave now.
Oh yes, exactly.
You are Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
He left you a message.
You can find it in the workroom of the villa.
You should definitely take a look at it.
He knew exactly that you would appear here one day.
I still remember Erich telling me...
Your fate is already decided.
Good luck.
Doctor!
I told you.
You don't have him around?
Oh. Did he kill himself?
What a nonsense.
There's an unpleasant cold shower on your back.
Mm?
What's that?
Why are you shivering, Doctor?
If you want it back, get the job done.
Take the money, and come to the bar on Tidewalk St.
Now, start making money and have fun!
Amazing. This is real bomb business.
And the money I got in advance will powers up my drug-specialty.
Attorney. I brought the doctor.
Soon our people will come and save you.
Nobody's coming.
Believe me, they won't come.
Nobody, I can feel it.
Stop the bleeding right now!
Come on, do it!
Or I'll shoot you!
I'll kill you!
I don't want to die.
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid to die?
That's how you all died.
All twelve you killed,
that's how they all died.
That's how it is when you kill people.
Disinfectant and scissors.
You'll have that.
With an arterial bleeding,
the low blood pressure puts her in shock.
I press the injured artery with my fingers.
The wound must be sewn.
I need a needle and thread.
But we don't have that.
Well, then a tacker.
What? A tacker?
Hurry up!
Yes!
Done.
Huh?
What are you doing?
That was just the first aid.
He has to go to a hospital.
A hospital? No way!
That's not possible.
Put him back right now,
or I'll shoot you!
Shoot me if you want.
But if you shoot me,
you'll have to bring him to the hospital.
Let me down here
and then flee.
Go away.
I'll struggle to get my way.
I'm convinced that everyone deserves a chance.
The police are coming.
Stay alive.
You are...
You are an excellent doctor.
Well, what about all the bills?
Hey, Doctor!
Hey, doc! Don't tell me you just left, once I've treated him.
Say something, doctor.
... guard.' market'.
But, to our surprise, we immediately found the killer.
We are not a welfare organisation, are we.
Do you hear me?
Do you hear?
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you