What? You're only here because of the Liebert family?
Then you have no interest at all.
I'm sorry. I'm looking for information.
I don't know anything about an officer who was supposed to have fled ten years ago.
I heard that the Lieberts adopted a twin couple when they used to live here.
I don't know anything about that.
And the owner of the house? Can I contact him?
It's not that simple.
Most of the properties and houses in the GDR used to be owned by Jews who fled from the Nazis.
The socialist government borrowed them from their owners who lived abroad or in West Germany.
The owner of this house also lives abroad. I'm sorry.
Our real estate company is from the West and has only been represented here since the fall of the wall.
We don't know what happened here before.
So, may I ask? I would like to close.
But is there really no one who might remember the Lieberts?
Well, yes. Many officials of the government used to live here.
But after the fall of the wall, most of them moved away.
Those from the interior ministry were in a lot of trouble.
Oh, I remember.
About ten houses away lives a former employee of the GDR Trade Ministry.
Oh, that Liebert…
He shouldn't have risked the escape to the West.
If only he had waited! The GDR would have collapsed soon.
I still can't believe that he fled to freedom and was murdered there.
Do you say that there lived a pair of twins?
A pair of twins, eh?
Yes, now that you mention it, the twins that the Lieberts brought from the orphanage.
An orphanage?
The two children were really exciting.
The Lieberts always wanted children, but it was not granted to them.
What was the name of this orphanage?
A good question.
Was it 511?
Yes, I think that was it.
The institution was called Kinderheim 511.
Kinderheim 511?
Kinderheim 511
The old Kinderheim is to be demolished and a supermarket to be built instead.
Stay down, or you'll get hurt again.
Hartmann.
The development of a child depends entirely on the adults who raise it.
It is our duty to help children find the right path.
Only in this way can they learn to dream and realize their dreams.
Your dreams?
And what do you dream of, Dieter?
Of football.
What?
I wish I had a football.
I understand.
Thank you for the meal.
I hope you'll tell me the whole story of Johann soon.
Yes, I'm sorry we couldn't finish our conversation.
We'll catch up.
I'll get back to you.
Dieter.
Excuse me.
Can I come in for a moment?
Mr. Hartmann?
It's me, Tenma.
Mr. Hartmann!
Mr. Hartmann! Mr. Hartmann!
Is everything alright? Mr. Hartmann!
Mr. Hartmann!
Mr. Tenma!
Dieter!
But what happened?
He fell. He climbed on the chair.
What are you doing?
Ouch! It hurts a lot!
Show me where it hurts.
It hurts a lot!
Quick, you have to call an ambulance.
Yes.
I'll take a look, okay?
Oh my God.
Where did all the injuries come from?
When I press here, does it hurt?
He has two broken ribs.
In addition, the left shoulder is dislocated.
How did he get so injured in a crash?
The ambulance is on its way.
There is no need to worry.
Where did all these injuries come from?
It's all right.
You are no longer needed here.
But...
Your abduction technique seems very professional to me.
It's almost as if you were a doctor.
No.
Tenma.
I knew I had heard the name before.
I would say you are a doctor.
The one who is wanted for murder.
The injuries.
Where did all these injuries come from in his body?
You should get out of here as soon as possible.
I didn't just call the ambulance.
I also called the police.
Mr. Hartmann.
Tell me right now where the boy got these injuries.
That's none of your business.
And I'm not going to let a wanted murderer tell me anything.
The typical behavior of a blind criminal.
That's what you did to him.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't do that.
You abused the defenseless boy.
Abused?
Now stop it.
That's a bad excuse.
Isn't it, Dieter?
What are you going to do now?
I'm taking the boy to a hospital.
First murder and then child abduction.
Don't move.
You run straight into the police's arms.
You walk straight into the arms.
You'll be okay.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I don't want to go.
I'm scared.
You don't have to be afraid.
The doctors will fix you up.
It hurts so bad.
They used to make me look healthy.
What are you saying?
You've got injuries all over your body and you've never been in a hospital before?
I'm scared.
The world we live in is evil and full of evil.
And that's why I have to get big and strong.
Very strong.
Did Mr. Hartmann tell you that?
This world is black.
And the future too.
That's not true.
The world is not black.
That's a lie.
Really?
Absolutely.
Oh, your football.
I almost forgot about it.
Tomorrow the world will look better again.
Please forgive the delay.
That doesn't matter, but it could take a while for him to be treated.
The emergency room is full today.
But couldn't you move him?
I'm sorry, there was a serious accident.
We still have to interrogate the truck driver.
He can talk with a broken leg.
He has to be treated first.
Then you can take him from me.
Well, then we'll probably have to be patient.
I have to... I have to do something.
Please, you have to take good care of the boy.
Nurse, you must not trust anyone under any circumstances.
No matter who comes to get him.
I thank you.
But...
Is the accident site clear?
No, the streets are still closed.
Oh, my God.
What am I supposed to do now?
What am I supposed to do with Dieter?
He should actually go to the police.
But I can't let myself be seen.
The girl came down to a home in another district.
I don't know more.
Another home?
That's it.
You want to put a child in our care?
Do you know how late it is to just show up here?
I know, it takes a lot, but the boy, he...
I'm aware that the boy is being abused.
But I don't even know who you are.
I am... I...
And we can't just take the child of a stranger here.
Wait!
Can you tell me if a certain Anna Liebert lived here?
Anna Liebert, you say?
You are friends with Anna Liebert?
Then Anna was actually here?
Ah, our Anna.
When was the last time you saw Anna?
And is she well?
Yes, she studies at Heidelberg University.
Who would have thought?
Then she must be happy.
She was such a treasure.
I remember that Mr. Liebert adopted her.
Together with her twin brother.
What was his name again?
Johan.
Ah, that's right, his name was Johan.
The two of them were a heart and a soul.
Really bad that at first they were housed in separate homes.
Before the two twins came to us,
they only had each other and were completely on their own.
They had been found near the Czechoslovakian border.
They held each other's hands and shivered in the cold.
Mr. Liebert first wanted to take Johan with him at home,
but the boy wanted to leave his sister alone in the world for nothing,
so he ended up taking both of them.
And so Anna finally found a fulfilled life.
There are supposed to be terrible conditions in the children's homes of the GDR.
Don't compare us to Kinderheim 511.
Inge, you can't go to the toilet there.
Come on, my little one.
Mom!
Don't cry, it's all right.
You don't have to be afraid.
Come on, you can do it on your own, can't you?
These children have not experienced parental love.
For the development of a child, love and affection are essential.
In many homes of the GDR, it was bad for years.
Every home had a number.
Here in the 47th, we made every possible effort to make it different.
To give the children a worthy home,
according to the best of our abilities.
Against what the State wanted from us.
I didn't want to ever be like Kinderheim 511.
Officially, both the Special Homes and the Ministry of the Interior
were being staffed by the Special Homes.
Do you know what güzelich I want to do?
no
The Ministry of the Interior actually kept the thread in hand.
It was back when the GDR regime was operating.
This is the example of the DDR regime.
This is the experiment lab.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you