Inge,
you're not needed in the bathroom.
Come on, my dear.
Mother!
Don't cry.
It's okay, you don't need to be afraid.
Come on, you can do it on your own, can't you?
You feel better?
We always responded to what the state demanded.
To never become like Kinderheim 511.
Officially, the special home is under both
the Department of Health and the Ministry of the Interior.
Do you know what the photo suggests?
No.
In fact, the Ministry had the final say.
Back then, the GDPR regime operated there.
A lab for experiments.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
Thanks.
It's okay.
Lord...Leader.
Are we not really going back?
We're making a little detour.
But I don't want to go back!
No, no, I don't want to!
Dieter.
Dieter, listen to me.
Are you a good boy?
Huh?
What did you do?
I told you not to trust anyone until I'm back.
But why?
This man is the caretaker of the boy.
And he was very friendly and very outgoing.
Much friendlier than you.
Excuse me.
But the man, he took the boy ...
You should know that the boy went with him voluntarily.
Dieter!
Dieter?
It's not here.
Hartmann's office.
Yes, but it's always the same place.
Where is this place?
I don't know.
Johan.
But who is the man standing next to him?
Of course.
The photos were all taken in the Kinderheim 511.
Both the old photos and the new photos.
All people who stayed in the Kinderheim at the time have died.
Teachers and orphans massacred themselves.
Dieter.
He doesn't have it.
Dieter!
Wait, Dieter. I'll be right with you.
Go up here and look.
Just look up and see.
I asked you, saying,
Well, yes.
Why aren't you like John?
Why can't you be like him?
Tell me why!
Stop it, Hartmann!
If you hurt him again, I'll shoot!
Get out of here!
This is none of your business.
Peter, come downstairs with me.
Dr. Tenmar.
You're looking for John?
Did I hear that right?
I'm wondering what you expect of him.
Do you really think that you can just turn him off?
Well, never mind.
But I'm going to give you one more tip.
This means if only you promise to disappear and leave us alone.
Search for General Wolf.
He was the first to discover Johann's talent.
Find him. He should be alive.
Is this the boy in the photo? In your working room?
The one who is standing in front of the orphanage with Johan?
Yes, he brought Johan here.
He definitely knows more than I do.
And now they are disappearing.
Do you hear me, Dieter?
If you want to come down to me, then get up.
You can decide freely.
Don't be afraid.
As soon as Hartmann puts his finger on the trigger of the rifle, I'll shoot.
Dieter!
You decide that alone.
That's your decision alone.
You can't separate from me at all, can you?
Or do you really want to do that, Dieter?
After all, you are my son and I am your father.
Do you understand now, Dr. Hartmann?
Do you understand now, Dr. Tenma?
So, disappear!
Dieter, don't!
Yes, very good.
Everything is fine.
Come down.
To me.
What is this?
Dieter, come back, my boy!
Dieter, please come back!
Dieter, can you really do it without me surviving?
Dieter, stay!
Stop it, Hartmann, or I'll shoot!
I love you, my boy!
Dieter!
You know the world is dark and the future is pitch black.
Mr. Tenma told me that tomorrow everything will be better.
Don't leave me!
Be brave, little one.
Don't be afraid.
Dieter!
It's impossible, I can't take you with me!
I can't take you with me!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you