The patient has no money and says in delirium again and again that I should not bring him to a doctor.
For the treatment costs, I put money on the table.
Damn! What does the guy think of himself?
Doctor, where do you want to go?
Describe him. What did he look like?
He looked Asian and he had a boy with him.
And what am I supposed to do with Mr. Fink now?
Let him have his sleep.
This man has only taken emergency measures, what makes him so angry?
Those were no emergency measures.
I have never seen such good work before.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
I'm going to show you how to do it!
We don't need controlled respiration.
The man is not Tenma.
His name is Dr Chang.
I am very sorry doctor, I fooled you.
He is also asian, that's why I tricked him.
I am sorry, this shouldn't have happened.
The doctor in the hot spot has made pretty big eyes,
Such a sucessful operation did not happen once again
in such a small villagelike praxis.
Tenmar!
Will you let this young doctor go?
I wanted to give him something to eat,
but he and the boy have left.
Tenmar!
Do not leave them here!
With us in the village you are safe!
You do not have to flee!
Dr. Schumann?
Dieter, you like it here in the village too.
That's true.
With him here, Dieter would be well taken care of, wouldn't he?
Of course! And you too!
Our whole village would protect you from the police.
Stay with us and treat the people with me.
The village needs you and you know that.
I know, but I have to go. I can't help it.
Why?
Do it well. Take care of Dieter.
Tenma, wait! I'm coming with you!
If you stay here, we can save the lives of many people in this area.
You and I, we work together.
Save the lives of many people.
Well, that's not possible. I have to kill a man.
What are you saying?
Tenma!
What do you mean by that, Tenma?
You can't kill! Never!
On the contrary, they give everything to save the lives of people.
He's really going. He's going and no one can stop him.
Go with him, Dieter.
You have to go too, because if you're with him, he won't get out of the way.
You'll have to be careful with him.
I love you.