If i understand you correctly ...you threaten me.
But no...
I am only interested in the truth.
That's a bit thin to support the theory, don't you think?
Did you look at the customer list of the woman?
Well, I tried, but the data is encrypted.
Not that easy.
I'll do it. Give me the floppy disk.
Really? But, Mr. Commissioner, you already have all your hands full.
No problem, I can do it.
I have a question that I have wanted to ask you for a long time.
And that would be?
I have a question when you find time to sleep.
And what does that have to do with the case?
Your question is irrational.
And when do you want to tell him, Mother?
Believe me, it's not that easy.
You know, he doesn't listen to me anyway.
He's never done that before.
But you have to tell him. It's very important.
Be so nice and speak a little quieter.
He's sitting over there in his study.
What? He is at home?
Ronge, it's about the prosecution of this prostitute.
Leave the mayor in peace.
Interesting. Is there a problem?
And whether big problems.
High animals from the Ministry of the Interior are annoying me.
I'm very sorry. Please deal with it as usual.
and also he works with some quite questionable methods.
For example women from the red light sector are housed on the promenade..
..that's how they're supposed to find information pretty easily.
You should prefer to be careful!
Dad, are you sure you didn't notice I was pregnant?
I assume you're taking the baby's father?
I have a lover.
But that'll probably be going out of season...
like everything else. You'll see.
There.
I guess you are marrying the father of the child.
I have a beloved one, but you probably left your case as did everything else.
But now you know.
Yes.
Commissioner, this is the secretary speaking of Voltzmann.
I will tell you everything, please come.
I understand, see you later.
I'm on my way.
I might be off. I'll explain after.
Mr. Commissioner...
What's the matter?
The secretary... he killed himself.
Daily annoying
It states here, Mr. Boltzmann is innocent.
The secretary written that in his last note
Listen, Runge, Inspector Kaminski will hand over this case immediately.
And also the murder of Reineke and two weeks ago ...
... the murder of the Galand company boss.
And what case are you giving me?
I have no more case for you, Mr. Runge.
You'll never get rid of it.
If it looks like it, I'm just in time for you,
Dr. Avery.
Well?
Mr. Commissar, I'm sorry, you have a visitor.
It's that lady again, Eva Heinemann.
Let them in.
[♪ sad music playing still slow ♪
[♪ sad music slowly fades out ♪
[♪ sad music slowly dissolves ♪
It was nice with you, Eva ...
[♪ gentle laughter ♪
[♪ gentle laughter new and fading back to diagnosis ♪
And when will I see you next time?
I don't know, maybe after the next business trip?
and you leave me alone now and drive home to your wife exactly do do good I get in touch
you will probably not come back I'm going to you
put a perfumed cloth in your pocket that will understand your wife you são
Or I shall forget all our worries.
I am very glad you like him.
This is where I'm planting mimosa,
and over there I'm building a large tree for roses.
It will bloom beautiful in the summer.
Maybe, with someone like you, it would be nice.
Do you think you can make a woman like me happy?
Daddy?
Hey! Are you even listening?
Hello, dad.
I'm sorry. How do you like your daddy's food?
I knew it. You are disrespecting me.
It's always the same with you.
That´s why my mother sought another one.
Please excuse me.
Very well.
This is cabbage pot, sweety.
What if...
...dad also finds someone?
Ah, nothing. No, forget it.
Doesn't taste good again, today?
Anyway, then...
It isn't uncomfortable, today.
I see. No discomfort, then.
Excuise me, actually you are only responsible for the nursery.
No problem.
But my cattle helps have made few of us avoid it.
If i can help, just tell me.
Ehmm...
We two should go out for dinner tonight.
Ahh well, I...
Why so nervous?
I am not used to the first class of restaurants like this.
If you want to fit in, you must be able to move securely in every ticket.
As self-confident as when you work in the garden.
That's true. When I work in the garden, I forget everything around me and just feel safe.
I love to design a garden according to my imagination.
Nowhere am I as happy as there.
And people who love gardens can't be bad.
You also said that you love your garden, Eva.
Does that mean I'm a good person too?
Yes, of course.
It's just...
It's what?
Well, I think you look lonely.
You do too.
You are lonely, aren't you?
Oh, sorry! My daughter is probably very worried about me already.
Kenzo...
Who knows? Maybe we're not even just two.
This man in the photos ruined me.
I'm sorry about that. I just wanted to clean.
His name is Kenzo Tanma, my ex-fiancé.
Are you drinking again?
At this time?
Of course, why not.
I just came in the Federal Police Department, I wanted to talk to Inspector Runge
This guy's completely unavailable and he's docked me
When will this useless Police arrest Thänna?
The Federal Police Department?
Accuse Tänna?
He killed my father and then fled
He blamed me for being innocent, but he made stupid comments
My father was Chairman of a big health clinic. I had a golden future
Three broken marriages only because of geh
From the beginning he claimed it was Johan.
Here, look at this.
This is Johan with my father.
Do you think this boy could kill my father?
And Tenma claims that it was so?
A cheap excuse.
Did you show the photo to the police?
No, why should I?
It could be a proof.
You don't know that before.
And Tenma is the murderer.
He has, as the commissioner put it, two personalities.
Why are you putting the photo of your father's murderer on the air mattress?
Deep in your heart you do not hope that Tenma is the murderer.
Probably you still love him.
You have seen too many lies.
From all of the men in my life,
he just suited my heart better.
He is such a brilliant brain surgeon.
He was such a brilliant brain surgeon that he was considered a genius and enjoyed a good reputation.
But above all, he never contradicted me.
No matter what I wanted, he said yes and amen.
Yes, yes, always yes.
He always agreed with me without contradiction.
He should have made me the happiest woman in the world.
That's what he was for.
Can't I try to make you happy instead?
I want to conjure the most beautiful gardens for you all my life.
I'll take care of you and you'll be fine.
Just because we slept together or what?
You're nothing more than a waste of time for me.
What do you think?
That was a nice little game.
And you learned something from it?
Idiot.
What do you think you are?
That's right. You really have to be very, very lonely.
Yes, and you too.
I'm going to celebrate Christmas with my daughter at home.
Come over if you like.
How great, this is a real party.
Did you do all of this by yourself?
Yes, but I can't guarantee that it tastes good.
But isn't that too much for the two of us?
What do you think?
Mom's coming back, am I right?
That's right, isn't it? Mom's coming today.
Colette, listen.
Mom's back.
Charlotte!
Mom.
Forgive me, my darling, forgive me.
автор субтитров A.T.
Not this one, go back.
What do I want with mimosa or with roses,
with a beautiful garden?
What with my father?
From me, all that will light up if it burns.
Everything should burn!
Everything's supposed to burn
Welcome
I'm really happy that you finally listen to me, Commissioner Runge
I happen to have time
that this man is the only thing that is still interesting to me.
As long as he has not gotten what he deserves,
I will not sleep a single night in peace.