Let us pray.
I'm going to take a picture of you and then I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm
going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take
a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you
and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take a picture of you and I'm going to take
Hey, that's against the rules! You're not the goalie!
What do the rules matter to me, you little bum?
Better tell me where I can find him.
Find? Who?
You, not so stupid. Tenma.
Oh, Tenma. He's got something to do.
He's looking for a man. And you should watch out for me for a long time.
What? Me? I'm supposed to watch out for you, you little toad?
Is this supposed to be a joke?
Of course not. I can't stand children.
That damn Tenma.
I had already written him off.
And then all of a sudden he shows up with this beam.
As a doctor for the underworld, he could have made a huge profit.
That idiot has no idea what he's done.
Pass!
Find?
You, not so stupid. Tenma.
Oh, Tenma. He's got something to do.
He's looking for a man. And you should watch out for me for a long time.
What? Me? I'm supposed to watch out for you, you little toad?
Great header.
Damn. What's that supposed to be, you little toad?
Hey!
I told you, handball is forbidden.
There's a yellow card.
I don't care about that. You'd better keep your big mouth shut.
You'd even get a red card for that.
Shut up!
Come on!
Why are you so late?
Suspended because of suspicion of drug abuse.
I have to admit, I was surprised when I came across the article.
I advise you to sit down.
I pointed a gun at you under the coat.
What do you want from me?
I want to know from you what you did 10 months ago in Heidelberg.
And what's more important, who enumerated you.
I don't know what you mean.
When you were arseulted. You killed the wretch Fortnoy and Mourer, the journalist.
No, I didn't. I was on duty, you know.
It was Müller, the guy who killed everyone.
Of course, you killed him.
Yes, of course.
He asked us for a lot of cash. A lot of money.
You're still in love with me, aren't you darling?
Why do you just keep staring at me, huh?
Is that the girl who wants to baby sit?
Y-yes...
Alright. Follow me.
Come on, let's go!
HOTEL
Please, wait a second.
Put your eye there and wait.
No, right on top of it, right in the middle.
That's good.
Do you remember this song?
It's got such a little rhythm that it makes you automatically dance,
my dear Nina Fortnas.
What's going on here?
And what happened?
This country needs a new leader.
Just like our protector The Hitlers wanted.
And the girl is the right bait.
No way.
Oh crap.
...Oh dear.
What is it, Uncle Heckel?
This whole neighborhood is now in Turkish hands.
...that must be an imitation.
What? That can't be.
Feel this fabric! This is more than a 100% handmade silk!
That's artificial fiber, but he will be my 100 marks.
And I'm sorry, Huck.
A good joke? Not at all.
The previous owner, a German man, ...
will give me at least 10,000 marks.
Then take your carpet and go to him.
Yes, and afterwards you want to have one indeed!
After all, the carpet is real.
If you want to see a real carpet, look at this one here!
A Hareki silkcarpet, high quality.
Come closer...
...and see how fine it was knitted.
150,000 marks!
That's definitely not a fraud.
What kind of businessman are you,
who doesn't recognize that my carpet is real?
Come on, Dieter. Let's go.
Great. And now? I'm hungry.
A real silk carpet.
Huh?
The carpet in there is quality work.
And that for 150,000?
With a little bit of skill,
I could sell it for 800,000.
It doesn't matter now. Let's eat something.
Shut up.
If I get this carpet in my hands,
you can eat as much as you want.
And how do you want to do that?
That with the carpet?
Let that be my concern.
Why are you looking so angry?
So you're a thief.
Huh? What?
Not so loud, you rascal.
Wait a minute. Not so fast.
Where are you going?
No, I'm sorry. I have no interest.
No, you don't. What are you talking about?
As Asian as you look,
it's dangerous for you to walk in there.
The shop is a meeting point of the right.
But you're Turkish, aren't you?
Isn't it dangerous for you to work there?
Are you crazy?
I'm not going to shop in a hole like that.
A good friend of mine
was dragged in there by the weird guys.
She knew about a secret.
That was her doom.
A secret?
I don't know the details,
but I have to find a way
to get her out of there as soon as possible,
otherwise it's too late.
A friend of mine is in there, too.
What does she look like?
A slim, young girl with long, blonde hair?
Good question.
I don't know what hair color she has now.
Maybe your friend was taken in a car earlier.
Where did he go?
I don't know.
But Baby was with her,
so maybe she went to his villa.
Baby? What car was that?
What color?
A deep red Mercedes-Benz.
Thank you. I have to find that car
as soon as possible.
Wait. You have to help me
get my friend out of there.
I beg you.
She has a little child at home.
You have to help us.
Please.
Help!
Look at him.
He seems to be still alive.
There we are.
Before you go in,
please give me your gun.
Good.
You will be expected.
Thank you.
Please find yourself a seat.
So you are the girl
who brought Baby here.
Look at me when I talk to you.
Oh, how pretty you are,
you are without a doubt
Johann's twin sister.
My name is Professor Giedritz.
The man you see
in the photo next to Johann
is General Wolf.
He, me and two others
founded our organization
a long time ago.
Can I offer you
some fruit?
I beg you.
Bring me to Johann.
You have to be patient.
I'm sure he'll come here
as soon as he finds out
that you're here.
He needs you.
He needs his sister.
Then they don't know
where he could be.
And more importantly,
we need him.
Do you know
why Hitler could become
so successful and powerful?
He was a smart businessman
and knew how to control
three areas of central importance.
These included the banks,
the arms industry
and, of course, the military.
Johann is best injured
in all these areas.
If you see this differently,
you may speak calmly.
I want to know what they're up to with Johann.
Unconditionally,
the key to Hitler's power
and success was his unique charisma.
Hitler failed
at the training test
at the art academy
and could only rescue him
during his Republic period.
His charisma was only
to be noticed
after he had already
surpassed thirty years of age.
John will find out, and he will want to see you.
I would would advise you to not try an escape.
You sit in a boat with us, so now.
No worries, I will not escape.
I will wait for John.
You always will.
Please, eat some fruit with me.
You're not looking for Johan, are you?
If so, what for?
I want to know where Nina is.
I just explained who's asking the questions here.
What are you going to do with her?
I'm asking the questions here.
Nina is a very important guest for us.
On the contrary to you, you little piece of shit.
That means she's fine, right?
At the moment, yes.
To be honest, she's a big danger.
She may look like an angel,
but we know she wants to kill Johan.
We would have to pull such a person off the road by now.
You are going to use her
as a bait for Johan.
Are you anything but cruel.
What are you going to do with Nina?
Again, no questions.
Poor breed like you have no right
to ask us any questions.
Just your plain cheekiness
should do you,
all those troublesome pills
Tomorrow evening the sky will be beautifully bright.
John, if I stay here, I will see John.
Yeah.
You will see him.
And you will see me.
Hello, who is there?
Please help me.
Tell me where you are.
On the second floor.
Can you maybe tell me who you are?
Where are you from?
I am from Turkey.
They want to kill me.
I have to get out of here.
Please help me.
So these men locked you up here?
The problem is that I have to stay here at all costs.
You have to help me.
I have to warn the others.
Otherwise they will all die.
And my son too.
Tomorrow we will throw a small welcome party for Johan.
Very soon only we will live in this world.
The men race.
And no one else.
The rest can and should burn quietly.
I heard about your devilish plan.
Tomorrow evening they want to burn everything.
They want to attack the Turkish quarter.
It should burn.
Everything should die.
Help me.
You have to help me.