Maurer, you haven't been
taking a bath, have you?
You promised, when I moved
to the desk next to you,
that you'd take one every other day.
You're such a pest.
You have a visitor
in the reception office.
I'm going home,
so make your own tea, will you?
A visitor? At this hour?
He hasn't had a bath, either.
He smells almost as bad as you do!
What the hell...?
Upsy daisy!
And whose fault is it that
I haven't been able to take a bath?
She doesn't realize that she's able to
make a living at this paper
with no future,
thanks to me.
Jeez.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Huh?
Uh... My name is Tenma...
I'd like to ask for your assistance!
Right... He really is filthy...
I see, so you're a doctor...
You don't look like one.
In other words, Doctor,
is this what you're trying to say?
The next target of the person
who's been killing
middle-aged couples
throughout Germany
is here in Heidelberg?
That couple is fostering a young girl,
and when that girl turns 20,
the killer will come to take her away...
And when he does, the foster parents
are sure to be killed...
But you have no idea
who that girl or her foster parents are,
or where they live...
If that's not delusional,
I don't know what it is.
It's not a joke. Please believe me.
Ridiculous! Not even the gossip rags
would write up that story.
I didn't come here
to get you to write it up!
After those twins
slipped out of the hospital,
there is at least
a 6-month blank period
before the brother showed himself.
So what?
I believe that,
after leaving the hospital,
those twins came to
Heidelberg together.
You believe...
And the two were raised by
the girl's current foster parents.
But the brother ran away from here
after a short period,
leaving his sister behind.
Why don't you write a novel?
'Course it probably won't sell.
It is possible that there is
a missing person's report out on the boy.
And there might even be
a newspaper article about him!
Please let me check the newspapers
from nine years ago! Please!
Please!
We mustn't allow
any more people to be killed!
Please...
The president has a thing against
computerization, you see...
These are smaller versions
of the daily newspapers,
and manuscript files.
And these are files
of cancelled stories and raw data.
T-Thank you very much!
Is that the Japanese bow...?
You're quite welcome.
Let me say this...
I just don't have the time
to spend on silly stories.
Hurry up and leave
when you're satisfied!
Jeez! Every once in a while,
I get a nut case like him.
Please...
Please let me find something!
Good morning, Nina!
Good morning!
Thank goodness.
You're looking well, Nina.
Fainting like that...
You startled me.
I guess you really didn't like
the boy we hooked you up with.
T-That's not true.
I just suddenly felt bad.
I have to apologize to him.
Oh, never mind.
You don't have to worry about him.
Huh?
That Otto... When I talked to him,
I found out that he's not
your "prince on a white horse."
He says he didn't send you
any email message.
Is that so...?
So you're saying that you fainted
because you saw that boy?
Yes...
What did he look like?
I only saw him for a second,
so I'm not sure...
What was your impression of him?
It felt very nostalgic...
Oh...
But that's not it...
I can't explain it well, but...
But...?
You needn't force yourself, Nina.
Absolute evil...
I don't know how to put it, but...
Yes, it felt just like
when I had that nightmare...
Absolute evil"...
It's beginning to sound religious.
I don't go to a church...
But, it seems to me that
everything will be cleared up
if I see that person again.
You feel that you will regain
the memory you've lost...
Yes.
That's one means you may be
able to employ...
But I don't think you should let that
be a burden on you.
Thinking about your future
without stressing, is also important.
Yes...
Don't worry. Just work up a sweat
playing sports,
and your insecurities
should disappear.
Maurer, pull another all-nighter?
Yeah...
Oh, by the way, were you the one
who let that guy use the file room?
That guy...?
Yes. I asked him
what he was doing there
and he said
you had given him permission.
You mean he's still there?
Jeez!
Hey, you! It's about time you... Huh?!
Oh! Hey!
Are you all right? Hey! Huh?
Come on. Eat up.
Yes...
Good, isn't it?
I always have breakfast here.
Don't you go home?
What about your family?
Haven't got one.
My wife left me, you see.
Huh?
I was always so busy with work.
When I finally realized it,
my wife had gone back to her parents
with our daughter.
Have you ever thought about
bringing your wife home?
Why would I do that?
She's the one who walked out!
Why should I go to get her?
Well, you seem to regret
being so occupied with work.
Don't be silly!
Work is most important to a man!
Any wife who cannot understand that
is welcome to leave me!
I'm sorry. It was none of my business.
That's right.
It's none of your business.
Oh, uh... One more thing...
You smoke too much.
I say that as a doctor.
I told you it's none of your business!
Quit saying the same thing
my wife said!
Your wife was worried
about your health, too.
Mind your own business.
Nina's birthday present?
Yes. I finally finished it.
Her sweaters used to be
this tiny before.
Dear, are you really going to tell her
that she's not really our daughter?
Why can't we leave it...?
You're right...
There's no need to tell her that.
Nina is our daughter, after all.
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Boy...am I hungry!
Think about the future...?
Dr. Gaitel may be right.
"Tomorrow, your birthday, let's meet at
Heidelberg Castle at 7:00 PM."
Tomorrow...at Heidelberg Castle...?
I'm so busy, but here I am staring at
a mountain of papers with you!
Isn't it about time you gave up?
Listen, Doctor...
If...it's just a thought, now...
If I were to go to get my wife...
Do you think she'd come back?
Yes. If you quit smoking, that is.
Oh!
What is it?
I found it!
Huh...?
11 -year-old boy disappears...
It is possible that he was kidnapped,
but there has been no word
from a kidnapper.
16 Necker Street...
Someone named Fortner has filled out
a missing person's report!
The raw data should be
in here somewhere...
Oh, here it is!
Huh...? Oh!
W-What is it?
You said that that killer would
come to take his sister away
when she turned 20, didn't you?
If the boy in this article
is her brother...
Look! His birth date is printed here.
Today is the 20th birthday
of those twins.
Uh, hello, Dad? It's me.
I just finished work.
I'm going to meet up with a friend
then I'll be coming home.
Yes... At Heidelberg Castle.
I see.
Your mom is making preparations
for a birthday party, you know.
Was that Nina?
Yes. She says she's going to meet
a friend before coming home.
I wonder who it is.
Nina's all grown up, after all.
Maybe this will help me
to remember things...
I want to know who I really am.
Doctor, what do you intend to do if
the twin girl is at the Fortners' home?
Whatever the case,
that family is in danger.
I will contact the police
and ask for protection.
Do you think the police will
do anything just from your reasoning?
Nothing has happened yet.
It'll be too late
after something happens!
Nothing's going to happen.
It's all in your head!
Listen, Doctor...
Of the four murder cases,
I myself went to
the crime scene in Cologne.
There was something different
about that scene.
I sensed no purpose,
no greed, no bitterness...
It was like someone simply ended
these people's lives.
I could tell just by looking
at the crime scene.
You said that a kid
who wasn't even 20, did it.
But do you think a youngster could
kill those people
without feeling any emotion?
That wasn't something done by a kid!
It was something bigger...
Bigger... What...?
That's just it...
I just can't find the right words
to describe this case.
If I have to describe it, it's trite,
but that was the Devil's work.
If that killer were to appear before me,
I would kill him without a pause.
16 Necker Street... We're here.
Good evening!
Sorry to call on you so late...
Yes?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Maurer of the Heidelberg Post.
What would a newspaper reporter
be wanting?
Uh...I'd like to ask you
some questions...
What is it?
- Oh...!
It's regarding this missing persons report
that you filed in 1936...
Y-You can forget about that matter!
Uh... Could you please talk to us?
Don't you have a girl living with you?
The twin sister of
the boy who disappeared...
Please! Please answer me.
Oh, dear...
Huh?
A cake...
They had a birthday cake prepared...
You took in a pair of twins
nine years ago, didn't you?
The girl still lives with you,
doesn't she?
Please leave!
We have raised her
as our true daughter.
Please don't make waves.
Please leave us alone.
You took in a pair of twins
nine years ago.
The boy had surgical scars
on his head
and the girl had amnesia.
Isn't that right?!
Mr. Fortner, you must contact
the police at once!
Your lives, and your daughter's,
are in danger!
Mr. Maurer...
W-What are you talking about?
Please let us see your daughter.
She is out at the moment.
Where is she?!
At Heidelberg Castle.
She said she was going
to meet a friend.
Please let me use your car!
W-Wait! We must
notify the police first.
We don't have the time
to explain things to the police!
Give me the key, quickly.
All right. I'll call them from here.
Thank you.
Hey, Doctor!
Be careful! As I said earlier,
he's a terrible person.
You'd better not die!
Mr. Maurer...
Come back alive...
Then I'll quit smoking.
I'll follow the quack's advice.
Your wife will be happy, too.
Now, how should I explain
this to the police...?
Our daughter... Is she all right?
What has happened?
Don't worry.
Let me use your phone.
What has happened to our daughter?
Please tell us!
Calm down!
Huh?
What in the...?!
The phone line's been cut...
Anna... Please be safe... Anna!
It's way past time...
I guess that message was a prank.
I'm going home.
You can't.
Huh?
You have to...wait here.
Who are you?
I was asked to make sure
you waited here.
I said to wait...
Don't you understand?
Wait!
You have to wait here!
That's what I was told!
Anna!
Anna... No, you're Nina Fortner,
aren't you?
Do you remember me?
I'm Dr. Tenma. I'm glad you're safe.
Anna... Dr. Tenma...
Let's go. You must go home.
Y-You... Are you...
my prince on a white horse?
Huh...?!
Who are you?
Don't butt in... Don't butt in, will you?
She's gotta wait here.
If she doesn't, I-I...
I won't get paid!
He said no one would come!
Damn...!
Are you all right?
I-I'm amazed...
I need something to tie him up with!
Oh...
Who asked you to do this?
I-I don't know.
When did he say he was coming here?
I don't know. He just said
he would come here
after doing something important.
Don't tell me...your home...
Huh?
I have to hurry back to your home!
W-What's going on?
I'll explain later!
We've got to hurry, Anna!
Anna...
-Hurry!
Damn... I can't get loose...
Please tell me! Who are you?
And I'm not Anna!
I'm Nina!
No, when you were brought into
my hospital, you were Anna.
And your brother's name was Johan.
My brother...