Here you go...your Manhattan.
Hey, what about my red cherry?
Huh?
There should be a red cherry in it,
or it isn't a Manhattan!
S-Sorry about that.
Humph! You'd better watch it.
My business goes well
when I have this in my mouth.
Huh?
It's a jinx, a jinx!
Please...
Let there still be something
of value left!
Okay, okay... It's just as I thought...
Everything's right here;
like a candy store.
Is there anything
valuable enough for me?
Life is fleeting. He may have been
touted as a candidate for governor,
but when he and his wife
were gunned down together like this...
Oops, I'd better get down
to business...
I figure the safe must be
in this room...
Wh-Wh-Wh-What's with this chill?!
It's the first time
I've felt anything so repulsive...
Someone's in this room...
No way! What am I so scared about?
It's not like me...
Don't move!
Raise your hands over your head!
Oh, no... He was behind me. Crap...
It's all because that bartender
forgot the cherry...
Hurry up and raise your hands!
All right, all right...
Give me a break, officer.
I haven't taken anything yet.
I'm not the police.
Huh? What the...? You're one of us?
In that case, why don't you
put that scary thing away and...
Put your hands on your head!!
What's with this guy?
He seems harder to deal with
than the police.
L-It's the cops!
You fouled up, didn't you?!
I'm getting outta here!
Don't follow me!
Somebody like you
will just slow me down!
Damn you!
Don't follow me, I said!
Damn! This is just not my day!
That's right...
I thought you looked familiar...
You're the guy in the newspaper...
You're the doctor who's
the "person of interest"
in the Councilman Springer
murder case.
And you're a thief?
Exactly! Unlike you, I wouldn't do
anything senseless like killing.
Do you know anything about the killing
that took place in that house?
No idea. Hurry up and get out
of my face, will you? So long.
Hey, Doctor!
You're supposed to be
a top-notch surgeon, aren't you?
My brilliant brain just came up
with an idea.
Do you think that meetings
happen by chance, Doctor?
They don't, you know.
All meetings between people
are determined beforehand...
You and I were destined
to become a team.
Huh?
The underworld is full of people
who need someone like you;
people who want to call a doctor,
but die because
the danger is too great.
Leave the management
to me...Heckel!
I'll make you into the best doctor
of the underworld.
You'd make a whole lot more
in the underworld.
You'll be a billionaire
before you know it...
H-Hey, Doctor! Where are you going?
There's something I have to do.
Wait a minute!
You want to know about the murders
in that house, don't you?
Huh?
Well, I saw the killer, you see...
What's that?!
What are you talking about?!
You want to know?
Wasn't he blond
and about 20 years old?
What do you mean?
Anyway, just tell me about that killer!
I'll tell you if you'll team up with me.
He's on the third floor
of this cheap apartment house.
How do you know this?
After I set my sights
on that councilman's house,
I spent about a month researching it.
Just when I was set to go,
that guy showed up.
When I looked in the window,
the councilman
and his wife were dead.
I figured I could squeeze some money
out of the killer, so I followed him.
Well, this proves that
you're innocent in this case.
Go phone it in to the police
if that's what you want.
Then you and I can go somewhere
and sit and talk over a drink
about our dream-like future...
H-Hey!
What do you want to see him for?
He's a murderer, you know!
You'll get yourself killed!
What is he thinking?!
I can't keep up with him!
But it's not often I'll find
a source of revenue like him.
I make it a rule not to
stick my neck out, but...
Hey...
It's another hot day, isn't it?
Actually, I'm looking for
a certain person...
Hey, Doctor, are you alive?
Doctor...
You fool! He's got a gun!
I often used to go walking
with my mother...
Huh?
...along the sunflower field...
on summer days like this.
Of course, she died a long time ago.
Didn't you use that gun
at someone's request? Some man...
Man...? Oh... One day,
he approached in a bar.
A blond man, about 20 years old?
Huh?
That's right. He had a beautiful smile,
that Erich.
So he's Erich, now...
We met a few times
and became good friends.
He invited me to his home...
to Councilman Springer's home.
He lived in that mansion
until recently?
Yes. He said they took good care of him,
like a son, since about a year ago.
Hey, I had my eye on that home
for a month,
but I never saw anybody like that.
They were a wonderful family.
Here's a picture...
That's me and the Councilman
and his wife.
But there was something
I just couldn't forgive them for.
There was a bed of sunflowers
on their property,
but he tore it up in order to
build a parking area.
When I said that was
an awful thing to do, Erich agreed.
Y-You don't mean
you killed them over that!
Besides, Erich told me...
that Councilman Springer
had a mistress.
He also said this.
I no longer want to be
a member of the Springers' family.
I'm not a member of that family."
Then he asked me to...
Please eliminate that family."
He's terrible to have a mistress...
My mother was
someone's mistress, too.
L-Listen...never mind that.
Do you know where the safe is,
in that house?
I believe it's in the back of the study
on the 2nd floor.
O-Okay!
Doctor, you'd better get out
of here fast, too!
Did you know...?
You can erase the past.
If you don't like it,
you can erase everything...
You can reset your life.
I don't think so. You may try to forget,
but you cannot erase your past!
That's right...
I wonder why I thought that...
Why did I think at that time that
I could erase the past
by pulling this trigger?
I wonder why I listened
to his request...
That's all I have to say. Please leave.
Oh, yes...
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
Please look at the message.
It's a message for you, from him...
You'll find it in the study of that house.
What...?!
He knew that you would come here.
Erich said,
"Your destiny is already determined."
Good-bye...
Doctor!
I told you, didn't I? Oh...
D-Don't tell me you...
Oh, this is a suicide.
What the hell...?!
What's the use in dying?
It's all over when you die.
There's nothing like living,
right, Doctor?
Yeah... You sometimes say
something worthwhile, don't you?
What do you mean, sometimes?!
And so...you're after that unbelievable
serial killer named Johan?
Why don't you forget about doing
something so stupid,
and team up with me.
Oh... By the way, when I tried to open
this door earlier, I got the chills...
What's this?
What are you shivering for, Doctor?
"Look at me! Look at me!
"See how big the monster inside of me
has grown, Dr. Tenma..."
Johan is... He is enjoying himself.
Hey, Doctor!!
Wait a minute! Listen to me!!
Hey, Doctor!
I offered you a great deal.
You should be grateful.
You promised to team up
with me, right?
Who said I'd team up with you?!
Hey! You need money in order
to run from the cops, right?
Get in the car!
This is your client.
He'll take you to your patient.
I'll hold on to your things.
If you want them back,
you'd better do your job, get paid,
and come to Frank's place
on Grasten Street.
So long. You'd better earn all you can!
This is a really profitable business.
Now, then... Since I got an advance,
I guess I'll have a drink.
Counselor... I brought you a doctor.
Thank goodness, Doctor... Hurry...
Please stop the bleeding.
Your axillary artery
has been damaged.
Did you get hit by a shotgun?
Yeah... Hey, Doctor,
you're empty-handed.
Did you get the surgical equipment?
No. It was too dangerous in the city...
I didn't get that far...
I couldn't operate on you here
even if I had the equipment.
You'd better get him to
a proper doctor as soon as possible.
I would have done that if I could!
Hurry up and fix him!
How long ago was he shot?
Never mind the questions!
Four hours ago...?
Were you responsible for
the terrorist attack this morning?!
What if we are?
I refuse!
Wha...?!
What did you say?!
I have no desire
to treat anyone responsible
for indiscriminate terrorist attacks!
Don't get funny! Do you realize
the situation you're in now?
Wait a minute.
Listen, Doc... Our friends will be
coming to help us soon.
Just stop the bleeding by then,
will you?
What's with that attitude?!
Do you want to die?
I told you to wait up.
B-But...Counselor...
This doctor has my life
in his hands now...
If I should die...
I want you to shoot him.
We're not running a charity here,
you know.
Pay us back the 250,000 marks
we lent you, will you, Heckel?
Mr. Gross... I do intend
to pay you back...
That's nice. I'm glad you feel that way.
Just break both his arms for now.
I understand! I'll pay you back! I will!
Good boy...
So, please wait another month...
-In the random automatic rifle shooting
Break both legs, too.
-by terrorists this morning
in Erfurt Station, witness accounts
have helped police identify
the suspects as Max Steindorf
and Karl Blunt.
Please wait... Huh?!
-The GWE has announced
that it will give anyone
with promising leads on these two
a reward of 300,000 marks.
So, they were the ones...
Huh?
I can pay you back that money.
I know where those guys are!
That'll cancel out my debt to you!
That had better be the truth.
Otherwise, I'll break your neck.
It's true! It's true! It's absolutely true!
Oh, but Tenma's there right now...
Oh well...
You said what I did was
an indiscriminate terrorist attack,
didn't you?
That's ridiculous! There was
a good reason for what I did...
Now that I've killed
the president of GWE,
I could die tomorrow and I wouldn't mind.
I feel so good.
Counselor...
I was a lawyer in East Germany...
This guy was secretary to a politician.
When the Wall came down,
we all lost our jobs.
Doctor... Can you understand
how we feel?
After the Wall fell, the GWE
used the power of money
to infiltrate into East Germany...
They aggressively built factories
on our land...one after another...
That is our country... I took pride
in shooting him. I took pride...
Oh! Counselor...!
It's cold...so cold...
H-Hang on!
Our friends will be here soon!
They won't come.
Our friends won't come.
I have a feeling...
Stop the bleeding!
Stop it now! Or I'll shoot you dead!
I'll...kill you!
I don't want to die...
Huh?
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid to die?!?
That's how they all died.
The twelve people you killed.
That's how they...!
That's what it means, to kill someone!
Get me some disinfectant
and a pair of scissors.
What?
You have that much, don't you?!
Arterial bleeding... He's gone into
hypotensive shock.
I will use finger pressure on
the damaged artery
to stop the bleeding.
I will suture the open flesh.
Needle and thread...
W-We haven't got anything like that.
Then a stapler will do!
A stapler...?!
Hurry up and get it!
Yes, sir!
Okay!
Huh?
What are you going to do?
I applied first aid.
I'm taking him to a hospital.
A-A hospital?!
What are you thinking?!
If you don't put him down, I'll kill you!
Shoot me if you want!
If you're going to shoot me,
then you take this guy to the hospital.
Put me down here...
You get out of here...
I remembered a while ago... I thought
I'd seen your face somewhere before.
You're that doctor who's wanted
in those serial killings, aren't you?
Hurry up and put me down!
What I did was not
an indiscriminate terrorist attack.
The guys I killed were the president
of GWE, his lackeys,
and his bodyguards.
So you're saying that there were
no unintended victims?
You mean the girl
who was at the news stand?
So, you did know about it...
That you had shot her.
Why did you save a man like me?
Not because you were afraid you
were going to be killed, right?
Your eyes tell me you weren't afraid
of being killed.
Why did you save
this indiscriminate terrorist...this killer?
Because I believed you...
That you were a human being.
Hurry up and go!
The police will be here...
You have to live...
You...
You're a brilliant doctor...
So what happened to the money?!
Hey, Doctor!
Don't tell me you fixed him and just left!
-The perpetrators of the terrorist attack
this morning at Erfurt Station
have been captured.
Say something, will you?!
-Police anticipated strong resistance.
But it seems they surrendered
without a fight.
We're not running
a charity here, you... Hey...!