Petra, open up.
Petra!
Today's the day I'm going to
take you in for a check up!
I keep telling you that it's
pointless to come here!
Who do you think
I'm coming here for?!
Nobody called you!
You stubborn, narrow-minded woman!
You're one to talk, you quack doctor!
I've never been to a doctor
since I was born, but I'm still healthy.
Now go away!
You stubborn...
Doctor!
Bad news–!
Dr. Schumann!
What's wrong?
Fink, the drunkard was hit
by a car on the highway!
So is he still conscious?
The man who brought him in
is treating him!
Huh?
It seems that some man who happened
to be passing by is examining him.
What?
What is the meaning of this?
You were visiting homes,
so that man...
You let him treat him?
Sorry. I tried to stop him,
but he said that he needed to
apply first aid
because there was a chance that
the patient would choke...
Who is he?!
Who knows?
He left without saying his name.
Oh...he wrote something
on the medical chart...
"The patient has no money."
"He kept repeating not to
take him to a doctor."
"Please take this money
as his doctor's fee"?
Damn!
Who does he think he is?
Doctor, where are you going?
What does he look like?!
He was an Asian man with a boy...
Umm, what about Fink's treatment?
Just keep him in bed!
B-But...the man only
applied first aid...
That was not first aid...
Huh?
His treatment was complete.
Say, Dieter...
It's really a problem if you follow me.
I can't stay in one place.
You can't go to school.
You can't make any friends.
I have a friend.
Who?
Tenma.
Listen, Dieter.
Was it you?
You're the one who
came to my clinic
and did unnecessary things,
aren't you?
Huh?
Don't underestimate me!
I know that Fink is a broke alcoholic.
I had no intention of
charging him for treatment.
Oh...well...
You're probably some elite
from a first-rate hospital
trying to show some compassion
while on vacation.
You're probably full of yourself.
Hey.
- Welcome.
Let's go, Dieter!
- Are you busy?
Yeah.
- Hey!
Listen to what I have to say!
I'm very sorry.
We're in a hurry...
Fink got into a hit-and-run.
Fink, the drunkard?
Yeah.
We're looking for witnesses.
Ah... That's a tough task.
Hey, Dr. Schumann.
How is Fink's condition?
His life's not in danger. I'm more
worried about his alcoholism.
And you are?
Well, I'm...
Dr. Chan.
An underclassman from college.
He's visiting this village
during his vacation.
Dr. Chan? Have we met somewhere?
He treated Fink for me
while I was visiting homes...
That aside, where do you think I was?
At Petra's house...
your mother, Heinz.
Mom?
Tell her to come to the clinic.
We may need to treat her
as soon as possible.
That's impossible.
That stubborn woman
won't listen to anyone.
Don't act as if it's not your problem.
It's all right. Mom won't die that easily.
Wha–?!
Besides, she raised me this far.
I don't think she has any regrets.
What?!
Hey, wait!
Petra's life has just begun!
Why did you lie?
That was for saving Fink.
He would have died if it wasn't
for your swift treatment.
Thank you very much.
You turned so pale
when you saw the police...
You...
Oh well,
at least it's obvious that you're not
an elite doctor from a first-rate hospital.
Thank you very much.
I don't know how to repay you.
Repay me, huh?
Then help me out a bit.
Huh?
Ow ow ow...
Your splint is misaligned.
This may hurt a bit,
but please be patient.
Ow...
Now it should be all right.
You can probably take it off
after two more weeks.
Doctor, I made some good cider.
Want a drink?
What are you talking about?
You're hurt.
I'll drink with you all night
once you've healed.
Progress is good. Five days
and you can go back to the fields.
Aren't you glad, Schone?
Doctor, take some potatoes.
This year's crop is good.
Next time, I'll come with a truck
and take a whole mountain of them.
Thank you.
My specialty is internal medicine.
I do what I can outside my specialty...
But things don't go very well
when I'm by myself.
This is wonderful.
Yeah. There's nothing here,
but it's a peaceful village.
No, I didn't mean that...
You're loved by the people here...
And you really love them too...
Love, huh?
I lost feelings like that a long time ago.
I'm just doing my job.
Now, come with me
to just one more house.
This one is difficult.
You really are persistent, aren't you?!
Yeah! I'll keep coming back!
It'll be the same no matter
how many times you come!
Just leave!
You quack doctor!
See?
She's the mother
of that police officer earlier...
She fell sick while farming.
I tried to get her to my clinic,
but on the way there
she said that she's fine
and went back home.
That's worrisome.
Yeah...
Shall I try to reason with her?
It'll probably be the same.
Are you still loitering there?!
I can loiter wherever I want!
Calm down. She'll never come out
if you yell like that.
I'm going to get you out. I'm not going
to lose my reason for living!
Huh?!
N-No, I just meant that I wouldn't
have anyone to fight with anymore.
A-Also, I wouldn't be able to eat
her goulash anymore...
Mister, your face is red.
What did you say?! You brat!
Open up, Mrs. Petra.
What's this? A different doctor now?
It's useless to talk to
that stubborn woman.
Why do you hate doctors?
Why? Well, humph!
They fiddle around
with peoples' bodies
and think that they're gods
or something!
God, huh? Sometimes I think that
it would be great if we were.
We try our best, but no matter what,
we make mistakes.
I wish that I could heal people
perfectly like God.
I'm always trembling inside
whenever I see my patients.
Please. At least let me see your face.
This smell... You're making goulash,
aren't you?
Who are you? Do you like goulash?
Yes. But it seems that Dr. Schumann
especially loves your goulash.
That's news to me. He always eats it
without a word whenever I make it...
He's self-conscious.
This looks really delicious!
Jeez...
My shoulders are stiff,
but it looks like
I have to prepare dinner...
Stiff shoulders?
Mrs. Petra, can you put
your chin to your chest?
Of course I can.
See? Ow ow ow...
Excuse me...
Four fingers fit...
What's that? Some kind of prayer?
No...nothing...
How is she?
It's probably...
a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
What?!
Petra!
Here's the fax of the arrest warrant
for the murder suspect.
Make copies of it.
Is your mom okay?
I heard that she collapsed
three days ago.
She's all right. She wouldn't die
even if you killed her.
It's been 72 hours
since the first stroke...
We can make it.
We've got to operate immediately!
I don't know if a helicopter
can make it if we call for one.
Can you do it?
Huh?
- Please,
perform the operation
if you can... If not...I...
It'll be my fault again for
losing another person I love.
You're sure that it's Kenzo Tenma?!
Yes.
- All right.
He might not have gone far!
Set up a barrier along the highway!
It'll be great if we catch him, Heinz.
Y-Yes!
Everyone, emergency deployment!
I did it! I can get a promotion
if things go well...
Hey, Heinz, you have a call!
Yes! This is Heinz...
Oh, hello, Nurse...
Mom collapsed again?!
If only I had forced her to
get a check up at a national hospital
after the first stroke...
You're the only one
I can count on, Dr. Tenma!
It's as I thought. It's an aneurysm
of the middle cerebral artery.
Damn it!
We don't have a surgical microscope
or a craniotome here...
I can try open surgery as long as
I have an aneurysm clip.
But it's too difficult even for you.
We've got to try.
She may not live the next time
the cranial aneurysm ruptures...
It's my fault that
this happened again...
What's wrong, Dr. Schumann?
You single-handedly took care of
the patients of this village.
It's not like you.
I don't know what happened
in the past, but...
We have to try our best
for the patient before us...
That is all we can do as doctors.
Yeah...
Hey, boy, is Dr. Schumann inside?
Yes, he's operating.
Operating on my mom?
They're operating at this clinic
rather than taking her
to a hospital in town?
It's all right, Tenma is here.
Tenma, you say?!
How's her blood pressure and pulse?
Blood pressure 126/84.
Pulse 88.
Amazing... He opened her head
so fast with just a wire saw.
He doesn't even have a craniotome.
What are you doing?!
As you can see, we are
operating on your mother!
What are you doing with that gun?!
Raise your hands, Tenma!
Tenma!
We're in the middle of an operation!
Are you trying to kill your mother?!
He's trying to kill her!
Tenma is a murder suspect
that's been on the run!
What?!
He killed a man in Heidelberg.
He's even suspected of
the serial killing of
middle-aged couples.
I never thought that I'd find him here.
Leave it to Mom.
She saw an opportunity for me.
Now, raise your hands.
If you don't, I'll shoot!
Get out of here!
This is a sterile operating room!
You're bringing in germs!
Your mother could die
from meningitis if you spread it!
Then quickly stop the operation!
Do you really want your mom to die?
Your mother has
a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
She first collapsed three days ago.
If we don't deal with it now
it'll be too late.
Now, get out!
You think you've got a hostage?!
You're planning to use my mom
as a hostage and run away from here!
Aneurysm clip and forceps...
Aneurysm clip and forceps!
Yes.
That's my mom!
I won't let anyone touch her!
That's right. Petra is your mother.
But what have you done for her
in the past five years?
Have you visited her even once
since you left the town?
What have you ever done
for your mother
after she raised you this far?
Listen, people who are dear to us
will pass away some day.
Do you remember the taste of
your mother's goulash?
Even now, Petra makes portions
for you out of habit.
I eat what's left over. It's delicious!
That taste is superb!
Dr. Tenma is desperately fighting
to save your mom.
If you want to eat that goulash again...
Get out!
See? Tenma is here, so it's all right.
Blood pressure 140/86. Pulse 82.
Vital signs are stable.
Pionier, you should get some rest.
But Doctor...
I'm all right. Get some rest.
Yes, then...
Good work.
Dr. Tenma, you get some rest, too.
I'm all right, too.
You performed a difficult operation
that lasted three hours.
I want to stay alert and watch her...
So that you can propose to Mrs. Petra
when she gets better.
What do you mean by "propose"?
You weren't sleeping?
I can't sleep.
Not until I take him away!
Besides that, what do you mean?
You're not going to propose
to my mom, are you?
Don't be foolish! Don't be foolish...
I'm...not someone who can
propose to anyone...
When I was
at the university hospital...
I never cared about talking
to my patients.
I only thought of how I could
raise my position in the hospital...
I got into the director's faction
and wrote papers for the director.
Finally...
I even married the director's daughter.
I pushed forward along
the path of success even after that.
I never paid any attention to my wife.
Yes. If I was a real doctor,
I would have noticed
when I had seen her face.
For a long time,
my wife had symptoms
which mimicked the common cold.
I would have noticed
if I were watching closely...
It was liver failure...
When she took her last breath...
You finally... paid attention to me...
I have no right to love anyone.
That's not true.
You've been paying attention.
You've been paying attention
to the people of this town.
Petra was saved because
you were paying attention.
Do you still plan on taking
this man away?
He's the man who struggled
to save your mother.
Do you still think he's a murderer?
Heinz!
This is Heinz. Get me the chief.
Chief, I'm sorry. I was mistaken.
Cancel the barrier.
The man I saw wasn't Tenma.
He was Dr. Chan.
I made the mistake
because he was Asian...
I'm very sorry.
The doctor of the national hospital
was sure surprised.
He probably never thought that
he would see such amazing treatment
from a clinic in the countryside.
Doctor!
Are you going to let
that young doctor go?
I was going to make him
something to eat, but he went off.
Tenma!
Don't go, this village is safe.
There's no need to run away!
Dr. Schumann.
Dieter, you like it here, don't you?
I see.
This village may be good for Dieter.
Not only for Dieter. This village
can protect you from the police.
Take care of the people here with me.
This village needs you.
But I have to go.
Why?!
Please take care of Dieter.
Tenma, I'm going with you!
If you stay here,
you can save the lives
of countless people in this area!
Let's do this together!
Save countless lives...
I...have to kill a man.
What?
Tenma!
What do you mean, Tenma?!
There's no way you can do
such a thing!
You try so desperately to save
peoples' lives!
He's going...
Tenma's going no matter
what you say...
Go, Dieter.
Huh?
Tenma won't lose his way
if you're with him.
Watch Tenma carefully.