Help...
If I don't let everyone know soon,
my baby will die...
I heard them talking.
They're going to set a fire...
tomorrow night...
They plan on burning our town.. .
the Turkish town!
Help!
If I don't let everyone know soon,
they'll burn my town. ..my baby!
Where the hell
are you going, Brat?!
I know the true worth
of the rug in the antique shop.
I should be the one to have it.
I told you not to look
at adults like that!
Thief.
Do whatever you want!
When I make a fortune, I won't
give you anything good to eat.
Listen up!
If you tell someone, you'll pay!
I won't ever be friends with a thief...
Ever...
I'm hungry...
There, there.
Don't cry, don't cry...
Mama's going to come back soon.
Doesn't that kid have a mama?
Yeah.
What about you? Don't stay there.
Return to your mama.
Oh... Could it be that you don't
have a mama, either?
Sorry. I said something bad.
It's all right... I have Tenma.
Tenma?
Eat as much as you want...
It's nothing special,
but don't hold back.
So you're waiting for Tenma
to come back...
You're the same as that kid...
Where did that kid's mama go?
Bad guys caught her.
Bad guys?!
It's really dangerous out there.
An Asian who was about to help me
was run over by them
right before my eyes.
Asian?
Oh, you said that Tenma
was Japanese, didn't you?
But... It can't be...
I'll go ! Where is it?!
My customer...
That man was a member of
an extreme right wing group.
I left the room
once I finished my job...
But I forgot my scarf,
so I went back to get it...
That man. ..was talking to
a friend on the phone.
I ran away. ..to try to
tell everyone in town.
But I was caught. ..
and brought here...
My child is still small. ..
He can't run away if there's a fire...
Who is it?
I was told by Professor Geidlitz
to send you some fruit...
Thank you.
I have a message from the professor.
General Wolf will be here shortly.
The man who was in the photograph
with my brother?
Yes. .. He's the one who
knows Johan the best.
Probably even better than you do...
That's what the professor said.
Whoops. You mustn't die yet!
His Excellency General Wolf
will be coming soon.
I want him to see what a good job
I've done by capturing you.
Wolf...
Refer to him as, "His Excellency"!
Look for General Wolf. He's the one
who first discovered Johan's skill...
It's like a dream to be receiving praise
from His Excellency.
Excuse me.
We've gathered the members
who will set fire to the Turkish town.
Are there any changes to the plan?
Everything's going as planned...
I'm going to have dinner
while I watch the red sky.
My fun dinner will be ruined
if the timing is off, even just a little...
Tell them that they'll be punished
if they can't do things as planned.
Yes!
Johan will not lead you.
It'll be impossible to have Johan
lead your organization.
He isn't as racist
or prejudiced like you.
Johan laughs scornfully at all people.
Shut up!
What an unusual customer.
Give this customer a drink on me.
The usual.
Okay.
That's quite impressive.
He'll be quite the troublemaker.
Disgusting! How can they
drink those things?
Tenma's jacket...
Tenma...
Where are you?
Well, calm down.
I want to get you out of that room,
but I'm not in the position
to do anything right now...
So I'll get out and warn your town.
R-Really?
What's the name of
the street you live on?
Calvin Street...
Calvin Street? What's your name?
Ayse.
Ayse, it's all right!
Your baby will be saved!
You'll be saved soon, as well.
Keep it up until then.
Understand?
Thank you...
Oh... What's your name?
Nina... Let's meet when I save you.
Nina... I've had a terrible time
since I came to Germany,
but you're the first good person
I've met...
We're friends, aren't we?
Yeah...
Say, what's the name of your baby?
Ayse? Ayse?
- Stop!
- Ayse?!
Ayse!
Sto...
Is that Tenma?
Yes.
I caught him...
Huh? Where is His Excellency?
He's waiting somewhere else.
We're going to take this man.
Huh–? Oh, but, this is my prize.
I was going to kill him
after I showed him to His Excellency...
What should I do with this kid?
Huh?
He said that he came looking
for this man.
Oh? Is he someone you know?
I-I don't know him.
I don't know this child. Let him go.
I can't take a filthy child like this
with me
when I go to see
His Excellency.
Get rid of him.
S-Stop!
Shut up. Do it right now.
It's noisy.
Okay.
Stop!
T-That's...my subordinate...
Doctor Tenma...
Forgive us for the rude treatment
you've received.
You are General Wolf's
important guest.
Ayse...
If I don't let everyone know soon,
my town...my baby
will be burned by them!
We're friends, aren't we?
That's right, Ayse...
We're...
...friends!
Huh?!
W-What's the meaning of this?
Professor Geidlitz...
Everyone's...dead...
We'll soon be arriving at the house
where General Wolf is waiting.
Is Nina there?
Yes, do not worry...
She's as important a guest as you
are.
Where's the Turkish woman?
Who knows...?
We don't know anything outside of
what we were ordered to do.
We've got to go to the town!
Calvin Street is going to burn tonight,
isn't it?!
If we don't let everyone
in the town know
the lady who fed me,
and that baby are going to die!
Unfortunately...
Our job is to take you with us.
Stop the car!
Tenma!
Can you go to
the Turkish town alone?
Huh?!
I'll go afterwards!
But right now, I have to go.
But...
You can do it.
You're a man, aren't you?!
If you go, everyone on Calvin Street
will be saved.
Go quickly!
Okay!
If you catch a car,
it should be thirty minutes!
Sorry for being rough. Go.
It's your fault for trusting me,
and giving back my gun.
But it didn't look like
you were going to stop.
It's okay...
General Wolf will be pleased to know
that your gun isn't just an accessory.
Right this way.
Where's Nina?
She's in this house, isn't she?
Let me see her.
First, we want you to meet
General Wolf and Professor Geidlitz.
First, I want to know if she's safe!
Geidlitz is dead.
Not only Geidlitz...
All of his subordinates
were also killed.
I've dealt with the bodies.
Where's Nina?!
She wasn't here when we came
with General Wolf.
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
Wh-Who are you?
You probably wouldn't recognize me
even if you saw my face...
Thank you for coming. I am Wolf.
B-But...
You look like
an entirely different person
from the picture
taken ten years ago...
It's fear...
It's fear.
Can't you go any faster?
Don't be foolish.
I'm going at 200 kilometers.
200 kilometers?
That speedometer is broken!
I won't make it in time!
People's names are mysterious...
The people that I've met,
know that my name is Wolf.
But I have to give my name
to those who I don't know...
But...where is the proof
that I am Wolf?
You're the one that discovered
Johan, aren't you?
Yes. It was 12 years ago...
He was sent to 511 Kinderheim
and was raised to become
an East German advance guard...
No, a leader...
That's right... He was to become
the person who'd support
this country before it's downfall.
And now, you want to make him into
the next Hitler
to expand your
extreme right-wing organization!
Right now, I'm only affiliated with
this organization out of convenience.
Everyone else wants to turn him
into another Hitler, but...
That's a stupid idea.
Someone like Hitler
took things that far...
If it were Johan...
That's right...
I was the one who gave him
the name "Johan."
We took the siblings into custody
as they were walking near
the Czechoslovakian border.
They surpassed
the heavy border security
and walked on; malnourished
and dying from the cold.
They passed out soon after
we took them into custody.
They probably would have died
if we hadn't found them...
It's the same as when you
saved Johan's life.
When he regained consciousness,
I asked him, "How do you feel?"
He replied...
"You'll know soon."
I have no proof that I am Wolf.
The people who know me
disappeared from the world
one by one...
My wife, children, parents, siblings,
relatives, subordinates, and friends
died one by one...
Johan did it all.
The only thing that can prove
that I am Wolf
is the large sum of money
that I brought with me
when I escaped
from East Germany.
Aside from those who believe
who I am, no one knows who I am.
"You'll know soon..."
This is what it meant.
Solitude...
Take a look at this.
"I'll be waiting at
the abandoned warehouse
of Hilden and Engels Company
in Romberg..."
Johan was here this morning.
And he killed Geidlitz
and his subordinates.
Now, one more person
who knew me has disappeared...
Nina probably saw this message
and headed there...
I want you to kill him!
What?! Is that true?!
It's true!
We have to let the people
of Calvin Street know immediately.
How amazing.
Luck has finally turned in my favor!
Huh?
I can use the fire to get the rug
for myself...
I'm lucky!
Looter!
Y-You idiot. Not so loud!
It would be bad if someone heard!
Let go of me!
It's not just the people of this town.
- We'll be dead if...
- Let go of me!
- ...the right wingers find out.
- Let go...
Especially skinheads...
- ...with swastika tattoos...
- Let go of me...
Was there a Turkish woman
imprisoned here?
That woman was dead
on the third floor.
Johan did not kill her.
It was the work of
Professor Geidlitz's subordinates.
Can that man kill Johan?
I don't know...
But... There still might be time.
What is this?