The neo-Nazis are trying to
burn that town!
That Turkish woman was killed...
We'll soon be arriving at the place
that Johan mentioned.
I don't know what will happen...
You can use a gun, can't you?
Take me to Frankfurt!
Calvin Street!
Weren't you going to kill Johan?
I'll do that later. Go quickly!
General Wolf will probably
be disappointed.
He asked you to kill Johan
because he thought that you could.
Asked me–?
I don't take orders from anyone.
I'm going to kill Johan
of my own accord!
Go to Calvin Street right now!
We've received confirmation that
the fires are ready to go at all points.
Good work!
Let's celebrate the superior people
with a wonderful fire!
Yes!
Now then...
What should we do with them?
There are people like them
even amongst the superior people...
One is a thief and the other is a kid
who was going to tell
the Turks our plans.
They're both scum.
They're going to be purged...
I feel the same.
This place is going to
be burned anyway.
Here. Don't cry.
Mom's going to come back.
Ayse?!
Ay...
Y-You're still alive?
How did you find me?
Dieter told me where you live.
Dieter... So that "Tenma"
he was talking about was you...
Where's Dieter?
He came here, didn't he?
Huh? No...
He hasn't come?
Anyway, where's Ayse?
This kid is Ayse's son.
I have to get him
to his mother quickly.
It can't be...
I don't believe it!
What is this kid going to do?!
He's so small, but has no mother!
What is he going to do–?
I don't want anymore victims.
Take me to the representatives
of this town!
What do you think?
Light the town on fire...huh?
We hear rumors about that sort of
extreme right-winger stuff
all year long.
We can't check out every single one.
First of all, it's suspicious that
this Japanese man
just waltzes into town,
even though he claims that
his life is in danger.
Ayse died because of this!
She was killed
trying to tell everyone!
I wonder about that.
Ayse is a prostitute like you, isn't she?
Doing business with a German
in that area and disappearing...
It happens a lot.
You're a disgrace to the Turks...
Who knows whose kid that is...
You know how difficult it is
to make a living.
If you want to live,
listen to what I'm saying!
Forget it!
Do what you like!
You can all burn!
Well, hold on a second.
Are you asking us to
form an alert committee?
Let's do as this Japanese man says.
Mr. Deniz.
Are you going to listen to
this suspicious Japanese man?
He's definitely suspicious...
But there are trustworthy people
among the Japanese.
Like General Nogi.
General...Nogi?
You don't know him?
General Nogi was a Japanese man
who saved the Turkish Navy
when they were stranded
in the Pacific long ago.
Oh...
Gather all the men in town!
It looks so delicious...
Another special dinner today.
Wait, wait.
Don't be in a rush to eat...
Dinner will be finished
before showtime.
The show will climax when
the main dish comes.
We will try this '76 Chateau Latour
I saved for tonight...
...and smack our lips over my favorite,
raw flounder with caviar.
And while we do that...
Ah...
Take a look.
The first fire has begun.
But that's still just an appetizer.
When is the main dish?
I told you, don't be impatient.
Take the time to savor your dinner
and enjoy the...
Where is the main dish?
If that fire is an appetizer...
What place are you going to burn
for the main dish?
- Over here!
- Water, water!
We don't have enough
fire extinguishers!
Don't go all at once!
Those who don't have their hands full,
come with me!
Just as I thought.
The flames started upwind!
That means that this area
is in danger, too!
Let's split up in three directions!
Oh my.
What a spectacular guest we have.
- Why you...
- Don't move!
I'll really shoot.
Put away that dangerous thing...
Why don't we enjoy this together?
Unfortunately, your appetizer
is going out.
That was just the appetizer.
But this is your favorite, isn't it?
Too bad.
Let's enjoy this.
It's a celebration...to welcome
your brother, Johan.
Johan doesn't want this.
Oh? How do you know that?
I saw it.
I went to the place in his message.
Huh?
Johan didn't want this.
Wh-What did you see?!
He...
He didn't want anything!
A-All right.
Relax... Calm down.
You killed Ayse!
I won't let you do
any more cruel things!
Where is the main dish?!
Where are you planning to
set that town on fire?!
Damn! They started fires in places
that the fire trucks can't get to.
Bring the wounded!
I'll go there immediately!
Tenma!
Did you find Dieter?!
There was someone
who said he saw
a kid who looked like him at the park
around noon, but...
Dieter...
Is it all right not to
go after that woman?
Yeah...
Let's continue dinner.
But that girl...
It's as I expected of Johan's sister.
Huh?
Her eyes earlier...
She really tried to kill me...
Because of that, I almost told her
the location of the main dish.
Then shall we continue dinner?
No, before that,
get me some underwear.
Huh?
What a terrifying girl.
Hold on!
I'm going to put it out right now!
You were very brave.
You're all right now!
I don't know who you are,
but thank you.
What happened to you?
Well...
Humph! It's that kid's fault!
Jeez. That was horrible.
Now then, I'm getting out of here.
They're not going to stop
with just fires!
Huh?
I lived here as I kid,
so I know this place well.
If I wanted to burn the town,
this place wouldn't do it.
I'm saying that this place is
a diversion!
Three locations upwind
were extinguished...
Mr. Tenma, we thank you.
Right everyone?
Yeah. Thanks to you,
it never became serious.
Now we have to
tend to the wounded.
I won't have any more victims!
Never!
What do you mean by a diversion?
The winds change.
At this time of night,
the winds stop.
Then suddenly, a wind from the river
comes blowing.
The wind...stopped...
Now then...
It's about time for the main dish.
All right!
It's all right now.
Thank you, doctor.
Let's have a toast.
What are you talking about?
The wounded are to stay still!
Loosen up. Right?
That's right. It's thanks to you that
this town didn't have a huge fire.
The extreme right-wingers
are probably fretting
because there aren't any flames.
They've got to be!
Don't underestimate us Turks!
Are there any other shelters
with wounded people?
The mosque by the river.
Hey, Dr. Tenma, take a rest already.
Have a drink.
I have to tend to the wounded first!
If the fires until now were diversions,
where are they going to light the fire?
Leave it alone. I don't care
what happens to this town!
Besides, I have a job I have to finish.
Wait!
Please tell me!
Where would you set the fire?!
It's as I told you.
The wind from the river
is going to blow soon.
There'd be nothing left of this town
if you set fire to
the abandoned factory by the river.
There should still be
some chemicals there.
It's almost time!
Time for the main dish.
Now, fill me up.
The plan is going as scheduled...
The celebration of
the superior people begins...
Why did you follow me?
I have to put out the fire.
I made a promise to Tenma!
Tenma?
This is it. The warehouse!
Thank goodness...I wonder
if they didn't notice this place...
Are these all chemicals?
There'd be nothing left of the town
if this many chemicals were lit.
All right. I'll protect this place!
I won't let them set fire here.
Are you all right?
I slipped...
What is this?!
It's gasoline...
Someone's...
...there...
It's all right.
I can walk by myself...
At any rate, let's go to the shelter
and let me have a look at it.
Sorry. I sprained it when I was
carrying my precious furniture.
Now that I have this rug...
I have no business in this town.
It's an excellent rug.
It'll go for 800,000,
no, 1 ,000,000 marks.
Heckel!
What happened to Dieter?
Oh, well...umm...
I asked you what happened to Dieter!
Uhh...Yeah.
That kid went to
the abandoned factory by the river.
Factory?
The wind from the river is
going to be blowing soon...
This town is finished if the chemicals
in the warehouse are set on fire.
Wha–?
It's this wind.
Tell everyone in the shelters
to get away from the riverside!
Quickly!
Huh?!
Let's go, Heckel!
Who is it?
Who's there?
Don't move!
Are you Johan's sister?
Throw away the lighter!
If I set the gasoline on fire
then this warehouse will be
a sea of flames in an instant.
I'm going to shoot you in the head
before you do that!
You'll stop moving
if your cranial nerves are severed.
Will you hit?
I've taken half a year of training.
I have 100 percent accuracy
at this range.
Threats don't work.
This is a celebration of
the superior people
in order to welcome Johan!
Johan doesn't want that!
Johan has indeed come to Frankfurt.
But he just killed one of your leaders
and his subordinates, then he left...
He left a message.
A message?
He's not the kind of person
you think he is...
He's...He's something
much more complicated...
What are you trying to say?
Something much more terrifying...
He's suffering in
the depths of sorrow!
I'm not responsible for becoming
enemies with these guys.
Which way is it to the warehouse?
Hey, that's good enough, isn't it?
I'm getting out of here.
What are you talking about?
Are you just going to abandon Dieter?!
Which way is it to the warehouse?!
A-All right!
I'll tell you, I'll tell you!
Your friend...you said his name
was Tenma, didn't you?
Huh?
I also have a friend named "Tenma".
Really? Is he also someone brave?
Yes... But I don't want him to
fire a gun.
I don't want him to kill anyone...
You shouldn't kill anyone either!
No matter how bad a person is?
That's right!
Don't copy what I'm going to do!
Close your eyes!
Don't look!
Don't shoot!
Tenma!
Heckel, put out the fire!
The rug! Quickly!
Wait. You idiot!
M-My 1 ,000,000 marks...
Nina...
Tenma...
It's the police!
Run away!
Leave that man to me!
There's a boat by the river!
Quickly, run away, Tenma!
My main dish...got cold...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Tell us the details at the station...
Wait a second!
I'll be right back!
Oh...H-Hey!
Tenma!
Nina!
Nina, make me a promise!
Don't shoot!
You shouldn't shoot people!
I saw Johan's message!
I also saw it!
I'm going there right now!
That time...ten years ago,
when I shot Johan...
I finally know what he meant when he
told me to shoot him in the head!
Johan...is not alone!
There are two Johans!
That's why...Dr. Tenma...
That's why...you aren't at fault...
I...I have to shoot Johan
in the head once more...
Hey, we don't need to
take a detour here.
Let's get going!
Jeez. I give up...
I'm starving and broke.
If only that rug were still safe...
Damn it.
What is this?
T-This is...
"Help me! The monster inside of me
is about to explode!"
There are two personalities...
within Johan–?