Hey, we don't need to
take a detour here.
Let's get going!
Jeez. I give up...
I'm starving and broke.
If only that rug were still safe...
Damn it.
What is this?
T-This is...
"Help me! The monster inside of me
is about to explode!"
There are two personalities...
within Johan?
That means that when you arrived
at the warehouse,
that Asian and the arsonist
were already fighting...
The Asian noticed you and fled...
Is that right, Miss Anna Liebert?
Yes.
Well, the culprit is
an extreme right-winger.
He turned himself in, saying that
it was a fire to celebrate his people,
or something like that...
Your identification checks out,
so that's enough for today.
May I leave, then?
Yes.
Oh, also...
The townspeople referred to
the Asian as Dr. Tenma.
Do you know anything about him?
I don't know anything.
What do you think?
Judging by her clothes,
do you suppose she was
trying to prostitute herself?
Not that.
Huh?
About Dr. Tenma.
At first, that's what
the Turks called the Asian.
But as soon as we told them that he
was suspected of multiple homicides,
they all said that
they didn't know who he was.
I became your reference.
Mr. Rosso.
I'm glad to see you're safe, Anna.
I was worried about you.
You just suddenly disappeared!
So you changed.
Yes! Those kinds of clothes
definitely match you better...
That earlier look didn't suit you.
Come on, you must be hungry.
Have something to eat!
Mr. Rosso, aren't you going to
have dinner?
I've already finished eating.
Just coffee is fine.
Now, eat up.
Yes, thank you for the food.
What is it?
You always pour five spoonfuls
of sugar into your coffee, don't you?
Of course.
Coffee isn't good if it isn't sweet.
You finally smiled.
Huh?
You looked pretty glum for someone
interviewing to work for me!
Is it that strange that I put a lot of
sugar in my coffee? Umm...Anna...
A-Anna Liebert.
Umm...
You're hired!
Of course!
Having a beautiful girl like you
working at my shop
would be excellent for business.
But...
But?
You should smile a little more!
It's a waste of your beauty.
Th-Thank you very much.
I'll work very hard!
There's no need to be so nervous!
This is an Italian restaurant
in a country town.
We aren't too busy.
Go around to the other side.
Okay.
I'll put out the food from here.
You carry the food out
to the customers.
Plates you've taken away are to be
placed on the right side of the counter.
The wine is here, and the glasses
are on this shelf.
There's also wine above this counter.
Order slips are placed here.
The wine is above the counter.
The glasses are over here...
This is for water.
Okay.
Morning...
Welcome.
I'm starving...
What?
Pleased to meet you, I'm Anna.
Pleased to meet you?
Whoa, you're not really the waitress
for this place, are you?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
There's no doubt, Anna is
waiting tables here, starting today.
Pleased to meet you.
Really?
Hmm?
Anna, get me a carbonara!
Anna, I'll have a bolognese!
Anna, could you get me some water?
Yes, right away!
Orders for a carbonara
and a bolognese.
All right.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Vongole and rigatoni.
The fettuccine’s also ready.
All right–!
Rosso, how did you trick this cutie
into working here?
I didn't trick anyone!
Anna, I'll take you to a store
much better than this place.
Are you free tonight?
Hey!
You'll pay if you harm my poster girl!
Whoa, "Crybaby" Rosso is
saying something courageous.
Anna, just the other day,
he was at my house crying
while he was watching a movie.
S-Shut up!
Another order of squid ink risotto!
Ah... "Summertime" is playing...
Huh?
"Summertime" is playing
in the classical movie theater.
See?
Isn't it great that Frankfurt has
a lot of movie theaters?
It was on TV recently.
Man... It just makes me
cry so much.
Have you ever seen it?
No.
I see.
The movie takes place in
the Italian town of Venice.
Venice was a port city
in medieval Italy.
It was called "the City of Water."
Oh?
It was a town that was built
on a tideland known as a lagoon.
There are canals running
throughout the town.
I'd like to show you Venice sometime.
Mr. Rosso, have you ever gone there?
Yes... And the soundtrack
is also good.
I think you've probably
heard its theme song before.
What's it like?
Umm...
Oh yeah.
Why don't we watch it right now?
We still might be able to get in.
Oh...yes.
But...
I see. It'll get late if we go now.
Yes.
I'm back!
Ah... Welcome back.
Oh... I'll do that.
It's all right.
Sorry for taking off from work
every afternoon.
It's fine. It's always slow
around this time.
I don't mean to be nosy, but...
Where do you go every day?
Oh...that's fine. You can do
what you like in your free time.
Gun training.
Shooting?
Yes. At Mr. Venkel's shooting range.
Ah, you're going to
Venkel's place, huh?
He's a good guy!
Mr. Rosso, have you ever shot a gun?
Not at all.
Just looking at guns
makes me tremble.
Here you go. Enjoy.
Thank you.
How is it this time?
Taste it.
What does it taste like?
Garlic, olive oil, parsley, and...
The flavors of the other things
you put in have disappeared,
haven't they?
Yeah.
Then that's not real pasta.
This is difficult.
Everything requires training.
Mr. Rosso, you can take a bath now!
Good night...
To think that there were movies
like this when I was young.
Mr. Rosso, you always cried
when you watched movies.
Yeah...when I was young,
I never had the time to watch movies,
even if I wanted to.
I ate a lot of delicious things then,
but I don't remember
how any of them tasted.
I didn't even know the taste of sugar.
The taste of sugar?
You know about me, don't you?
I checked up on you after you left.
Nina Fortner.
Disappeared after her parents
were murdered...
What did you want me to do?
A request?
Did you want me to teach you?
I thought of...having you teach me.
How did you find out about me?
A professor at my university's
law department was researching you.
The Ristorante Nino Case.
The Sacco-Milano Case.
The Sabatini Murder Case.
You were called as a witness
for all three of those cases.
And all three fell apart due to
lack of evidence.
But that professor had
an interesting theory.
According to his theory...
You're a professional hitman.
An incredible first-class one...
How many people
do you think I killed?
To be honest, I don't know.
I was still a kid... Before I knew it;
I was a member of an organization.
I stole, extorted money, everything.
In the end, I became a hitman.
I was able to eat well, as a reward.
I didn't care.
It was my job.
It was the same on that day as well.
The same as usual.
It was noon at a cafe.
I didn't know how many I'd already
killed by then or who my victim was.
I had him in my sight.
He had ordered a coffee.
And began putting sugar in it.
One spoonful...
Two spoonfuls...
Three spoonfuls...
Four spoonfuls...
When he poured the fifth spoonful
of sugar,
I could taste the coffee I always drink.
The man savored that coffee.
That's when I dropped my gun.
That was it... That's why I couldn't
kill people anymore.
Why didn't you ask me how to kill
during the past six months?
I...
I didn't want to get you involved.
Must you go?
Now then...
Thank you, Mr. Rosso.
It's easy to kill people.
You just have to forget
the taste of sugar.