I got divorced three years ago...
No. More accurately,
my wife ran away from me.
Because instead of listening to her...
I mostly listened to this.
My wife told me that I was
"just a collector of people's
innermost thoughts..."
Doctor...
You're weird.
I may be.
I peer into the deep abyss harbored in
the depths of peoples' hearts.
There is a chance I may sink
into that deep abyss.
Your fourth victim was
an 18-year-old woman
from Munich, right?
Did you experience
any sexual pleasure
when you butchered her?
Doctor...
That aside, ask me
about my 12th killing.
Mrs. Hanna Kemp
from Krupp-Haus...
She was 52, wasn't she?
At that time...I...
No...
You don't have to talk about that...
I'll probably ask you about it
sooner or later,
but right now, I want to hear about
the 11 killings before that.
Understand?
Now, I ask you,
when you commit a murder,
when do you reach
the peak of your sexual pleasure?
Before or after?
As discussed, the victims were
all long-haired girls
between the ages of
16 and 18 years...
These cases definitely fall
in the realm of sexual homicide.
But he has also confessed
to his 12th murder.
The victim in this case...
Mrs. Kemp, is not only older
than his other victims, at 52,
but does not appear to have
sexual scarring.
Since he claims to have carried out
the killing for a friend,
it appears that he is trying to
disrupt the investigation.
Who is it?
Who's there?
It's me, Rudy.
Tenma?!
Well, I was surprised...
Sorry. This was the only way
I could visit you.
You know my reason, don't you?
Yeah, I've heard.
Do you think that I'm a serial killer?
I don't know...
I only have newspapers, television,
and rumors from college friends...
But why did you come to me
of all people?
We weren't that close...
Besides, you despised me.
I always thought that you despised
me whenever our eyes met...
Ah ha... I see...
You want me to return the favor.
Is it money?
No, it's not.
I heard that you were an authority
on criminal psychology...
I have something I want you to
take a look at.
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"See how big the monster inside
of me has grown, Dr. Tenma!"
"Help me!"
"The monster inside of me
is about to explode!"
What is this?
I see. This Johan is the one
who really killed the director
and went on to kill the foster parents
who took care of him.
He disappeared once more
leaving messages like this.
I've got to find him
as soon as possible!
And you have to prove your
innocence as soon as possible...
Nearly 20 years ago, there was a man
who had been at the top of his class
at a famous medical university...
But then, a Japanese student
transferred to his school,
and that man's position changed.
The student was sociable
and quickly earned
everyone's respect.
Furthermore,
he got excellent grades.
The man who was always
at the top of the class
easily slipped down
after the first semester test.
During the second semester test...
the man became desperate
to take back his place
at the top of the class...
He did perfectly in all of his subjects.
But...
The final test was on
forensic medicine,
a subject that the man
struggled with.
All his work would be for nothing
if he failed this test...
He used his last resort...
Now I can be at the top of the class!
But...
But the Japanese man
never told anyone...
As a result, the man
returned to the top!
So is there anything you can tell me
about these two messages?
Does he have what you would call
a split personality?
Are you trying to say
that one personality
is committing the crimes
and the other is trying to stop them?
Indeed, there are examples
of serial murderers
leaving messages like these
at crime scenes...
But, sometimes, they can be a means
to escape their crimes.
Telling the difference is
the job of a psychoanalyst!
Most people think that serial
murderers are introverted,
but that's a big misconception.
There are some who are intelligent,
sociable, and good conversationalists.
They are skilled liars.
Is he just playing with me?
Now, hold on.
It's not good to jump to conclusions.
Could you tell me
a little more about Johan?
I became divorced three years ago...
No, more accurately,
my wife ran away from me...
Thank you, Rudy...
That was very interesting, Tenma.
I'd like to research this thoroughly!
Give me a call in two weeks.
What do you think of this man?
I can relate.
Oh? What can you relate to?
The monster...he talks about...
I see...
There's a monster, huh?
Indeed, there is one.
There is a monster within you,
within him, and even within me...
Stop.
Huh?!
That's armchair theory.
What?
I'm saying that monsters
exist in this world.
What's with that look?
Don't look at me like that.
I hate being looked down on!
Wh-What are you...
W-Warden...
Are you scared?
Are you scared?!
Are you?!
There are scarier things in the world.
I'll tell you something interesting.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're sure he's going to come to you,
aren't you?
He'll come.
I'll call you as soon as he does.
But...
But?
I want him as a research subject
after you arrest him.
Dr. Tenma is
a very interesting criminal...
I'll tell you something interesting.
Go to Mrs. Kemp's house.
Go to the underground storeroom.
You'll understand if you go there.
There's proof that monsters do exist...
Yes?
Ah, Tenma...
Yes, I'd like to meet you...
Hmm... All right...
Then, I'll be waiting.
Sergeant Kohl?
I promised to meet Tenma.
8 PM at the Oder Park,
in front of the fountain...
Bye...
Right now, I am verifying
Jurgens route on the day of his crime.
According to his confession,
he broke into this storeroom
and spent several hours here.
When Mrs. Kemp returned home,
he forced his way into
the second-floor bedroom
and committed his crime.
Nothing out of the ordinary...
But...
There are many picture frames...
Mrs. Kemp is shown...
A doll, huh?
I don't see anything abnormal...
There is no proof of the monster
that Jurgens spoke of!
As I thought, the 12th murder was
done to disrupt the investigation.
He confessed that he committed
the crime as a favor for a friend...
By calling that friend a monster...
When I was a child, I was
disciplined by my mother daily.
There was a big doll
that my mom cherished...
It was a long haired...girl doll...
I asked that doll for help
as I was being hit.
But it only looked at me and grinned...
And that storehouse was filled
with pictures of my mom.
Wherever I looked, there was
Mom... Mom... Mom...
She was watching me all this time!
What's the meaning of this?!
It's exactly as he described...
Did Jurgens change this storehouse
to be like the one from his childhood?
This is Jurgens when he was a child!
Impossible!
He shouldn't have any connection
with Mrs. Kemp when he was a child!
What's with this photograph?
Jurgens' childhood face is pasted on?
This one too...
And this one... And this one...
And this one...
Mrs. Kemp never had any children...
This boy...
Who are you?!
There's proof that monsters do exist...
I...just did as I was told
in a letter from my friend.
F-Friend?
One day...I received a white envelope
without a return or mailing address.
At first, I was annoyed
by his familiarity.
He said that he understood me...
The letters came every day.
He loved to write letters.
But before I knew it,
I could hardly wait for his letters...
I enjoyed them...
I thought...that he might
really be a friend.
Then one day, I was called out
by those letters
to go to the storehouse
of a certain home...
Was it Mrs. Kemp's storehouse?
I wonder how he knows...
I wonder how he knows
about my childhood...
I was confused
at Mrs. Kemp's house.
"What's the meaning of this?"
"Mrs. Kemp is...my mom?"
Before I realized it,
I had gone to the second floor
and killed Mrs. Kemp.
He loves to write letters!
That friend also sent letters
to Mrs. Kemp.
What's this?!
Here too!
And here...
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"See how big the monster inside
of me has grown, Dr. Tenma!"
"Help me!"
"The monster inside of me
is about to explode!"
It's the message that Johan left!
It's the same...
The friend... Johan...
...actually exists?
Not yet?
It's already far past eight.
Sergeant Kohl...
What's that?
He's come...
The longhaired Asian...
Sorry to bother you
when you're busy, Rudy.
I analyzed what you said.
I thought that you made it up.
I didn't think that Johan existed.
I thought he was an imaginary person
you made up...
Wha–?!
Rudy, listen to me! I...
Currently, I'm researching
a serial murderer named Jurgens...
There's only one case that's different
from his usual crimes.
Forget that, listen to me!
Listen up!
We're finished for today!
Come again!
The carnival is over.
Tell everyone to apprehend him
when I give the signal!
Yes!
Don't fail to catch
Dr. Tenma's conversation...
Tenma...
You despised me, didn't you?
You despised me ever since
you saw me cheating in college...
Isn't that right?
S-Sergeant Kohl, this is bad!
Dr. Gillen and Tenma are headed
toward the west exit!
They'll get lost among
the leaving carnival crowd!
Indeed, I probably
should be despised...
Rudy, forget about that, right now...
Do you remember?
Back then, I hid a cheat sheet
right here...
Like this.
Run away you're surrounded
by the police.
Don't look! Let's walk.
Is the doctor being threatened?
W-Well...
There's too much noise around,
so I can't hear them...
- Wait...
Jurgens said that he killed
Mrs. Kemp for a friend.
Th-This is...
It's something from
the basement of Mrs. Kemp's house.
Mrs. Kemp never had any children...
Your Johan and Jurgens' friend
are probably the same person!
They've passed through the west exit.
Shall I apprehend him?
Wait! Tenma may be carrying a gun!
There was a letter
with the same message as Johan's
in Mrs. Kemp's house.
Johan lived off Mrs. Kemp
and disposed of her
when he no longer had a use for her.
As you said, he might have done it
to erase his past...
You're innocent.
I can't talk specifically at this point,
but I'll tell you what I've figured out...
I don't know how,
but Johan can smell out murderers.
He can pry into their loneliness
and control them.
There haven't been any murders
of any foster parents
that Johan was taking advantage of
during his young adulthood.
I think it's probably because,
age-wise,
he no longer needed foster parents.
But there's another possibility...
Johan finally found
his ideal family and joined them.
But why would he try to
erase his past?
Does he have some sort of reason?
For what purpose could he have
joined this family?
For what?
Now then...
We've arrived at the bus terminal!
Confirm what bus he's getting on!
Get cars to the terminal!
Prepare to track him!
Yes!
I bought you a bus ticket...
Tenma...there's a way to
turn yourself in now
and prove your innocence!
I'll help you!
I'm...not chasing Johan
to prove my innocence!
Huh?
Thank you, Rudy.
Tenma...
Could it be that
you're going to kill Johan?
Oh yeah!
I never despised you...really...
I thought you were an interesting guy,
but I never had the chance
to talk to you.
But now we've finally become friends!
But...when I cheated back then...
You looked in my direction.
I also cheated back then.
What?!
The five buses left at
about the same time?!
Tenma...