I bought you a bus ticket...
Tenma...there's a way to
turn yourself in now
and prove your innocence!
I'll help you!
I'm...not chasing Johan
to prove my innocence!
Huh?
Thank you, Rudy.
Tenma...
Could it be that you're
going to kill Johan?
Oh yeah! I never despised you...
I thought you were an interesting guy,
but I never had the chance
to talk to you.
But now we've finally become friends!
But...when I cheated back then...
I also cheated back then.
Tenma...
Did you see the sign just now?
Oh, sorry. I was looking at this map...
Is it this way?
Or that way?
Which direction are we facing?
Where did you get that map?
Oh. Why, at the car rental counter,
of course.
I thought so.
It was probably while I was
using the bathroom.
At my age, it's impossible for me
to read intricate maps like this
to begin with...
That's because you left
your reading glasses at the airport.
Wippenhausen, Ampertshausen,
Gartelshausen...
What's with those convoluted names?
That's interesting. I wonder if
Germans think the same thing
when they come to England.
Anyway, where's the next crossroad?
Hmm...
Oh my.
There's a person.
We can ask for directions.
It's all right. Let's keep going.
Oh my...
But they're hitchhikers...
Why don't we give them a ride?
And what'll we do if the stranger
gives us trouble?
But look.
He's with such a small child.
I feel sorry for him. Let them on.
Aren't you glad, Tenma?
They stopped for us!
Yeah...
Guten tag. Bitte...
I don't know German.
Can you speak English?
Oh, you're English.
I want to go to Freiham.
Could you give me a lift?
Lend me that map.
Here.
Where is that place?
Huh?
The place you want to get to.
Oh... Umm...
Right now, we're around here,
so it's further south...
Oh my. It's in the same direction
we're going.
Yes...
Now, hop on in.
Danke schön!
What's your relationship?
Huh?
You clearly aren't related.
You're Asian and it seems like
that kid is German...
O-Oh...
He's the child of a friend.
Judging by the way you look...
Are you working in
some specialized field of work?
Huh?
It's the way you talk...
and your demeanor...
Dear...
Stop already.
It's that bad habit of yours...
Sorry. He can't shake off
that bad habit.
He's an ex-police officer.
What did she say?
Well...
It seems he's a police officer.
Let's get out, Tenma...
No...
Oh... Um... So...
You're taking a trip
now that your husband's retired?
Yes...well...
My husband is devoted to his work...
He never would have thought of
taking a trip together.
Sorry for interrupting
your time together...
Umm, if we're being a nuisance,
we can...
No... We were able to rent a car,
but we can't read the map.
We also have problems
ordering food...
We'd feel more secure
traveling with someone
who could act as a translator.
Really...
What'll we do?
We can't do anything about this...
We've got to go to
a nearby gas station.
Oh, there's a car!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
What's wrong?
We're out of gas.
Oh...
Well, that's a real problem out here...
Well, I can take two of you.
Mr. Jones...
It's fine. Just get on.
But...
You don't have to bother
sticking around with us.
So, when I get to
the nearest gas station,
I'll inform someone
that your car broke down.
Okay. I would appreciate
if you could do that.
Aren't you glad, Tenma?
We switched rides so easily.
Yeah...
At any rate, take me to the gas
station.
There are no stations here.
Huh?
They sure are late...
Yeah...
Someone from the gas station
should come if that man
Let them know that
we're stranded, okay?
Yeah...
That man...
Huh?
He might have just run off...
Dear...
That can't be.
I think he's a nice person.
I wonder about that...
Huh?
What a beautiful sky...
I've heard enough about
the setting sun.
I've seen enough of it.
Oh, I'm not talking about
the setting sun.
That's already gone...
Take a look. Look at the color
of the sky where the sun set...
Yeah.
I wonder if Robert is
looking at this sky.
Oh my...
That's...
Say, take a look at that.
Someone is coming...
Oh, look.
I knew it.
Look...I knew it...
I borrowed gas and a lamp
from a nearby farmer.
Oh my...
See, Dear?
Ah... That was delicious,
wasn't it, Dear?
We were able to eat
a spectacular meal
because we had the menu translated
from German.
Right?
Especially that wine.
Forster Ungeheuer.
It's from the Palatinate region.
Yes!! And that liver dish.
Liver Knödel!
Yes, that.
Ah, I'm so glad!!
If you weren't around,
we would have passed by
the nice parts of Germany
without knowing it!
It was nothing...
Thank you as well
for paying for dinner.
Dieter, do you want more ice cream?
No, that's fine.
Do you think this guy is the culprit?
Huh?
This man on trial accused of
murdering his wife.
What do you think?
Well...who knows?
Though I may not look it...
I had quite a few exploits
when I was a detective.
Oh...
Honestly...
Bragging at a time like this...
Well...
When I saw a person,
I could usually tell whether or not
he was the culprit...
or a bad person.
O-Oh.
Stop that already.
Did you have too much wine to drink?
But...
After a while, I couldn't tell.
Good and bad people...
Guilty and innocent people...
I no longer could tell the difference.
Well, it means that
I wasn't much of a detective.
Indeed... I must have
drank too much wine.
What was the name of this wine?
It's Ungeheuer.
It's delicious.
My...how cute...
I hope you make a lot of friends
at your new place.
Huh?
Yes...that would be nice.
Everyone has a happy childhood...
How nostalgic...
Yeah.
Whoops. Oh no.
It should be around here.
What should?
Here, Dear...
Sorry, but I'm going to take a detour...
Go right ahead.
Ah...here it is.
The police?!
I'll be right back. You wait in the car.
W-What are we going to do,
Tenma–?
Tenma...let's run away.
What's wrong?
Someone's parked in
the officers' parking spaces again.
He appears to be a foreigner...
Oh well...
What should we do?
Umm... We want to get to Freiham.
You're going in
the opposite direction.
Oh...
Sorry, it won't take long.
I just want to go to
Steinbach Castle for a bit.
Dear...
Steinbach Castle?
There's something I want to see.
Are you all right?
Yes, thank you...
My son wrote in his letter...
Huh?
The view from this castle
is wonderful.
He said that he wanted to
show it to us.
Oh...is your son here?
We're going to go see him.
But we keep taking detours...
Wow...
He was looking at this view...
My son...
...killed a man...
We came to this country to see him.
We'll be going from here.
Thank you very much.
It was nothing.
I thank you from
the bottom of my heart.
Huh?!
Thank you...take care.
What a nice man.
Yeah... He's wanted
on suspicion of multiple homicide.
Huh?!
It can't be! That man?!!
No...
I'm sure of it.
I saw his wanted poster earlier.
But...
His picture was posted
in the police station
when we went to greet the detective
who arrested Robert earlier today.
I can't believe it... That nice man...
Yeah... I was suspicious
when I saw his picture earlier.
And I met him to confirm that...
...he's innocent!
He's not a bad man.
Robert...my son has committed
a murder...
I couldn't even tell anything
about my own family.
When I realized that,
I quit my job as a detective.
But...
I'll try to have confidence
in my eyes once more.
Robert committed a crime,
but he's not a bad man.
Now...let's go see Robert.