Barbara...would you like
a Moscow Mule?
Thank you, Michael.
Okay.
Fritz, I have juice for you.
Fritz, thank your father.
Thank you, old man.
Fritz!!
It can't be helped.
He'll get used to me eventually.
The antique business I just started
will also take off eventually.
But it was just so sudden for me.
Huh?
I suddenly get to live in
such a wonderful home,
and my sweet husband
makes delicious cocktails for me.
Say, did you see something?
Huh?
The house next door.
Sometimes I get the feeling
that someone is watching us
from the window of the second floor...
No. That house is empty, isn't it?
I know, but...
Well, Mrs. Daughtry,
from across the street,
told me something...
What did she tell you?
Twenty years ago, a couple
was brutally murdered next door.
She said that ghosts have
been seen in that house.
What's wrong, Michael?
Huh?
Don't tell me that
you believe that story.
O-Of course not.
Going out?
Yeah.
I'll get the car.
Oh... No, that's all right.
I think it would be good for
just the three of us to go out together.
We probably don't need a bodyguard.
I see...
Well, Fritz will probably warm up
to you faster that way.
Exactly. That's the plan.
Good luck, Dad.
Well, shall we get going?
Detective, what are the results
of the investigation?
First off, regarding Dr. Tenma...
The police are chasing him as
a suspect in the Fortner murder case.
But they couldn't find out
anything about him.
When Dr. Tenma was
summoned by the police,
he said that a boy whose life
he saved ten years ago
had murdered the director of
Eisler Memorial Hospital
and three others, and had run away...
The boy's name is Johan.
Later, the adult Johan murdered
someone right in front of Dr. Tenma.
Next is Nina Fortner...
She was the daughter of
the murdered couple.
Her whereabouts are also unknown.
Now, as for Mr. Mesner...
I followed him to Frankfurt.
What is he doing now?
He's dead.
He was brutally stabbed
two months ago.
The official line is that
he was killed in a drug dispute.
Mesner was my partner
when I was a police officer.
I see...
Mr. Mesner was dismissed from
the police for narcotics possession.
A man called "The Baby" saved him.
He's the boss of
an extreme right-wing organization.
What does that
have to do with anything?
Last winter, a group of people tried to
set fire to Frankfurt's Turkish district.
Remember?
There are rumors that
"The Baby" was the ringleader.
An Asian man stopped the fire.
His name was Tenma.
He might be Dr. Tenma...
One more thing. Rumor has it that
"The Baby" started the fires
to welcome a certain young man
to his organization as it's leader.
A certain young man?
What was the name of the boy
who Tenma saved ten years ago?
Johan...
The youth who "The Baby" tried to
install as his organization's leader
is also called Johan.
Ah...
So you're coming at me that way...
Say, Roberto, my life is like
this chess piece, don't you think?
Is something bothering you?
Back then...
I was always a loser in life.
Until I got that phone call.
I was a detective who sold
confiscated drugs on the black market
with my partner Mesner.
The caller knew everything...
We just had to kill a certain couple
if we wanted him to keep quiet.
We'd be saved if we killed
the Fortners in Heidelberg!
There was one more person
that night...
A newspaper journalist, or something,
was also in the house.
Mesner and I
killed all three of them.
After that, we were given
a large sum of money.
When I left the police force,
I was picked up by the Syndicate.
I was even given a good post.
The money I made
was easily laundered...
Then you met your wife
and went straight.
How did I get out of
that organization so easily?
Who made that phone call?
Who gave me
that large sum of money?
Who's controlling my life?
Roberto, I'm grateful to you
for protecting me all this time...
Then could you take back
that last move?
Huh?
That's something that I can't do.
That's harsh.
I'll be off now.
Okay. Be careful.
Buy me a toy!!
Say goodbye to your father, Fritz.
It's pointless.
All he can think about are toys...
Goodbye, Dad...
Goodbye!
Roberto, were there any calls
from the detective?
He should have come by now...
Roberto!
Roberto, it's the detective!!
Come quickly!
Roberto!
Y-Y-You're...
I'm the daughter of the Fortners,
the couple you killed.
Did you kill him?
Roberto!
Your bodyguard, Roberto,
was the one who killed that man!
Roberto did this?
I saw everything from
the house next door!
That's impossible!
Roberto is a friend I can trust.
W-What about you?
You came to get revenge on me!
R-Roberto!
Roberto...
I'm taking this bag.
You can stay here if you want to.
You have someone you can trust.
What's wrong, Mr. Muller?
Mr. Muller?
Drive out of here, quickly!
Now!!
You've been watching me
all this time from
the house next door, haven't you?
What were you planning to
do with me?
I hate you from
the bottom of my heart.
I want to kill you!
I-I was forced to do it.
He said that he'd reveal that I was
selling narcotics on the black market
if I didn't kill your parents...
So...I had to team up with Mesner...
We had to do it!
You had to...?
You...had to?!
Stop!
Stop the car!!
They were wonderful people...
They were really wonderful...
My mother and father loved me
from the bottom of their hearts.
W-Wait!
I'm not even their real daughter.
My mother and father...
really...really...
S-Stop...
Please stop–!!
But they were killed by
a scoundrel like you!!
Barbara... Fritz...
Come here.
What?
What are you talking about?
What the hell?!
So this is what it's like to be killed...
Fritz called me Dad for the first time...
I don't want to lose them.
I've got things I don't want to lose...
Barbara... Fritz...
Düsseldorf...every morning
at 8:30 at that cafe.
When I joined the Syndicate,
my boss ordered me to pose as
a businessman each morning.
Every morning, a mother
passed by with her child.
It was my only connection
with normal life.
H-Hey 'morning.
Good morning.
What did you ask
your detective to do?
Find you and Tenma...
And find information about Mesner,
my former police partner.
But Mesner is dead.
Huh?
He was murdered.
I hired an investigator
who was familiar with the case.
I had a call from
the detective last night...
Things are getting strange.
- Strange?
- Yeah.
Mr. Mesner was
already a junkie.
He wasn't someone who would get
in a dispute with the Syndicate.
One more thing. The culprit wasn't
from Frankfurt's organization,
but from Düsseldorf...
Düsseldorf?
Well...I'll tell you
the rest of the details in person.
Here it is.
A draft of the report...
"The culprit of...the Mesner case."
"Who is...Roberto?"
Do you know what this means?
Hello?
I want you to return my bag.
R-Roberto?!
Your wife and Fritz
are with me right now.
W-What did you say? Hey!
Put my wife on the phone!
You should come back quickly
to your "happy home"...
A gun...
Huh?
Could you lend me a gun?
You can only use
that gun at short range.
There are only four shots...
That's good enough.
I was once a police officer.
Be careful!
If I die, I can't tell
the police the truth...right?
That's right. You can't die.
I'll cover you from
the empty house next door!
Dad!!
F-Fritz...
Dad, look, it's a fishing pole!
He absolutely insisted on
going fishing with his father.
Barbara...
W-Where's Roberto?
Uh...Oh yeah.
Some of his friends from
the security company have come by.
It seems like something happened
while we were out.
Friends?
Don't worry. Nobody was hurt.
Oh, Roberto, Michael's come home.
Don't worry. A window was broken.
One of the neighborhood kids
was probably causing trouble.
There's nothing to worry about.
W-Where's the body?!
What happened to
the detective's body?
It was right here!
There wasn't anything here.
Roberto! Who...Who are you?
Your wife and Fritz are coming.
Now then, don't
make things complicated.
Come on...
Good. Nothing happened today.
Today was a peaceful day.
It will continue to be peaceful.
Nina...
Nina!
She was a beautiful girl, wasn't she?
Nina... What did you do to Nina?
We are treating her well.
She is an important guest
to a certain individual.
A certain individual?
The name of that young man
is also Johan.
Johan! Johan! Johan!
Who is Johan?!
Who are you guys?!
You want to live a happy life
with your wife and Fritz...
Isn't that good enough?
That's good enough.
Thank you for your assistance.
We go our separate ways today.
What are you going to do to Nina?!
Are you going to kill her?
Be happy...
When are you going to
take me fishing?
Hm? Yeah...
Tomorrow, if the weather's good...
All right!
I no longer see ghosts...
That's a good look.
You look a lot like Johan.
When can I meet Johan?
I'm cooperating because you said
that you would let me meet Johan.
Indeed, he wants to
meet you as well...
Where is he right now?
He's living happily in Munich.
Munich?
That's a very good look.
It's truly a shame...
Now then... All that's left is...
Dr. Tenma, huh?
Why...Why did you come?
I told you.
I'm an ex-detective.
We're almost at your house.
Yeah...
Tomorrow...I promised Fritz
that I would go fishing with him.
I see...
I hope the weather's good...
I'm sure it will be...