Come on, get out of the way!
Don't interfere with the investigation.
At least tell us what you
think of the case.
Do you think that this incident
is one of the serial murders?
The victims, the Joppes,
did they have any children?
No matter how I think about it,
this is exactly like the murders
of middle-aged couples
that have been happening
throughout Germany!
No comment!
I've heard that an agent from the BKA
who's in charge of that case
has come.
Does that mean that there's
a connection to the serial killings?
No comment!
It looks like it would be quicker
to ask the BKA agent directly.
Leave it to me!
I'll get ahead of the other papers!
Leave me a giant space
for the headline.
Take care of it!
Excuse me.
I'm Kipper from the Hamburg Tag.
You're the agent from the BKA,
aren't you? I'd like a comment.
Is there a connection between
this case and the other murders
of middle-aged couples?
Kipper of the Hamburg Tag...
I'll give you an exclusive.
That's precisely correct!
This case is one of the murders
of middle-aged couples!
I thought so! Then the suspect is
that Japanese doctor!
I just saw the report. It was carried out
in the same way as the other killings.
That's quite the scoop.
Thanks.
Hold on a second.
Yes?
The Hamburg Tag is the leading
paper around here, isn't it?
I expect your article to be in
the leading papers across Germany.
Of course. Thank you
for your cooperation.
I am the culprit.
I have just become the culprit.
Should I knock?
Ah, it would be best not to
startle the Joppes.
They're a friendly couple.
They casually welcome me in
and lead me to the living room.
They aren't suspicious of me.
The husband's chair...
Of course, I sit in the guest chair.
The husband dies over there
on the floor a few minutes later.
But I still haven't made my move.
Where is the wife?
That's right, she still isn't in this room.
She should be pouring out tea
in the kitchen.
The wife is stabbed in the back
before she can serve it.
Which means that I should
make my move about now.
I take out my knife.
As the husband panics
and tries to stand up,
I stab him!
Whoops. I missed.
The husband runs away
with a wound on his left hand.
The next strike is on
the husband's right shoulder.
I miss again. I'm really an amateur!
The husband screams
his wife's name.
But his wife, who's in the kitchen,
cannot hear him.
His wife has become
hard of hearing lately.
That's right. I knew about that.
Make noise. Cry and scream!
I can take my time and deal with
your wife after I kill you.
I've cornered you!
The husband's left hand print.
I've cornered the husband
in front of this sideboard.
The final blow!
No, I don't finish him off here either.
It's 5 meters from where
the husband died.
Why?
Why don't I finish him off here?
Did...
Did this man kill the Joppes?
No, that may not be the case.
I just want to ask a favor
of everyone in the neighborhood.
Behave normally if this man appears.
And give me a call
as soon as possible.
That's all.
Okay.
You won't be in any danger.
I guarantee it.
This was such a terrible incident
for such a quiet neighborhood.
Indeed. The Joppes were
really good people.
Mrs. Joppe always greeted me
cheerfully every morning
when I called out to her.
When you called out to her?
Mrs. Joppe became hard of hearing
about a year ago.
Huh?! It can't be.
It was written on
her physician's medical chart.
She shouldn't have heard
most of your greetings.
Oh my.
Knowing her, she probably greeted
me when she sensed my presence.
Didn't anyone in the neighborhood
know about her hearing?
No. I don't think so...
Well... What a wonderful business
you have.
You've made such rapid progress
at such a young age.
It's not an easy thing to do, Mr.
Giebel.
No, the contracts I made
with car manufacturers
just happened to work out.
I'd like to give my sincere condolences
for your uncle and aunt's misfortune.
Yes. My uncle and aunt
were my only relatives.
That couple never had any children.
They must have taken good care
of you as their nephew.
Yes. It was if I was really their son.
So, will the culprit be caught?
Yes. I'm pretty sure I know who it is.
Is it that Japanese ex-doctor?
You're familiar.
Of course. There have been cases
like this before.
How much will your inheritance be?
Huh?
Well, Mr. Joppe was
quite a wealthy man.
Does that have something to do
with this case?
You are the only heir to their estate.
Am I right?
What about it? That's not something
to be talking about.
Companies can be hard on money
even if they seem to be doing well.
It happens often.
What are you saying?!
You talk as if I was
after their inheritance!!
It's all right. You have a perfect alibi.
You went out to dinner
with your secretary and subordinates
after a business meeting.
There are witnesses.
W-What are you trying to say?
You're not the culprit.
Isn't that right?
Inspector Lunge!
Oh, you.
What's going on?!
What are you talking about?
Don't act dumb.
I've been investigating that nephew
for the past few days.
His company might look profitable
at first glance,
but it's holding a lot of
bad stocks and bonds.
It's pretty strapped for cash.
You've even thoroughly investigated
the area around the nephew's company.
What is the truth?
Do you really think this case
is connected with
the middle-aged couple murders?
All the newspapers are taking
the same take as our exclusive!
It'll be a huge false report if it's
not related to that string of murders!
It's as you say.
It's the work of a copycat.
It was made to look like
the serial killer's work.
I thought so!
I've got to rewrite
my article immediately.
No. It's fine as it is.
Huh?
Continue writing your article
as if it was one of
the middle-aged couple murders.
No way!
I can't write an article of lies!
Just do it.
I-I'm still a journalist.
It's useless to pressure me.
Kipper, was it?
She was quite an attractive woman.
You have a comfortable household...
a lovely wife and daughter...
It's impossible to resist the charms
of such an ideal, attractive woman.
Keep writing features on the middle-
aged couple murders as you've been doing.
No, write even more about it
than before.
He will come if you do.
Huh?
I'm counting on you.
Yes?
There's something I wanted to
ask you about.
I see. They were such
a wonderful couple.
Yes.
Did they have any foster children?
No.
Did they ever live with any children
you've never seen before,
even for a little while?
Never. They took good care
of their nephew.
Oh. Would you like another
cup of tea?
Oh...no, I'm already...
Don't say that.
There's no mistake.
It's the man from the photograph.
He's in my house right now.
I see. Thank you
for your cooperation.
Inspector Lunge, there's someone
who wants to see you.
Who is it?
It's the nephew of the Joppes
who were killed.
You think that I'm the culprit,
don't you?
Don't you? Isn't that right?
I killed them for their fortune.
That's what you're really thinking.
True, I have countless debts
at the moment.
Their fortune they left for me
would save me from this fiasco.
But I'm not that kind of person!
Is that all you came here to say?
Huh? Is that all?
You have no right to say that
after treating me like the culprit!
I have somewhere
I have to go right now.
Wait! I want you to take back
the rude things you said before!!
The police stopped following you.
The police here think you're innocent.
Isn't that good enough?
Then who do you think
is the murderer?
You mean the culprit?
That doesn't matter.
Huh?
As long as I catch that man.
There's a bloodstain there.
Which means...
He missed?
Does this mean you don't think that
the Japanese doctor did it?
Well...
It's a crime made to look like the string
of middle-aged couple homicides.
How can you be so sure?
There's one thing in this case
that the others don't have.
The culprit cornered the victim here.
But instead of here...
He's finished off over there.
Why?
Why does he hesitate for a moment?
It isn't him.
There were emotions.
Emotions?
The crime scenes
of the man I'm after...
He takes a few valuables and tries to
make it look like a robbery.
But no emotions can be sensed
at those crime scenes.
But this crime scene is full of
emotions.
The culprit panics at the sight of
the victim's face
and his face in a mirror.
Well, don't worry.
The police here are incompetent.
No matter how I think about it...
This is a crime made to look like
Johan's crimes...
How long is this going to continue?
How long...
It's been a while.
We finally meet, Dr. Tenma.
I've been looking for you.
For a long time...
I've wanted to have
a quiet talk with you.
There's no use in
running away anymore.
Let's have a quiet talk.
How long are you going to
keep doing this, Dr. Tenma?
It's over.
If only you weren't here...
Out of the way!!
I-I did it. I killed the Joppes.
I'll turn myself in! Forgive me.
I'm not interested in you.
Don't get in my way.
S-Shit!!
What's with this wound?!
At this rate, you're going to
bleed to death.
Who stabbed inspector Lunge?
I've got to drop him off
in front of a hospital and run away.
Damn it.
So you've regained consciousness.
Where are the keys
to these handcuffs?
It's pointless to look for your gun.
I have it.
Just quickly hand me
the keys to these handcuffs!
I can't help you like this.
I looked at your wound.
Luckily, it hadn't penetrated
your abdominal cavity.
But the large amount of blood
you're losing...
You'll die if we don't
stop the bleeding!!
Confess...Dr. Tenma.
What?
You murdered the director
of Eisler Memorial Hospital
along with three others.
You've been killing middle-aged
couples for the past three years.
Confess that it was all your doing.
You're really going to die.
It's all Johan's doing.
You're looking for the real culprit,
right?
Johan doesn't exist.
You are Johan, Dr. Tenma!!
Confess.
There wasn't anything good
in this warehouse,
but I found what I needed
to perform an emergency procedure.
All that's left are these hands!
I can save you as long as
these hands are freed!!
You are a skillful doctor
when you're Dr. Tenma...
A good-natured man with no faults.
How many people did you kill
with those hands?
You're mistaken.
When are you going to
change into Johan?
When is that good-natured face
going to turn into that of a killer?
You're mistaken.
I don't make mistakes.
You're losing consciousness
as your blood pressure falls.
At your crime scenes...
You shouldn't talk anymore.
there are no emotions.
Don't talk.
You lose your emotions
when you deal with life and death
every day, don't you, Dr. Tenma?
That's it. That calmness
is always at the crime scenes.
Perfectly calm.
You're mistaken.
Whenever I performed a surgery...
Would I make a mistake?
Could I do this well?
Would trouble happen
all of a sudden?
I was always tense...
People's lives are at stake
with my hands.
My hands...
There's no way that I can be calm.
Don't...move.
I'm going to save you!
I'll...shoot.
I'm going to stop your bleeding!
Where are the keys?!
Are they in your pants pocket?
I'll...shoot.
I'm relieved.
You look well.
You look better than
when you're working.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
It seems that that emergency
procedure was perfect.
The doctor said that
you would have died
if it that exact procedure
wasn't performed.
I guess this means that Tenma
saved my life.
Well, Tenma got away,
but Giebel confessed to
the murder of the Joppes.
You did good, Lunge.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Huh?
Tenma saved Lunge's life.
This might be problematic
in catching Tenma.
Should I remove Lunge
from the Tenma case?
Oh, I'm sorry if Inspector Lunge
is being a nuisance.
He's not a nuisance at all.
He was a very pleasant man.
I keep telling him that he doesn't
have to recover that quickly,
but he's squeezing that ball
and walking down the halls.
It seems like he's having a lot of fun.
Fun?
Yes. He keeps saying that
nothing could be more fun.
What was that culprit's name?
Oh yes, Tenma.
He's said that he was having
a wonderful time
chasing a culprit like Tenma.