Get out!
Leave me alone.
What are you talking about?
Wake up!
Jeez, you're hopeless.
This isn't a hotel!
What?
Don't touch me!
Don't you know who I am?
Here. These are your belongings.
Make sure everything's there
and sign this form.
Eva Heinemann... Don't come to
this drunk tank ever again.
You got drunk and fell asleep
in a back alley.
Just be thankful that you're safe!
Got a cigarette?
Huh?
I'm asking if you have a cigarette.
You can't smoke in the station.
Go outside if you want to smoke.
Lighter...
Where's my lighter?
My bag!
Where are you keeping my bag?!
That's the only bag you had.
You're lying! I had
a large shoulder bag!
Someone probably stole it from you
when you passed out in that alley.
What are you going to do about it?!
I had valuables in there!!
Anyway...
Want to fill out a robbery report?
But I don't think it'll do you any good.
You lost your keys?
My bag was stolen.
Open this door already!
Huh?
W-What is this?!!
Goodness...you've been robbed.
What a bother.
I've got to change the lock.
Anyway, Ms. Heinemann,
I asked you about it the other day,
but about the rent...
The money you paid in advance
has already run out.
I need you to pay the rest.
My suitcases have been pried open.
Are you listening?
The remainder of the rent
and the fee to change the lock.
I don't have any money.
Huh?
I just have to get out, don't I?!
What an unfortunate incident.
So, you want me to help you?
You're the one who said you didn't
want so see me anymore and left.
It's been a while since we met.
At least get me a drink.
Hey, Eva, even if your bag was stolen,
it's not as if you don't
have any money, right?
I've never seen anyone spend money
the way you do.
You'll never have enough.
Whatever the case,
you've run out of money, right?
How much will you pay?
Huh?!
I'll sleep with you.
I'm asking you how much you'll pay.
You idiot!
What kind of man would pay to sleep
with a woman he's already slept with?
Get me a drink.
Stand on the streets around there.
Someone interested
may buy you.
Even if you are
a middle-aged alcoholic!
I'm sure that you didn't leave it here.
Are you sure you didn't leave it
at the place you went to afterwards?
I don't remember anything
after this place.
You said that something important
was in that bag,
but if it's something of value,
you should forget about it.
It's not worth any money.
Any money.
Hey, I've been looking for you.
I was just at that pub there.
I heard that you went this way.
Who are you?
Come on... We had such a fun time
drinking last night.
I went drinking with you?
Here's your bag.
I've been meaning to give it to you.
Oh. I guess this means that I should
introduce myself once more.
I'm Roberto. Care to have lunch
somewhere around here?
That's horrible.
Your hotel room was ransacked?
But it doesn't seem like you did it.
Of course. I haven't even
opened your bag.
My key is in here.
But I no longer have a use for this key.
Sorry. You wouldn't have been
thrown out of your hotel
if I had given you your bag earlier.
It's not your fault.
Besides, I'm thankful that
you gave me back my bag.
I'm thankful for that bag.
Huh?
I never thought I would see you again
when you left your bag
at the pub last night, but thanks to
that bag, here we are, together again.
You had something important in there,
didn't you?
Yeah.
This is all that I have left.
Oh, an album, huh?
Mind if I take a look at it?
Go right ahead.
That is my father.
What a great man.
He was a hospital director, right?
Did I tell you that last night?
Yes. You told me that
you admired him a lot.
He died ten years ago, right?
You were very upset about it
when you told me last night.
And...ah...this is your ex-fiancé.
I told you about that as well?
Yes I believe he was
called Tenma or something.
You still can't forget him?
What did I say last night?
You should forget about him already.
I was a little jealous.
There's nothing on this page.
Oh, really?
Something was here.
There are tear marks.
They were photographs I didn't need,
so I tore them out.
I see.
Say.
Want to go drinking?
That sounds good.
Is that so...?
You had a security company.
Yes. In Nice, in Southern France.
But then a long-time client
I was guarding was killed.
So I closed the company.
We're both having tough times.
Let's forget about it.
Now's what's important!
We have to enjoy ourselves.
This song.
It's AI Green.
Do you also like this song?
Yeah.
Let's dance.
What's wrong?
No, I'm no good at dancing.
Put your arms around my waist.
Yes.
I knew a man who loved this song,
but who was no good at dancing.
So...is this what he always did?
Yeah.
Oh, how fun!
Would you like another drink?
No, that's enough.
You sure are weak!
Shall we go to bed?
Yeah. Sounds good to me.
Before that, there's just one thing
I have to ask you.
What's that?
Where's the photograph?
What photograph?
Don't act dumb!!
The photograph you tore
out of the album.
Where have you hidden it?
Huh?
I'll tell you if you give me
the photograph.
You're looking for Tenma,
aren't you?
What?!
I know that you haven't burnt
that photograph. You have it with you.
Y-You know where Tenma is?!
Yeah.
The photograph you're talking about...
It's the one with the boy in it, right?
His name is Johan.
I saw him. He's become
quite a handsome blond.
I saw him a year ago in Düsseldorf.
Kenzo...
I want to start over!
You have to be with me.
Kenzo...
You're mine.
I'll take you back once more.
Because you're mine.
So...
What are you up to right now?
I've heard all sorts of rumors.
The rumors are right.
I've been married and divorced
three times.
I live well off of
my father's inheritance and alimony.
What about you?
How are you doing, Dr. Becker?
Huh? Me?
I'm the same as always.
I still have no chance at a promotion.
Speaking of moving up,
Tenma is the chief of surgery.
It's been said that he's going to
become the director.
He's gotten quite ahead of me.
But this is still pretty fun.
Life isn't all about getting promoted.
I'd hate to be wrapped up in my work
and not have the time for women
or fun like Tenma.
Kenzo...
Dr. Tenma hasn't
gotten married yet?
That's right. I've introduced him
to lots of women.
His work comes first.
He just isn't interested.
Oh yeah, so I set him up
on another date.
She's the daughter
of a state senator.
She's a beauty! If this girl
isn't good enough, then I give up!
So why did you want to see me, Eva?
As the ex-director's daughter, you
never paid attention to me before.
I never thought that
you'd want to see me.
I understand. You're well off,
but you're lonely, aren't you?
I'll help you out any time.
I don't want you to let him meet her.
Huh?
That state senator's daughter.
Don't let Kenzo meet her.
Could it be that you're
still in love with Tenma?
Please.
Be sure to make her yours this time!
I went out of my way to set this up.
I won't know until I meet her.
Oh, this is it!!
This is the clock that Mr. Junkers
was talking about at the hospital!
Excuse me! About that clock
in the show window...
Hey, what's with that?
It's already time to meet her. Hey!
What a wonderful watch.
Who are you?
My watch is just an accessory.
I no longer look at the time anymore.
I wonder why it seems like
time is moving faster.
Umm... Excuse me,
but who are you?
You're Angelica, the daughter
of Senator Belgar, aren't you?
Yes.
You're very beautiful...and young.
Oh, no...umm...
You think that the whole world
revolves around you.
Huh?
You don't think that there's anything
that you can't have, don't you?
Umm... What are you trying to say?
Just who are you?
I have a mole on my inner thigh.
He used to kiss it.
Dr. Kenzo Tenma would
always kiss that spot.
Oh, no.
Look! Going into that store
made you late.
She left.
Well, I see. I'm sorry about that.
Could you apologize for me?
Huh? Oh. Hey!
She'll feel better
if you call her right now.
Come on. Hey!
I want to go to the hospital for a bit.
Work, again?!
Cut it out!
Jeez.
Kenzo...
Mine...
You're mine!
Mr. Junkers!
Wait!
Kenzo?
What's wrong?
Wait...
Kenzo!!
There's something I want to tell you!!
Mr. Junkers!!
Kenzo! Please, wait!!
Kenzo...
My high heel...
Kenzo!
Kenzo?
I saw him...
One year ago in Düsseldorf.
That was Johan, wasn't it?!
You saw Johan, huh?
I guess...I should kill you.