You saw Johan, huh?
I guess...I should kill you.
It seems I've seen something
I really shouldn't have.
That handsome blond I saw
that night in Düsseldorf...
Death to all who see Johan...is that it?
I heard three gunshots.
I became afraid and ran away.
I thought that Dr. Tenma
had been shot.
But the following day,
there was an article in the paper
that said that a man called Junkers
had died from three gun shots.
He did it, didn't he?
Is it all right if you shoot me?
If you shoot me,
you'll never be able to get
the photograph of Johan as a child.
The thing that you were looking for...
What do you think would happen
if you shoot me?
I arranged it so the photograph would
automatically go to a BKA agent.
If you want that photograph,
tell me where Tenma is.
What's so funny?!
Your legs are shaking.
You act tough, but you can
barely stand, can you?
What an amusing woman.
I'll tell you.
What is Tenma doing?!
He's practicing medicine, of course.
But without a license.
Where?!
There's a man in Hanover
who's the number-two man
of a certain syndicate.
His boss feared him
and tried to have him killed.
But he failed and
only left him wounded.
So Tenma is taking care of this man
at a mountain villa near Füssen.
Why are you just standing there?
It's almost lunch time.
What are you doing?
Well...
The weather's nice.
I thought of having lunch outside.
Lunch outside?
Dieter, bring the plates.
Okay.
Your wounds are healing well.
You should get some sun.
Dr. Tenma, you saved my life.
You treated me brilliantly
at that run-down country clinic.
Well, your head was just grazed
and the bullet went through your leg.
Your anterior tibial artery
was unharmed.
You're lucky.
Lucky, huh?!
Now then, it's finished cooking.
Wow, that smells good!
What do you think? It's good, isn't it?
Though Heckel doesn't look it,
he's quite the chef.
What do you mean by that?!
This is Chicken Marengo.
The sauce is the key.
It's a recipe from Le Petite Besson,
a three-star restaurant.
Your explanations are
always long-winded.
Kids can't appreciate
this attention to detail.
It looks like it would taste even better
if you poured a little soy sauce on it.
You put soy sauce on everything.
Do you have a problem
with the way I flavor my food?!
This is dining.
This is what dining should be like.
I did anything to make money.
What did I want to do with that money
once I had it?
I abandoned my parents,
became enemies with my siblings,
and my wife and child were killed.
All I wanted was to sit down
and dine like this.
Money makes people go mad.
Did you ever hear this story?
Five years ago,
a bank-like organization was formed
to control Germany's
underground funds.
The work it did was impressive.
Dirty money flowed in from
underground companies
and suddenly became clean money.
Money laundering, huh?
That's right.
It made loans and other transactions
as if it were a real bank.
It grew quite large.
They made a huge fortune
in just five years.
Whoa...
But this year, the person at the top
who was controlling things,
suddenly disappeared.
What do you think happened?
It was chaos. Beyond imagination.
Those who were left,
fiercely fought over the funds.
Most of them died
and the organization collapsed.
They should have just
sat around a table and had a meal.
So...
Where do you think he ran off to?
Huh?
Well, that man who disappeared.
Do you suppose he was killed?
No...he's alive somewhere.
He might even
be a student somewhere.
A student?
Yeah. It's surprising.
According to rumors,
that man...No, that kid,
was only fifteen when he started
the syndicate five years ago.
At fifteen?!
That's just silly!
What could a kid do?!
But he did it. It was as if he was
conducting an experiment
to see how adults treat money.
It was like how a child plays
with a line of ants.
Where...
Where was that underground bank?
The organization was
based in Düsseldorf,
but the man at the top
constantly moved around
and gave orders
from various locations.
Where was he when
he gave his final orders?
I don't know the details,
but those money-hungry subordinates
all rushed to Munich.
Munich...
What's wrong? Doctor, you look pale.
Say, let's call that man further down
to have lunch with us.
Y-Yeah. That's right!
Sorry, but my bodyguard
has a job to do.
You're already considered dead.
Do you think people are still
going to come after you?
Do you plan to continue
living with guards?
He's been with me for a long time.
Boy... Bring Helmut.
So that man's name is Helmut!
Yeah. Tell him that his job
as a bodyguard is finished.
He's the last of my family...
Tell him that we're going to
talk about what we're going to do
from here on at this table.
Okay!
Mr. Helmut! It's lunch time!
Everyone's waiting for you!
Tenma's waiting at
the mountain villa.
You want to kill him don't you?
What is it?
Something happened to Helmut
at the bottom of the hill.
What?!
Helmut is probably already...
I-Is it one of the guys after you?
I don't know...but...
Someone's headed towards
this villa.
Mr. Helmut!
Tell him...
Huh?
Run away quickly.
Tell him to run away quickly.
Quickly!
M-Ma'am!
G-Go quickly.
But your leg!
J-Just do it now!
Which way?
Which direction were you shot from?
D-Did you hit him?
I don't know. Nevermind.
Go right now!
I can't!
You'll be shot if you stay here!
Don't worry about me. Go quickly!
I can't! We've got to
hide in the bushes!
What's this? That woman...
...didn't want to kill Tenma after all.
Are you all right, ma'am?
I'm all right...but I wonder
if he's gone up already.
No. This is the only route
to get to the villa.
What do you mean?
I've gone up and down this mountain
many times.
The other paths lead to cliffs
that you can't climb.
Which means that if we keep watch
from here, he can't go further up.
Who is he?
Roberto.
He wants to kill Tenma.
Tenma?!
Who are you, ma'am?
Are you a friend of Tenma's?
What's so funny?
I'm not old enough
to be called "ma'am"!
Now, quickly! Go to Tenma
and tell him to run away!
But...ma...I mean, Miss, you're...
I'm telling you, I'm all right.
But all that blood is coming out.
Tenma should have
heard those gunshots.
He should come to save us soon!
Don't you understand,
that guy...Roberto is after Tenma?
He wants Tenma to come here.
But ma'am, if we run away like this,
you're going to bleed to death!
I said that I'm not old enough
to be called "ma'am"!
What are you to Tenma?
A friend.
What about you, Ma...Miss?
You're Tenma's friend, aren't you?
You're getting hurt trying to save him.
You like Tenma, don't you?
Are you Tenma's girlfriend?
Keep watch over there!
Do you like Tenma?
Yeah, I like him a lot.
What do you like about him?
What about you?
Why do you like him?
Roberto!
Don't bother trying to shoot me
from the bushes!
I told you!
I set it up so the photograph that
you want of Johan will automatically
go to a BKA agent if I die!
Get out of here if you
want the photograph!
You have something over him,
don't you?
It's a lie.
Huh?
He might not fall for such a lie.
Are you all right, Miss?
Of course I'm not all right.
You...Run away by yourself.
I can't do that.
Tenma will come soon.
He won't come!
That's not true. Tenma is...
He won't come to save me.
He won't come.
Dieter!
Dieter, where are you?!
Tenma, I'm over here!
I'm going right now!
Stay right there!
Don't come!
He's going to shoot you
if you come right now!
He's here to kill you!
Th-That voice. It can't be.
This lady is one
of your acquaintances!
She's been shot. Blood's gushing out!
Eva...
I can't let you die now!
My dream is to turn you
into the police alive!
And live the rest of your life
in jail with regret!
Regret for the rest of your life
that you dumped me!
You shouldn't talk so loudly.
Dieter, can you hear me? Dieter!
Can you tell where the enemy
is from where you are?
I don't know!
I don't know where he's shooting from!
Don't come. I can't have you die.
Hang on, Ma'am!
He won't come.
Not to save me.
Ma'am!
He won't...come.
Tenma...
What are you doing?
Lunch.
Your wounds are healing nicely.
You can now eat lunch
in this weather.
You're lucky.
Lucky?
Yeah. The man who shot you
was quite a pro.
He calmly determined
how difficult it would be
to break into this mountain villa.
There was only one route
to get here.
There were security systems
everywhere.
It was clear that if there were people
with weapons at the villa,
he wouldn't be able to fight them off.
That's why he used you.
He used me?
That's right. The only way to get in
was to have a woman wander in.
But you betrayed him.
That was the end of his plan.
He left in a hurry.
He left?
That's right. He wasn't in the bushes.
This is called Chicken Marengo.
I tried to duplicate the recipe,
so I can't guarantee it's any good.
There's one more thing
you were lucky about.
You had a great doctor
like Dr. Tenma treat you.
Where is Tenma?
He already left.
Where did he go?
He was interested in Munich.
Munich...
Now, let's eat.
It seems that, like me,
you've forgotten how to sit
and dine like this.