"Oh, Corinna, why are your letters
ever so short?"
"As with Eupolis the astro...astro,
astrologist, you drive my heart mad."
"Even the gold of ideas fades,
and the work of Galonius..."
That's enough.
I said that there's no need
to read any further.
Umm... Is there something wrong?
That's enough from you. Get out!
I-I'm very sorry!
Did I do something to upset you?
Those who cannot
pronounce Latin correctly
do not have the right to
read books to me!
I-I'm sorry.
I'll be careful next time!
I told you to leave!
You got quite the scolding
at the mansion.
Cheer up, Mr. Business Admin
Student, Karl Neumann!
How do you know who I am?
Who are you?
I'm Lotte Frank.
I'm in cultural anthropology.
Do you read books for him
part-time as well?
No, I look after him.
He only has male students
read to him.
You're in charge of Tuesdays.
Other students read to him
on other days. He can barely see.
So, what do you think of
the mysterious tycoon,
Hans Georg Schuwald?
I-I don't know. I jumped at the job
because the pay was good.
Have you heard all the rumors
about him?
It's said that he can control the stocks
of businesses throughout Germany
with a single phone call
from his mansion.
He's called
the Howard Hughes of Bavaria.
He has no family!
There's no one close to him!
But his fortune continues to grow!
What do you think he's going to do
with that money?
Who knows?
But there's an even greater mystery.
His other nickname is
"The Vampire of Bavaria."
Vampire?
When the bell tolls at 2:00 AM,
he drives into town with his butler
in a hearse.
It's like something
from a gothic horror story.
He's probably just taking a walk.
I'm going to find out soon
if he really is just taking a walk.
What do you mean, "find out"?
It's for my research paper!
"The Intellectual Activities
of Medieval and Present-day
Business Men of Bavaria."
He'll be a great sample.
Is that why you looked me up?
I just looked up
your name and department.
Well, don't worry that
Schuwald yelled at you.
He says mean things
to all the other students.
Well... I'm used to being
yelled at and being hit.
Used to it?
Y-Yeah. I was shunted around to
different foster homes as a kid.
I went through a lot.
Come to think of it, you're not from
any of the local prep schools, are you?
You really did look me up.
I see. So you don't have parents.
To be honest...
I came to this university in Munich
because I thought I could
meet my mother.
Your mom's in Munich?
So, did you meet her?
No. It doesn't matter anymore.
What?! Why?
You're already so close.
You know your mom's name,
don't you?
Yeah.
What's her name?
I said it doesn't matter anymore.
Tell me!
I'm already interested.
I'm going to find out anyway!
Margot...
Margot Langer.
It'll be easy to find her
if you know that much!
Go meet her.
Your mom will be delighted!
I said...it doesn't matter anymore.
Margot Langer...
No way!!
"His dash, like a chestnut mare"'
"gathered thunder in his blood
and caused great waves..."
I can't stand listening to this.
I only love beautiful things.
Why didn't you tell me something
so important?
I looked up your mom.
I don't know what to say.
I said it doesn't matter anymore,
didn't I?
Karl... Is there some way
I can help you?
Thank you. It's all right.
Karl...
Lotte...you said that you were
going to find out where
Hans Schuwald goes at night,
didn't you?
Huh?
Can I go with you?
Yeah, of course!
It'd be great if you could.
I'm telling you, it's true!
It's the greatest scoop since
the Supernatural Phenomenon
Research Group was started.
I wonder about that.
Anyway, there's no mistake that
this poem was written in 1502
by Bishop Gropius, one of
the founders of this university!
This verse is the important part!
"On the second to the last great year"'
"Thursday's boy will
come to this land"
"and the books shall be
engulfed in flames."
"The entire world will be
engulfed in sorrow."
So, what about it?
Don't you understand?
Look. "The second
to the last great year."
This is 1996.
In other words, this year.
Why?
The "great year" is a leap year.
The only leap year after this one
in this century is the year 2000.
He will "come to this land"
"and the books shall be
engulfed in flames."
"The books of this land" means that
this university is going to burn down!
Then what's "Thursday's boy"?
Thursday, or Donnerstag,
comes from the word, "Donner."
In other words, "thunder."
Which means that
it's the god of thunder!
That's pretty far-fetched!
This isn't funny!
This is the feature of our next bulletin!
I don't mind printing this,
but who's going to believe
that a god of destruction
is coming to this university?
Vampire of Bavaria, huh?!
This is the truth behind
his mysterious prowling?
How disillusioning.
He came out.
How stupid. I'm leaving!
Okay, be careful!
Huh?
I'm going to go.
Go where?
Hey, let's not do this!
Yeah. This isn't a place for a girl.
Go home!
"I only love beautiful things."
Huh?
I want to know
how pathetic a man he is!
It's open.
If you're looking for a girl,
you've come to the wrong place.
I retired a long time ago.
Who are you?
You should introduce yourself first
when you go to someone else's place.
I'm Margot Langer.
You look like students.
Y-Yes.
I'm working part-time
for Hans Schuwald.
So what do you want from me?
Why does he... Why does
Hans Schuwald come here?
He comes for fun.
Or so I'd like to say, but it seems like
he can't function down there.
He comes to give me money.
Huh?
It's only right.
He wept and apologized to me
when I told him my name.
He made me bear a child
and threw me out like trash.
Karl...could it be that
you're Hans Schuwald's child?
Oh...but...
That's a lie. You're...you're...
not Margot Langer!
That's right!
It was in the newspaper a year ago!
"Former Prostitute"... Oh...
"Former Prostitute, Margot Langer,
Murdered. Culprit Still Unknown."
His mother is already dead!
You used that to pretend to be
my mother...Margot Langer.
So you could swindle money
from Hans Schuwald.
He knows.
He pays me knowing that
I'm not the real one.
He knows that the real Margot,
the one he should be
paying money to,
is no longer in this world.
This is his way of atoning
for what he did to her.
Money, money, money!
He lived only for money.
This is the only way.
You talk big, but people
aren't that different.
He's an old man without much time.
You should tell him that you're
his son and get that huge fortune.
What are you trying to say?!
You call me a liar, but...
I'm not so sure about you, either.
There's one more.
There's another boy
who says that he's his son.
He came here like you did
and had the same story.
No way. It can't be...
It's a lie. He's lying!
I don't know who's lying.
Both look like fakes to me.
Who is he?
He's the same as you.
You take turns during the week
to read books to Schuwald, don't you?
He's one of the readers.
Yes, I believe he was Thursday's boy.
Why don't you tell her
that you're the real one?!
I...I was shunted around to
different foster homes as a kid.
I went through a lot.
But my current foster parents
are really good to me.
No matter how grateful I am to them,
it's not enough.
That's why I want to meet
my real parents.
I thought by learning how pathetic
my real father was
I could love my current foster parents
from the bottom of my heart.
That's all it was.
Have you ever seen
Thursday's boy?
I'm off on Thursdays.
But once, I went to
get something I forgot.
You've seen him?
What was he like?
He was blond and had
a very handsome face.
Who is Thursday's boy?
There is someone in this university
who is pretending to be me.
Listen, Karl.
Listen well to what
your mother has to say!
Take this money and ride the train
at Platform 5.
Get off at the eighth station.
There will be a lady called Marta.
What about you, Mom?
I told you that I can't go with you.
Are the police after you?
I'll stay with you.
No!
You'll be put in the orphanage here,
if you stay with me!
You'll continue to be called
a prostitute's child if you stay here.
Now, quickly.
What about Dad?
Huh?
My dad is Hans Georg Schuwald,
isn't he?
Who told you that?
Mrs. Bella from across the street
told me so.
He's really rich, isn't he?
She said that he abandoned me.
You weren't abandoned!
Then I'm going to where Dad is.
Not right now!
When would be okay?
When you're bigger.
If you're an adult
and still want to meet him.
But you mustn't expect anything.
You mustn't hate him
even if he's cold to you!
Why?
Because I don't hate him.
Take this with you.
This is something your father
gave you when you were born.
Karl, I found out!
I found out who Thursday's boy is!
What?!
His name is Edmund Fahren!
He's a student from
the literature department.
There's no mistake.
He's working part-time
reading books at Schuwald's place.
He's in charge of Thursdays!
Edmund Fahren...
Here it is!
This class has just finished a lecture.
Say!
I want to see Edmund Fahren.
Oh...
Edmund! Are you here?
Edmund?
He didn't come to class today.
That's the case.
Is that so?
That's too bad.
But it's only a matter of time
before we catch that fraud.
You're the one who's going to inherit
Schuwald's great fortune!
That's not it.
Huh?
His fortune doesn't matter.
But...
Schuwald can have all the money
sucked out of him...
But...
But?
But...I can't forgive
this Edmund Fahren
for saying that he's my mom's son.
"As the petals of your silk flowers
which swayed in the breeze"'
"the mockingbird cried in my heart."
You're not saying anything today,
Mr. Schuwald.
I yell at you so much.
Why don't you quit?
Is it because the money is good?
That's...
That's...not it.
Is money the only thing
you can talk about?
It's as you say.
Who are your parents?
I was taken in by foster parents.
I see. I asked you
something unpleasant.
Don't you want to meet
your real parents?
To be honest...
I...
It seems that boy who came to me
is the real one.
Huh?
He's not after money.
He?
No. I'm just talking to myself.
You can leave already.
Oh, also...
Your Latin has gotten better.
Thank you very much.
It seems that Edmund Fahren
is absent again today.
He's probably in bed with the cold.
Honestly...
There's no need to be hasty.
Tomorrow is Thursday.
He'll go to Schuwald's.
Ah, I see!
You're going to expose him
right in front of Schuwald.
Let's do it! Let's get him!
He hasn't come.
An hour has already passed.
If he has a cold,
we can attack him in bed.
Say...
Want to barge into his room?
You even looked up
Fahren's address?
204, 204, 204...
Here it is.
Let's do it.
Things have gotten pretty serious.
The whole school is
talking about Edmund Fahren.
Who would have thought that
he had committed suicide.
His suicide note was printed
in the school paper, wasn't it?
"I can no longer
continue to deceive."
This is probably...
Yeah.
He was weighed down by
a guilty conscience
for pretending to be Schuwald's son
to get close to him.
He shouldn't have done it
in the first place
if it was going to drive him
to his death.
Lotte, you must have had
a rough time yesterday.
Oh.
Yeah. We were questioned all day.
The reading job was called off today.
Mr. Schuwald was very depressed.
Oh...Karl, let me introduce you.
He's in charge of Fridays.
Pleased to meet you.
A pleasure! I'm Karl Neumann
in the economics department.
I'm Johan Liebert
in the School of Law.