You haven't touched alcohol
since then, have you?
I haven't had a single drop.
Good!
You can start over again
as long as you don't drink.
I can't drink when I see you
once a week.
I'm afraid of lightning.
What do you mean by lightning?!
I'm a respectable counselor!
Well, I don't have
the time to drink.
I've got my first big case
since becoming a private detective.
Big case?
Doctor, what do you think of this guy?
What do you mean?
Dr. Reichwein, using physiognomy,
what kind of man do you think he is?
Physiognomy?
Richard!
Aren't you mistaking me
for a fortune-teller or something?
But that's what you're known for.
They say that you can tell a person's
personality just by looking at him!
That's the result of many years
of interviewing clients.
Then using the results
of those interviews,
see if this guy is a con man or not.
A con man?!
He's no good!
He doesn't have
the face of a con man.
He's the type that would
immediately expose himself if he was.
Uh-huh...
Then what's the possibility that
he'd commit suicide.
None at all. People with faces like this
would never kill themselves.
Your physiognomy
is strangely convincing
when said so straightforwardly.
It's the result of interviews!
So did something happen
to this man?
Hans Georg Schuwald...
Schuwald?
Doctor, you know who he is,
don't you?
Yeah. You mean the wealthy...
Vampire of Bavaria?
Yes. That tycoon is my client.
The man in the photograph...
Edward Fahren, was pretending
to be his son.
He gave himself away, didn't he?
No, Schuwald
completely believed him.
He cleverly deceived him.
Even I had trouble figuring out
that he was a fake.
But a mystery still remains.
How did he know enough
about Schuwald's son
to make Schuwald believe him?
You should ask him that yourself.
Well, he's actually
already killed himself.
Come on, Martin...
We're old friends, aren't we?
At least let me see
Edmund Fahren's suicide note.
The handwriting has been analyzed.
It is definitely his writing.
We don't need to show
outsiders like you.
Karl Neumann and Lotte Frank,
the ones who discovered the body...
They worked at the same
part-time job as Fahren, didn't they?
They're just friends.
Just friends, huh?
So how are you doing?
Same as usual?
Yes. I'm always shorthanded.
I haven't had a break
since I took over your position.
"Slowpoke Martin" has
become a big shot.
Don't call me that.
You're no longer my superior!
Come on, Martin.
You clearly don't know
how much trouble we had back then.
We took all that time
and almost arrested
that multiple homicide offender.
But you were drunk
and shot him to death.
All that trouble
to clean up afterwards.
I want you to leave.
We don't have the time to deal
with a simple suicide.
Oh.
I'd like to check out the scene.
You've preserved it, right?
Not really. It's not a crime, so
permission has already been given.
They should be clearing out
the possessions of
the deceased today.
Jeez!
When did "Slowpoke Martin"
become so efficient?!
I made it.
A broker will be coming to
take everything away soon.
Oh. It'll just be 2 or 3 minutes.
He hung the rope from this pipe.
He wrote his suicide note
at this desk.
A paper he was writing...
The Birth of Tragedy, Process and
Reality, World Views on Psychology...
I see. A typical
philosophy student's bookshelf.
These were the materials
he used to write this paper.
This is Caesar's Gallic Wars.
Why is only this book
unrelated to the others?
Spanish?
No, is this Latin?
I can't read this at all.
It's a clean book,
but it's only underlined here?
Room 204... Here it is!
Hey, bring more cardboard boxes!
Okay.
Put the books in the boxes first.
Understood.
Good work.
What should we do with this desk?
Put that over here.
Okay.
Yes?
I'd like to ask you about
the room next door.
I already said everything I know.
No, I'm not with the police.
I'm a private detective.
Whoever you are,
you're being a nuisance!
I have to turn in a paper tomorrow.
I haven't been able to concentrate
because of all the trouble next door!
All right, all right.
Then just one question!
Were these two close to Fahren?
Who knows?
I've never seen them here.
The guy next door...didn't seem like
he had many friends.
Is that so...?
That's enough, right?
Hold on, hold on.
Just one more thing!
What is it?!
Could you translate
this underlined part?
Huh?!
You've got to be kidding!
It'll be your fault if I fail my class!
Sorry.
Umm... "I no longer..."
"...can continue"...
" ...to deceive."
What was that?
I don't know!
That's enough, right?!
"I no longer..."
"...can continue"...
"...to deceive."
I've heard that somewhere.
Do you like this place as well?
Hey, if I remember correctly,
you're...Johan.
Come up here. You can see
the view better from here.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Whoa. It's kind of scary.
It's not scary.
H-Hey, stop!
Stop that.
Stop that! It's dangerous!
Do you come here often?
Y-Yeah.
The lights of the houses go on
at about this time.
Families are coming home.
It starts to smell like
dinnertime everywhere.
I long for that.
You long for it?
Yeah. I've never had dinner with
my family ever since I was a child.
What's your family like?
Oh.
Sorry. Did I ask
something offensive?
I was actually taken in
by foster parents when I was a child.
Could you tell me about it?
Huh?
Tell me about yourself.
It wasn't anything!
This is it!
"I can no longer
continue to deceive."
It's Fahren's suicide note.
No.
That wasn't a suicide note.
It was just a translation
of that line from this book.
That's my life story.
It's a bit depressing, but...
It's strange. I can talk to you
about anything.
Your story just now...
Your rich father...
Are you talking about Schuwald?
Are you crying for me?
Hey. We've got to do something.
I take care of Schuwald
and I can't help but worry.
He hasn't been eating much
since Fahren's suicide.
At this rate, he's going to die next.
Karl... Why don't you tell him that
you're his real son?
I just wanted to see
what kind of person he was.
If I told him the truth...
He'd think that I was someone
who was after his money.
Schuwald is that kind of person.
Everything is about money.
He won't understand my feelings.
But you've got to do something!
Your true father is suffering
in the depths of despair.
I see. So that's it.
Huh?
In that case, I have a plan.
"I can no longer continue to deceive."
The note that Fahren left
wasn't a suicide note.
This Latin book was in his room.
He was just translating
this underlined part in Gallic Wars.
It doesn't look like this is a suicide!
I don't have conclusive proof.
It's just my intuition
from many years as a detective.
Are you listening, Mr. Schuwald?!
You don't seem very energetic.
It's...fine already.
Huh?
What are you saying?
It's not fine!
If he didn't commit suicide,
your life may be in danger!
He...
He was my son.
H-Hold on a second!
I already informed you!
Neither his birthplace
nor his background
has anything to do with you!
He was a fake!
Fahren was indeed a good person.
He wasn't the kind of person
who would con people.
But he tried to trick you.
The master is tired.
Please leave now.
I refuse to end the investigation here!
And I'm not saying that because
this is my first high-profile job!
I can feel it.
There's an even bigger evil
in the background.
In life...
There are things we can never redo.
Do you understand?
I understand...very well.
I'm continuing the investigation.
Understand?
A treaty of children's rights?
That's right.
You could call it
an international standard to protect
the civil liberties of children.
It's what I'm working on right now.
But volunteering to take care of
the children at this facility
is unrelated to that.
I do it because I want to.
So...could you tell us more about
what you said earlier?
Schuwald went bankrupt
three times in the past.
Yeah. Each of those three times,
he'd disappear temporarily.
And when he'd reappear,
he worked tirelessly
to regain his fortune.
He told me about that
when I did my Friday reading job.
Did you ask him where he went
when he disappeared?
Yeah.
We should take him there, right?!
Everyone has a place
that makes him feel better.
Like how you look at the houses
from the roof of the university.
Huh?
Mr. Kuntz, it looks like
the bathroom sink is clogged.
Could you take a look?
It's that sink.
Lotte, what's wrong with it?
Hey! Open up.
Stop messing around!
What are you thinking?
Hey! Open up! Hey!
What are you going to do
with the master?!
The master can't see!
Open up!
Kidnappers, kidnappers!
Okay!
Our plan was a success!
All right, let's go!
Where are you taking me?
A nice place!
I know that
you're not Margot Langer.
I just want information on Fahren,
the boy who died.
He came here, didn't he?
Fahren...which one was he?
Which one?
Two groups came claiming to be
Schuwald's son.
Is it the blond one?
Or is it the black-haired one?
Black-haired?
The black-haired one came with a girl.
I can't believe he'd bring a girl
to a place like this.
Black hair...and a girl?
Could they be these two?
Yeah...that's right.
This boy...
...said that he was Schuwald's son?
Is it really here?
There's no mistake.
It should be around here.
Where have you taken me?
Well...
It's the Owenberg Woods.
We thought it would cheer you up.
Let me out.
Can you see the lake?
Y-Yes.
Are the autumn leaves
of the woods beautiful?
Yes, very.
What about the wrens?
I can't hear the chirping of the wrens.
I'm very sorry.
This place has become...
an industrial area.
Can't you hear it?
Huh?
Listen very closely.
They're chirping so beautifully.
Many apples have fallen in the grove.
Hold out your hand.
Come this way.
What a sight.
The autumn leaves look like
they're on fire in the afternoon sun.
It's being reflected like a mirror
on the calm surface of the water.
You see it, don't you?
I can't believe that
such a sight exists.
I see it.
I can see it.
Wait a second!
What did you just say?!
You said that two groups came here.
The black-haired boy brought a girl.
Then Fahren didn't come by himself?
Yeah. The blond came with someone.
The Fahren kid you speak of
couldn't speak properly.
The boy he called his friend
told me the details.
To tell you the truth...
I would have believed him if he said
that he was Schuwald's son.
Who is he?