You look well.
Yes.
How's work? Things going well?
That's good.
Is Rosemary also doing well?
She's fine.
She's made a lot of friends.
I see. That's good.
Yes, I'm glad.
I'm sure she's gotten
used to school and...
Excuse me.
Sorry, but I have to get going.
I've brought a photo of Rosemary.
Could you let me see her?
How about the day after tomorrow?
At this restaurant...
I've completely quit drinking.
My life's back in order.
No. This may be the first time
I've been living a normal life.
I realized how much I lost.
I'll let her decide whether
she wants to see you or not.
Okay. Yeah, you're right.
I've got to get going now.
Okay.
Yes?
Some more coffee.
Doctor!
What kind of person do you think
this man is?
Hey, Richard!
Huh?
Why do you think you're here?!
You're here for counseling.
I keep telling you,
I'm not a fortune-teller!
It's the result of many years
spent interviewing clients, right?
Who is that boy?
He was the first person at the scene.
This guy was the one
who discovered Fahren's corpse.
It seems he's just a friend.
Say, Richard...
Huh?
Working hard is fine,
but you need time to relax as well.
I'm taking it easy!
Well, that's good.
Actually...Doctor...
What is it?
I may be able to see my daughter.
Oh? You must be
looking forward to that.
Yes!
- But...
- Huh?
Even if you see her, you can't
regain what you've lost.
Be prepared for that.
Yes.
Whatever happens,
don't touch any alcohol!
Got it?!
Don't worry about it!
Are you going back to work again?
Yes.
How about it?
Isn't it about time you deal with
the event that got you
kicked off the police?
Yes...of course.
He was 17 years old...
a serial murderer...
I shot him dead.
I was drunk on the job.
Good. You cannot escape from it.
You cannot rid yourself of it.
But what's important is...
That I move on...right?
Good. You're a pretty good student.
Was that a perfect score?
Don't be silly! I don't give out
perfect scores that easily!
Besides, perfect people are boring.
No way!
Karl Neumann...
A business major with the University
of Munich's Economics Department.
Like Fahren, he told that prostitute
that he was Schuwald's son.
I don't know whether
he was telling the truth.
But this boy may somehow be...
Yes?
Mr. Richard, I'm finished cleaning,
so I'll be going now.
Oh. Thank you always
for your hard work.
It's not hard work at all.
It's pretty rare for a man
living by himself to be so neat.
Well... I was pretty bad before.
You've got a new picture
of your daughter.
Yes. I'll be able to see her soon.
Oh my! That's wonderful.
Your daughter will be delighted!
You think so?
Of course. Any girl would be
happy to see her father.
Oh? That's good.
So were you able to
turn in your paper?
Karl Neumann...
Why don't you tell Schuwald
that you're his son?
Are you also a swindler?
Or are you the real thing?
If you really are Schuwald's son...
You should know parents always
want to see their children.
Sorry. She said that
she doesn't want to see you.
Well, that's fine.
Sorry, I also...don't have time.
Okay.
Oh...I see. That's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be off then.
Okay.
Yes?
Can I get you something?
G-Get me a whiskey.
All right.
Here you go.
Huh?
Excuse me...
Then I'm going to where Dad is.
Not right now!
If you're an adult and still
want to meet him...
But you mustn't expect anything.
You mustn't hate him
even if he's cold to you!
Because I don't hate him.
Take this with you.
This is something your father
gave you when you were born.
"The daffodils of Lares bloom proudly
with no one to admire them."
"The trees of Pieria rustle
with no one to mind them."
"Oh, bloody tracks
of a nameless man..."
Wonderful.
Huh?
Neumann, you've really become
a wonderful reader.
Oh. Thank you.
I'm impressed that you've
mastered Latin in such a short time.
Actually, I'm being taught.
Oh? You have a splendid teacher.
Who is he?
Johan... Johan Liebert.
Johan, huh? He's perfect.
Yes.
It's not only his Latin.
Huh?
It's also his knowledge of law
and economics.
No, he has a perfected philosophy
for everything.
He's a boy who has been perfected
to the point of beauty.
U-Umm...Mr. Schuwald...
What if a boy like him...
What if he was your real son?
He smiled.
Schuwald actually smiled.
It seems that you're worthy enough
to be his son.
To be honest, I was jealous.
No matter how you look at us,
you're clearly better than I am.
I felt ashamed of my envy.
Why don't you tell him who you are?
Huh?!
Tell Schuwald that you're his real son.
Stop that!
I keep telling you that I never intended
to do that from the beginning!
He'd never believe me
even if I did tell him!
Not only that, but he'd think that I was
some hyena who's after his fortune!
I don't want that!
The life that my mother led
until she died.
The way I've been living until now...
For him to think of me like that
without knowing these things...
I don't want that!
That's why you're going to
tell him who you are.
You're going to make him
see the truth.
He won't believe anything!
You should have something
he'd have to believe.
Huh?
Something that will make him
believe that you're his son.
I-I don't have anything like that.
Think back.
You should have something.
I said that I don't have anything!
I don't plan on telling him!
Then why are you
learning Latin from me?
Is it because you want him
to be happy?
Is it because you
want him to like you?
I'm thinking of quitting my job
reading to him at his place.
I'll quit already.
Thank you for worrying about me.
It's fine already.
Johan... Just between
you and me...the thing is...
I do have proof.
What is it?
But I have no intention of using that
to convince him that I'm his son!
My foster parents are coming
to visit me next week.
I've made up my mind. I'm going to.
I see.
Just so your determination
doesn't waver...
It might be best if
I held on to that proof.
We're glad you're doing well.
Right, dear?
Yes.
I was worried about whether
you were eating properly.
Well, I'll get fat if I keep eating out,
so I'm being careful.
You'll get fat on
your mother's meals as well.
That's because they're so delicious!
How's college?
Did you make any friends?
Yeah. I can talk about
anything to them.
I see. That's the best.
We can tell that you're doing well
just by looking at your face.
I'm grateful to you that I can
study here like this.
Whoa, what is this all of a sudden?
I've been moving around from
foster home to foster home until now,
but the both of you
really treated me well.
That's because
you're a very wonderful kid.
That's right, Karl.
Thank you very much, Mr. Lindner.
Could you stop calling me
Mr. Lindner already?
Wii you accept our offer to adopt
you?
You said to wait a while
after you got into college,
but I think it's about time...
We trust you.
You trust us as well, don't you?
Of course.
Your true father and mother
might be alive somewhere.
No matter what we do,
we may never be the real thing.
That's not true!
The both of you...
are my real father and mother.
Dear...
Let's have a toast! We'll have
an especially expensive wine today!
Yes!
You there, could you
bring a wine menu?!
Today's a special day!
Yes, hello?
Neumann? It's me.
Mr. Schuwald...
I was told that you were
going to quit your part-time job.
Yes.
That's unfortunate.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
You've worked hard.
I'm impressed at how far
you've come with your Latin.
Thank you very much.
It's very unfortunate.
I'll really miss you.
If it's fine with you, could you read
something to me one last time?
Yes, I'd be glad to.
How about the third part
of "From Aeolis to Lemnos"?
Ah, that would be nice.
"That mysterious sea even wishes
for the death of the god, Phoebus."
"What pleasures could there be"
"other than to wish for the death of
the sons and daughters of Cerberus?"
"'Now, go on"Zeus whispers,
'go on, go on."'
"Dance in the temple
of the dark gods."
"Gods of Juno who dwell in the sea,
the earth, and the heavens..."
"Steal Campania's forbidden apple
from the summit of the Parthenon..."
"...and all come here."
"My heart...my desire..."
"My heart..."
Mr. Schuwald...that call just now...
That was wonderful.
It was the most pleasant reading
that I have ever heard.
Why have you hidden this
all this time?
Th-That's...
This is definitely the rabbit's foot
that I gave to your mother, Margot.
It was a charm to bring you good luck
when you were born.
This is yours.
Karl...
I put you through a lot.
Father!
My son.
This is all thanks to him.
He told me.
He's going to be working with me
as my secretary.
He's a young man I can trust.