"That's good enough"?!
"That's good enough"?
What do you mean, Mr. Schuwald?
I'm calling off the investigation.
Hold on a second. I'm through
investigating Karl Neumann.
He really is your son.
I'm grateful to you.
N-No, hold on a second!
Not everything's been solved.
There still is a possibility that
Edmund Fahren, the boy
who pretended to be your son,
didn't commit suicide!
It isn't clear who was pulling
the strings behind Fahren!
Everything's been solved.
I've poured some tea, Father.
I see.
Oh, hello.
Would you like some?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
Good work. Send me the bill.
The weather sure is nice.
Yes.
Johan's coming as well.
Ah. So Johan's coming along.
He was a cold man.
Reserved and untrusting.
Who would have thought that
he would transform into
such a good-natured old man
as soon as he found his son...?
That smile...
I would never guess that people
call him the "Vampire of Bavaria."
"Ah. So Johan's coming along."
So you're looking for this puppy?
Yes.
It seems that
my client's ex-husband took it.
Even custody disputes over puppies
can get messy.
Jeez...
Sorry, but I'm going to
have some wine.
Go right ahead.
Water is good enough for me.
Your work is slow, but you don't
seem interested in alcohol.
Yes. I'm all right in that account.
That account? Is there
something else bothering you?
Well, I have some free time
so I do trivial things.
Oh?
I look at my personal scrapbook
of unsolved crimes from my time
as a police detective.
I see.
So how do you feel
when you look at it?
Frustrated.
This murder, that murder...
When I think that the culprits
are still at large...
I just can't see them through.
Not with my incompetence.
You have the skills.
But you get too desperate, Richard.
You get too involved in your cases.
You were annoyed that you couldn't
read the criminals' minds,
and you got frustrated.
So I turned to alcohol.
Yes, that's right!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah, it's time to eat!
But I don't think that there's
anything wrong with that.
Looking through your scrapbook
of old cases.
I just become annoyed again.
No, you're all right now.
I want you to tell me what you think of
when you look through them
from your current point of view.
You were drunk and shot down
that young serial killer.
You're ready to face that truth
head on.
But you're still running away from
the thoughts you had
when you pulled the trigger.
You still see that boy's ghost,
don't you?
Yes.
When everything clears up
and is brought to light,
that ghost will disappear.
"When everything is
brought to light"' huh?
The "accountant murder case".
The victim, Joachim Holmer,
had a steady career.
He wasn't the kind of person
who would make enemies.
He was stabbed to death.
There was no indication
that he was robbed.
The "Voice of God murder case".
The victims were a former
housekeeper and a chauffeur.
The message, "I heard the voice of
God"' was left at both crime scenes.
The "Dornach Company president
murder case".
Lute Gauk was one of
the wealthiest men in Bavaria.
His body was found
in Hartholz Forest.
The "Spira couple murder case"...
The Spiras' drowned bodies
washed up upstream
along the Isar River.
It is being investigated
as one of a series
of middle-aged couple murders.
The material witness,
a Japanese doctor, is still on the run.
Oh man...
The more unsolved cases I had,
the more alcohol I drank.
But it's different now.
I see. It's as the doctor said.
So this is what it means
to think while sober...
H-Hold on a second.
Think hard!
Think hard.
So...
What did you figure out?
Well...about that.
I thought of something, but...
You saw that boy's ghost
and you lost your thoughts?
Yes.
There's no need to worry!
Your thoughts will
come back to you sooner or later.
What did I realize?
It was an important key
to solving one of those cases.
Was that just my imagination?
Who is it?!
Who's following me?!
It's the same as before.
Back then, I was running after him
through an alley just like this.
I'm sorry for coming
so late at night, Doctor.
Well, you finally feel like
telling me everything!
Tell me about it.
Back then, I saw something
within that boy.
That's when I knew it existed
in this world.
True evil.
That's why I. ..I shot him.
All right! I'm glad you told me.
You've finally recovered!
There's still more.. .I realized.
The idea that popped in my head.
The unsolved cases I had been
working on were actually...
...a single case.
Dear Dr. Gillen...
The other day I read the book
that you sent me,
"An introduction to Transcendental
Criminal Psychology."
Your book was
a very interesting read.
It pleases me to see that a student
of mine from Düsseldorf University
is now a leading authority
in the field of criminal psychology.
That aside, regarding the interview
you conducted with
the serial murderer Peter Jurgens.
You told me that Jurgens claimed that
a friend told him to murder his victims.
My memory isn't clear,
so could you tell me again
the name of Jurgens' alleged friend?
PS.
You were a very good student
in college,
but there was a student in your class
who was just as brilliant
and always fought you
to be top of the class.
He moved on to become
a neurosurgeon.
At any rate, it seems that
he's become a material witness
in a multiple homicide case.
I want you to tell me anything
you know about him.
What kind of person is he,
and where might he be right now?
This Dr. Tenma...
Well, if it isn't that detective
from before!
Well, I'm just a private detective
right now.
I'm sorry for bringing up
a painful subject,
but may I question you once more
about the "Voice of God case"?
Of course!
It's been four years
and the police aren't
putting any more energy
into the investigation.
Schuwald?
Yes. I believe your mother was once
a housekeeper for the tycoon.
Yes.
But that was already
twenty years ago.
Why did she quit?
She became ill at the time.
After that, she only took jobs
close to home.
Could it be that she was
having problems with Mr. Schuwald?
Not at all!
My mother loved to read poems.
She said that she used to
read poems with Mr. Schuwald
when he could still see.
Oh yeah, come over here.
Take a look. I've kept these
in memory of my mother.
The poetry collections on this shelf
are all presents to my mother
from Mr. Schuwald.
So, the detective in charge of
the "Dornach Company president
murder case"
is now just a private detective.
You used to be
the president's secretary.
I'd like to ask you once more
if anyone held a grudge against him.
His enemies? There's not
enough time to count them all.
The police should have already
investigated the businesses
that went bankrupt
because of Mr. Gauk.
There's another powerful
businessman in Bavaria, isn't there?!
What was Mr. Gauk's relationship
with him?
Mr. Schuwald, huh?
Well, they were life-long rivals.
Did you know?
Schuwald went bankrupt twice
in the past.
His second bankruptcy was the result
of a fierce business war
with Mr. Gauk.
In other words, Mr. Gauk
crushed Mr. Schuwald.
There were times when Mr. Schuwald
defeated the president as well.
They both hated each other?
Of course!
It was terrible if they
happened to meet at a party.
They had explosive fights.
Those two?
Yes, even though
they're both cold-hearted.
But they were the only people
they could talk to on the same level.
They weren't really rivals.
They were really more like friends.
Be careful!
Yeah. I knew Hans well.
He was one of the two people killed
in the "Voice of God murder case."
He was such a good man.
How unfortunate.
Was Hans really such a good man?
Yeah. He'd often treat me to a drink.
He used to drive for Schwald, right?
Apparently. But that was
thirty years ago.
Do you know why he was fired?
Well, it was around the time
that Schuwald went bankrupt.
Oh...I see!
They never had any problems
between them, did they?
Listen. I'm going to say this
in honor of Hans...
He was a good-natured man
who could get along with anyone.
Even filthy rich bastards like
that "Vampire of Bavaria"'
or poor people like us.
He often said that he was the one
who taught that tycoon how to bird-watch!
Bird-watch?
Yeah. Hans said that Schuwald
was more like a happy child
than a vampire when
he took him to the forest.
It's already been two years since then.
But still, whenever I think
of my husband...
My husband was always
a very serious man
who never did anything
to be hated by anyone.
But...he was killed
in such a terrible way.
I'm very sorry.
Excuse me for asking,
but I believe your husband was an...
Yes.
He lived in an orphanage
when he was younger,
and was shoved off
to various foster parents.
After a miserable childhood,
he became an accountant.
Mr. Schuwald asked your husband
to be his corporate accountant,
didn't he?
Yes. Many times.
But my husband always
turned him down.
Not only was he busy with
the work he had at the time, but...
His philosophy towards money was
very different from Mr. Schuwald's.
My husband was very honest
when it came to money.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Will the culprit be caught?
I'll try my best.
I'll catch him!
Well, I'll be off.
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
Do you know how your husband
and Mr. Schuwald met?
Yes. He said that they met
in the forest.
The forest?
It was when Mr. Schuwald
could still see.
They met in the forest.
What were they doing there?
They were bird-watching.
They went together
many times after that.
Bird-watching.
Like a happy child.
Read together.
Friends.
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
Thank you.
What horrible driving.
It looked more like he was
trying to hit you!
Dr. Reichwein, I've collected
all the evidence.
It's as I told you before.
The many cases that troubled me
when I was a police detective...
...all point in the same direction!
The "Voice of God murder case"!
The "Dornach Company president
murder case"!
The "accountant murder case"!
They appear to have
nothing in common.
The methods in which they were
committed were different.
The victims didn't have any relation
to one another.
Furthermore, they didn't have
any financial ties.
But there is something
that wasn't recorded.
There is something
that connects them all.
The deaths of all the victims
were used to isolate Schuwald.
There is also
another strange connection.
In the "Dornach Company president
murder case",
it was the man who Mr. Gauk
was supposed to meet
right before he was murdered.
In the "Voice of God murder case",
it was the god whose name
the murderer scribbled on the walls.
And there's the middle-aged couple
multiple homicides.
The one case that seemed
to be unrelated.
It was the culprit named by
the material witness,
the Japanese doctor.
They all had the same name!
Johan.
My former student,
a criminal psychologist,
was studying a murderer
who committed his crimes
on a friend's orders.
He told me in his letter.
That friend's name was also...
Johan!
It's a common name. It's possible that
the cases are related.
But if this is true,
he's been systematically murdering
people for the past four years.
The man known as Johan
is trying to force Schuwald
into complete isolation.
Margot Langer, the woman who bore
Schuwald's son conveniently died.
And the student who pretended
to be Schuwald's son.
He also conveniently killed himself
as soon as he made his claim.
If Johan really does exist,
where is he right now?!
I see.
So Johan's coming along.
Johan, the weather is beautiful.
Yes. Very.
He's right next to Schuwald!