Doppel Ranger Kick!
Hey, that's not fair!
I kicked you! Fall over!
My evil empire is planning to
take over the world.
We won't be defeated that easily!
In the TV show, we always
defeat you at the end!
Are your plans for world domination
going well?
Oh, Johan!
He's not falling over at all!
Things will be rough after you
take over the world.
What kind of world are you
going to make?
I don't care.
I'm finished after I mess it up!
What?! It sounds like more fun
to mess it up.
I'll quit the Rainbow Rangers
and join the evil organization!
Now then, shall we start
heading back?
Okay.
All right, let's all head back.
Don't forget anything.
It's getting a bit warmer, isn't it?
Yeah.
Did Rosemary catch a cold
this past winter?
Yes. She was running around
outside with her friends.
She gets a terrible fever every year.
Yeah, it was around this time.
We had to rush to the doctor
in the middle of the night.
Do you always carry around
pictures of her?
Yeah. She's probably gotten big.
She's growing, so her face
has probably changed
during the time we've been apart.
But I know that I'll be able to
recognize Rosemary,
no matter how big she gets.
Oh yeah.
Show her this when
you think it's appropriate.
They're newspaper clippings
and a copy of the report
from when I shot
that young serial killer.
I'm not going to ask you to explain.
The truth is that I killed someone.
I'm not justifying my actions.
It's just that I want her
to know the truth.
I understand.
When...can I meet her?
I'll ask her once more
if she wants to meet her father.
I-I see ! I'll be waiting for a call !
I return home every night at 9:00!
Richard, you're back
to your old self again.
Huh?
You have the same look in your eyes
as when you were younger...
When you first became
a detective... When we first met.
I see.
What do you think? You'll get a bonus
if you sign up now.
Well, we already have insurance.
Just listen to what I have
to offer, Mr. Liebert.
The insurance I have right now
is enough.
I can't afford another policy.
We bought a policy four years ago
when we moved in.
Four years ago?
Where were you living before then?
In Bruntál, near Mannheim.
Bruntál, huh? That's a nice place.
Are you from there?
Yes. We lived there
before coming here.
By the way, ma'am,
do you have any children?
Yes, our son is currently attending
the University of Munich.
A college student!
In that case, I have a policy
that's perfect for young people.
Just hear me out!
Huh?
Oh.
Is this your son?
He was very cute. What's his name?
It's Johan. Would you like some tea?
Oh. ..you don't have to.
Don't mind me.
He only calls once in a while
now that he attends the university.
That's how boys are.
Boring, isn't it?
I'm back, Dr. Reichwein.
Yes, to Johan's home.
Yes. Well, they were
a pretty ordinary family.
So what do you think, Richard?
Well, my experience
as a police detective tells me that
the more ordinary something is,
the more suspicious I should be.
I see.
Anyway, I'm going to do more
research on Johan's acquaintances.
Something...
There's got to be something.
Johan's prep school report
describes him as
a well-behaved student
with good grades.
But I know that I'll be
able to recognize Rosemary,
no matter how big she gets.
That baby's face... It couldn't have
grown up to become Johan!
Here. This is the birth certificate.
Oh...thank you.
Johan Wilhelm Liebert...
Born February 9, 1976...
He was definitely born in this town.
Nothing... out of the ordinary.
Mr. Hertz!
Huh?
How many times must I tell you?!
No smoking in this office!
Don't be so stiff. Get me an ashtray.
No!
There was a fire here
four years ago, remember?
We've had such a terrible time
since then.
All of our documents were destroyed.
Did you redo all the documents?
Y-Yes.
We had to have people give us
their information to redo everything.
It's a small town, so we were able to
get everything back to normal.
Hey, thanks for coming, Dr. Gillen.
It's been a while, Dr. Reichwein.
Dr. Tenma appeared before you
and said that he was looking
for a man named "Johan"?
Yes. He didn't have any grounds
for anything he said.
But if this person is the "friend"
who incited Peter Jurgens,
the serial killer I'm researching,
we'll be able to find a clue
to all these cases.
Take care of it, Dr. Gillen.
Yes. I'll get permission to interview
Jurgens as soon as possible.
We'll be able to prove
Dr. Tenma's innocence
based on his reaction
to this photograph.
He's dead?
Yes. The real Johan Liebert,
who was born in Bruntál,
died when he was two years old.
Does that mean that the Lieberts
used the fact that the office's records
had been destroyed
to pretend that their son
was still alive?
Probably.
Then...
The Johan Liebert
who exists right now...
Who in the world...is he?
At any rate. .. As I told you, I've given
Dr. Gillen a photo of Johan.
Let's hope to get an answer from him.
How about some dinner?
No, I've got to get back.
What? Going back to work
after running around all day?
Well, I might get a phone call.
I may be able to meet my daughter.
Oh?
It's all right. What's important is that
I move forward...right?
All right! You've completely recovered!
Yes?! Hello?!
Dad? It's me.
Rosemary...
Yeah, I'm doing fine. Yes... Yeah
Of course I can see you.
I can see you.. .at any time.
Mr. Richard...
It's Johan.
This boy. Jurgens...
Have you seen him before?
Have you met him before?
I don't know him.
You said that your friend Johan
only sent you letters.
That you'd never met.
But Johan knew a lot about you.
Could I borrow your pen?
Huh? Sorry, but I'm not allowed
to give things to you.
Lend me the pen.
The park.
Huh?
The park. It was the day
after I had killed someone.
I was thinking, "I'm going to quit.
This is going to be the last time."
I went to the park.
He was with a lot of children.
Hold on a second.
I forgot to rewind the tape!
Start over from the beginning.
"Come with us."
Huh?
"Come..."
W-What do you want?!
We met at Mr. Schuwald's place.
I'm Johan Liebert. I called you
several times and you didn't answer,
so I came to see you in person.
Yes? Ah, Dr. Gillen.
How was it?
What happened when
you showed Jurgens the photo?
He's dead?
Yes. Just now in the hospital.
The police are questioning me
right now, so I can't go anywhere.
Our key witness is dead
because I was careless enough
to give him a pen.
But, Dr. Reichwein, his suicide
was clearly a response
to Johan's photograph!
I'll come over after
they're finished questioning me.
All right!
I'll contact Richard immediately.
Richard...
A college paper?
Yes. I'm researching the Convention
on the Rights of the Child,
which was formed in 1989 by the U.N.
Would you like something to drink,
Mr. Richard?
I'm fine.
You quit drinking, didn't you?
That's right.
You were drunk
and executed that boy.
Am I right?
Y-Yeah. I was drunk,
and I did something unforgivable.
I want to know something
related to that.
The boy you killed. ..
Stephan Yoss, age seventeen.
What crime did he commit?
Boy, huh? A seventeen-year-old boy
committed those demonic crimes.
Nine counts of rape and murder,
two counts of attempted murder.
Is that why you executed him?
It wasn't an execution!
Oh. ..sorry. By the way,
you are aware that Article 40
of the Convention on the Rights
of the Child states that every child is
"to be presumed innocent until proven
guilty according to law"' aren't you?
Yeah, I know. I was once
in the juvenile department.
I see.
So what about Article 37?
"Neither capital punishment
nor life imprisonment"
"without possibility of release
shall be imposed for of fences"
"committed by persons
below eighteen years of age."
Most of the convention concerns
basic human rights,
which are given to people
of this country regardless of age.
I did not set out to execute him!
It was a drunken mistake.
I know it is something
I cannot take back.
I've accepted
society's judgment and...
Now, now, just hold on a second.
I wanted to meet you
in order to write my paper.
I'm sorry if I upset you.
Shall we take a walk
for a change of pace?
I'd like this whiskey.
The night air is still chilly.
Ah, Dr. Gillen, I still haven't
been able to contact Richard.
He said that he might be
able to see his daughter.
I don't think he'd be meeting her
this late at night.
Anyway, when you get a hold of him,
tell him to move with caution.
I'm heading over right now.
Stephan Yoss's history. ..
Do you know about it?
I believe. ..he was in an orphanage
in East Germany when he was young,
or something like that.
You need to know more.
That's the most important thing
when talking about him.
The orphanage he was in.. .
It was a horrible place.
He was a good kid.
But horrible things happened to him.
The way his mind was warped there.
Convention on the Rights of the Child,
Article 6.
Rights to life, and assurance
of survival and development.
Article 8. Preservation of identity.
Article 19. Protection from abuse.
Yes. It was a demonic place
where no one was concerned
with such things.
The place was called 511 Kinderheim.
Will you be able to see your
daughter?
W-Why...
How do you know about her?!
Was that your daughter calling you
at your house?
Will you be able to see her?
Maybe tomorrow?
What's. ..your motive?
To write a paper.
Not that!
What's your motive for staying
at Schuwald's place?!
Who... Who...are you?!
You said that you were drunk
when you shot that boy.
Answer my question first!
On that day, you were seen drinking
at a bar after you had killed the boy.
But isn't that strange?
As far as I can determine,
there isn't a single person who saw
you drinking before you killed that boy.
You weren't drunk
when you shot that boy, were you?
What?
You were sober. You were calm.
You calmly pulled that trigger
in order to execute him.
Am I right?
No!
Why are you trying to forget?
Or are you lying?
Are you lying to other people?
Or to yourself?
Were you certain that
he committed his crimes?
Did you have the right to execute
him?
Do you think that by lying,
your sins will go away?
What a serious crime.
Can someone who's done
such a serious crime
really face his daughter
and act as if he's been rehabilitated?
How about it?
Want a drink?
Gillen? Is that Dr. Gillen?
It's the police.
Your patient, Richard Braun...is dead.