He has been called to the heavens.
What lies here is nothing more than
the hollow shell of Richard Braun.
His soul, though, will live on forever.
Let us swear on his soul...
To live our lives with hope.
Psalms 23...
I can't get over it.
What a sad funeral.
He was such a good detective.
But nobody from the force has come.
He had alcohol related problems
while on the force.
He got drunk and fell off a building.
Isn't that what the police are saying?
Richard would have seen his
daughter on the day after the accident.
What. .. What did I do for him?
Dr. Reichwein...
I just sat in a chair and listened to
what he had to say.
"You've completely recovered"?!
What did I ever do for him?!
Dr. Tenma...
If we find him, there's a possibility
we'll be able to solve everything.
Dr. Tenma...
Don't you think it's odd, Doctor?
This isn't an accident!
This isn't a suicide!
Richard was talking to his daughter
a few hours before he died.
They were going to meet the next day.
Doctor...
You did all that you could do and
Richard was recovering wonderfully.
Stop blaming yourself.
And then...
Listen to me, Doctor!
My husband stopped talking to me
after I found out
he was having an affair.
He just washes the car
and cleans the yard everyday.
He even avoids me.
Well, it's better than not coming home.
I feel like I'm going to go crazy
if this keeps up.
Doctor, are you listening?
Y-Yes. Please continue.
So I went over to
the other woman's place.
What do you think happened, Doctor?
Possibility of murder?
There isn't any.
It was just an accident.
That evening, Richard Braun went
to the roof of building Number Twelve
at the University of Munich alone.
He drank a single bottle of whiskey,
got drunk, and fell off.
The bottle. ..did you
check it thoroughly?
Yes. ..we found Richard's fingerprints.
Could you show me the bottle?
Well, sure, but...it's in pieces.
Richard...
Don't you think it's odd?
Richard was talking to his daughter
a few hours before he died.
They were going to meet the next day.
Yes, this person came here that night.
Alone?
Well, I don't remember that far.
You say that you remember
when he came,
but can't remember
if he was with anyone?
Well. ..it's because he ordered coffee.
Coffee?
It's unusual for someone to come in
at that time and not order alcohol.
At that time, was he with this boy?
Who knows?
Try to remember!
I don't know.
Lots of customers came and went.
I just know that
he bought a bottle of whiskey.
It's written on the order slip.
Did Richard really buy it?
I don't remember!
I just know that it says one bottle
of Racke on the order slip.
What did you say just now?
One bottle of Racke!
Why didn't I notice this when I saw
the bottle label at the police station?
Huh?
Are you drinking again?
Well...just a little.
What did you drink?
Whiskey! I only drink whiskey.
You made my entire room
smell of Racke.
Racke?! Are you kidding me?!
I never drink that domestic stuff!
If I'm going to drink,
I'll drink genuine scotch!
Nothing else!
Richard didn't buy the whiskey!
Johan...
It must have been him.
W-Wait!
Hey, wait!
Hey!
W-What do you want?!
Why did you try to
shove me onto the tracks?!
I-I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't act dumb!
Hey, old man.
What do you want from my friend?
Wh-Who sent you?
Think about your age. Old men should
be looking after their grandkids.
H-Hey, wait!
Huh?
Wait!
I was trained as
a border police officer!
Why did you try to
shove me onto the tracks?!
I-I don't know!
Don't underestimate a former officer!
S-Someone asked me to do it!
Who?!
A large man.
A large man?!
A guy I met in the subway
gave me money!
He told me to push you
onto the tracks!
I bought you something, Richard!
It's genuine scotch.
You wanted to have some, didn't you?
That's good enough... Have a drink.
Richard...leave it to me.
I'll figure out his. ..Johan's true identity.
Doctor, I told my husband
that his infidelity is a disease
and that he should be the one
in counseling with you.
Doctor, are you listening?
Oh.
Yes, of course, Mrs. Hesse.
What do you think?
If my husband keeps this up,
my depression will only get worse.
Well. ..you don't
really have depression.
Huh?
Besides, I'm more worried
about your husband,
silently washing his car
and cleaning the yard every day.
Aren't you? It's strange, no matter
how you look at it! Doctor, please.
Please see him.
Fine. Well, I'm open
the day after tomorrow at five o'clock.
I'll ask my husband.
Straighten out that oversized cheater.
Doctor, that's the last of
your appointments for today.
All right, that's good enough
for today, Mereth.
Then, I'll be off ahead of you.
Oh yeah. Mereth, you forgot to
lock the back door again yesterday.
Oh, oh no. I almost forgot
to do it today as well.
Aww, I did it again.
Good work.
Hey, Dr. Gillen... It's Reichwein.
I saw the newspaper.
Yeah, your newspaper ad.
"Let's talk about
our memories of cheating."
"From Rudi."
Do you really think that Dr. Tenma
will contact us with this message?
Yes... Tenma definitely will
if he sees it.
It's something only the two of us
know about.
I see.
Doctor, don't do anything rash
until he comes.
I know...but there's just one thing
I want to look up.
What's that?
The prostitute who pretended to be
Margot Langer.
Richard told me...
Fahren, the boy who killed himself,
was with another boy
when he met her!
A handsome blond boy!
Be careful, Doctor.
I know. I've got to be careful
if I want to uncover everything.
It's for Richard's sake!
Well, I'll call you later.
Mereth, you've forgotten
to close the window today.
Margot Langer?
I don't know her.
Well.. .her trade name right now
is Blue Sophie or something like that.
Ah... That fat old hag.
Gramps, is that what
you're interested in?
No, it's not like that.
Shy at your age?
Make a turn at the corner,
two blocks down.
The second floor of the old building.
Thank you.
But she's not there right now.
Huh?
I haven't seen her lately.
She's probably gone somewhere nice.
Somewhere nice?
Jeez. Why is that fat old hag
so popular?
A really rich guy
was seeing her until recently.
Where did she go?!
Say, what do you think of me?
I'm a lot more fun than that hag.
Do you know where she went?!
I don't know. She probably went off
with that new guy.
New guy?
Yeah. He became infatuated
with that hag despite his age.
He was a big guy.
Big guy?
He seemed like he was
big elsewhere as well.
Umm... Doctor...
Is it all right if I leave for today?
Ah, oh yeah. ..
You're only working until five today.
That's fine. The only appointment
I have left is that cheating husband.
It's a date, isn't it, Mereth?
Oh, Doctor!
Just make sure to lock the doors!
I've got to show this picture
to the prostitute called Blue Sophie
who was pretending to be
Margot Langer.
If Johan was with Fahren,
and I can get her testimony,
I'm one step closer to
getting to the bottom of this.
Yes?!
My wife made the appointment.
I'm Hesse.
Ah, come right in.
I'll visit that woman once more tonight.
Pleased to meet you, Dr. Reichwein.
Welcome, Mr. Hesse...
Pleased to meet you.
Please, come in.
It's the first time
I've been in counseling.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
Just relax and talk about anything.
Our conversation will be confidential,
so don't worry.
Even to my wife?
Of course.
How are you lately?
Do you have any concerns?
Concerns?
Yes.
My wife...found out about my affair.
I see.
I don't have a place at home.
I just clean the yard and wash my car.
That's how it is everyday.
Does that make you feel a little
better?
No.
I never talk to my wife.
You want to talk to her,
but don't have the chance?
Well...I don't know about that.
What about the other woman?
Huh?
Have you broken up with the woman
you were cheating with?
Yeah.
I killed her.
Huh?
No. ..I saw a dream where I killed her.
Do you see dreams like that often?
Often? No. ..I haven't seen any lately.
I was lonely.
Is that why you had an affair?
No.
It was after I met him.
Him?
A handsome blond boy...
No matter how many people I killed,
even when the country fell,
it all felt like a dream.
But. ..that all changed when I met him.
Everything seemed real.
I was no longer alone.
W-Would you. ..like some tea?
No, I'm fine.
I'm a little thirsty.
Could you wait for a second?
My secretary already left.
It seems she's got a date.
Her tea is very good. It's unfortunate
that I can't pour you any of hers.
Doctor...
W-What is it?
A lot happens in
this line of work doesn't it?
You find out people's dreams.
Nothing good happens when you
find out a dream you shouldn't know.
Especially the fact that I'm a hit man.
A-Anyway, if you want to fix things
with your wife...
...talk it over once more.
Hope you forgot to lock
the door today, Mereth!
Y-You're...
Quickly, run away!
Doctor Tenma...
I've been keeping watch over you!
You're in danger. Run away!
Quickly!