Come on, eat!
The weisswurst here is especially good!
Isn't it delicious?
Umm...Dieter, was it?
Come on, if you don't eat anything,
Dieter will eat it all.
There's no need to worry, Dr. Tenma.
This place is safe.
Only regulars come here.
If a stranger comes around
Otto here will drive them out.
Business has been bad
since I've been doing that.
Who ordered the spätzle?
Oh, that would be me.
I made a bed in the attic.
You can sleep peacefully if
you can ignore the rats.
Thanks, Otto.
He's unsociable,
but he's a good guy.
Come on, you can't do battle
on an empty stomach!
Thank you for everything,
and for finding me a room.
I should be the one thanking you.
I'd be in the morgue right now
if you hadn't saved me.
I can eat good food like this
because I'm alive.
Now, eat!
I've contacted Dr. Gillen.
He's also relieved that we found you.
He left an ad calling out to you
in the newspaper.
Let's talk about our memories
of cheating"...
You knew?
Yes.
Why didn't you contact him–?
I didn't want to get him involved.
Don't be so reserved.
Friends are good to have.
So, what's this about you
keeping watch over me?
The Richard Braun case...
Richard?
The time he shot a young serial killer
while working on the police force.
While I was reading the article,
Dieter saw the boy's picture.
He said that boy was
in 511 Kinderheim.
511 Kinderheim?
It was an East German orphanage.
A very special one.
Dieter's foster parent was
an instructor there.
He kept a lot of pictures of
the children that were there.
What happened to the orphanage?
Johan was also there.
Are you saying that
there's a connection
between Johan and the boy
that Richard shot?
I don't know.
Richard was dead before I
could get the details from him.
I saw you in front of Richard's grave...
Richard...
It's as if he led you to me.
You've done your best
by yourself until now.
But you're not alone anymore!
Your innocence will be proven.
Johan is right before your eyes!
The photograph...
Oh no. I left it in the office!
We would have understood everything
if I showed you Johan's photo...
That man who was trying to
kill you probably...
He probably destroyed it, didn't he?
That man...came into counseling with
his wife under the name Hesse.
I tried to contact him,
but there was nobody by
the name of Hesse.
Johan is right before our eyes.
He's here.
That means we can meet him, right?
Yes.
I can meet Johan...in person.
Thalbach & Schuwald AG...
The company at the center of
the Schuwald financial group.
Schuwald hardly ever went out in public,
but lately has.
Around this time in the morning,
he goes to his affiliated companies.
It's something that Richard discovered
when he was still alive.
Not only this company,
but all the businesses in
his financial group
have seen a huge growth in profits ever
since that boy became his right-hand man.
Here he comes.
Schuwald's the one in the wheelchair.
Karl's the one pushing him.
And...
So is that him?
There's...no mistake.
All right.
This is the first time.
This is the first time I've seen
Johan in broad daylight.
That's right. Let's bring everything out
into the light!
This is my only chance.
Yes. Now's your only chance
to prove your innocence!
But for now, you should keep
hiding out in Otto's attic.
We'll prove your innocence soon.
Richard's file is around here...
Here it is.
I'm glad I took it home with me.
Just a little longer.
Just a little longer, Richard.
We'll avenge you soon.
We've cornered Johan!
We've found Dr. Tenma,
the decisive witness.
All that's left...
All that's left is to find someone
who saw Richard the night he died.
There's got to be someone.
Once we do,
we'll be able to prove that Johan was
the man who was with you that night.
Even if we can't do that,
there's Fahren,
the student who claimed he was
Schuwald's son and committed suicide.
If we can find the prostitute he visited,
then we'll be able to prove that the boy
who accompanied him was Johan.
No, that's not all!
We'll be able to
find out who Johan is
if we question the couple who say
they're Johan's parents!
That's because we've found
Johan Liebert's grave.
We've closed a trap around Johan!
Say, Dr. Tenma...
I think of Richard when I look at you.
It's as if you're trying to shoulder
the burdens of the entire world.
But you're not alone!
There's Dieter and
Dr. Gillen and myself!
Things are all right now.
Rest easy tonight.
I didn't want to
get him involved!
This is the first time.
This is the first time I've seen
Johan in broad daylight.
This is my only chance...
Y-You're...
Quickly run away!
Quickly!
Reichwein speaking.
This is Gillen.
Ah, I was just about to call you.
I'm on the way!
What is Tenma doing?
He's at the safe house.
Tell him firmly that he is not
to leave that place.
There's something that's bothering me.
Me too.
Huh?
He... Dr. Tenma's not chasing
Johan to prove his innocence.
I didn't want to believe it...
but I was also worried about that!
Dieter...
Why are you here?
Tenma...told me to come here.
Where's Tenma?
He left.
Where?
He plans to do it.
Huh?
Tenma plans to do it.
Stop him, Mr. Reichwein...
Stop him.
Tenma's going to become
a murderer!
Let's leave it at that for today.
Don't say that.
Ask me about it, Doctor.
It gets interesting from here.
No.
I'll ask you about it next time.
The third woman I killed...
This one is great.
Come on, Doctor.
Come on, listen to me!
How do you think she screamed
when I strangled her?
Come on, Doctor.
Listen to me, Doctor.
That woman...
Where did you go, Tenma–?
We finally meet, Dr. Gillen.
Who are you?
I'm Lunge of the BKA.
I've heard rumors about you.
You've apprehended several of the serial
homicide offenders I'm researching.
I've read your book.
Thank you.
Transcendental Criminal Psychology.
A wonderful book!
There is no other essay that goes so far
into the mind of a serial killer.
Especially the study on Heinz Kaul
in Chapter 3 on pages 262 to 294.
I read with great interest about
how his childhood trauma was
linked to his crimes.
You seem well versed.
I am honored that you have read
my book so carefully.
My investigative technique also involves
getting into the mind of the criminal.
I try to figure out their actions
by becoming them.
It seems like you have quite
some experience.
Tell me about it later,
when we have the time.
It seems we both don't have that much
time, so I'm going to ask you right now.
You've been going to Munich a lot, lately.
Haven't you?
What about that?
Well, sit down.
I won't take too much time.
You've been seeing Professor Reichwein,
a counseling psychologist.
You went yesterday as well.
Yes. He was my professor in college.
At the Düsseldorf University?
Yes.
There was a brilliant neurosurgeon
who was in the same class as you
at Düsseldorf University, wasn't there?
What are you trying to say?
Have you seen Dr. Tenma?
What are you talking about?
Let's talk about our memories
of cheating. Rudi."
You placed that classified ad in all the
leading newspapers across the country
from May 1 st to the 22nd.
I'm surprised.
I never thought that brilliant people
like you or Dr. Tenma
cheated when you were students.
It's good to have a best friend.
I wasn't really best friends with
Dr. Tenma when we were students.
Last May in Oder Park.
With your help, the Velbert police
were able to surround Dr. Tenma.
They almost took him into custody.
But he escaped.
The wiretap on me malfunctioned.
You could have helped him to escape.
He... Dr. Tenma is innocent!
Oh?
Listen to me with an open mind.
The murder of the director of
the Eisler Memorial Hospital
and three others in Düsseldorf.
The murder of a patient in a building
under construction.
The murder in Heidelberg.
The murders of middle-aged couples
across the country.
Tenma isn't the one who did them.
This is the conclusion I have drawn
as a criminal psychologist
from interviewing him in person.
I see... So where is he right now?
He's gone off somewhere again.
Why did he run away?
Why would he run away
if he's innocent?
He didn't run away!
So why has he disappeared from you,
his best friend?
I have proof that
he isn't the culprit.
Take a look at this.
This is an analysis of all the information
concerning this case.
This is a considerable amount of work.
So...do you understand?
Yes.
The unnatural death of Fahren,
the boy who pretended to
be Schuwald's son.
The unnatural death of Richard Braun,
the ex-police detective who
was investigating this case.
The questions surrounding
Schuwald's illegitimate child.
There is a boy at the center
of all of this.
His name is the same one
that Tenma said was the real culprit
when he was questioned...
Johan Liebert.
The gravestone of a person with
the same first and last name
was discovered in Bruntal.
Furthermore, someone went after
Dr. Reichwein after he picked up
the investigation from where
Richard Braun left off.
I understand very well.
It's impossible.
It is impossible to prove that
all these events are connected.
Tenma went into hiding because
he understands this the most.
Am I wrong?
Your hand movements.
Yes. Don't pay any attention to it.
It's just a mnemonic tool.
As a psychologist, it seems to me
that your anxiety is manifesting
itself in your hand.
I'm the same. instead of my hand,
I have my cassette recorder.
But the sound that's recorded
on this tape is objective.
The information that you remember
through your hand movements
immediately becomes tainted
with your opinions.
That's probably how you've done
your job until now.
You believe that
your hand's memory is correct–
that your judgment isn't wrong.
Do you have a family?
Do you have any hobbies?
Do you live for your job?
Have you ever made a mistake?
Aren't you terribly afraid
to make a mistake?
To you, Tenma has to be a bad person.
If not, then your self-identity would suffer.
Look at the truth.
This is a photograph of Johan Liebert.
Can you prove that
these are all Tenma's lies?
This boy... Where is he right now?
He's a student of the University of
Munich.
At the moment, he's Schuwald's
secretary.
Do you mind if I hold on
to this photograph?
From here on,
this is a matter for the police.
I might have made a terrible mistake.
Where is Dr. Tenma right now?
H-He should be in Munich.
Yes...this is Lunge.
Get me the Munich police.
I need to request
emergency deployment.
Tenma is within the city of Munich.
A sniper rifle?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You should have had a call
from Mr. Heitmeyer
from the mountain villa in Fussen.
10,000 marks in advance.
I have it ready.
Your order is a little troublesome,
so it'll take a week.
Meanwhile, do something about
that pale body of yours.
It's a waste if you have a lot of
good tools, but can't use them.
Next in the news.
A reception was held for the
Munich Electronics Industry Trade Fair
which is going to be hosted next week
by the state chamber of commerce.
Leading political and business figures
from all over the world have gathered.
With the formation of the EU,
the industries of Bavaria
are trying to become
the center of the new media network.
This will be the largest trade fair
that this city has ever hosted.
Hans Georg Schuwald' who hasn't
appeared in public for nearly 20 years
attended this reception and received an
applause from the whole audience.
Mr. Schuwald was in a wheelchair,
but he appeared healthy
and demonstrated his vitality to political
and business figures in attendance.