Hi, Karl.
Hey, Lotte.
Do you have a moment?
No, not really. What is it?
N-Nothing.
I was thinking we could get
tea or something.
I thought that we could
talk a bit more
about the events
surrounding Mr. Schuwald.
It's okay, everything's fine now.
But...
Sorry. I'm in a hurry right now.
My father has a meeting
he has to attend.
See you later.
There's going to be a dance.
I thought that we could...
The library will be closing.
O-Okay.
We're closing.
That girl's here again.
She's beautiful...
God sure is unfair.
I'm sure that she doesn't
have any problems.
But that girl...
It's closing time!
Oh, yes!
Jeez...
I've seen her somewhere.
A dance?
Yes, that's right.
I'm not really interested in
those kinds of things,
but a friend forced me to
buy some tickets.
Sorry. I can't tonight.
Huh?
I have a dinner with members
of the state assembly.
It's not a normal dinner party.
I'm sure there are lots of guys
who'd escort you.
See you later.
Oh.
It's not as if I really want to go.
You're...
Oh?
You're investigating
Margot Langer, too?
There's no need to erase it!
I'm also investigating her.
Huh?
It's for a paper.
I'm Lotte Frank,
a cultural anthropology major.
What about you?
I see you're quite brilliant,
Miss Nina Fortner.
This is the accountant murder case.
This is a newspaper article about
the voice of god murder case.
And this is the middle-aged couple
murder case.
You're amazing.
I have confidence in my ability
to gather information,
but you put me to shame.
I've been investigating
the unsolved murder cases
that have happened in Bavaria
over the past four years.
Could you tell me more about the murder
of Margot Langer, the ex-prostitute?
I just told you what I know.
The child born to Margot Langer
and Hans Schuwald, the tycoon,
has been recognized by his father
and is now his heir.
What is the possibility
that his son was involved
in the events
surrounding Schuwald?
That's not possible.
Not at all.
I see.
You're rather enthusiastic
about your topic.
For someone who's just writing a paper,
you seem pretty involved in your topic.
Y-You think so?
This isn't for a research paper, is it?
To be honest,
I'm looking for someone.
Can I ask you one question?
Do people like you have things
they worry about?
Huh?
Well, beautiful girls like you get
everything they want, don't they?
What are you trying to say?!
For example, you've never had
romantic problems, have you?
It's okay. You don't have
the worries I have, do you?
God really is unfair.
Say! Want to come with me tonight
to a dance party?
I don't really care for places like this.
Come on, don't say that.
Guys will talk to us as long
as you're with me.
Look. Everyone's looking at us.
Hey.
I'll just take the leftovers.
Lotte...
Hi.
Look, they're coming.
Hi!
I'm Constantine from
the Supernatural Phenomenon Club!
Pleased to meet you!
My goodness.
A really weird one's come.
You sure got some nerve,
talking to Nina with a face like yours.
Uh, Lotte!
Huh?
Would you like to be
my partner for tonight?
M-Me?
What's the meaning of this?
Aren't you glad, Lotte?
I'll be off now.
Hey, wait, Nina!
He's not my type!
He's not my type at all!
Stay with me, Nina.
Damn it.
We're kind of depressing.
Yeah.
Yeah"? So many people
talked to you!
Nina, you're too cold.
I'm not trying to be.
But I'm having fun for the
first time in a while.
Huh?
Students are hanging out and everyone is
having fun joking with each other.
It's really been a while.
Nina, are you...
N-Nothing.
You're pretty straight-laced,
despite your looks.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, Lotte.
Please, dance with me.
Woah, he's come again.
You're being pushy.
Just a little is fine. Just a little...
And you're drunk.
Come on.
No. Let go of me.
Cut it out!
It's not as if I'm asking you
because I like you!
What did you say?! That's rude!
Anyway, dance with me just once.
No! Stop.
I'll get paid if you do.
Paid?! What do you mean?
It doesn't mean anything.
Karl asked me to.
He asked me to be
your partner for tonight.
By Karl?
So all you have to do is dance
with me a little.
Stop.
Don't say that.
Stop!
Just for one song is fine.
Huh?
Ow ow ow! Ow! Ow!
Sorry. It hurts.
I won't do it anymore!
Ow! Stop!
Let's go.
I liked him, that's why...
I liked Karl, that's why
I helped him find his father.
I liked him.
But ever since he proved
that he's Schuwald's real son...
He has business with his father.
He promised his father something.
His father. His father.
It hurts. It hurts...
I never thought that being dumped
would hurt so much!
It does hurt.
There are only painful things.
But it's all right.
It'll be all right.
Bad things don't last forever.
You mustn't let them continue,
all right?
All right, I'll be going now.
Tell me where to contact you, Nina!
Sorry. I still haven't found
a place to live.
Then call my house!
Promise me.
Okay.
Today was fun.
I hope you find the person
you're looking for.
Nina... She...
I thought I saw her somewhere.
She looks exactly like Johan.
You're pretty good with that, Doctor.
Well, it's rather the efficiency of
the gun rather than your skill.
That rifle was rejected as the official
sniper rifle of the German army,
but it can hit the center of
a 5-cm target from 300 meters away.
Even an amateur could do it.
I don't know what
you're going to shoot,
but your aim gets better
the closer you get to the target.
All that's left is finding a place where
you can get a clear shot at your target.
The bullets are .338 Lapua Magnums.
There are four of them in there.
But you don't have the time
to fire all four of them.
It's over if you don't finish
the job on your first shot.
You come here every day, don't you?
Bird-watching?
Oh... Yeah.
A lot of visitors come to
this forest on Thursdays.
Those two young people with
that old man and you.
Do you like this forest?
Yeah...
U-Umm... What about you?
Me?
I'm apologizing to this forest
and I have been for over 60 years.
Haven't seen him before.
He's barely touched
my special dishes!
Come on' answer today's quiz
to win fabulous prizes!
Our first contestant is
Mr. Weindler from Frankfurt!
Here's the prize' an RV!
Woah... It's what my family
has always wanted.
Mr. Weindler is very pleased!
It would be wonderful
to go camping in this!
But you'll only get it if you answer
ten questions correctly.
The first question!
Are you planning to leave without
touching anything again?
You came about a week ago,
didn't you?
I always remember my customers,
no matter how crowded it is.
If you're not hungry,
at least have this soup before you leave.
It's on the house.
You look terrible.
Thank you.
This is the place.
I can only shoot him in this forest!
You saved me.
I never thought that I'd trip after walking
in this forest after all these years.
I must be getting old.
I don't think you have a fracture.
I've applied first aid.
Afterwards, go to a hospital
and have someone take a look at it.
Are you a doctor?
When I first saw you,
I thought you were a hunter.
But that doesn't seem to be the case.
I'm amazed.
What's wrong?
The birds.
They're gathering.
Long ago, there was a man on whose
shoulder wild birds would come to rest.
The wild birds would come and rest
on his hand when he held it out like this.
When he was a child, he would always
spend his time in the forest with the birds.
But then, the age of Hitler came.
The man became a member
of the police.
The Nationalist Socialist German
Workers Party truly believed
they could turn this country
into an ideal one.
The man received an order.
A vicious criminal escaped into this forest.
He was chosen to go after him
since he was familiar with the forest.
"Shoot that vicious criminal
when you find him"' they said.
The man chased the vicious criminal
through the forest.
He chased him and chased him.
But when he finally cornered him,
the vicious criminal was just an
ordinary foreigner you'd see anywhere.
But it didn't matter who
the foreigner was.
The man had no choice.
He carried out his orders.
Since then, the birds never came
to rest on his shoulder.
60 years later, he's still apologizing.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry"' he tells them.
But the birds never come near him.
Amazing.
It's all right.
Never again...
Never again will blood be spilled
in this forest again.
Isn't that right?