Amazing.
It's all right.
Never again...
Never again will blood be spilled
in this forest ever again.
Isn't that right?
You don't remember anything?
What were you doing on the roof?
Tell me anything you can remember.
Talk to him, Martin!
If you hadn't hit the eaves
on the first floor
and gotten caught in that tree,
you would have died!
Talk to the doctor!
We have to bring an end
to this foolishness!
Now, now, ma'am.
But if he were to die, I...I...
Listen, ma'am.
I've come to counsel your son.
I know. I know. But...Doctor...
Let's talk outside, ma'am.
Dieter, stay right there.
Don't go into the room.
Is he your grandson?
No. I'm just taking care of him
for a bit.
H-Hey.
Hey.
I'm Dieter.
I'm Martin.
Does it hurt?
Does what?
Those wounds the ones
that are bandaged.
Was it scary when
you fell off the roof?
N-No, what are you doing?!
My shoes are in that bag.
Get them for me!
What are you saying?
You've got to lie down!
Get my shoes!
Where are you going?
You'll get scolded.
So what if someone scolds me?
It's not as if I'm afraid to get scolded.
Ah! It's just as he said.
If you come back to life, go outside.
The world will be different. "
No, the world hasn't changed. I have.
That's because...I was chosen.
Boring.
I never knew that this world
was so boring.
Oh! Look out...
Come on.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
H-How could you do that?!
Hey, look! He's afraid!
S-Stop that!
I'm telling you to look.
I don't want to die!
Help me! Is that it?
Fine. I'll let you live.
I'll answer your question.
Huh?
You asked if I was afraid
when I fell off the roof, didn't you?
Y-Yeah...
Of course I wasn't afraid.
It was a game.
A-A game?!
B-But several people have died!
It's fun. It's just a game.
Two people face each other on the ledge
of the roof of an empty building.
Then they close their eyes and walk
towards each other, one step at a time.
It's a duel!
It doesn't matter if you fall or do anything.
You win so long as you survive.
Why would you do that?
To bet on your fate.
The survivors are the chosen ones.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
The survivors can play again.
Play... Play?
The world is boring.
It's fun. Only the chosen ones
can keep on playing.
Don't you see?
I thought you were one of us.
Come, I'll show you.
If you see it and you still don't get it,
you really are an idiot.
H-Hey, you're not planning
to go to the roof, are you?
The chosen ones...
The superior survive...
That's what he is.
Who's "he"?
The person who taught me this game.
Who is he?
A friend to all of us superior children.
Now, hurry up and come!
L-I don't want to.
Just come!
Let go!
You should understand. Come!
Stop!
Those scars...
Who did that to you?
Was it your parents?!
Do you plan to stay with them
even though they did this to you?
Do you still plan to stay
in this worthless world
even though they did this to you?
Come! Come and see!
What do you think of the view
from here?
How does it feel?
Stand up. What are you afraid of?
Stand up, close your eyes and walk.
Stand up!
All right. I understand what
you're talking about.
What?
I thought that the world was dark.
I thought that the future was dark.
What's your favorite food?
Recently, I ate a really
delicious sausage!
But if I died, I'd no longer
be able to eat it again!
Coward.
I like soccer!
But if I died, I'd no longer be able
to kick around a ball!
Weakling.
I like Doctor Reichwein!
His secretary, Mereth, is a kind person!
But if I died, I'd no longer
be able to see them!
Scary things will never go away!
That's why he said we grow up!
He said that tomorrow will be a good day!
Tenma said that!
If I died. If I died, I'd no longer
be able to see Tenma.
I'm scared!
Don't panic.
Get on your knees slowly.
I can't be like him.
I can't be like Johan.
Johan?!
Johan is playing an even
more terrifying game!
Johan said that he was going
to be killed soon!
He said that he was going to
be shot by a Japanese man soon!
I closed my eyes and
walked across the ledge of the roof.
It's true. I walked across!
I wasn't scared at all!
Joachim was supposed to be
walking across from me.
But when I opened my eyes,
he had disappeared!
I saw it! I saw someone die
with my own eyes!
People really do die.
Have some tea.
Oh, thank you.
Honestly! He doesn't seem
to realize what he's done.
I'm glad he's alive, but when I think of
what Joachim's parents are going through.
Please say something to him!
He'll listen to you.
She complains to me like that every day.
She doesn't understand
anything at all.
She won't let me out of the house,
and I'm not allowed
to watch TV or read comics.
You seem bored.
I'll bring you something.
What?!
Really?
Comics aren't allowed,
but a picture book is all right, isn't it?
A picture book?
That's boring.
Say, what about that terrifying game
you were talking about?
You said that you were going
to be shot dead soon!
This is exciting.
When is it going to happen?
When is that Japanese man
going to shoot you?!
Hey, Johan!
Hermann Hesse.
A first edition of Steppenwolf!
And this! A first edition of
Hoffmann's Night Pieces.
There's a complete collection
of Goethe's poems.
Impressive.
Even as the head librarian
of the University of Munich,
Freidrich Emmanuel Campus Library,
I am dazzled by this collection!
I didn't go to college.
I've come this far through
educating myself.
I thought that I should at least read.
I never expected you to donate
such a collection to our library.
I cannot express my gratitude!
I have become blind,
and can no longer read.
Rather than having these books
lay unread in this library,
they would be of more use
if they are with the students.
Yes! They're all valuable books,
but we're considering making them
available to the public.
Oh yes... We've already decided
where we'll store them.
There will be a ceremony as well,
so please come to the library
to discuss it with us.
How's the security?
Huh?
Ever since Mr. Schuwald
reentered public life,
we've been on the lookout
for dangerous groups.
Please check
your guest list thoroughly.
Right, Johan?!
Yes.
Johan and Karl thought
of donating this collection.
They should be the ones
to go to your library.
I'm Gherrmann, the head librarian.
Pleased to meet you.
This room is where we will store
Mr. Schuwald's collection.
The general public isn't allowed here.
You've never come here before,
have you?
Of course, the temperature and
humidity are perfect for storing books,
and we're also secure
against theft and fires.
What an amazing number of books.
It's a testament to mankind,
isn't it, Johan?
A testament to mankind...
And we plan to hold the donation
ceremony in this central hall.
The library will be tightly secured,
just as Mr Schuwald's butler requested.
I want Mr. Schuwald to feel safe.
Yes, my father would
be happy to attend.
Right, Johan?
What's wrong, Johan?
Excuse me for a second.
Are you looking for something?
Yes...
I was looking for
a good picture book for a friend.
A friend?
Yes. A friend.
Well then, how about this one?
See? Aren't these wonderful pictures?!
Yes, these are nice.
But they're a bit grown-up.
Oh, your friend's not an adult?
Then what about this one?
Oh no...
Oh, thank you.
I'm so clumsy.
This always happens.
Yes, I recommend this one.
Do you like that one?
Oh... What nice pictures!
I wonder whose book it is?
Excuse me...
Emile...Scherbe?
Moravia Publishing.
It's a Czech publishing company
in Prague.
There are a lot of good
picture-book authors in Czechoslovakia.
But I've never heard of Scherbe.
Maybe he's not that famous.
What's wrong?
S-Somebody!
Somebody, come help!
This summer heat is really terrible.
Here...
From here, I'm going to...