He was discharged?!
Yes. Johan Liebert was
discharged this morning.
I see...
I heard that he collapsed.
I guess it wasn't anything serious.
Oh?
You come to the library often.
You're the college's librarian...
I see... He was discharged.
Thank goodness.
I was worried about what
would happen to him.
You saw him collapse?
Yes.
He was looking for a book.
So I helped him look for one.
Then he suddenly collapsed?
Yes. He screamed.
Screamed?
He was holding a picture book.
And when he turned
the page like this...
Picture book?
Shouldn't you rest a little more?
Then again,
there's nothing peculiar about
your brain or brainwaves.
You're completely healthy!
The doctor said it was
probably anemia or fatigue.
Or that you experienced
some sort of shock.
That's what he said anyway.
By the way, I didn't know that you have
scars on your head from a major surgery.
Anyway, for now, you should take
a break from work and studies and relax.
Oh yeah. You received a letter
while you were in the hospital.
A letter?
It's unsigned.
Well, I don't think it's a letter bomb.
What is it? What's so funny?
Who's it from?
It's from the Red Hindenburg.
Huh?
A pretty one's wandered in.
Are you lost?
Or is it your first time?
I'll be gentle. Come here.
Do you know
the Red Hindenburg?
Huh?
The Red Hindenburg said
that she was around this area.
You sure are into some
pretty freaky stuff for your age.
She's in the back.
Drugs... Give me drugs.
Is the Red Hindenburg up here?
Come in!
I'm glad you came.
Sit there.
Just look at that face.
It's very pretty.
I saw you on the TV news.
You were with Schuwald.
First you call yourself
Margot Langer...
and now you're going
by "Red Hindenburg"?
Before that it was "Blue Sophie."
But names don't matter.
Isn't that right, Johan Liebert?
Anyway, that's what
my boyfriend calls me.
He's right behind that door.
Right, Dear?
So don't try anything funny.
He's on guard behind that door,
and he's got a big gun.
He's big in other places, too.
Excuse me.
You're really close to
that tycoon, Schuwald.
What an ingenious plan.
No, it's really impressive.
Before, you brought me
that Fahren boy.
But who would have thought that
Schuwald's real son would show up?!
I feel sorry for Fahren.
As soon as he wasn't of use,
he was forced to commit suicide.
Well, who knew that
it would take two years?
Two years ago, the real Margot Langer
died very conveniently.
Of course, she died and
I received quite a blessing.
I wasn't really close to her.
She's wasn't a prostitute!
She had already washed her hands.
I only went drinking with her
two or three times.
She never had anyone to talk to
for a long time, did she?
I'd get her drunk, act as if I was crying
and she'd talk on and on.
Her love affair with Schuwald...
How she left her son up for adoption...
But she was killed.
Thanks to that, I became Margot Langer
and got a lot from Schuwald in her place.
When Margot was killed, the police
said it was the work of a phantom killer.
The police probably never knew
that such a plan was in the works.
Oh...That's right.
You did a pretty horrible thing
to Richard, that detective!
He never would have had to commit suicide
if he hadn't poked his nose into this.
Now then. How many people
have you killed?
All right... Let's end our fun little chat
and start negotiating.
You can't get away.
You have to give up!
Right, dear?!
Tell me, how much
will you give me?
Are you listening?
What do you think is
the most terrifying thing?
Huh?
I thought I had reached
the darkest place.
It's no use to change the subject.
But...beyond that...
I saw an even blacker darkness.
Huh?
Hold on a second!
Do you think I'm just
going to let you leave?!
I've already given up.
I don't have anymore
interest in Schuwald.
Don't mess with me!
It's useless.
I'm someone who doesn't exist.
Don't think you can
make a fool of me!
Dear!
Dear, come out!
D-Dear... W-What are you...
R-Roberto!
Could you give me a balloon?
Use this to buy some drugs.
Doctor, are you ready yet?
My head's bleeding!
What are you talking about?
My kid is first!
- It hurts. It hurts. It hurts.
Shut up. Don't cry over
a little fracture.
Stop making a fuss and
sit and wait for your turn.
No matter how much noise you make,
there's only one doctor here.
What is that long pole-like thing?
Oh... Well, umm...
ls the doctor here a good doctor?
Of course! If this doctor weren't here,
all the Asians here would be dead.
Especially the Vietnamese.
I see.
You're not Vietnamese, are you?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, wait in line! You look sickly,
but the injured come first.
Well, I'm not a patient, so...
Hey, sit down and wait!
Hurry and see me, doctor!
My kid is first!
Excuse me.
What is it?
Hey, stay in line!
Excuse me...Doctor!
There's something I want to ask you.
How many times do I have to say this?!
Wait outside!
I don't have the time for this!
A woman...
and what's more...
Didn't you hear me?! Get out!
This Doctor...
How old is she?
I'm suturing this wound,
so don't interfere.
If something happens to this patient,
it'll be your fault!
A stab to the thigh...
It's from a knife.
Her suturing is very clean.
But...
You should insert a drainage tube.
Don't talk next to me!
If not, you should take him
to a real hospital.
A real hospital?!
This is a rea–
This is not a hospital.
I can tell that you're
not a real doctor.
I would have taken him to
a real hospital if I could.
Most of the people here are
illegal immigrants or illegal overstayers.
If they went to a real hospital,
they'd be sent to prison.
And deported to
their native countries!
How many people here
do you think have died
because they couldn't get
to a real hospital?
Don't talk as if you know anything!
Insert a drainage tube.
Huh?
He probably got stabbed
with a dirty knife.
If you don't insert a drainage tube,
the wound will fester
and an abscess will form!
O-Okay!
Remove one or two stitches.
Okay!
Insert the drainage tube
about five centimeters in.
All right. It went well.
All right, who's my next patient?
You've regained consciousness.
Your patients tell me that you had
been treating them for 48 hours straight.
I checked on the other
patients' post-operative status.
You're pretty good for
an unlicensed doctor.
How old are you?
17.
I'm surprised. You're so young.
You have the skill of
a practicing physician.
By chance, the doctor who did business
here disappeared and left his tools.
This isn't something you can do
just by holding the right tools.
Where did you learn your skills?
My father...was a doctor.
Was?
My father was a Vietnamese doctor.
He took me with him when
he came to study in East Germany.
He stayed and opened a clinic.
But the Wall was destroyed.
Even so, he tried to help
Asian immigrants to the best of his ability.
That's when...
my father was killed by a thug
who called himself a Neo-nazi.
He was killed...just because
he had a different skin color.
I became an orphan and
was sent to an orphanage.
Afterwards, I was adopted
by a German family.
But they only adopted me
in the spirit of social service.
I was just a poor yellow-skinned girl.
So I ran away.
I helped my father as a child.
I read a lot of the books
he left behind.
I decided that I would do
what my father tried to do.
Out of the way!
I'll do the rest.
There we go.
Don't do anything reckless
if you want it to heal quickly.
Okay.
All right, next patient.
I saw most of them.
You should go back home
and study.
This country will provide opportunities
for those who want to learn.
I guess you're a real doctor.
Are you saying that amateurs
should stand aside?!
That's not what I'm saying.
I just...
If I'm gone, what'll happen
to the people here?!
Who's going to take care of them?!
Well... I just...
Mommy!
W-What's wrong?!
My p-pimp suddenly snapped.
H-He shot m–
Mommy!
She was shot and
walked all the way here?!
Mommy said that
you could fix her!
W-Well...
Save her!
Please save Mommy!
All right.
It's all right!
Leave it to me!
I'm counting on you, Doctor!
She's a prostitute from this town.
This kind of thing always happens
to these kinds of people.
I'd like to help her,
but this is impossible!
I'm getting her on the operating table.
Carry that side!
It's impossible! We've got to
take her to a real hospital!
If we carry her to a hospital right now,
it'll be too late!
I know my limits!
This is too much for me!
Don't give up until the end!
As long as the patient's breathing,
don't give up hope until the very end!
Don't give up hope!
If the artery in her abdominal cavity
had been damaged...
Her blood pressure would
have immediately plummeted,
and she would have
gone into shock.
But she walked all the way here.
It means that her blood pressure
dropped gradually,
and she's in pre-shock.
From the look of her bullet wound,
there's a big possibility that
her spleen is damaged.
In other words, we can perform
an emergency abdominal operation
while we do a blood transfusion.
Now let's begin.
Take the scalpel.
Well, he fell asleep peacefully.
It's a miracle that she didn't suffer
any damage to her bones,
small and large intestines,
or any part of the digestive system.
We were lucky that all we had to do
was remove the damaged spleen.
It was a magnificent operation.
That's because you were here.
Mommy...
Dr. Tenma...
Stay here.
I came here to ask you something.
This newspaper article...
Blue Sophie"' also known as
the "Red Hindenburg"...
I heard that you were
the first person at the murder scene.
Yes.
Could you tell me what it was like?
That night, I received a call
from one of the townspeople.
She was shot in the head.
She died instantly.
I've seen scenes
like that many times.
But that was a first.
The feeling I felt
as I entered the room...
It wasn't a robbery.
It wasn't revenge.
It was just a murder.
Johan.
When you're in darkness,
you just sink deeper into it.
Shine some light.
Listen, study hard.
You can do it!
You can become a good doctor.
Wait. Where are you going,
Dr. Tenma?!
You...You look like someone who's
sinking deeper into darkness.
You'll come back,
right, Dr. Tenma?!