Domo. I look forward
to working with you.
Oh, Domo. Likewise!
I'd like to play golf
with you sometime.
Well, if we do, don't be
too hard on me.
We look forward to
continuing business with you.
Oh, Domo.
Domo!
Domo... Domo, huh?
What an incomprehensible bunch.
Oh, domo, domo.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My business meeting ran a bit late.
I'm Iwai of the Kadofuku Corporation,
Munich branch.
I'm inspector Lunge of the BKA.
Pleased to meet you.
Domo.
"Domo" and a bow?
I'm flattered.
One coffee.
Oh, and a refill as well.
You wanted to meet Yamamoto...
Right now, he's gone to
the Czech Republic on business.
He's going to return tomorrow.
You seem busy.
Well, do you know about Schuwald,
the business tycoon?
He's come out of seclusion and
restarted his business activities.
All the businesses under his control
and their subsidiaries have
recently been reinvigorated.
We Japanese businessmen are
very busy with Mr. Schuwald.
Why is he laughing?
So, Yamamoto can't help you today.
But he and I are just as
close to Kenzo Tenma.
I see...
I was surprised. I didn't think
he was still under investigation.
Yes. We still haven't solved the case.
I was surprised when I heard that
Tenma was a suspect.
You were surprised.
Was it that unexpected?
Very surprised. I never would have
thought him capable of murder.
Well, actually,
I never thought he would do that.
I went drinking with him twice
three years ago.
He wasn't a bad person.
He's not a bad person...
Does that mean he's a good person?
A good person... Or rather...
He didn't reveal himself freely.
Is someone who doesn't
reveal himself a good person?
Well, anyway, it just means
that he wasn't too unsociable.
Japanese people don't
usually wear these.
Japanese people are
handy with chopsticks.
I am a Japanese person.
Domo.
I am...Tenma.
Yes?
Oh. ..Dad?
Hi.
Are you doing well?
Yes. I am.
I called because I heard that
you were in Munich.
I'm living here now.
Actually Dad' my son was born.
I see... Congratulations.
A lot has happened' but...
I want you to see your grandson.
Will you come to see us?
Of course.
Is tomorrow all right?
Yes. If it's after 6 P.M.
We'll met at...the Marian Platz.
Okay. All right.
See you then.
Domo.
Huh?
Ah...
You're so skillful with chopsticks.
Really?
Of course, lately,
there have been a lot of foreigners
who are even better at using chopsticks
than Japanese people are.
So, Doctor Takahashi...
As a colleague,
what kind of person was Tenma?
What kind? Well...
He wasn't that unsociable.
Well, he was a bit indecisive.
But...
But?
When he held a scalpel,
he was like a different person.
He's been called a brilliant brain surgeon,
and that's not an exaggeration.
What about his parents?
He didn't like to talk
much about them.
But he said that his father and
his older brother were also doctors.
Well, he probably had no choice
but to become a doctor.
Come to think of it,
he said that he hasn't gone back to Japan
since he became a doctor in Germany.
And his parents didn't come here
during that uproar.
They also didn't argue
for their son's innocence.
I suppose that means that
he has weak family ties.
I'm sorry.
Yamamoto contacted me.
He's arrived in Munich from Prague.
But he has to go make a deal.
He seems busy.
He's going to meet us afterwards
at the place we're going to.
Place?
Oh yeah! Would you like to come,
inspector Lunge?
This must be fate! We might also be
indebted to you in the future, so...
No, today, I...
I suppose that means that
he has weak family ties.
I...am Tenma.
Huh?
That sounds good.
Please allow me to accompany you.
Farewell Pleiades...
I'm going...
Farewell Pleiades!
Yea!
As I expected of you Iwai!
How about you, Inspector Lunge?
All right!
Whoa. My song's next!
That's great!
We've been waiting for this!
A love letter from Canada!
- A love letter from Canada!
- What a fun trip it would be
- That's great!
- If you were with me...
- Woo hoo!
I am Tenma.
- A love letter from Canada!
- I am Tenma.
I cannot blend
into Japanese society.
I can't ask for help here.
I have no place to go home to.
I am... alone.
Ah...
Domo, domo.
I'm sorry I'm late!
Oh.
We've been waiting for you,
Yamamoto!
This is Inspector Lunge,
the one I told you about on the phone.
Oh, domo. I'm Yamamoto of
Kadofuku Corporations' Munich branch.
Domo.
How did your negotiations go with
Mr. Kocht in the Czech Republic?
Well... He's tough.
Oh, yeah. I found it!
"It"?
The thing that Schuwald's right-hand man
asked us to find.
You know, the blond boy!
Huh? You found it?
Right now, getting on
that secretary's good side
is the best way to close a deal
with Mr. Schuwald!
I searched countless
used bookstores in Prague,
and I finally found one!
Ah. So this is the picture book!
The cover's gone and it's worn.
But it'll look good
if we package it nicely.
Excuse me. I'll have a beer!
May I see that for a moment?
Oh, go right ahead.
It's in Czech.
Whoa. My song's next!
All right!
- All right!
That's great!
- We've been waiting for you!
He's going to show off
his singing talent!
That's great!
Inspector, what are you looking up
in that dictionary?
Czech.
Czech?
Does it have something to do
with your investigation?
No...not at all.
I'm surprised you're looking up
something unrelated to your case.
It's a line in a picture book.
I liked the pictures.
I wanted to know what
its captions said.
The inspector with a picture book...
That's unusual.
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"The monster inside me
has gotten this big."
I see...
Johan's finally controlling that tycoon.
I heard about Johan from you before.
He's a complete monster.
A monster, huh?
Yeah. I've done quite a few murders.
But he's become something that
I could only wish to become.
Johan's my hero.
I see. I have one more thing
I want to ask you.
What is it?
If you were Johan,
what would you do next?
Next?
It's obvious.
I would kill my current parents...
the Lieberts.
Mr. Liebert.
Mr. Liebert!
Why would you do that?
Why? Because I've
grown bored with them.
Mr. Liebert!
Yes? Who are you?
A psychoanalyst?
What business do you have with us?
I have no intention of
giving a long introduction.
I want to ask you about
your adopted son Johan.
Johan...adopted?
What are you talking about?
He's our child...
It's no use playing dumb!
The grave of your real child is in Bruntal.
You used the fact that
the town office's records had burned
to reapply for a birth certificate
as if your child were still alive.
Who in the world are you?
I didn't come to threaten you.
I came to help you.
I want you to read this!
Huh?
This is a report about Johan.
About Johan?
Yes... A certain man investigated
and compiled it.
Oh...
This person...
He came to sell us insurance.
That's former police detective
Richard Brown.
Former police detective?
He's...dead.
Now read.
It begins in 1986,
when a certain East German government
official sought refuge in West Germany.
Is he after money?
Money?
He's not interested in that.
Then why would he
stick around a tycoon?
You did it when you were a kid,
didn't you?
Did what?
You'd take a line of ants...
and play around with them...like this.
This can't be.
I can't believe something
so terrible.
This is silly.
I understand why you
don't want to believe it.
You lost your son
when he was young.
When you couldn't
have children afterwards,
a boy about
your son's age appeared.
Furthermore, he had money.
He gave you a wonderful house.
He gave you a beautiful yard.
And he gave you affection.
I understand why
you want to believe in him.
But what's written there is the truth!
Who is Johan?
Who in the world is he?
Johan is a good boy.
He's a kind boy.
He's smart.
And clever.
He's our reason for living.
Is that all?
You've been his parents
for nearly five years.
Is that all you can say?
You don't know anything about him.
Please help me.
Because of him, my friend,
Richard, is dead!
And right now,
a man called Tenma is...
is about to do something
that cannot be undone.
Please help me!
No. Besides that...you'll become like
the middle-aged couples mentioned here...
Like Johan's foster parents...
You'll be killed.
Get out of here! Come with me!
The apple tree has borne small fruit.
Yes... Next year,
they'll be even bigger.
I'm looking forward to that.
Yes... Me too.
He's going to be killed by
a Japanese man soon?
Is that what Johan told those kids?
Yes... What do you think about that?
I'll say this, he doesn't have
any wish to kill himself.
Then what does it mean?
Who knows?
It's difficult to think like a hero.
But...
But I can say this.
Even if a nuclear war burned everything
to the ground, he'd still survive.
So there's nothing we can do...
All we've done was for naught.
We couldn't even save Richard.
Dr. Reichwein...
We can't locate Dr. Tenma...
Or even stop him from killing Johan!
It's all in vain!
Dr. Reichwein,
let's calm down and think.
Sorry.
Playing with a line of ants...
Even ants...have souls.
Doctor, where are you going?
At this point, we've got to
take desperate measures.
Huh?
I'm going to talk directly
to that tycoon Schuwald.
Huh? Fifty more seats?
Yeah. We'll be packed!
For Mr. Schuwald's
book donation ceremony tomorrow?
Yes. Lots of big names
will be attending.
When Mr. Schuwald does something,
it's big news, even now!
The library will soon be closing.
Umm...
Excuse me,
could you get that for me?
Huh?
That Czech dictionary.
I can't reach it.
O-Oh, is this it?
Sorry. Thank you.
No problem.
I borrowed a Czech picture book,
but I didn't know what it says.
Oh, I see.
My friend suddenly collapsed
when he read this book.
Oh...
I thought that maybe the contents of
this book had something to do with it.
Did your friend get better?
Yes. Completely.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Umm...
"Once upon a time,
in a land far away..."
"There lived a nameless monster."
"The monster was
dying to have a name."
"So the monster set out
on a journey."
What an odd book.
We're closed!
Okay.
We're closed tomorrow
for the ceremony.