Has there been any change
in the patient's condition?
Oh, No. But...
How is his blood pressure
and pulse?
Excuse me, Dr. Tenma, but what
about mayor Rodecker's operation?
I'm beginning the operation.
Oh... Okay.
Oh yeah.
What's the patient's name?
Huh?
What's this boy's name?
Well, umm...
You don't know his name,
do you?
It's all right. Hang on.
I'll save you!
Kill...
Those children!
The twins are nowhere
to be found!
Did you search carefully?
I did! I've searched everywhere!
Do you suppose that they're playing
hide-and-go-seek somewhere?
Playing hide-and-go-seek
somewhere...
Tenma the coward!
Tenma the coward! Hey!
It's no use hiding,
Tenma the coward!
If you try too hard to hide,
you'll pee in your pants again!
Look at how late it is.
How long are you going to play?!
Okay!
See you tomorrow!
See you later!
Bye bye.
Huh?
Oh... What about me?
Hey, everyone... I'm over here.
Find me.
I'm here!
Find me!
Tenma the coward, huh?
What should I do?
The man that came by this evening
is still in front of the mansion.
Who is he?
He's Richard Brown's
personal psychiatrist.
Brown's the detective we hired.
I'll throw him out right now.
Karl, I cannot see.
What kind of man is he?
Okay.
He's a man past middle age.
What do you think of him?
He doesn't look like a bad person.
And he seems kind of...
desperate.
I see...
Thank you for agreeing to see me,
Herr Schuwald.
Let's forget trifling introductions.
Time is short.
Let's hear what you have to say.
I also don't have much time.
It's up to you whether
this ends quickly.
Didn't you come to talk about him?
Huh?
Johan.
It seems it is.
I knew someone like you would
come to me sooner of later.
To solve this mystery.
Mystery–?
He's too perfect.
Those who can see
might not be able to tell.
I can sense when I'm before
something perfectly in harmony.
I wonder if it even exists
in this world.
He definitely exists!
Fragments of his past
are written here.
I'll read it to you right now.
You'll agree that he's not an illusion.
The story begins in 1986
and starts with
a certain boy with a critical injury
being carried into a hospital.
And he appeared before you.
Richard died...no, he was killed.
According to his findings,
Johan was the one who had
Fahren act as if he was your son.
But when Karl,
your real son, appeared,
he changed his plans and
allied himself with Karl instead.
And Fahren was
forced to commit suicide.
Why did you accept your son whom
you've been separated all these years?
Over the past few years, how many
of your trusted associates have died?
The driver who served you
for many years...
The maid who
read books to you...
Your accountant friend
who was a fellow birdwatcher...
They all died.
Johan has isolated you in order to
worm his way into your heart!
Please help me!
Expose everything to the public.
If not, that Japanese doctor...
Dr. Tenma will.
You said that it was as if Johan
was playing with a line of ants.
A line of ants, huh?
Do you know what I am called?
That's right.
The Vampire of Bavaria.
I happily accepted that name.
When I try to prove myself,
for some reason, it keeps getting bigger.
The monster inside me.
But what of it?
My nickname is exaggerated,
but I'm very small.
Come to think of it, I wanted to
be able to play with a line of ants.
Like this.
What I wanted to become...
he's trying to become.
"Who is like unto the beast?
Who is able to make war with him?"
The Apocalypse of
St. John the Divine, is it?
The only thing that would be
able to defeat the monster...
would have to be
a bigger monster, right?
Father.
What did you discuss?
It's already morning.
So...where's Johan?
He's headed to the ceremony
directly from the Esterhoven office.
Anyway, you look very tired.
Shall we cancel today's ceremony?
No. Let's prepare to go.
Kill...
Doctor Tenma... It's not your fault.
You just did your job as a doctor.
It's not your fault.
Survive. And try to save
as many people as you can.
Nina...
How unfortunate.
Are you really going to quit?
You just got used to working here.
Thank you very much.
If you come around here again,
give me a call!
Yes. Good bye.
She was a good girl.
Oh... Hello?
Is Lotte Frank there?
Lotte's out at the moment.
I see. Please tell her that I'll be
departing Munich on the 3:00 train.
All right. I'll tell her.
Oh. Could you tell me
your name again?
It's Nina.
Nina Fortner.
He's here!
His car's arrived at
the back entrance.
The Vampire of Bavaria
finally makes an appearance.
He can hear you.
Did you see the guests
at the assembly hall?
Yes. Bavarians aren't
the only ones here.
People from the rest of Europe, and
Japanese businessmen are here, too.
It's crawling with ambassadors,
and high-ranking politicians
and businessmen.
You'd never think that this was
a book donation to a college.
Yeah.
That's because it's said that
all of Mr. Schuwald's actions
affect the European economy.
He doesn't show
his face very often.
So I suppose people
are bound to gather.
But for him to suddenly come here
and donate his book collection...
It's as if he's distributing mementos.
Hey, don't say such things.
He's an important part of
the EU's economy.
He has to live a little longer!
Karl.
Yes?
I forgot that there are important
documents that I want you to fetch.
What sort of documents?
Just go fetch them
from the mansion!
They're on the desk in my study.
But Father...
Johan's coming soon.
Leave this to him.
O-Okay.
What's going on
with the investigation?!
It's going smoothly.
Smoothly?!
I told you that
Tenma was in Munich
because I thought that you would
put more effort into the investigation.
But what are you doing?!
Did you investigate Johan Liebert,
who's working as Schuwald's secretary?!
There's no doubt that he's the true culprit
of the multiple homicide case.
Are you listening?!
If you don't hurry, Tenma will...
Tenma is trying to
settle everything by himself!
Don't worry.
The investigation is
going very smoothly.
Excuse me.
Johan is right before our eyes.
Investigate him quickly.
As I expected of a teacher
of criminal psychology.
That's a wonderful expression.
Johan does exist.
In Tenma's head.
Have you gathered
any new testimonies?
No. It's all the same stuff.
The gun is a Mauser SR93.
It was sold to a Japanese man.
Should we squeeze him
a little more?
No. That's probably all he knows.
A Mauser SR93 is
a sniper rifle, isn't it?
Yes. It's of high efficiency.
Who do you think
he plans to shoot?
I am Tenma...
I am Tenma. I have obtained
a highly efficient sniper rifle.
I am Tenma. And I...
I am Johan.
Who am I going to
shoot with this rifle?
I killed the director and
others at my hospital.
I killed many middle-aged couples.
And, right now,
who am I going to kill?
I am...chaos.
I like chaos.
You should eat something.
Oh... Thank you, Dieter.
I'm all right. Don't worry.
I won't give up!
I may not look like much,
but I strengthened my body and mind
when I was a medic for
the border patrol police.
I'll do anything I can
to save your friend!
Anything!
Don't underestimate
a former police medic!
Now, you took the time
to make this.
And I'll gladly eat it.
You can't fight if you're hungry.
This is it.
Did you figure something out?!
Schuwald's
book donation ceremony!
Is Tenma there?!
Dieter, wait here!
Don't follow me!
Schuwald!
Huh?
I need to meet Hans Georg Schuwald
face-to-face. Contact him!
Okay.
Oh...
Wait, today he's at
the book donation ceremony
at the University of Munich Library.
We need an emergency
deployment there immediately.
Huh?
Tenma is after Schuwald.
So let's bring up to the stage
the man who donated
this huge collection to our library,
Hans Georg Schuwald!
Is Johan... Is my secretary here?
Huh?
He's over there.
You've come.
I.. .brought him back to life.
I brought back that monster.
Nina!
Lotte, you came!
Sorry.
I looked all over the place, but I couldn't
find the person I was looking for.
We had just become friends.
It's unfortunate, but...
Could it be that you're twins?!
Aren't you?
What is this picture book?!
When he saw this,
he suddenly collapsed!
Picture...book...
Kill...