I.. .brought him back to life.
I.. .brought back that monster.
This is it.
Did you figure something out?!
Schuwald's
book donation ceremony!
Is Tenma there?!
Dieter, wait here!
Don't follow me!
Schuwald!
Huh?
I want to meet
Hans Georg Schuwald.
Contact him!
Okay.
Oh... Wait, today he's at
the book donation ceremony
at the University of Munich Library.
We need an emergency
deployment there immediately.
Huh?
Tenma is after...Schuwald.
Nina!
Lotte, you came!
Sorry.
I looked all over the place,
but I couldn't find
the person I was looking for.
We had just become friends.
It's unfortunate, but...
Could it be that you're twins?!
Aren't you?
What is this picture book?!
When he saw this,
he suddenly collapsed!
Picture...book...
Kill...
Once upon a time' in a land far away
there lived a nameless monster.
The monster was dying
to have a name.
So the monster set out
on a journey to find one.
But the world was
such a very large place'
so the monster split into two
and went on their way
One monster went east.
The other went west.
The monster who went east
found a village.
At the village's entrance'
there lived a blacksmith.
"Mr. Blacksmith' give me your name' "
said the monster.
"I can't give you my name' "
the blacksmith replied.
"In return for giving me your name'
I'll go inside of you and make you strong."
"Really? If you make me strong'
I'll give you my name."
The monster went
inside the blacksmith.
Thus' the monster became'
Otto the blacksmith.
Otto the blacksmith was
the strongest man in the village.
But then one day..
"Look at me. Look at me."
"The monster inside me has
gotten this big' " he said.
Munch-munch' chomp-chomp'
gobble-gobble' gulp.
The hungry monster ate up Otto
from the inside out.
Once again' he was
a monster without a name.
When he went inside
Hans the shoemaker, however...
Munch-munch' chomp-chomp'
gobble-gobble' gulp.
The monster was
nameless once again.
When he went inside
Thomas the hunter, but...
Munch-munch' chomp-chomp'
gobble-gobble' gulp.
The monster was
nameless once again.
The monster went to a castle
to find a nice name.
Inside the castle
lived a sick boy.
"If you give me your name'
I'll make you strong."
"If you can heal my illness
and make me strong' "
"I will give you my name"
The monster went
inside the boy
The boy became full of vigor.
The king was overjoyed.
"The prince is healthy
The prince is healthy "
The monster liked the boy's name.
He also liked living in the castle.
So he restrained himself
even though he was hungry
Day after day he would be terribly
hungry. but he restrained himself.
But the hunger became
just too great.
'Look at me. Look at me. '
'The monster inside me has
gotten this big' ' said the boy
The boy devoured the king
and all his servants.
Munch-munch' chomp-chomp'
gobble-gobble' gulp.
Everyone was gone'
so the boy went on a journey
He walked for days and days.
One day the boy came upon
the monster who had gone west.
"I have a name.
It's a wonderful name' " said the boy.
The monster who
went west replied'
"I don't need a name.
I'm perfectly happy without one."
"After all' that's what we are–
nameless monsters."
The boy ate up the monster
who went west.
At last he had found a name'
but there was no longer anyone
around to call him by it.
Such a shame' because Johan
was such a wonderful name.
You know about this picture book,
don't you?
Can you read Czech?
Are you Czech?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Long ago...
I think someone read it
to me long ago.
Who are you?
Are you really Nina Fortner?
Answer me honestly.
Who in the world are you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
We're talking about you!
You should know!
Answer me.
Tell me what's going on.
Why did you get a bad feeling
when you read this picture book?
A student named Fahren who claimed
to be Schuwald's son committed suicide.
The detective that Schuwald hired
fell off a building and died.
The prostitute who called herself
Margot Langer was shot to death.
After reading this book,
why does it occur to me
that all the strange things that
happened recently are connected?
I feel like everything
is connected to Johan!
Sorry. I got carried away.
That person...
The person who collapsed
after he saw this book...
Does he really look like me?
Like twins?
Your friend Johan looks like
he's my twin, doesn't he?
Where is he right now?
He's at the book donation ceremony
at the University's library.
Oh, hold on.
Hold on.
Hey, Nina! Wait a second!
Wait!
The grand collection that Schuwald
Financial Group representative
Hans Georg Schuwald
has donated today
to our University's Friedrich
Emmanuel Campus library
is very important and valuable.
You could call it one of
Germany's great treasures.
We have a duty to preserve this
grand collection of humanity's wisdom
for the next generation!
Next up...
A greeting from the Friedrich
Emmanuel Campus chancellor...
Professor Steinbeck.
Damn!
Pull the trigger.
If I pull the trigger,
everything will end.
Move!
Help me' Doctor!
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
Mr. Maurer!
I've got to shoot him.
I've got to shoot him!
Finally. let's bring today's
guest of honor up to the stage!
- He is vital to the Bavarian economy
- Watch closely!
- And has been a tremendous influence
- This is how you shoot a gun.
In developing the EU's economy.
By donating such an enormous
collection to our school'
he has done Bavaria
a great cultural service.
I am proud to introduce
him to you now.
Ladies and gentlemen'
I give you Hans Georg Schuwald!
With a gun,
you have to shoot it like this.
People have gathered here
in great numbers.
It's a great success.
Mr. Schuwald is really popular.
He sure is.
By donating such an enormous
collection to our school'
he has done Bavaria
a great cultural service.
I am proud to introduce
him to you now.
Ladies and gentlemen'
I give you Hans Georg Schuwald!
Your target is me, isn't it?
A lot of people came.
They all came
crawling here for you.
So that's it...
How could you?
Whoa.
Don't make any noise!
Watch quietly.
Got it?
Everyone' listen to me.
I want you to stay quiet.
And stay calm.
I'm blind. I don't know how many
people have gathered here.
Don't move all at once!
That's right. Stay right there.
Watch me at work.
Get out of here.
Slowly. and in a single file.
What's this?
What's going on?
It's over there, too!
Is it a short?!
It's a fire!
Get me a fire extinguisher.
Quickly!
What's the meaning of this?!
It's my job to shoot Schuwald!
What's with this fire?
I see! You changed your mind,
didn't you, Johan? This is better!
Much better!
They're like ants. Everyone is
running away from the fire like ants!
Amazing!
You're amazing, Johan!
You're amazing!
Come and watch...
The books...
The books are burning!
Everyone is running
all over the place
without a thought for anyone else
and they are piling up on one another.
Can you feel it?
This fear...
I have to shoot him.
You can't do it.
You're just a doctor.
You can only give life.
Taking lives is my job.
You can't do it.