What's this?
What's going on?
It's over there, too!
Is it a short?!
It's a fire!
Get me a fire extinguisher.
Quickly!
What's the meaning of this?!
It's my job to shoot Schuwald!
What's with this fire?
I see! You changed your mind,
didn't you, Johan? This is better!
Much better!
They're like ants.
Everyone is running away
from the fire like ants!
Amazing! You're amazing, Johan!
You're amazing!
Come and watch.
The books...
The books are burning!
Everyone is running
all over the place
without a thought for anyone else
and they are piling up on one another.
Can you feel it?
This fear...
Two paths will open up to you
depending on whether or not
you can shoot your first target.
That will determine if you'll
be able to use a gun or not.
Have you been taught
how to shoot?
No.
So you have your
own shooting style?
No.
I've never shot a gun before.
Not even once?
That's right.
Be sure to pull the trigger twice!
Your chances of finishing the job
rise drastically!
If you can't do that...
don't expect to live!
I have to shoot him.
You can't do it.
You're just a doctor.
You can only give life.
Taking lives is my job.
You can't do it.
Be sure to pull the trigger twice.
I didn't get hit anywhere.
My trembling has stopped...
Johan...
The smoke's in the way.
Quick...I've got to hurry.
I'm not letting him get away!
I'm not...
D-Don't push.
Help us!
This side is no good.
Open up. Open up.
Please calm down!
Everyone, act calmly!
Follow the directions of
the security guards and get in line.
I-It's no good!
All the doors have been locked.
What?
A-Anyway,
take Schuwald with you!
Yes, sir!
Have you found an escape route?
Where do you plan on taking
Mr. Schuwald in this sea of fire?
Break down the door!
Yes!
- Yes!
Many books are burning.
The flames are consuming everything.
Is this all you wanted to do?
Are you satisfied telling me
about this hellish scene
in the same way that
you read to me?!
Your goal...
Wasn't it to become me?
I gave that up.
Something else
popped into my head.
You're not afraid, are you?
Where did you come from?
Who are you?
Can you see me?
You can barely see,
but if I get this close to you...
What can you see in my eyes?
I was born in a village
straight out of a fairytale
Many people were dead.
I held hands with my other self
as I walked there.
It seemed like we were
the only two people in the world.
We didn't have a name.
Hey lady!
Y-You're...
Dieter...do you know
this young lady?
It's a fire.
Karl.. .there are important documents
I want you to fetch.
Go fetch them from the mansion.
They're on the desk in my study
This, huh?
Mom...
Th-This is...
"investigative report concerning
the death of Margot Langer."
"Herflich Detective Services..."
"Margot Langer, whose
real name was Helenka Novakova' "
"was born in Prague' Czechoslovakia
on August 12' 1955."
"In 1970' at the age 15' "
"she illegally entered what was then
called the Federal Republic of Germany."
"In Munich'
she became a high-class call girl' "
"with a clientele consisting mainly
of politicians and businessmen."
"Her name was a secret in high society
but she became famous."
"Our client' Hans Georg Schuwald'
was one of her clients."
Dad... You were still
investigating Mom...
"At age 22'
she bore Mr. Schuwald's son."
"That boy's name was...Karl."
Listen' Karl.
Listen well to what
your mother has to say!
Take this money and
ride the train at Platform 5.
What about you' Mom?
I told you that
I can't go with you.
I'll stay with you.
No!
You'll be put in the orphanage'
if you stay with me!
You'll be called a prostitute's child
if you stay here.
Now' quickly.
What about Dad?
- Huh?
She said that
he abandoned me.
You weren't abandoned!
I don't hate him.
Mom!
Her son was passed around
to many foster parents.
He had many experiences.
He even had some
wonderful foster parents.
But he was alone...
always alone.
I guess they wouldn't
put that anywhere.
"Margot Langer became one of
Germany's most exclusive call girls."
"She retired in 1992."
"Furthermore' are rumors that
Langer was conducting an affair with"
"the president of an underground bank
right before her retirement."
"However, this has
not been confirmed."
"Moreover, this underground bank
laundered money for"
"Germany's black-market companies
for five years from 1991."
"Money launderer" is the term for
an organization that is"
"in the business of taking illegal funds
and turning them into legal funds."
"During her retirement' Margot Langer
lived in Offenbach' Hesse."
"This is a picture of the apartment
she lived in at that time."
"She roomed with a boy of about 18.
Their relationship is a mystery "
"On November 2' 1996' Margot Langer
was found dead on Heide Street."
"According to police files' her death
was the work of a phantom killer."
"The culprit has not
been prosecuted."
Mom...
"Margot Langer sent a letter to
a friend three months before her death."
"We obtained the letter and have
attached a copy to this report."
This is...
Mom's handwriting...
"I have quit my job and am now
living a very peaceful life."
"In this peace' I think about my son'
whom I am separated from..."
"And the friend whom I crossed
the Czechoslovakian border with."
"My friend was caught at the border
and forced to return to Prague."
"Later, I heard that she had twins
and is living happily."
"Recently I got to know a boy
who is the same age as my son."
"He looks exactly like my friend
from Czechoslovakia."
"When he's around'
it feels as if my son is around."
"I'm sure he's grown
splendidly as well."
"I'm sure he's living
happily somewhere..."
"That's what I believe."
It's all right, Mom.
I'm no longer alone.
Dad wanted me to read this letter.
I finally understand what Mom meant
when she said that she didn't hate Dad.
It's all right, Mom. I'm...
This is terrible!
All the doors have been locked!
Dieter, did you contact
the fire station?!
I already did that!
Crap!
What is the world's
going on in this library?!
Help us.
- Get us out!
Get away from the door!
It's opened, it's opened!
Don't rush. One at a time!
Slowly!
Form a line and get out
in an orderly fashion!
Women and the elderly first!
Thank you.
How can we ever thank you?
Two more shots...
Hey...wait!
Hey you!
Johan!
Don't!
Dr. Tenma, you must not shoot!
Nina!
D-Don't...Nina.
Don't!
Crap!
Don't shoot.
You mustn't shoot!
Nina!