There are five dead and
thirty-four injured in the fire
at the University of Munich's Friedrich
Emmanuel Campus Library.
A grueling search for the missing
is now underway
We've interviewed some of those
who have been rescued.
Let's take a look.
I-I just suddenly found myself
in a sea of fire...
I couldn't breathe
because of the smoke.
I thought it was all over.
Someone saved us!
Yes. It was an Asian man.
Is he all right? He shot the hinges
off the door to get it open.
If he hadn't been here'
a lot of people would have died.
The police have confirmed
that the fire was arson'
started with kerosene
and gasoline.
And have promised do their best to
find the arsonist as swiftly as possible.
It's completely burned.
"Humanity's wisdom"
or "treasures" they may be,
but once books have been burnt,
they're gone for good.
Did you find any fingerprints
on the sniper rife we found?
It survived the fire, but I don't know
if we'll get any fingerprints from it.
It's definitely a Mauser SR 93,
the same type of rifle that was
purchased by a Japanese man,
whom we believe to be Tenma.
It'll be difficult to find any evidence
of the perpetrator on it
when it's burnt like this.
There's no such thing as
a crime scene without any evidence.
Huh?
Here's a cuff link.
Send it to the lab.
Okay.
There was someone here.
No one can be anywhere
without leaving a trace.
If there was such a person,
he's not human.
Then in the event that
there wasn't any trace of him,
what would that make him?
A demon.
No such thing exists, so there
isn't a culprit we can't arrest!
Can I see Schuwald?
Oh... He's in
the intensive care unit.
His burns aren't that severe,
but because of his age,
the doctors won't allow him any visitors.
We're going there.
Huh?!
You're being very troublesome, sir!
I cannot permit you to see him!
He's conscious, isn't he?
I'll leave after a few minutes.
Mr. Schuwald is suffering
from severe shock.
He needs absolute quiet.
Who's he?
That's Mr. Schuwald's son.
I'm sorry that such a terrible thing
has happened to your father.
I'm Lunge of the BKA.
Umm... I've already asked
the police, but...
There's someone I want to find.
Who's that?
The person who tried to
assassinate your father.
You really don't know him?
I don't know this man.
But it might be him.
Him?
That's right.
That's what I wanted to say!
Please find Johan Liebert!
Johan...Liebert...
Johan attended the ceremony
at the library with my father.
But I've searched everywhere,
and I can't find him!
Johan...
Johan Liebert...
All right.
I'll order a search immediately.
This is the room
that Johan Liebert rented.
He moved out two weeks ago.
His name wasn't in
the Law Department register.
He's a fake student.
Did you contact his parents
in Offenbach?
Well, that was also a dead end.
Apparently, they didn't associate
much with their neighbors.
At the very least, shall we
collect fingerprints from this room?
We probably won't get anything.
Huh?
No data to input.
This the first time I've seen a room
so devoid of human evidence.
Okay.
I am Johan.
I am Johan Liebert.
Who am I?
I was here.
But I don't exist.
Is he a demon?
Thank goodness, Nina.
You only have light injuries.
Sorry for worrying you, Lotte.
That's right. I was really worried!
They were rescuing people.
But I didn't see you.
I was worried about
what happened to you.
But it's amazing you got out of
that fire with just these wounds.
The firefighter was also surprised.
That's because I was saved.
You were saved? You were
the last person to come out of there.
A Japanese man.
Do you know whether
a Japanese doctor
was among the survivors
at any of the hospitals?
There were several Japanese people
but they were all businessmen.
That's impossible.
Huh?!
When I was trapped
under that curtain, he...
Nina!
He was definitely there.
Right before the fire started,
you told everyone attending
the ceremony to get out.
Why did you do that?
You sensed something beforehand.
Am I right, Mr. Schuwald?
Umm...
You should leave it at that.
Also, do you know this man?
Can you see it if I put it
this close to your face?
This is the man who
tried to assassinate you.
There are witnesses who
saw him at the library.
But according to the witnesses,
this man was trying to save people.
That's enough, isn't it?
Please stop this.
Please contact me if you
remember something.
One more thing.
Do you know where your secretary,
Johan Liebert, went?
Please leave already!
It seems he's gone
completely senile.
Well, it can't be helped,
when you see something that terrifying.
And at his age...
This is the end of the Vampire of Bavaria,
the emperor of the business world.
No.
Huh?
Those were the eyes of a man
who understood everything.
Okay.
Let's question other witnesses.
Do you have a list of the victims?
Oh, yes.
But what does this mean?
We have testimonies that the person we
believe to be Tenma was saving people.
Could this also be
multiple personality disorder?
Nina...
Nina Fortner.
What about her?
If you're looking
for Nina Fortner,
she checked out of
the hospital this morning.
Her address in
the police register is fictitious.
What does
the hospital register say?
Oh, yes. I'll look it up.
Nina Fortner...
That's the name of the daughter
of the Fortner couple
that was killed in Heidelberg...
Her whereabouts are unknown.
Thank you for telling me about
such a painful experience.
It completely matches Tenma's story
of the past ten years.
Tenma?!
That's right. He followed a string
of events that led him here.
And he immediately
left to kill Johan.
That day,
I went to the library because
I thought that Tenma was going to
carry out his assassination plot.
But there was that fire.
I don't even know if Tenma was there,
let alone Johan.
Listen, Nina.
Forget about chasing Johan already.
He's not someone you can handle.
Sure, the police
aren't very helpful,
but we should sit back and
take our time to fight this.
The truth will be
revealed in time.
It's all right. We're with you.
You must be tired.
Stay here for a while.
He was there.
Huh?
He was there in the library.
Tenma was there.
You've got to eat something.
Thank you, Dieter.
The bread is a kaisersemmel.
It has roasted ham and
gouda cheese in it.
It's Tenma's favorite.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Really?
Yes. I feel energized whenever
I eat something delicious.
Tenma always
used to say that, too.
I want to see him.
I want to see Tenma.
Yeah.
We're going to enter
a good season soon.
Oh yeah.
When you get better,
why don't we take a trip?
How about Asia?
I think it would be a good
change of atmosphere.
Rest a bit longer.
Dad, you've been through
more than enough.
Bridge.
Huh?
Three...
What is it?
What are you trying to say?
Three...frogs...
Huh?
His eyes...
Eyes?
Hell was reflected in his eyes...
There was hell reflected in
a living person's eyes...
Karl.
Yes?
There's something I want you
to tell a certain man.
Y-Yes.
There's a man
waiting in Dresden.
Dresden?
What should I tell him?
Okay.
Y-You want me to tell that to
that man in Dresden, right?
Sh-Should I go immediately?
All right.
I'll go immediately.
Karl...
Your mother... Your mother
hated me, didn't she?
No. She didn't hate you.
Karl...
Will you stay with me always
when you return from Dresden?
Yes.
I'm afraid.
Afraid? Of what?
I don't really know.
But I'm very afraid.
Remember what it is.
There's no need to get anxious.
Slowly...
A village straight
out of a fairytale...
A village out of fairytale?
Where was it?
That thing you felt when
you saw this picture book...
Tell me anything that
pops into your head.
Dr. Gillen...
No, just a little more.
Please stop!
Three...
Three frogs...
Frogs?
What are you talking about?
A picture...
Is that picture in the picture book
that made Johan faint?
There weren't any frogs
in that picture book.
Where did you see them?
That's enough.
Let's leave it at that for today.
Okay.
It was a mistake to trust
that BKA detective Lunge.
Yes. I think we should
change our plan.
From now on, whenever we
bring evidence to the police,
we must negotiate directly
with the upper divisions.
We've also got to take time to hit them
with absolutely corroborative data.
Take time? How much time?
Right now, our information on Johan
is vague and unimpressive.
Johan was Schuwald's secretary.
Schuwald might have
some information.
But he won't see
anyone right now.
What about his son Karl?
Well, he went somewhere
two days ago.
I haven't been able
to contact him.
It's not certain, but some witnesses say
that an Asian man was saving people.
But if Tenma's fingerprints are on
the sniper rifle found at the scene...
those testimonies mean nothing.
How long do we have to wait?
We don't have time!
By the time the truth is revealed
and the police move...
By that time,
Tenma will already be...
Nina...
S-Sorry.
Nina, I understand how you feel.
As I told you earlier,
I lost my dear friend Richard to this case.
He had a bright future.
But Johan cut his future short!
I'm not retreating! Never!
Now, let's eat.
Three frogs...
A village straight
out of a fairytale...
I got it.
Dieter...
I'm going, too.
What are you saying?
You can't!
You stay here, got it?
Tell Dr. Reichwein I said thank you.
See you later.
Dieter!
I want to see him.
I want to see Tenma!
The third day also
wasn't any good.
He told me to wait at the public square
in front of the station,
but this place is just too big.
Dad, it doesn't look like
I'll meet the man you talked about.
Karl...
You're Karl, aren't you?
Y-You're...
The man who was planning
to assassinate your father...
Is that what the police said?
Y-Yes.
I've been watching you from
a building for three days.
The police don't seem
to be following you.
Can you tell me the message?
Get a hold of yourself!
We're almost out of here.
Get out of here quickly!
The police are coming.
B-But...
Dresden... Wait at the public square
in front of the station.
My son Karl
will have message.
Give me the message, quickly.
Here...
edok Bridge... Three frogs?
And my father also said,
"If the monster you're
chasing is a twin..."
The mother of the twins
is still alive in Prague.