Get out of here quickly!
The police are coming.
B-But...
Dresden... Wait at the public square
in front of the station.
Give me the message. Quickly.
Here...
edok Bridge... Three frogs?
And my father also said,
"If the monster you're
chasing is a twin..."
The mother of the twins
is still alive in Prague.
There!
Give it back!
Hey, here you go!
Nice!
There it goes.
Stop.
Give it back!
Pass it to me!
How is it going Mr. Grimmer?
Did you find the data
you were looking for?
The school's structure
has completely changed
since the reunification of
East and West Germany.
We don't have any earlier data.
Well, thank you for your time,
Principal Garbrecht.
It's unusual to have retained
this much data.
When the Berlin Wall fell,
most of East Germany's
unsavory data disappeared.
But...
I am certain that children were abused
in East Germany's orphanages.
I just can't find any
information to prove it.
I can imagine.
East German orphanages
were usually managed by
the Ministry of Public Health
and Welfare.
But there were problems when
the children's parents were
Criminals, anti-government protesters,
spies, defectors to the west,
or those who were caught
trying to cross the border.
The orphanages where
these children were kept
were managed by the infamous
Internal Affairs Ministry.
No one knows how much abuse and
inhumane personality corrections
those children endured there.
I've been trying to gather
as much information as I can
so that I can find out exactly
what happened there.
Exactly what, huh? I see.
That's a tedious investigation.
Most of those involved have
either passed away or kept silent.
That's right. Even Mr. Schnurr,
the instructor here...
Mr. Schnurr?
He was a teacher at
East Germany's 62 Kinderheim.
I asked him for an interview,
but he refused.
You should be careful.
There is the possibility that Mr. Schnurr
abused children while in East Germany.
Oh! Is it all right if
I make copies of this data?
Y-Yes, go right ahead.
Mr. Grimmer, you're really a journalist
from West Germany, aren't you?
No. I'm from this side.
I was a reporter for
a newspaper in Leipzig.
Oh... I never expected a civil libertarian
like you to be from the East.
Well...
During that time, I flew around the world
as a special overseas correspondent.
They were missions given
to me by the government.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I was a spy.
Heave!
That's a big bag you're carrying.
It's packed with data I've collected
from around East Germany.
I'm looking forward to
reading a good article.
So where are you going now?
To Prague, in the Czech Republic.
Thank you for your help, Director.
You were treated
pretty badly back there.
Did they end up
taking your shoes?
Don't cry.
People can live without shoes.
We were born barefoot.
But...
Those who pick on people
by taking their shoes...are terrible!
There's no need to cry over what
those terrible guys have done to you.
See you later.
Were they so big that
they were an inconvenience?
Umm... Excuse me.
Huh?
Do you have a second?
Okay. What's wrong?
Well... I have a problem.
My bag with my passport was stolen.
Your passport? That's bad.
It is. I was going to see
my younger sister in Vienna.
Yesterday, I received word
that she had collapsed.
Collapsed?
You should go quickly!
You should go to the police.
Oh, I-I already did that.
Actually, right now...my sister doesn't
have any money for a doctor.
Oh... That's terrible.
My bag also had my wallet in it.
Oh...
I can't go, but my sister will
be all right if I send money.
But I can't even do that.
How much do you need?
Oh...you don't need to!
I don't need too much money!
I just need money to
pay for a doctor to see her.
I can only give this much.
Th-Thank you. Danke schön!
I'll pay you back.
Write your address here.
No, that's all right.
If it will help your sister get better.
Thank you! God bless you!
Take care of your sister!
How could you
give money to him?
Huh?
He was lying!
Lying?
He's always waiting in front of
the train station for a sucker.
Don't be fooled by those types.
I was fooled?
The express train to Prague will be
departing from track seven at 3..15.
Huh?
Oh. Thank you for helping me.
No problem.
Thank you for earlier.
Is it all right if I sit here?
S-Sure.
Where are you going?
To Prague.
You're Japanese...aren't you?
Huh?
Konnichiwa.
Domo.
I've been to Japan before.
Okay...
I wonder how many
years it's been...
It was 1982, so...
Oh yeah,
I went to Akihabara.
I ordered a lot of wire taps and
other high-tech gadgets.
Also, this song was popular.
Um...
Kita no...
Hakaba doori na wa...
Huh? That's not right.
Kita no...
Sakaba doori ni wa...
Yeah, that's it!
Kita no...
Sakabadoori ni wa...
And there were robots.
My son would have been happy if
I had brought back a plastic model kit.
Where's your son now?
Huh? Oh...
He died.
Entry inspection.
Present your passports.
Oh...okay.
Danke schön.
The Elbe River.
How's the trout fishing
this year?
Not very good.
I see. Last year,
I caught one this big.
That would be
impossible this year.
Danke schön.
He knows you have
a fake passport.
You should run away,
Dr. Tenma.
H-How do you know me?
Never mind that.
The border police realized
that your passport is a fake.
They're coming.
You should get out
of here quick, Dr. Tenma.
Hey, you!
We want to pass.
Oh... S-Sorry.
My bag is too big and got caught.
I can't move.
What are you doing?!
Whoa! Don't be rough!
What's in here?!
Important things.
Ow! Ah, I got loose!
Do you know where
the other man went?
Huh?
There was an Asian man
with you in this room.
Who knows?
He probably went to the dining car.
Hey, check the next car!
Yes, sir!
This is passenger car two.
Emergency!
An Asian passenger was
using a fake passport!
Oh!
What's wrong?
- Hey!
Stop this train immediately!
Very good. Very good!
They aren't chasing us this way.
The train stopped,
so I got off.
Oh... I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Grimmer.
If you like, I can show you
the way to the border, Dr. Tenma.
I'm familiar with this area.
I come here often to fish.
Climbing this mountain
is a bit rough.
But I can see familiar sights.
Why did you help me?
Huh?
Oh... I worked at a newspaper
company in East Germany.
Right now,
I'm just a freelance journalist.
I read some articles on you.
I was interested in you.
False accusations were a part of
everyday life in East Germany.
Political prisoners falsely charged...
Accused murderers who aren't guilty...
Because of that, I can tell
who's really guilty or innocent.
You're innocent.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Could you please stop
calling me doctor?
Huh? You're a brilliant neurosurgeon,
aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
I'm no longer a doctor!
What do you think?
It's a nice view, isn't it?
We can tell if anyone's
coming after us from here.
Now then.
Let's take a bit of a break here.
Would you like a sandwich?
I also have wine!
And delicious cheese.
No thank you. Umm...
I don't have time.
The sun is still high.
It's better to cross the border
when it's dark.
Picnics are fun aren't they?
It nice to do this every so often,
right Dr. Tenma?
Delicious food and
an amazing view.
This is when I can feel
the pleasures of living.
I respect doctors like you.
Journalists like me can make people
happy to be alive by writing good articles.
But you can provide
people with life itself.
I...
I shot a man.
Last month in Munich,
I shot a man for the first time.
He probably died.
Until then, I couldn't aim because
my hands would tremble.
But once I shot him...
my hands stopped trembling.
And now I have to
shoot another man.
I'm...no longer a doctor.
Whenever I go
to the Elbe River,
I think about how I would have
wanted to fish with my son here.
Your dead son...
You can catch trout this big.
He died without knowing
the pleasures of fishing.
He would have been saved if
a doctor like you had been by his side.
But really, you can
catch trout this big!
Beyond that mountain
is the Czech border.
Past there, when you leave the forest
path, you might be able to get a car.
I'm going back to
the station from here.
Thank you.
You were a real help, Mr. Grimmer.
I wish you the best of luck,
Dr. Tenma.
If we meet again,
let's have a picnic.
Dr. Tenma!
Everyone has their sins.
They don't go away.
But you must do,
what you must do.
Wonderful...
Well, this is beautiful.
It's the first time
I've come here,
but at night, Prague looks like
a village out of a fairytale.
Excuse me...
Is it all right if I sit here?
Yeah.
I'm completely
taken by this town.
You're Mr. Pedrov, right?
You bought Russian citizenship
and are currently living here
in the Czech Republic.
I have some things
I want to ask you.
Will you help me,
Mr. Pedrov?
No, your real name
is Reinhart Biermann.
There was a special orphanage
in East Berlin, wasn't there?
It was an experimental lab where
scientific personality corrections
were performed on children.
511 Kinderheim
You were the director there.
You should know everything,
since you were the director.
What were you trying to
achieve in East Berlin?
At 511 Kinderheim...