Mr. Pedrov...
No, your real name
is Reinhart Biermann.
There was a special orphanage
in East Berlin, wasn't there?
It was an experiment lab where
scientific personality corrections
were performed on children.
511 Kinderheim.
You were the director there.
You should know everything,
since you were the director.
What were you trying to
achieve in East Berlin?
At 511 Kinderheim...
Wait!
Wait a moment, Mr. Pedrov.
You were a psychologist
and a psychiatrist.
When you were with
the Internal Affairs Ministry,
you specialized in scientific
personality programming.
In other words, brainwashing.
That doesn't sit right with me.
Why would
a brainwashing specialist
be appointed director of
an ordinary orphanage?
If they wanted to raise children,
there were people who
were more suitable, right?
Leave.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
Leave.
Where did you hide the results of
the 511 Kinderheim experiments?
I've heard rumors.
When the Berlin Wall
was destroyed,
a countless number of
secret documents disappeared.
There's a theory that they were sent to
the Soviet Union via rail to Romania.
Unfortunately, there was a revolution
and the Ceaușescu government fell.
Supposedly,
the documents were lost.
But I don't think that the data
concerning 511 was lost.
Why?
Because you're a scholar.
A scholar's research reports and data
are more important to him than his life.
You wouldn't easily let go of
something that important, would you?
I'd like to see that data.
I know nothing.
What were you trying to do
at 511 Kinderheim?
I know nothing!
Was your experiment
a success?
Did you enjoy using humans
as your guinea pigs?
Your experiment failed,
didn't it?
In 1985, 511 Kinderheim
burned down.
According to rumors, the children of
the orphanage killed each other.
I was no longer
director at that time.
It doesn't involve me.
I see... You escaped death.
The director who succeeded you
was killed first in the riot.
That wouldn't have happened
if I had been there.
My experiment was a success.
Oh?
So are you saying that the experiment
was going well while you were director?
Ah...
That means that even though
all the 511 Kinderheim data
was lost during the riot,
the experiment data from your time
as director still remains.
You're treading on
dangerous territory.
Who knows what'll
happen to you?
Was that a threat?
I'm not afraid.
Go away.
No. I'll follow you
until I get the truth.
Go away!
Don't come near me again!
Disappear!
Grandpa!
We came for you because you
were taking so long to come home.
Who is that man?
O-Oh, it's nothing.
Let's go home.
Leave this case alone.
A man who has committed
atrocities against children
is enjoying the remainder of his years
surrounded by his grandchildren.
Yes?
Who is it?
You have a package
from Mr. Pedrov.
Pedrov?
Hold on a second.
Corner rooms with bad views like
this one are convenient at times like this.
Well... I had a close call
this morning.
Strange men came to my hotel.
Are those your grandchildren?
A life free of worldly cares
is wonderful, isn't it?
Back in those days, when I was working
for a newspaper in East Germany,
I never would have dreamt that
I'd be living like I am now.
I'm a freelance journalist.
Free!
That was unimaginable
in a socialist country.
Freedom is good.
I've been following you.
I've been following you
since you left your house.
You have a nice house.
I bet it's got big rooms.
Rent is expensive, isn't it?
When it's cloudy,
you spend your time at cafés
and take walks with
your grandchildren.
You can maintain this
lifestyle without working.
Where are you
getting the money?
What did you sell? Did you sell
the data of your failed experiment?
For a high price?
It was a success.
All the more reason why
it would fetch a high price.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone already.
My, my...
He's taking his grandchildren to movies
and eating chocolate parfaits at cafés.
Different children again.
One... Two...
Three... Four...
Five... Six...
It can't be...
Hi... This is Mr. Pedrov's house, isn't it?
May I come in?
Hi!
This is terrible.
He's doing it again.
He's trying to repeat
the same experiment.
This is terrible.
He's trying to repeat the experiment.
There's a red light district
on the German border.
These children were born there.
Some on them were abandoned
because of the poverty
that stemmed from
the Berlin Wall falling.
You gathered these children
and are continuing
your 511 Kinderheim experiment.
Oh? Mr. Pedrov,
do you have a guest?
Yes. Don't mind him.
He's going home now.
Will knedlíky be fine
for tonight's dinner?
Yeah. Everyone loves
your knedlíky Mrs. Anna.
The continuation of
the 511 Kinderheim experiment, huh?
I tell you again,
that experiment was a success.
There's no need to continue it.
What do you mean
it was a success?
It means that the educational
program I created
produced wonderful
personalities.
Education?
What part of that
was education?!
That was human
experimentation!
Think hard.
What is education?
Isn't education supposed to create
people who are needed in society?
What kind of education is needed
to create such a person?
Education is an experiment.
511 Kinderheim...
An advanced educational system
was established there.
You did such horrible things.
How can you say that?
Horrible things?
Yeah! Think about what
you did to those children!
Think about what horrible
things you've done!
You're just a freelancer.
Don't act as if you know anything
with your surface data!
What's with that look?
The incident that happened
at that orphanage...
Are you saying that your experiment
led the children to kill each other?
I told you! That happened after I was
removed from my position as director.
The program went awry when
an unexpected factor arose.
Unexpected factor?
Darkness.
Hate... Nihilism...
Destructive urges...
Those are factors that
people easily succumb to.
They possessed 511 Kinderheim
when a certain boy appeared.
Are you saying that
that's also not your doing?
As I'll keep on telling you...
the experiment was a success.
That's a lie. Those from 511 Kinderheim
are all missing something in common.
They can't love.
That's a very interesting observation.
Now, this is the end of our chat.
I ask you to leave.
Don't bother me anymore.
No. The Czech Republic
is a democratic country now.
I'm going to report this
to the police.
You don't have the right to run
an orphanage in this country.
This place is unauthorized.
If I report you,
you'll be arrested.
Are you trying to make a deal?
Are you offering to not report me in return
for handing over my experiment data?
Everyone...let's go!
What are you going to do?
That's it! Let's play soccer.
Soccer!
- I wanna play soccer.
All right, let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
- What are you thinking?!
As you heard...
we're going to play soccer.
Say, everyone!
Mr. Pedrov made me a deal.
But for your sake,
that deal doesn't matter.
If I report him to the police,
you'll be free.
You all want to leave that house,
don't you?
No!
- No!
You'll be freer outside!
Listen to me.
Old Man, that ball's coming to you!
You suck!
Ow...
They're...laughing...
How can they laugh with
such genuine happiness?
It can't be...
Oh, Sir!
Wait, Sir!
What a beautiful woman.
Yeah.
Mr. Pedrov,
could it be that you...
What the–?
Mr. Pedrov!
Mrs. Anna!
- What's wrong, Mrs. Anna!
Mr. Pedrov!
Get a hold of yourself!
G-Grandpa?
Grandpa.
Who shot you, Mr. Pedrov!
- Grandpa, what's wrong?
Grandpa.
That woman.
Woman?
Grandpa!
What's wrong, Grandpa?!
You're bleeding, Grandpa!
Mr. Pedrov,
could it be that you...
The key...
Huh?
The key...the card...
the pin number...
They're behind
my third drawer.
I have my experiment data
and the tape in a safe box.
Tape?
A tape of an interview...
with a certain boy.
He retells his past through
the use of hypnosis and drugs.
He's the monster that led
511 Kinderheim to destruction.
Grandpa!
Don't die, Grandpa!
What do you think
of these children?
Are they lacking anything?
Mr. Pedrov, you educated
these children in a different way
from those in 511 Kinderheim.
Hate... Nihilism...
Destructive urges...
I wanted to make a person who
wouldn't succumb to darkness.
How do you think that's done?
Love...
Honestly...
That's a new discovery.
Mr. Pedrov...it's pretty natural for
parents to give that to their children.
No. It's an experiment.
Grandpa!
- Grandpa!