The key...
Huh?
The key...the card...
the pin number...
I have my experiment data
and the tape in a safe box.
Tape?
A tape of an interview...
with a certain boy.
He's the monster that led
511 Kinderheim to destruction.
This room.
Inspector Zeman,
I brought him.
Huh?
Inspector?
Hm? Ah...
Ow, ow...
Oh, this is the person who discovered
the murder scene yesterday.
Yes. Mr. Grimmer.
Sorry for keeping you
at the station overnight.
I dropped my nail clipper
under my desk.
I'm big, so I bump
into everything.
Oh? You're pretty big, too!
Yes. I bump into everything.
I'm Zeman.
I'm in charge of this case.
I'm Grimmer.
Please have a seat.
Sorry, but I was in the middle of
cutting my nails when you came in,
so I'm going to finish them.
Oh, go right ahead.
My wife nags me.
Huh?
Whenever my nails grow out,
she doesn't like it
when I have the white part
of my nails showing.
Thanks to her,
I always cut them too deeply.
Oh...
It must have been
terrible yesterday.
Yeah.
Who would have thought
that would happen?
You're a freelance journalist,
aren't you?
Did you know of
the victim's past?
Mikhail Ivanovich Pedrov...
His real name was Reinhart Biermann.
He was German.
After the German reunification,
he was accused of various counts of
suppression of human rights,
illegal detention and child abuse.
He escaped to the Czech Republic
after the Wall fell.
The German government
upheld the charges against him,
but we let him remain free and
kept him under surveillance.
Surveillance?
That's right.
We kept an eye on him
and some troublemakers
from the former Czechoslovakian
secret police.
Secret police?
You know how terrifying
their restriction on free speech
and thought was during
the Cold War, don't you?
They also lent their support
to the terrorist activities
of extreme left organizations.
The Czech Republic
and Slovakia's split
and democratization
were done peacefully,
so they were able to go
underground without being indicted.
Pedrov was contacting them.
He was probably selling them
the information he had.
Ow!
Look at that.
I've cut my nail to the quick.
Oh yeah...
Did you see a woman?
Woman?
It seems that Pedrov's murderer
was a woman...
and quite a beautiful one.
The children said that she passed by
in front of their house.
But I...didn't notice her.
I see...
Those children...
What's going to happen to the orphans
that Mr. Pedrov was in charge of?
Right now, we're keeping
them at the station,
but, today, several are going to
be taken to various orphanages.
I see...
It must have been terrible
to get dragged into all of this.
Not at all.
Come to think of it, what kind of
information are you gathering?
Oh... Well, various things that
you talked about concerning Pedrov.
Did he tell you anything?
No. Before he could he...
All right, that's perfect!
Now my wife won't
get mad at me.
You can go now.
I'm sorry for holding you
here for such a long time.
It's all right.
Oh.
Before he died,
did Mr. Pedrov say any last words?
No.
Mirosraph... Joseph...
And where's Tomáš?
Here.
You're all here.
Now get in the van!
Hurry up. Get in!
Next!
Three to Winovlady Care Center!
Honza, Antonín, Izzy!
Here.
It'll be sad.
You all got along well
and are being pulled apart.
But even if you're apart,
you're all under the same sky!
The day will come when
you can all play soccer together.
Cheer up! Antonín,
you're the leader, aren't you?
You can still send
letters to everyone!
Take charge of that
and cheer everyone up!
Okay.
All right. That's the spirit!
Kam jdete pane?
Huh? Oh... Hotel Kafka...
Oh, wait, before that,
go to Procházka Bank.
Banka procházka
je na cestě k hotel...
Umm... I don't know Czech really well.
Could you speak in German or English?
Hezkej den źe ano?
Why are you stopping?
We're still not...
Kam to bude, pane?
Dovezte mě do průmyslový
zóny svoboda!
Hey, give me a warning if you're
going to let on any other passengers!
Dival jste se včera na
fotbalový zápas v televizi?
Ano ovšem ale byl
jsem velice zklamán.
U-Umm...
Why are we going to
the outskirts of town?
I want to go to
a hotel in the city.
The key.
Huh?
W-What are you talking about?
Ta nám ale nedělá starosti.
Neboj se!
Nepust' ho!
Well...
Are you all right?
I thought you might be in danger,
so I followed you.
Are you hurt? Are you all right?
Inspector...
They were probably agents
of the former secret police.
Did they want
anything from you?
N-No. Not really.
I don't think they'd do this
for no reason.
No, they really didn't...
Are you hiding something?
N-No.
You must know why
they did this to you.
N-No, I really don't.
Then did you already take it from
the safe deposit box at the bank?
Huh?
The tape.
The tape recording.
They're looking for the roots.
They're looking for the roots?
The monster's roots.
It would sell for a lot.
M-Monster?
We'll know when
we hear the tape.
We'll know where in the Czech Republic
the monster's mother is!
Oh, hello?
This is Inspector Zeman.
The suspect who robbed
the supermarket...
Did he give up his accomplice?
I see. Good work,
Detective Suk.
Me? I still have something
I have to do.
Yeah. I'll return to the station
in about an hour. See you later!
If you don't leave it at that,
he won't be able to talk.
Do you feel like talking now?
Where's the key?
I-I don't know what
you're talking about.
Why you...
- Now, hold on.
Mr. Grimmer, there's no reason
for you to hide it from us.
Where's the safety deposit key
you received from Pedrov?
I-I told you, I can't tell you
what I don't know.
I see. You want money.
I'll make you a deal.
How much do you want for it?
I'm a third-rate journalist, but thankfully,
I don't have to worry about not eating.
Mr. Grimmer...
This is no good.
Your nails are so long!
I told you, didn't I? My wife nags me
whenever my nails are long.
Whoa! You shouldn't move
or I'll cut your nails too deeply.
Where is it? Where's the key?
Where is it?
Even if you were to open the bank's
safe deposit box with the key
and get the tape and the data,
neither would be of use to you.
That tape is important
to their organization.
They're trying to revive
the Eastern realm!
The identity of the monster
is recorded on that tape.
They need that monster.
That monster can unite them.
The graduates of
511 Kinderheim.
The graduates of 511 Kinderheim
were raised in East Germany
to be elite communists.
He can summon them.
They are the most
select group out there.
It is said that he was able to control
all of 511 Kinderheim and destroy it.
He's the only one who
can unite that elite group.
Now, where's the key?
Elite Group?
What's so funny?!
What do you want?
I understand if you want money.
I'm a capitalist. I love money!
I just want to sell it to them
to make a lot of money.
Why are you doing this?
For social justice?
There's no reason
to go this far for that!
Who are you?
You say you're a journalist
from the East Side,
but most of those people
were intelligence agents.
At best they were spies.
Who sent you?
Are you just acting like 007?
All right.
Are you used to torture?!
You're really going to die.
This is your last chance!
Where's the key?
Do you know
the Magnificent Steiner?
It was a cartoon that aired
in West Germany in the 60's.
You could also watch it
in secret in East Berlin.
The main character was
a pretty weak guy.
But when he'd get into a predicament,
a secret friend would save him.
But that main character never realized
that this special friend was himself.
When the main character
got into a desperate situation,
he'd transform into
the terrifying Magnificent Steiner.
When he came to,
the evildoers were all defeated.
Then transform!
Transform right now!
Pour water on him.
He'll spit it out soon.
It's only a matter of time.
Who are you?
Huh?
A woman came in and...
A woman...came in and...
There was one gun shot.
One of the bodies was shot.
The other two bodies...
didn't have bullet holes.
The Magnificent Steiner...
did it again.