Where's the crime scene?!
It's down in the basement.
Who are the victims?!
Three men!
Examine the surroundings closely!
I was going to wait for Detective Kratky
to come and give orders.
I'll take responsibility!
If you find anyone suspicious,
take them into custody!
B-But what kind of people
should I look for?!
Anyone suspicious!
But...
Are you saying that you can't follow
my orders because I'm a rookie?!
Get moving!
I'm Detective Suk
of the Prague Police!
This is really terrible.
Inspector Zeman...
He was savagely
beaten to death.
You can't make out
his facial features.
If he hadn't had his police
pocketbook with him,
we probably wouldn't have
known who he was.
The bodies of two other men
are over there...
We still don't know
who they are.
One was shot in the head.
The other was beaten to death.
Just like the Inspector.
Secure the crime scene!
Oh... Detective Suk!
Umm...
What kind of person would you
consider suspicious?
Give me a break.
They're making fun of me
just because I'm a rookie!
The uniformed officers
won't take my orders!
That's because
you're so unreliable.
Yeah!
What?!
You threw up at the crime scene,
didn't you?
Why would they take orders
from such a poor detective?
Just because you admire police dramas
doesn't mean that you can do the job.
Jan, always got carried away,
even in college!
What do you know about me?
Inspector Zeman was killed.
Do you know how well he treated me?!
As a rookie,
I didn't know right from left.
But Inspector Zeman taught me
how to be a detective.
I respected Inspector Zeman
from the bottom of my heart.
I will avenge Inspector Zeman!
I'll catch his murderer myself!
U-Umm...
We start work
early tomorrow, so...
What? Hang out
with me longer.
I'm...
fighting for justice
so you can work safely!
Come on. Drink more!
Cut it out already!
You serve justice every day.
And you just get killed.
It's unbearable.
There are no rewards.
What's wrong?
The girl from the supermarket...
Huh?
I saw her twice when I went to
the supermarket after my night shift.
That girl...
I wanted to talk to her,
but I couldn't.
And now I see her here.
Hey, give it up!
She's too pretty for you.
U-Umm...
H-Hi! Do you remember me?
I-I see...
But I know you.
Oh, I'm Jan Suk.
I'm not suspicious at all.
I may not look it,
but I'm a real police detective.
No. Don't be scared
because I'm a detective.
I'm off-duty right now.
This is my personal time.
I don't think he's got a chance.
Well, let's help him for now.
Sorry for butting in!
He's depressed today.
Could you talk to him for a bit?
Something terrible happened
to a superior he admired.
He's been depressed.
Wh-Who's depressed?!
I've never met a person
as kind as he was.
I wanted to become
like Inspector Zeman.
That's why I won't
forgive his murderer.
I'll catch him.
Oh... Sorry.
I'm the only one talking.
Not at all.
You've got to try your best
for the inspector's sake
to catch his murderer.
Yeah.
Oh... I talked a lot
about myself,
but I didn't ask you
anything about yourself!
What's your name?
I don't know my real name.
W-What?
Oh. Wait a second!
I'll guess who you are.
I'm a detective.
Leave this to me!
Umm... Your name is...
I don't even know that.
There's no way that you would know it.
What I know about myself is...
Cedok Bridge...
Three frogs...
That's it.
What?
Oh!
Wait a second!
When can I see–
See? It wasn't any good!
Give up this fleeting dream!
CHECK PLACEMENT We've identified the two men
who were killed along with Inspector Zeman.
One is Čestmír Marat.
The other is Yakov Suhacek.
Both were sergeants in
the Czech secret police.
After the fall of socialism,
they did shady underground jobs.
Our analysis of the blood at
the scene of the murder revealed
blood belonging to someone other than
Inspector Zeman, Marat and Suhacek.
Blood type AB, RH positive.
Judging from the amount
of blood he left behind,
we believe that this person
was also seriously injured.
We are trying to
determine who he is.
Detective Suk!
Suk!
Y-Yes!
Why are you daydreaming?!
We lost a brilliant colleague in Zeman.
We're in a desperate situation now.
What's with your attitude?!
I...
I'm very sorry.
Anyway...
As I said at the beginning,
according to a witness,
there was a man who was
walking around the crime scene
immediately after the murder.
He was tall, thin man who
was carrying a large bag.
He looked like a traveler.
Do your best to
find out who he is!
That girl...
She won't come again,
will she?
Mr. Great Detective.
Did you find the murderer?
N-No.
How pathetic.
The murderer is walking free
while I'm just sitting here.
Inspector Zeman...
He was investigating a murder
all night the day before.
What kind of case was it?
Someone killed an old man who
was running an illegal orphanage.
They killed his maid, too.
He was questioning the man who
first discovered the scene of the crime.
Who was he?
Huh?
Who discovered
the crime scene?
Well... He seemed
like a nice man.
He was tall and thin, but he was
lugging around a heavy knapsack.
Thin... Tall... Large bag...
Could it be?!
Do you know
where that man is?
I-I think I know!
If I check at the station...
Hello?
Oh!
Good luck,
Mr. Great Detective!
Oh... Hello?
Oh, hold on a second!
Hello?
Cedok Bridge...
Three frogs!
Cedok Bridge is in
the Mikalska area of the old city.
Three frogs.
Here it is.
I can meet that girl
if I come here!
He checked out?!
When?!
Umm... Mr. Grimmer,
Mr. Grimmer...
Mr. Grimmer checked out in
the morning the day before yesterday.
There's no mistake.
The man who killed Inspector Zeman,
is the man who stayed here. Grimmer!
Crap! Why didn't I figure
this out earlier?
Inspector Zeman,
I will catch him!
I will!
Oh.
Oh?! Suk, why are you here?
Detective Chief Patella,
I'd like to ask you the same thing.
I see.
You got this far all by yourself.
Impressive.
Yeah.
But I thought I would
be the first one
to accomplish something in
the Inspector Zeman case.
If you've already
come this far...
Well, an accomplishment is
an accomplishment. Good job!
Okay.
Or so I'd like to say.
Keep this a secret!
Huh?
Why?! It's our job to catch Grimmer
as soon as possible!
This case is a little more
complicated than you think.
Huh?
Did you know
that Inspector Zeman
was assigned to
a top-secret investigation?
Inspector Zeman had
He was investigating former
Czechoslovakian secret police agents
who faked their records and
were in the Prague police force.
Former Czechoslovakian
secret police?
The two other men who were killed
were secret police agents, right?
Only a few others aside from
the chief and me know about this.
You might get yourself killed
if you inquire further!
Keep quiet about this.
Got it?
Then... Then what
should I do?
Well... Anyway, Grimmer might
come to this hotel again.
Keep watch.
Y-Yes, sir!
By the way, Suk,
did you get a girlfriend?
Huh?
When you were sitting
at your desk at the meeting,
you were daydreaming.
Sh-She's not my girlfriend!
She just goes to the bar
I visit every so often.
Is she pretty?
W-Well...
Come on!
Introduce me to her.
Which place is it?!
I can't introduce you.
But she's not your girlfriend,
is she?
W-Well that's true, but...
Suk's not coming today.
I'm surprised!
You're really something!
Who are you?
Oh, Me?! I'm Suk's superior.
My name is Patella.
He said that there's a real beauty
that comes to this bar.
He couldn't come tonight.
He's doing a stakeout.
Care to have a drink with me?
Oh... Hey, hold on.
Why not just a little?!
Hey, Suk!
Oh! Detective Janacek.
Good morning.
I heard from Patella that the girl
you're after is a real beauty!
Patella, you went to that bar?
Yeah.
Y-You didn't do anything to her,
did you?!
Now, now, Suk.
Don't get excited!
B-But Detective Chief Patella
is a notorious womanizer.
Don't worry.
She jilted me pretty quickly.
She'll be pretty tough to get
if Patella can't get her, Suk.
N-No way!
I-I...just want to talk to her.
It's fun just doing that.
What are you mumbling about?
Section Chief Farobek wants you to
go to Inspector Zeman's office.
Oh... Yes, sir!
Oh yeah.
Someone gave me these.
Do you want
a whiskey bonbon?
I don't need any!
Suk, how about one?
Oh... No thank you.
Hey, Suk!
Yes?
Don't say anything about
our tall suspect.
Yes, sir!
Inspector Zeman's desk has
pretty much been cleaned out.
All that's left are
his personal belongings.
Gather all the things here
and send them to his wife.
Yes, sir.
It's a gym locker key.
This is pretty bad!
There are a ton of
sweaty shirts and towels.
Documents?
What is this?
It's a file containing detailed histories
of all the members of the force.
Even my file is in here.
Do you know
that inspector Zeman
was assigned to
a top-secret investigation?
He was investigating former
Czechoslovakian secret police agents
who faked their records and
were in the Prague police force.
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
Why are Detective Chief Patella
and Detective Janacek's files
the only ones not here?
Yes indeed, this is an unusual
amount of money.
Y-Yes, Head Chief!
So... Suk, what do you
surmise from this?
Yes! Inspector Zeman was
performing an internal investigation.
A-As a result,
he discovered that Detective
Chief Patella and Detective Janacek
were former Czechoslovakian
secret police agents and...
It's very... It's very unfortunate,
but Inspector Zeman probably
took the money in return for
keeping quiet about the truth!
This is a serious problem.
I-It's very unfortunate.
Detective Suk...
Yes!
Don't talk about this for a while.
Yes, sir!
I'll contact you later.
Return to your normal duties.
Yes, sir!
How frustrating.
Yeah... Things have
become troublesome.
It was foolish of us to underestimate
young guys like Suk.
We haven't even settled things with
that tall guy who killed Zeman.
And another problem arises.
Should we offer money,
like we did with Zeman?
If it doesn't work,
there's only one thing to do, right?
No matter what,
I don't want any trouble
for knowingly accepting
former secret agents into the force.
We just have to
cover it up well.
Ah, I'd like to have a drink!
I have some whiskey bonbons.
Don't say that.
It's a gift from a real beauty.
Here.
What's wrong?
You look depressed.
I can't believe
anything anymore.
What's wrong?
I'll listen if you want me to.
I believed in him.
I didn't think that Inspector Zeman
would do such a thing.
What happened?
I believed in him.
Right now,
my only peace of mind...
is you.