How frustrating.
We just have to
cover it up well.
Ah, I'd like to have a drink!
I have some whiskey bonbons.
Don't say that.
It's a gift from a real beauty.
What's wrong?
You look depressed.
I can't believe
anything anymore.
I'll listen if you want me to.
I believed in him.
I didn't think that Inspector Zeman
would do such a thing.
What happened?
I believed in him.
Right now,
my only peace of mind...
is you.
An unbelievably dreadful event has
taken place in the Prague police station!
Chief Hamrik, Detective Patella
and Detective Janacek
were found fatally poisoned.
Why would their murderer want to
commit such a brazen act?
According to some rumors,
the police force has a dark connection
with the former secret police.
Will this incident be the cause
of an even bigger scandal?
Oh! Someone's coming out!
Do you know who
the murderer is?
I heard that the drug used to commit
the murder was a muscle relaxant.
Is it true that even Chief Hamrik was
involved with the secret police?
Oh... Well...
ls there a connection to
inspector Zeman's murder last week?
W-We're investigating
that at the moment.
Does that mean that
the investigative department
believes that all of
the incidents are linked?
Well... We're going to
investigate that.
I'm very sorry
He's in charge of a different case.
Don't say anything unnecessary.
Just go!
Y-Yes!
When are you going to hold
an official press conference ?!
We will have press conference
when we gather enough information.
Please wait until then.
You're taking too long
to deal with this!
Enough of this!
Is this another questioning?
I'm very sorry.
I was told by my superiors to investigate
this case from the bottom up.
I've already finished
questioning the children
who were taken to
the other orphanages.
Think of the children.
Mr. Pedrov raised them
as if he were their father.
They saw him and his maid die
right before their eyes.
Even now, some of them
cry at night.
I want to make them forget
that as soon as possible.
But that's not something
one can forget.
Someone that they loved
was killed.
15 minutes with each child.
Don't ask questions that
are too detailed. Got it?!
Yes. It was fun living there.
Mr. Pedrov and Mrs. Anna
were really nice people.
I see... I'd like to talk to you
about the day of the murder.
Mr. Grimmer came that day.
Did he come before?
No. That was the first time.
Why did he come?
I don't know.
Was Mr. Grimmer friendly
with Mr. Pedrov?
Hmm... They didn't seem
very friendly, but...
But?
They were talking about something
difficult to understand.
You know a little German, don't you?
What did they talk about?
They said that this place
was "unauthorized"...
and "report" to the "police."
Did Mr. Grimmer say that?
Yeah.
He also said "education" or something
and "experiment."
"Experiment"...
Anything else?
Also...
You don't have to remember
if you don't want to, Honza.
A-Also "511 Kinderheim!"
511 Kinderheim?
Do you know where that is?
I don't know!
Do you?
There's no such place in
the Czech Republic.
Hmm...
Now, about Mr. Grimmer...
What kind of person was he?
He was really nice.
You too, huh, Izzy?
We played soccer together!
He wasn't really good.
But Mr. Grimmer looked like
he was having fun.
His header was so bad!
He fell on his butt!
He's probably as bad as Honza. Also...
You were the leader at that orphanage,
weren't you, Antonio?
I'm not really the leader.
I'm just a little older than everyone else.
Now about that day...
Is it about Mr. Grimmer?
Huh?!
I heard that Honza and Izzy
were asked about Mr. Grimmer.
Y-Yeah. And?
He's a nice person.
Is Mr. Grimmer a suspect?
No...I'm not really...
Mr. Grimmer isn't the murderer.
Mr. Pedrov and Mrs. Anna were killed
when we got back from playing soccer.
I told this to
the police already, but...
I saw a beautiful blonde woman
come out of our house.
Are you going to arrest him?
Who?
Mr. Grimmer.
No. That hasn't
been decided yet.
I'm going to meet him.
I promised him! We've decided
where we're going to meet.
Can you tell me where that is?
Okay.
Is it all right?
I might arrest him.
Well, there's no way
that he'd murder anyone!
Hey!
- Hey!
It's been a while.
How've you been?
Great.
You haven't been crying,
have you?
He's wet his bed twice!
I wet my bed until I was
much older than you!
What?
- What?
Antonio, do you have
the thing I gave you?
Thank you.
I'm glad you held on to it!
This is something important that
your grandfather left behind.
Now then...
I don't have much time.
Everyone, take care!
Let's play soccer,
Mr. Grimmer!
Oh. Sorry.
I really don't have the time.
Let me introduce you!
These are our new friends!
All right! I'll play just a little!
All right!
- All right!
Go! There's a chance.
Pass it to me!
They took it!
That dribbling isn't
good enough!
Try harder as a defender!
You got me there.
Here I go.
There!
You're Mr. Grimmer,
aren't you?
Did you come to arrest me?
You're in front of children.
Don't wave around a gun.
Toss me your gun.
I don't have a gun.
Did you throw it away?
I've never walked
around with a gun.
Did you kill Inspector Zeman?
I don't know.
Because I was half-dead
from being tortured.
Your nails...
I didn't shoot the gun.
I might have killed the other two.
But I don't remember.
Mr. Grimmer!
Why are you resting?! We don't have
enough members on our team!
Give me a break!
I'm worn out.
I asked the children to
invite you to play soccer.
I've been watching you.
So what do you think?
Am I the murderer?
I don't know.
Many people betrayed me
these past few days.
I don't know what to
believe in anymore.
You can only
believe in yourself.
In the end, you're all
that you can believe in.
Aren't you going to arrest me?
Can you promise me
that you won't run away?
Where are you staying right now?
Pavla Hotel, room 302...
Come by when you're sure
I'm the murderer.
I'll let you hold on to that.
I think it's the cause of
all these incidents.
It's the key to a safe deposit box.
This sign? It's pretty old.
It was the sign for
a pub 200 years ago.
It's been up even though
the pub is gone.
It's completely faded,
but it's a landmark even now.
There have been wars and disasters.
It's amazing it survived.
There was even a fire
about a decade ago.
A fire?
Yeah. A woman with a child moved
into the second floor here.
She was a beautiful woman,
but she was kind of somber.
She hardly ever went out.
It seems she was using an alias.
One day, a black car
took her and her kid.
The woman was rumored
to have participated in
anti-government activities.
That sort of thing happened
often in those days.
It was a government of terror during
the final stages of communism.
It was a terrible time.
It wasn't unusual for
someone to disappear.
Did that woman have
twins with her?
No. She only had one child.
A real pretty one.
Was it a boy or a girl?
Huh? Come to think of it,
which was it?
Sometimes you can't tell
the difference when they're little.
Honestly...
Everyone was saying that taking
away the mother is one thing,
but taking away an innocent child
is too much.
That's when the fire started.
I didn't think that anyone
was in that room.
But when the fire started coming out
from there, I found the child inside.
The child was probably released,
got hungry and started the fire
to cook something to eat.
Where is the child?
I don't know where it went afterwards.
I wonder what happened to it.
What if that child
was one of the twins?
Huh?!
What if one child was taken and
the other was left in that room?
I see. That's another
way to think of it.
But why do you care
so much if they're twins?
That tall guy, Grimmer, that
you said I should check out.
I don't think he's the murderer.
I see...
Sorry for saying something
so groundless, Mr. Suk.
He's not a bad person.
I learned a lot of things
from following him.
At first, I thought this was a battle
to avenge Inspector Zeman.
I was frantic.
But as I learned more,
I discovered that Inspector Zeman,
the detective I looked up to,
was corrupt.
In the end, my head chief and two
of my superiors were poisoned.
I was shocked when I
received word of the incident.
I thought, "How far has darkness
spread throughout this world?"
Darkness?
The Czechoslovakian secret police
are behind these incidents.
They were an organization that was
under the direct supervision of
the Internal Affairs Ministry
during the former government.
They were tools of
the Soviet Union.
But they were disbanded
nearly ten years ago
during the democratic revolution.
Their leaders were put on trial,
but several of them
escaped underground.
Even now, they're planning to
take back their former power.
At least I know that much.
But why must they claim
so many victims?
Was this incident really
only their doing?!
Who knows how closely
the darkness has encroached
upon the world we live in.
I can't believe in anything.
But Mr. Grimmer told me that
I can only believe in myself.
He said that when he entrusted me
with a certain something. Sorry.
I keep talking about this.
Not at all.
I still don't know your name.
Oh... It's all right!
You don't have to tell me.
I thought that people
gained trust in each other
when they learn each other's
names and pasts.
But...I can talk so much
about anything to you.
My parents are both teachers.
But my father participated
in democratic activities,
so the authorities had
their eyes on him.
My mother broke up with
my father to protect me.
My mother was fiercely opposed to
the idea of me becoming a detective.
Why did you want to
become a detective?
My friends said why
at that bar, remember?
Could it be that you really did
watch too many detective dramas?
It was my childhood dream.
I always played detective.
Bang.
Don't laugh so much.
Come on...
So what were you
entrusted with?
Huh?
Earlier, you said that Grimmer
entrusted you with something.
Oh... It's a key to
a safe deposit box.
A safe deposit box?
It seems that something
really important is in there.
Pedrov, a German man who was
running an illegal orphanage,
was killed recently.
Okay...
Inside the safe deposit box
is the data from Pedrov's
human experiments or something.
It seems that that's the cause
of all these events.
Don't say anything.
Don't tell anyone, even the police,
anything about that!
But this isn't something
I can handle by myself.
Your mother...
Huh?
Do you know why your mother didn't
want you to become a detective?
She was worried that
something might happen to you.
I have a very bad feeling!
So don't tell anyone.
I feel the same way
about you as your mother.
Sorry.
My name...
I'll tell you my name.
Anna...
Anna Liebert.
Anna... That's a nice name.
So you are German.
See you later.
Anna...
Good evening, Mr. Tulunka
Oh... It's a nice night,
isn't it, Anna?
Oh, good evening, Anna.
Good evening, Mrs. Jalka.
A safe deposit box key...