This is the most scandalous case
we've ever had
since the founding
of the Czech police.
The three men who were killed
were virtuous men,
but they were also affiliated with
the Czechoslovakian secret police!
I'd like to believe that their deaths
have rid the Prague station
of the last of
its dark connections.
You are proud officers
of the Czech force.
I expect conscientious behavior
from all of you.
Also, as the new head chief,
I must regain our citizens' trust.
I shall introduce the five members
of the special full-time investigative team
that was dispatched here
from headquarters.
I hope to cooperate with them
and close the book on this atrocious
case as soon as possible.
You're Detective Suk, right?
Yes.
As the new head chief, I'd like to
thank you for your investigation.
T-Thank you very much.
By the way, which case are
you in charge of right now?
The case that Inspector Zeman
was investigating.
The murder of Pedrov, a man who
was running an illegal orphanage.
I see. Concentrate on
your investigation.
Yes. Excuse me.
Oh. One more thing.
The tall man who has surfaced
as Inspector Zeman's killer...
Do you know anything about him?
No. I don't know anything
about the suspect.
All right. You may leave.
Excuse me.
Jan Suk...
It's been a year since
he was assigned here.
He was close with Inspector Zeman
from the beginning.
He revealed the hidden pasts of
Detective Patella and Detective Janacek,
and talked to Chief Hamrik
right before he died.
Keep an eye on him!
Yes, sir.
Hi.
I was really glad when
you answered the phone
when I called the place
you said you were staying at.
Did you think that you
would be betrayed again?
Well...
Orange juice.
You chose a crowded meeting place,
Mr. Grimmer. Will you be all right?
All right?
The new head chief still thinks
that you killed Inspector Zeman.
Also, aren't the former Czechoslovakian
secret police also after you?
Oh. Could it be that a crowded place
is actually safer?
There's no such thing
as a safe place.
Huh?
If they're coming after me, they'll do it
at any time and at any place.
For example... They could do it from
that window with the red curtains.
Mr. Grimmer, who exactly are you?
I'm just an unsuccessful journalist.
Oh. Then why is this
happening to you?
I just got in a little too deep.
This isn't funny!
Your life is in danger.
No, it's all right.
I wanted to do this.
Suk is currently at a café
in Republic Square.
He's meeting the tall man.
It's definitely Grimmer.
Okay. Should I let him
continue for a little longer?
So this happened because you
were gathering data on Pedrov,
who conducted brainwashing
experiments on children in East Germany?
Yeah.
Before he died, Pedrov entrusted you
with a safe deposit box key.
Yeah. He also said something
about "the monster's past."
"The monster's past"?
I don't know what that means,
but it seems like there are
a lot of people who want it.
The secret police?
And a blond woman.
The children from the orphanage also
told me that right after Pedrov was killed,
they saw a beautiful blond woman
leaving their house.
Do you know who
she might be?
I don't have a clue.
Are you all right?
Huh?
You haven't told your superiors that
you've been meeting me, have you?
Is it all right to
betray the police?
I'm not really hiding it
from them.
I've decided on
my own to do this.
I plan on reporting this to my superiors
once I have finished gathering evidence.
If I can investigate this thoroughly,
I can prove your innocence.
What's wrong?
Don't look to your left yet.
Huh?
The man to the left under
the parasol reading a newspaper...
He's suspicious.
Is it the secret police?
Who knows?
Now then...
Shall we go?
Go? Go where?
You brought the safe deposit box key
I entrusted you with, didn't you?
Yes.
Don't you want to know
the identity of the monster?
Yes.
Then let's go.
Though it might be
better not knowing.
You look pale.
That woman was
just in my sight.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It was just my imagination.
Suk is on the move.
I'm going after him.
I'm Suk of the Prague police.
I called you earlier on the phone.
Please wait one moment.
Thank you for waiting.
This way. Come in.
Here are the safe deposit boxes.
Verify the contents
in that room.
A research paper
and a cassette tape...
I have a tape recorder.
Are you ready?
I'm going to play it.
Where are you?
511 Kinderheim.
A child's voice.
What's your name?
My name is.. .Johan.
What's your last name?
I'll ask you once more.
What is your last name?
My name is Otto.
My name is Hans.
My name is Thomas.
My name is...
Which is your real name?
Once upon a time, in a land far away
there lived a nameless monster.
The monster was dying
to have a name.
Is that some sort of story?
I was waiting for Anna.
Who's Anna?
I read a picture book
while I waited for Anna.
This boy was drugged
before he was questioned.
Who's your father?
I don't know.
Who's your mother?
I think she's alive.
You are a very brilliant child.
ls there anything you're afraid of?
What are you most afraid of?
Let me change the question.
Have you ever killed anyone?
Many people were dead.
It was as if Anna and I were
the only people in the world.
Where was that place ?
Let's go back.
What are you most afraid of?
The monster inside me
is getting bigger.
Munch-munch, chomp-chomp,
gobble-gobble gulp!
The thing I'm
most afraid of.. .is...
I feel sick.
I feel like throwing up.
Are you all right, Mr. Grimmer?
Yeah.
What is this tape?
Is this the identity of the monster?
I don't understand what it means.
Even if we don't understand it,
there are people who want it
more than anything in the world.
The Czechoslovakian secret police...
It doesn't matter whether we listen to it
halfway through or to the end.
There's already no turning back.
What should we do with that tape
and the research paper?
Should we leave it
in the safe deposit box?
No.
Under normal circumstances, we should
store it here as evidence, but...
You're going to hold on to it?
Then let's exit separately.
I'm the one they're after.
Oh yeah.
Give me your cell phone number
and home address.
Let's contact each other
so that we know we're safe.
I got back home safely.
I have a bad feeling.
He's just so hopeless.
A flat on Lanover Street...
What is the meaning of this?
That's what I want to ask you.
You know who we are, right?
The special investigations team
dispatched here from headquarters.
This is third-rank detective, Novak.
I'm third-rank detective, Zanda.
Why are the two of you
in my room?
How long have you
been meeting Grimmer?
Don't tell us that you don't know.
You two met at a café
in Republic Square
and went to
Prochazka Bank.
You know the man in
the picture, don't you?
Huh?
Captain Karel Lanke...
An important figure in
the Czechoslovakian secret police
who has gone underground.
I-I don't know that man.
I checked your bank account.
This month you received
a large sum of money.
What is it for?
W-What are you talking about?!
I don't know about that money!
Right now, your mother
is being hospitalized
in Krumlov National Hospital
for a serious illness, isn't she?
It seems like it would cost quite a bit
just to pay for her hospital expenses.
What are you trying to say?
After separating from your father,
your mother raised you by herself.
You seem like you care
very much for your mother.
What are you trying to say?!
We want to check your room.
Go right ahead.
I haven't done anything wrong!
Zanda, come here.
What is this?
This was in your sink cabinet.
I don't know.
I know nothing about this.
I can't say what kind of drug this is
until we analyze it back at the station.
But in the bodies
of the three victims,
we found something with
muscle relaxant mixed into it.
They were Whiskey Bonbons.
Come back with us to the station
and tell us your story.
Fine.
Investigate me all you want.
All right.
Sorry.
Before we leave,
could I just change my shirt?
All right.
Calm down. Calm down.
I haven't done anything wrong.
They'll understand if
I explain things to them.
The smell of gunpowder?
Suk!