CHECK PLACEMENT Honestly.
This has turned into an awful case!
Is there any new information?
Yes. The police said that they're going
to hold a press conference at 3 PM.
We're going directly
to the Prague station!
This is the first time in my career
that I've seen a case like this.
Have you been examining documents
there since last night?
Oh, hello. Thankfully,
I found the article I was looking for.
Ah. That's good.
Oh. Wait a second.
I'm busy right now.
Umm.. .
About Mr. X in this article...
Mr. X?
Yes. An article from
three years ago titled,
"The Truth About the Former
Czechoslovakian Secret Police"...
Oh. That's the article describing how,
after the Wall fell,
the German right-wingers and the
former Czechoslovakian secret police
suddenly extended their influence
and are behind crime syndicates now.
I wrote this one.
Really?
Could you introduce me to Mr. X,
the former Czechoslovakian secret
police agent who was interviewed?
You said that you were a special
correspondent from Japan, right?
What do you want to
find out from Mr. X?
O-Oh, well...
I was thinking of finding out
how abductions,
imprisonment and other things they
did were done here during the Cold War.
They're pretty scary.
Huh?
I risked my life to
do that interview.
They're still scary.
Thanks to them,
our world is in an uproar!
Huh?
What? You don't know about
the incident with Detective Suk?
Are you really
a special correspondent?
Well...
You said that you don't
know any Czech,
but if you're investigating
the secret police agents,
you should at least
follow the big headlines.
Here's our newspaper.
You can read German, can't you?
Suk, a young detective
from the Prague station,
ran away after shooting two detectives
from a special investigative team
that was dispatched
from the main station.
Inspector Zeman's murder is
what exposed the dark connection
between the former secret police
and the current Czech force.
Furthermore, it was Suk who revealed
that the Prague station chief
and two detectives were involved
with the secret police.
Someone conveniently
poisoned those three.
Suk was commended.
But the special investigative team
was watching over Suk.
However, Suk wound up killing the
two detectives who were watching him.
A promising elite detective...
Hm?
Once did a great deed...
What are you mumbling about?
Three superiors poisoned to death...
Whisky Bonbons... Muscle relaxant...
Johan...
Excuse me.
Is Jan Suk's mother here?
Are you with the police?
No.
Room 409.
Thank you.
Umm...
I don't think meeting her will
be of any help to you.
Are you Jan Suk's mother?
Jan?
Jan.. .you came.
No, I'm...
I'm glad you could come, Jan.
Come closer and let me
see your face, Jan.
You should lie down.
Oh...Jan.
Did you receive any phone calls
or letters from your son?
Listen... Katrina in the next room,
won't give me back my stuffed animal.
It's the precious stuffed animal
that Aunt Mary gave me.
Your son is...
Your son is innocent.
I'll be going now.
You...
Jan. .. Were you
playing there again?
You always play
detective there.
What place are
you talking about?
You might think it's a hideout,
but I know about it.
The abandoned building
on Bruno Street.
You found out about it?
Yes. I did.
See you later.
Don't get hurt.
Be back by dinner.
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there lived a nameless monster.
The monster was dying
to have a name.
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there lived a nameless monster.
I bought food and a newspaper.
You've leapt to stardom.
Do you suppose anyone has noticed
the cassette tape and research paper
from the safe deposit box
that I sent to my mother?
Who knows? Well, it's safer than
if we had them with us.
But upon reading
all these articles,
your incident is a lot
like that other incident.
"That other incident"?
It happened ten years ago
in Düsseldorf, Germany.
The director of a hospital
and two doctors
died from eating
poisoned candy.
The culprit was
a promising young surgeon.
What happened to him?
He's currently on the run,
trying to prove his innocence.
You're still all right.
You have me as your witness.
You passed by her
on the stairs of my flat.
Yeah. The blonde beauty.
Even if that woman is the true murderer,
we're finished if we can't find her!
Suk...
Are you saying that we should
just keep running around?!
Why is this happening to me?!
What did I do?
Calm down.
Are you saying that I should just
disappear off the face of the earth?!
Calm down!
Calm down! I told you to
believe in yourself, right?
I told you that, in the end,
all you can believe in is yourself.
All right. That's a good boy.
Now, let's eat.
This room...
I used to play detective
in this room when I was little.
That was the police
detective's desk.
I'm surprised that
it's remained as it was.
I gave orders to everyone from here
just like the TV dramas.
Gentlemen...
This case is difficult,
but I want you to conduct
the investigation to
the best of your abilities.
In the name of justice,
we mustn't let evil spread.
How nostalgic.
Suk!
Suk...
We're surrounded.
Get a hold of yourself, Suk!
It's dangerous near the window.
Get behind the desk!
I-I can't go on.
Get a hold of yourself!
Who shot at us?!
Was it the Czechoslovakian
secret police?
Where are they
shooting from?!
It's all right, Suk.
They missed any vital spots.
I'm going to borrow your gun.
The tape.
Suk!
Suk...
Hold on.
I'm coming for you right now!
They're missing vital spots
on purpose.
The tape.
We don't have it here!
They can see us
from the window.
Mr. Grimmer!
I'm here. I'm right here, Suk!
I'm going to save you now.
It hurts. It hurts!
All right. There, there...
It's all over.
Be quiet!
Mr. Grimmer.
Don't talk.
I-If at least you...
If at least you...escape...
Don't be foolish!
From above...
Czech. ..
What are they saying?
The tape!
It hurts!
I don't want to die.
Can you speak German?
Just a little.
What are you doing here?
W-Who are you?!
Answer my question.
What are you doing?
O-Okay.
We're already finished.
We all charged into that building.
The young detective and the thin man
have already been taken care of.
I was too late.
It's quiet.
You're that man.
The Magnificent Steiner...
Mr. Grimmer?
The Magnificent Steiner's
done it again.
Mr. Grimmer!
Hi, Doctor.
You finally came.
Save him.
He's a good guy.
Please save him.
There are a lot of
other patients as well.
What in the world is this?
It was probably me.
My other self inside me.
I'm...from 511 Kinderheim.
The Magnificent Steiner!
Hey everyone, are you gathered
around the television?!
I wonder what kind of adventures
are waiting for us today!
If you're in danger,
call out my name!
I'll come to save you
anytime, anywhere!
Steiner,
the invincible super man!
He doesn't abide by evil.
His name is the Magnificent Steiner!
I was glued to the TV when I watched
the Magnificent Steiner in action.
The main character was
a weak young man.
He'd always be cornered by
the bad guys at a critical moment.
But when he
regained consciousness,
he'd find the bad guys defeated
by the Magnificent Steiner.
Without my realizing it,
the Magnificent Steiner
started coming out for real.
He'd appear whenever I was in
danger and he'd defeat the bad guys.
All I remember about
when I was little was watching
the Magnificent Steiner on TV.
That's it.
All of my other memories
were taken away
by 511 Kinderheim.
All of them.
What nonsense. This doesn't
have anything to do with you.
All right.
I've applied minimal first aid.
Will Suk. ..
Will he be all right?
All of the bullets
passed though him.
But the wound that runs
from the auxiliary artery
to the brachial artery
is serious.
I've applied enough pressure
by hand to stop the bleeding.
This is all I can do for now.
We have to get him to
a hospital as soon as possible!
Mr. Grimmer.
You say that 511 Kinderheim doesn't
involve me. But it does involve me.
Now, let's call an ambulance.
There are three men here!
We need another ambulance.
Prepare another one
immediately!
How are the injured?!
We need to hurry! But...
What's wrong?
All of them have
received first aid!
And proper first aid at that!
Proper first aid?!
The news is on.
What are they saying?
It's in Czech, so I don't know.
But I found out the name of
the hospital where they're being kept.
Jakuba Zimy Memorial Hospital.
The police are probably
going to arrest Suk.
But he's...
He's innocent, right?
Yeah.
If I go and testify...
Dr. Tenma, why were you...
Anyway, about what
you were saying earlier...
Could you tell me
about 511 Kinderheim?
Actually, I don't really
remember it.
I can't remember.
I can only remember fragments.
A dark passage...
A stain on the ceiling...
The sound of a squeaky door...
A musty bed...
My memories become lucid from
around the time when I was released.
Someone said that
I was 14 years old.
Now that I think of it, I was enrolled in
a strange school and given a name.
Wolfgang Grimmer.
My home was in
an incredibly artificial town.
We weren't allowed to
go outside of that area.
I had a father figure.
I had a mother figure.
I was taught some languages.
Russian, English, Spanish, French...
Spy...training?
What do you think was
the most difficult thing to learn?
Learning how to smile.
Now then, we've got to go
to the hospital Suk's in.
Mr. Grimmer...
I saw the newspaper.
You're wanted as
an important witness.
I'm the only one who
can prove Suk's innocence.