Hi, Anna.
The wind's gotten cold,
hasn't it?
What's wrong with her?
She's pretty unsociable today.
Oh?
Are you going
home now, Anna?
Nina!
The restaurants in this area
are already closed.
Let's go back to the hotel, Nina.
What's wrong, Nina?
For some reason,
the people on this street know me.
They call me "Anna."
Oh?
What's the meaning of this?
Suk is a suspect in
a multiple homicide case,
but I don't see any
police or police cars.
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm going to
check on the situation.
Well... Whatever the case,
I've got to go.
It's the same inside.
There's no sign of the police.
Excuse me. There's an injured man
named Suk being hospitalized here.
Huh?
Jan Suk... He's a detective.
Detective?
There were a lot of injured men at
the abandoned building on Bruno Street.
Oh. One of those unemployed men
who were injured in the fight?
Unemployed? Fight?
Yes.
I don't know what they
were saying on the news,
but that's probably the story.
And? What room are
they in right now?
They had terrible wounds,
but after we treated them, they were
all moved to a different hospital.
Moved to a different hospital?
Which one?!
Who knows? An ambulance came
and loaded up all six of them.
There were six men
who attacked us.
What about Suk?
Where's Detective Jan Suk?
He was shot.
There weren't any patients brought in
with gunshot wounds.
Then is there any record of a patient
brought in with the name Jan Suk?
None at all.
Research data concerning
511 Kinderheim and a tape?
Yeah.
A former director of 511 Kinderheim,
named Pedrov,
gave it to me before he died.
He was running an illegal orphanage
in Prague.
Who would be after it?
I don't really know.
But I'm sure that the former
Czechoslovakian secret police are after it.
Where are the data
and the tape right now?
I don't have it with me.
I'm keeping it in a certain location.
Because of that,
Detective Suk was seriously injured
and was kidnapped from the hospital.
We don't know what they'll do to Suk
to get what they want.
How depressing.
The data and the contents
of the tape.. . What are they?
The research data was
a list of technical terms.
There was also a list of names.
I didn't examine it closely.
I only listened to
the main parts of the tape.
What was it a recording of?
A child's voice.
A child?
He was probably drugged,
then questioned.
When asked what his name was,
he answered, "Johan."
What's wrong, Doctor Tenma?
511 Kinderheim...
Research data...
Johan...
Where's the tape right now?!
Can you come with me?
Where is Suk?
Let's do this in
a business-like manner.
Where's Suk?
Can you come with me?
Leaving me aside...
Doctor Tenma, you don't need
to get involved any further.
No. I also have something I want to
ask the Czechoslovakian secret police.
What are you trying to do?
Well, the question is whether we
can negotiate with these guys.
You're not inviting us to dinner,
are you?
Welcome. ..
Come right this way.
That man...
Apparently, he's an important figure
with the Czechoslovakian secret police.
Yeah. I looked him up at
the newspaper company.
Captain Karel Lanke...
So the big boss
has finally appeared.
I'm very sorry that my subordinates
were rough with you.
This unintended situation was the result
of an error within our chain of command.
We have been terribly
misunderstood... by you and the world.
We're viewed as
a gang of killers.
Where's Suk?
He's at one of our hospitals.
His life isn't in danger.
I'm tired of people telling me
that this is a misunderstanding.
We haven't killed anyone.
What about that woman?
Woman?
Wasn't that blonde woman
acting on your orders?
I've received information on her,
but she isn't involved with us.
She's been quite
an inconvenience to us, too.
We don't want peoples' lives.
A German friend wanted
that tape and the data.
We've been carefully
negotiating with Pedrov.
That's when he was killed.
There must have been
a lot of money involved.
Yes. This is a business.
I just want to talk business.
I want that tape and data
in return for Suk.
I don't know where it is.
Let's not talk like that.
We mustn't let that
happen again.
If such a thing was in the world,
who knows what would happen?
We mustn't let that happen again.
Let's not talk about things
like that for now.
It doesn't have anything to do
with our current discussion.
I'm a graduate.
I'm a graduate
of 511 Kinderheim.
How old are you?
When did you leave that place?
I was supposedly fourteen,
but that was 30 years ago.
When were you placed there?
Who knows?
I was probably seven or eight.
Around 1963, right?
Who knows?
Do you know this boy?
He's my nephew.
In the early 60s,
I was officially stationed in Berlin
as an intelligence officer
for the Czechoslovakian
ambassador.
I had a younger sister.
She married a German.
But my younger sister
and her husband
plotted to defect and
cross the Berlin Wall.
They were shot dead.
Their child was all that
was left of their family.
I signed him up.
I heard that it was
a wonderful place.
An ideal educational environment
to educate children with dubious pasts
into the future communist elite.
I signed him up to be put
into 511 Kinderheim.
I don't know him.
I have no memories.
I can't remember what happened
there or what happened before that.
I can't even remember
my real name.
You're...
You're trying to make money
on something horrible.
You're trying to sell
the information
that includes experimental data
on your own nephew!
We've got off topic.
I want you to approach this
in a business-like manner.
All right.
You may leave for today.
I await a favorable response.
Please give these gentlemen
a courteous farewell.
What are you going to do?
Right now, saving Suk
is what's important.
I think he'll release Suk if
we give him what he wants.
Mr. Grimmer...
Hot Cocoa...
I remembered.
I remembered!
Mr. Grimmer!
Our weekly hot cocoa... He
looked forward to getting hot cocoa!
When I got a fever and
slept in the infirmary,
he brought me hot cocoa.
His hot cocoa.. .
Even though he liked it so much.
It was delicious. It was the first time
I had hot cocoa that was so delicious.
So I wanted to thank him
in some way.
That's when he said,
"remember me."
Back then, we all did that.
We talked about each other
to our friends.
I don't really know why,
but our memories would fade
day-by-day at these strange lessons.
We could hardly
remember our names.
That's why.. .
That's why...
We had our friends
remember who we were!
He loved hot cocoa,
drawing pictures, and bugs!
But he didn't like bug collections
because you have to kill the bugs!
The most enjoyable
time he had
was when he went to the forest
with his parents.
He caught
a lot of butterflies!
But when he went home, he let
the butterflies out of the bug cage.
His dream was to
become an entomologist!
His...
His name was Adolf Reinhart!
That was my nephew.
Welcome home.
Don't keep secrets from him.
People can become
anything they want to be.
Cheers!
Hey, welcome home.
What's wrong, Nina?
I...
I know this place.
The road leading up to here...
This scenery...
This sign...
I know all of it.
Did you live here?
I don't know. But...
But?
I'm afraid.
Do you also know this door?
I don't know. But...
I'm afraid.
I also know these stairs.
Mr. Grimmer,
I thought about this all night.
There's something
I want to tell you.
Doctor Tenma... That tape and
the data have nothing to do with you.
No, they do.
It looks like we don't
have time to talk.
They seem like they
can't wait to negotiate.
The former Czechoslovakian
secret police...
Have taken the time
to make an appearance.
Have you thought
everything through?
Yeah. I don't plan on handing over
the tape and the research data.
So you're saying that you don't care
what happens to Detective Suk?
If something
happens to Suk,
that tape and data will disappear
from this world forever.
Let's stop with such
trifling exchanges.
But I'll let you listen to the tape.
My condition is that
you forget doing business
with the German friend
who you plan on selling it to.
I'll let you listen to the tape
if you want to listen to it yourself.
No, you should listen to it.
For your nephew who was sent
to 511 Kinderheim, as well.
You should listen to Johan,
the boy on the tape.
Is that your deal?
I am not making a deal.
Stop already.
Now's not the time
to be doing this.
As we speak, someone might be
killed because of that tape.
How many people involved with
the Czechoslovakian secret police
have been killed?!
Who do you think killed them?!
The person who wants
the tape the most.
The person whose voice
was recorded.
Johan!
Doctor Tenma...
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't act dumb!
Your German friend should have
told you what kind of tape it is!
What did he tell you to obtain?!
"The Monster's Identity."
That's all.
I didn't want to get you involved.
But I'll tell you everything.
Before anyone else is killed.
It happened ten years ago.
I see. So Johan has come to Prague
in search of his roots.
I don't know. He might be
trying to erase of all of it.
What in the world did you
do to him 15 years ago?!
A mother and her child lived near
Cedok Bridge in the Mikalska District.
One day, they were taken away
by the secret police.
What did you do to Johan
when you took him from the building
with the sign with three frogs?!
These stairs...
Big brother...
What's wrong, Nina?
Dragged down these steps
and taken away...
Who was?
Big brother?
Indeed,
during that time,
I was in a position where I could
get all the information I wanted.
But the three frogs. ..
Taking away a mother and child...
I don't remember that at all.
Don't act dumb!
Even so, there was information
that even I didn't receive.
Things that man did...
We didn't know which branch
of the secret police he belonged to.
Or even what chain of
command he followed.
He could freely detain many people
for whatever reason without reporting it.
What was he doing?
He was only a captain, but he was
granted a luxurious mansion to work in.
Yes.
He was called
"the Man of Red Rose Mansion."
Are you saying
that man was involved?
He was a very elegant
and quiet man.
He didn't wear a uniform
and liked tea and cake.
What was that man's name?!
Franz Bonaparta.
Franz. .. Bonaparta...
But I don't know if it was his
real name. He used a pseudonym.
A pseudonym?
He also wrote picture books.
Are you afraid of this door?
I...
I was reading
a picture book in here.
The door opened.
Someone came back.
Picture book?
Yes. It was a strange picture book.
It was called,
The Nameless Monster.
There's nothing here, Nina.
What's with this memory?
I was reading
a picture book here.
But the one who opened the door
and came back.. .was me.
I was greeting myself?
Welcome home.