What's wrong, Nina?
Dragged down these steps
and taken away...
Who was?
Big brother?
He was called
"the Man from Red Rose Mansion."
What was that man's name?!
Franz Bonaparta.
Franz. .. Bonaparta...
But I don't know if it was his
real name. He used a pseudonym.
A pseudonym?
He also wrote picture books.
I ... I was reading
a picture book in here.
The door opened.
Someone came back.
Picture book?
Yes. It was a strange picture book.
It was called,
The Nameless Monster.
There's nothing here, Nina.
What's with this memory?
I was reading
a picture book here.
But the one who opened the door
and came back.. .was me.
I was greeting myself?
Welcome home.
Jan Suk's mother?
Oh, Mrs. Suk is in room 409.
Her memory comes and goes.
I wonder how she is today.
Jan? Jan, is that you?
No.
Oh. What a beautiful girl.
Are you one of Jan's friends?
Yes.
What beautiful flowers.
I'll put them there.
Make sure that Auntie Olga
can't take it.
Auntie Olga is always
taking my things.
Just yesterday she
took away my doll.
She's mean, isn't she?
But she passed away over
ten years ago, didn't she?
Oh. That's right.
I'm surprised you know.
I've heard a lot from Jan.
I see. Where's Jan?
Is he still at school?
No.
Oh, that's right.
He already graduated...
and became a detective.
It's all right. Jan's safe.
There's no need to worry.
You have very kind eyes.
Tell me anything.
Whatever you remember.
Well... Katrina, in the next room,
is very fashionable. And...
Oh, how fun.
It's been a while since
I had this much fun.
That's good.
I must thank you in some way.
You don't need to thank me.
I just wanted you to show me
what Jan entrusted to you.
Entrusted to me?
The cassette tape.
Oh. That's over there.
I never would have thought that
you would leave it with Suk's mother.
I'll wait here while you fetch
the cassette tape and the data.
Just forget business.
That's our promise.
Let's go, Doctor Tenma.
I'm sorry I said that
you weren't involved.
I don't know what to say
about that story you told me,
about what happened
ten years ago.
But this cassette tape
may be a clue
to help us reveal the whole story
and prove your innocence.
You too, Mr. Grimmer.
Yes, I was investigating the story
behind 511 Kinderheim.
But my life won't change
even if I learn everything.
You want to see
Mr. Suk's mother?
She's in a very
good mood today.
Thank you.
It seems she enjoyed talking
to the person that just visited her.
Visited her?
Who was it?!
Who knows?
A beautiful, long-haired blonde...
The tape!
You came. I heard that
you would come shortly.
Where's the tape?
The tape.. .is right here.
How is Jan?
Right now... He's...
Take me to the hospital
where Jan is.
Huh?
Something terrible
happened to Jan, right?
My mind is very
clear right now.
That person who came earlier
reawakened me.
But it might just be for today.
Let me see Jan!
I'll take you. ..to the hospital
where Jan Suk is.
Mr. Grimmer...
I'm done with talking
to the secret police.
Mom...
Jan. ..why didn't you call me?
This is nothing, Mom.
You tried to keep me from worrying
about you, didn't you?
Just like the last time.
Last time?
When you were nine,
you fell from a tree, remember?
I was so worried, but you
acted as if nothing was wrong.
You had a terrible sprain.
Oh, Lord.. .
Don't let me forget him.
Jan is my child. Even if many things
disappear from my memory...
Please Lord.. .
Don't let me forget about Jan.
Let's go back.
What are you most afraid of?
The monster inside me
is getting bigger.
Munch-munch, chomp-chomp,
gobble-gobble, gulp!
That's enough.
I don't want to hear anymore.
No, you have to.
Your nephew you sent
to 511 Kinderheim,
is the same as this child, who
has been drugged and interrogated.
You should know what was
done to your nephew.
That's as much as
I listened to the other day.
We have to hear
what comes next.
The thing I'm afraid of the most...
That would be forgetting Anna.
Everyday my memories fade
because of those strange lessons.
Please.. .
Don't make me forget Anna.
Anna and I are
the only ones in this world.
Just this memory.
Please.
That's all I can let you hear.
What's this?!
It's a young man's voice.
Did he erase
the old recording?
I finally figured it out.
And record something new?
I figured it out by
listening to this tape.
Did the person who came
to meet Suk's mother tape it?
Doctor Tenma?
It's Johan's current voice.
I finally figured out where
I should go, Doctor Tenma.
He took a vacation?
The Inspector?
He's so dedicated to the job.
I can't believe it!
I hear it's his first long-term leave
since he joined the force!
Well... Lately,
he hasn't been very busy.
He was among the BKA elite,
but he went too far.
He doesn't know his limits.
I hear his wife and daughter ran away
from him because of that.
So where's the Inspector
going on vacation?
He said to Prague in the Czech
Republic. But does he know how to rest?
What will you have?
Coffee.
Okay.
No, I'm on vacation now.
A beer.
What kind of beer is this?
Prazdroj, a local beer.
Do you think that the public will accept
an investigation report like this?!
We don't know
where Detective Suk is!
And even the former Czechoslovakian
secret police are involved.
We can't announce
such half-assed findings!
The media will be all over it!
B-But since all those who
were involved have died.
With the situation
we are in right now,
we don't have the luxury of
laying blame on the dead.
Y-Yes, sir.
Now continue the investigation.
And find out where Suk is!
Immediately!
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Umm... Chief, there's someone
who wants to see you.
I won't meet anyone
without an appointment.
Besides, now is not the time!
But... Umm... Oh...
Y-You're...
Well, this is a surprise,
Inspector Lunge!
It's the first time we've met since
the Interpol meeting two years ago.
The lecture you gave at the sectional
meeting was very interesting!
I'm sorry to come so suddenly
at such a busy time.
Not at all. I never expected you
to come here on your vacation.
I'm jealous.
I can't take a vacation
in my current situation.
You seem to be busy,
New Chief Nepela.
Yes. If it's possible, I'd like you
to advise me on some things.
This case is just so chaotic.
The connection between
the Prague station and
the former Czechoslovakian
secret police.
It all happened when we discovered
the body of an inspector
by the name of Zeman with the bodies
of several secret police agents.
Inspector Zeman was investigating
the murder of a man
who was running
an unauthorized orphanage.
We found out afterwards that Zeman
and the orphanage manager
were both involved with
the secret police!
Who's the suspect in that case?
Grimmer, the man who discovered
the manager's murder, was suspected.
But the children at the orphanage
saw someone else
leaving the scene of the crime
immediately after it happened.
Someone else?
A beautiful blonde woman.
But the case didn't end there.
It spread.
The former head chief of this station
and two veteran detectives
were murdered with
poisoned candies.
They were also involved with the
former Czechoslovakian secret police.
Who was the suspect
in the poisoning case?
A young detective
by the name of Suk.
He was Inspector Zeman's
direct subordinate.
Do you have any
conclusive evidence?
We don't have any.
But two detectives from a special
team who were watching Suk
were found shot dead
in Suk's room!
I see.
So where's Detective Suk?
His whereabouts
are currently unknown.
The circumstantial evidence
points at Suk.
But he doesn't have
enough of a motive, right?
Y-Yes.
He doesn't seem like
he would commit such a crime.
Y-Yes. Umm...
How do you know that?
I know of a very similar case.
As I would expect of you.
That hand keeps on moving
even when you're on vacation.
You're accumulating objective data,
aren't you?
And at the lecture, you also said
that you use that data to perform
a completely subjective
investigation at the same time.
In other words, you become
the criminal, right?
What do you think?
If you were Suk, what would you be
thinking and where would you be right now?
Sorry.
Unfortunately, I'm on vacation.
Oh... No, I'm very sorry!
How is Prague?
I've been going to
second-hand bookstores.
Second-hand bookstores...
Are you searching for something?
I looked in thirteen stores.
I finally found one.
Actually, I came to you today
to ask if you could translate
this Czech into German
when you have the time.
Oh? A picture book?
I'm surprised.
I didn't think you were
interested in such things.
Leave it with me.
I'll have a subordinate
do it by tomorrow!
Is it for your child.. .
I mean, your grandchild?
Yes. I guess it is.
Suk is completely innocent!
As his friend,
I believe that he's innocent!
The police asked me
all sorts of questions,
but he isn't guilty at all.
If you're involved with the police,
please help him.
We'll help you
as much as we can!
Unfortunately, I'm on vacation.
I can't be of much help to you.
Is there anyone else he trusts?
He was getting close to a girl.
He'd just managed
to find out her name.
What was her name?
Anna.
Oh yeah. Anna Liebert!
She was a really
beautiful blonde woman.
He was glad that things
were going well with her.
Anna Liebert.
Ten years ago, the family
of a high ranking official
who defected from
East Germany was killed.
She was one of the twins
who survived.
I don't think there's
anything left.
My company was the one
that published Emile Scherbe's
The Nameless Monster,
but that was during
the old regime,
when the previous company
president was around.
Is Emile Scherbe a pen name?
Yes. It probably is.
He has many other pen names.
Something Bonaparta. ..
and Jakov Farobek...
Klaus Poppe, etc...
Klaus Poppe's box
is right here.
What? I'm surprised
you found that.
Can I open it?
Yes. Go right ahead.
They're just a mountain of
old rough sketches, right?!
A pregnant woman.
And she gave birth.
A girl.
Twins...
I see.
You translated it for me.
Thank you, Chief Nepela.
Oh. There's something
I've been wondering about.
Could you read me
the last page?
Umm...
"At last he had
found a name, "
"but there was no longer
anyone around to call him by it."
"Such a shame because Johan
was such a wonderful name"
What a strange
picture book.
Johan...
inspector Lunge, would you
care to have dinner with me?
How long is your vacation?
You there.
Yes?
Cancel my beer.
Make it a coffee.
It looks like I'm going to
be taking a long vacation.