CHECK PLACEMENT Honestly.
You're such a troublemaker!
How many times are you
going to pretend to run away?
The next time you do it,
you won't get dinner!
Understand, Milosh?!
All right.
Take your hands out of your pockets
when you talk to me!
All right.
Really?!
It's true.
It was the blonde lady.
You saw her on
Dominican Street, right?
I wonder if she lives
in that area.
Why didn't you follow her
all the way?!
I was hungry and
my stomach was growling.
In that case, we've got to find out where
the lady is and turn her over to the police.
Mr. Grimmer didn't
kill the director.
We've got to prove
his innocence.
Prove his innocence?
Will that save Mr. Grimmer?
That's right! We're having
a strategy meeting right now.
Milosh, hurry and eat your food.
This is the underground orphanage,
where the first incident occurred.
Someone killed the former director
of 511 Kinderheim.
The children say that
a blonde woman
walked passed them
right after the incident.
He was conducting
an experiment here.
It was the complete opposite of
what happened at 511 Kinderheim.
It seems he was experimenting
with giving the children affection.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to go in?
The police probably stripped away
all the evidence already.
Mr. Grimmer, what's that?
"To Mr. Police Officer!
Mr. Grimmer is innocent."
"To Mr. Detective!
The blonde lady is the killer."
It's those children...
The orphanage children came back
and posted these up.
"To Mr. Grimmer..."
Milan Boucek. ..
A card of a famous soccer player.
It's valuable to the children.
How should I react?
What kind of expression
should I make in this situation?
My emotions were taken
from me at 511 Kinderheim.
Afterwards, I was taught various
emotional expressions at a strange school.
But situations like this
are the most difficult.
What's the right way
to react to this?
Why don't you go and
see those children?
You're Mr. Grimmer?
I always hear things from
the children about you.
The children are out playing.
They haven't come back yet.
If only they'd come back earlier.
Take a look! The children's journals...
Or rather, a lot of letters written to you!
"Mr. Grimmer,
let's play soccer again."
"Mr. Grimmer, I'll teach you how to play
soccer since you're not very good at it!"
"Mr. Grimmer,
let's all play together again."
I'm smiling right now, aren't I?
I learned this.
I learned the form
of a smiling face.
I'm remaining in
peoples' memories?
Why...do those children. ..
care about me?
That's because they love you.
Love...
Before, when my son died,
I was thinking of how I should react.
How should I cry in this situation?
How long should I cry?
Should I scream,
or should I clench my teeth?
Even now,
I still don't know what to do.
I don't know.
Mr. Grimmer!
Hey, Antonio.
Mr. Grimmer, bad news!
What's wrong, Antonio?
We got word from the kids at
Ceske Orphanage ! I-It's terrible.
Calm down, Antonio. Calm
down and tell me what happened.
They found the blonde lady.
Yesterday,
we all kept watch to find her.
And then, Milosh...
Milosh disappeared!
CHECK PLACEMENT I see. The
people who have come to see you were
a middle-aged gentleman,
a tall German man,
and a long-haired
Japanese man?
Yes.
I think you may have forgotten
another person who came to see you.
According to the nurse, a long-haired
blonde woman came to see you.
Woman? No.
A woman never came.
No, the nurse was sure.
She was very beautiful.
Yes, very beautiful.
But he was a man.
I see.
What's your name?
Milosh.
Have we met somewhere?
Huh?
N-No.
What were you doing there?
Nothing.
You walk around this area often,
don't you?
Y-Yeah.
What are you looking for?
U-Umm. .. My mom.
Don't just stand there.
Why don't you have a seat?
There's some juice.
Umm.. .
Are you going to move?
Why do you ask?
Because you have a big bag.
And there's nothing in this room.
Is your mother somewhere
around here?
Huh?
You said you were looking for
your mother, didn't you?
Yeah. But I don't know if
she's around here.
Then how will you find her? Do
you have her picture or something?
I don't have one.
Then you won't know her face.
I'll know! I'll know my mom
when I see her face!
No one at the orphanage
believes me!
Everyone says that
I won't be able to tell.
But I'll know my mom
when I see her!
And...
And?
Mom will know me
when she sees me!
Even if you find her, what if she
acts as if she doesn't know you?
Huh?
Were you born because
you were wanted?
Why were you abandoned?
Didn't your mother abandon you
because she hated you?
N-No!
There's nothing special
about being born.
Huh?
Most of the universe is "death."
Compared to the universe, the lives created
on Earth are short and insignificant.
Death is normal.
So why live?
Was it because
someone wanted you?
Who wanted you?
What's your reason for living?
A beautiful,
long-haired blonde woman?
Oh, that would be Anna.
A-Anna!
Does this woman, Anna,
live around here?
Yes. I believe she lives
in the apartment
at the end of the dead-end street
two corners down.
Well, she's a very nice girl.
She's good-natured
and always greets me.
Anna? Yes, yes,
she's a nice girl.
She always calls out
to me with a smile.
Do you know which room
and which floor she lives on?
Yes. Over there.
That window on the third floor.
If what the children said is true...
And... If it's true that
that woman kidnapped Milosh...
If that woman, Anna, who's living here
is the same one we're looking for, then...
And if that woman is
the person I think she is,
everything will end now,
right here!
She got away.
Where did Milosh go?
No. Was he captured?
He was following that blonde woman
to prove my innocence.
What should I do, Dr. Tenma?
How should I react
in this situation?
Those children got involved in this because
they were trying to prove my innocence.
The children told you that Milosh
usually walks around Prague
in search of his mother,
didn't they?
He wants to meet
his mother, huh?
I didn't feel anything
when my own son died.
One day, a female coworker
from the newspaper company
where I worked spoke to me.
She told me that she loved me.
I married her.
I was told that I wouldn't be suspected of
conducting spy activities if I was married.
She got pregnant
and she had a boy.
One day, my wife went shopping
not far from home.
When I went into
my son's room,
he was lying down flat
and wasn't breathing.
I applied artificial respiration.
At the same time,
I called the doctor.
I did everything I should have done.
Perfectly.
But he died.
At the funeral,
my wife raged at me.
"How can you stay so calm?"
"How can you not cry?"
"You're always,
always like that."
"You were like that
with me, too."
"You can't love people."
"There's nothing
in your heart."
Then my wife left.
I have to find Milosh.
You said that Milosh was
the child of a prostitute
from a red-light district near
the Czech border, didn't you?
Yeah.
If the person that was here,
is the person I think she is...
I don't think they'll
let the boy live!
But they won't just kill him.
The person
I'm thinking of
would probably kill him after
doing the cruelest thing possible.
Germany is straight this way.
Is my mom along
the way there?
There's a lively place
up ahead.
I can meet my mom, right?
I'll wait here.
You go on alone.
You'll know who your mother is
if you see her.
And your mother will know
who you are if she sees you.
But if no one calls out to you, that
means that you weren't wanted by anyone.
What will you do then?
What will you do?
Go.
Mom.
Cruel, huh?
Thank you, thank you.
What is it, kid?
I'm looking for someone.
Looking for who?
My mom.
Your mom?!
This is great.
What's so funny?
Yeah, I know your mom.
Huh?
Where?! Where is she?
Well...
Of the ones I know. ..
there are about 50!
Why were you abandoned?
Hey Kid!
Kid, Kid!
Who are you, Ma'am?
It's all right. It's all right.
Umm.. .
I'm...looking for my mom.
Just let me hold you like this.
What's with that kid?!
He's not your kid, is he?
Of course not!
I don't make mistakes like that!
You get diseases, though.
Shut up! Want to fight?!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
H-Hold on. No!
Not here!
I paid you. I'm a customer.
Do as your customer says!
But hold on.
Oh! A child's watching!
Wait.
Watch. Don't run away.
I'm a teacher in Germany.
At school, I'm a gentleman who's
highly praised by parents,
and a wonderful teacher.
I'm a wonderful teacher.
Take this.
Who wanted you?
Kid... Money...
Are you sick, Ma'am?
I'm.. .I'm going to die soon.
Why are you here?
I told you, didn't I?
I'm going to die soon.
Gimme money.
I only have this.
Most of the universe is death.
Who wanted you?
What's your reason for living?
I see.
So that's it.
The red-light district
ends around here.
There are several people in town
who have seen Milosh.
Shall we turn back?
He still might be in there.
Milosh...
It's all right. It's all right.
Okay. Now come here.
You tried your best to clear
my name, didn't you?
It's all right now.
Come here.
It's all right. It's all right.
Is this good, Dr. Tenma?
Would it be better if I cried?
I was never taught. ..
such a difficult emotion.
What's wrong, Milosh?!
What did you see?
What have you seen?
What did you find out?
Milosh. .. Listen to me.
You have no mother.
But... But...
You were born for a reason!
You were born because
someone wanted you!
Definitely...
Someone definitely wanted you.
Say, Dr. Tenma.
I'm not wrong, am I?
No...
What expression. ..
do I have...right now?
You're crying.