Oh, that mansion
is right up this hill.
I see. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Roses, huh?
Just like sleeping
beauty's castle...
My name is Anna.
Anna Liebert.
Good luck,
Mr. Great Detective!
She was worried that
something might happen to you.
I feel the same way
about you as your mother.
Anna...
Were you dreaming,
Detective Suk?
W-Who are you?
Lunge...
An inspector with the BKA.
BKA?!
Oh.
You can lie down.
I didn't come here to arrest you.
This is a pretty nice
hospital room.
I arrived here by checking out
hospitals that were involved with
the former Czechoslovakian
secret police under the old regime.
Judging by your treatment...
You must be pretty important to
the Czechoslovakian secret police.
No. I just...
I know everything about you.
The fact that Inspector Zeman, who
had close ties with the secret police,
was beaten to death...
The fact that the Prague police chief and
two detectives were poisoned to death...
The fact that the two detectives who
were following you were found shot dead...
And the fact that you are being pursued
because you are an important witness...
In any of these incidents, if you were to
look at just the circumstantial evidence,
you're the culprit.
No! I didn't do anything!
Then what about Grimmer, the tall
man who Inspector Zeman questioned
the day before
he was beaten to death?
Grimmer's also not the culprit!
He's not the sort of person to do that!
Then who's the culprit?
You know, don't you?
You know who the culprit is,
don't you?
W-What are you talking about?
This wouldn't be happening
to me if I knew.
I've been betrayed by
all sorts of people.
I've been made out to be the culprit
and the police are after me.
I've had enough ! I don't want to be
betrayed by anyone anymore!
You're a detective, aren't you?
If you're a detective,
you must dissect everything calmly.
You must dig up the truth
as rationally as you can,
even at the expense of
destroying your own happiness.
If you don't want to be
betrayed anymore,
doubt the people you
don't ever want to doubt.
Who gave you permission
to see him?
Take me to your boss.
Tell him I want to talk to him
about the Rose Mansion.
That'll make him
want to see me.
Inspector Lunge of the BKA...
I've looked up your identity
and your past.
I also heard rumors
about you
when the old regime
was in force, Captain Lanke.
And now, you're essentially the leader
of the Czechoslovakian secret police.
It's a big position with quite a lot of
trouble attached to it at the moment.
Thank you for your concern.
I envy the fact that you can
take a long vacation.
I hear that two years ago your forceful
investigation drove a man to suicide.
He was the secretary
to Senator Boltzmann,
a candidate for the leadership
of the German Democratic Party.
You have to know how
to get ahead in the world.
You're fools!
If you took a softer line and
actually managed to conceal
your activities during democratization,
you could have emerged as
the secret president of this country.
But the fear that the people have
of you is now all but a mere illusion.
I see. You're smart.
If you're so smart,
what do you want from me?
No. As you know,
I'm on a long vacation.
This is partially for fun.
I'm looking for something.
For true fear...
I want to know if a real demon was
born from the illusion you created.
Would you be referring
to Red Rose Mansion?
I went all over the place
to reach that mansion.
This author had many,
many pseudonyms.
The author of The Nameless Monster
is Emile Scherbe.
He lived in an old building
in Prague.
A company is renting
that room at the moment.
Under another alias,
Klaus Poppe,
was an old farm in the suburbs.
The farm has already
been destroyed.
Under another alias, Jakub Farobek,
was a rental office.
So. ..you've finally arrived.. .
at Franz Bonaparta?
What is that mansion?
Who is Franz Bonaparta?
No matter how hard I search,
I can't find anything on him.
Which means that
he's one of you.
He's with the former
Czechoslovakian secret police.
What do you want to know?
I want to know what you know.
I don't know anything.
But...
But?
There is something I've been
consciously trying to forget.
I tried to forget the existence
of that mansion.
That's why it still
stands there untouched.
The political criminals
who were taken there,
all the researchers who were there,
disappeared one day.
That's all.
What's the reason for the wall?
Wall?
I went inside the mansion
the other day.
There was no sign of any human
entry. It was completely abandoned.
But the wall to the north
on the second floor...
The wall was plastered over as if
to hastily seal something away.
That wall...
May I break it down?
What are you afraid of,
Captain Lanke?
You might die.
If you get any closer to it, you
and I might end up seeing true fear.
Franz Bonaparta?
That name
brings back memories.
Would you like milk or sugar
in your coffee?
Oh. Black is fine.
What is it?
Well...
I never expected a Franz
Bonaparta fan to appear now.
I heard from Moravia Publishing
that you, Mr. Zobak,
were Mr. Bonaparta's editor
for a long time.
Yes.
But I was in charge of him when he
was using the pseudonym, Klaus Poppe.
I want to know what
kind of person he was.
Franz Bonaparta, huh?
He came to this house to
make work arrangements.
Yes. He sat right on
that chair just like that.
He often played with
my daughter in the yard.
But at the time, my daughter
said something strange.
She said,
"that man is scary."
My daughter probably doesn't
remember that now.
Did he work for a government agency
during that time?
Probably. I assumed that was the
case when I was doing business with him.
But judging by his demeanor, the way
he talked and the clothes he wore...
He had a mildness and elegance
that was nothing like
the important figures
of the old regime.
Bonaparta had
a doctorate in psychiatry.
He was also a psychologist.
His specialty was neurosurgery.
O-Okay.
When was the last time
I saw him?
I believe it was
the summer of '81 or '82.
Yes. That day, he wandered to
my house. He told me his new story.
Oh, he looked strangely sullen.
New story?
What kind of story was it?
A story where
a monster falls in love.
But it was like a mix between Beauty
and the Beast and Sleeping Beauty.
I rejected it.
Then, at the door,
just as he was about to leave...
He turned and said,
"then what about this?"
"A story about a door that
should never be opened."
I asked him whether there was
paradise on the other side
or whether a monster
would come out.
He said, "No. It should never be opened,
so I guess it's not much of a story."
He laughed as
he said that and left.
That was the last time
I saw him.
Did he tell you anything important
about Bonaparta?
No. Nothing important.
Mr. Grimmer,
what were you doing here?
I was thinking that
it sure is a nice day.
It sure is.
I knew it.
Oh, hello? Is this the police?
My name is Zoback at Schweig Court.
A man just came to my house.
I think he's a prime suspect in a multiple
homicide that happened in Germany.
Yes. He's Japanese.
The neurosurgeon, Dr. Tenma!
Ethanol...
the smell of disinfectant.
Death? How many?
How many people died here?
Ten... Twenty...
No. More.
That woman...
The woman from
the sketchbook...
The mother of the twins...
If you don't hurry, the older students
will take the soccer field!
Hurry up, Milosh!
Oh. Okay.
Go! Counter attack!
Oh no!
Stand back!
The goal's wide open!
They got us!
They got a goal!
Milosh!
Are you all right, Milosh?!
Get a hold of yourself,
Milosh!
Nice defense,
Nice clear!
You protected the goal!
That laugh...
He's all right now, isn't he?
What do you think,
Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
Mr. Grimmer, aren't you going to
see Milosh and the other children?
I realized why
I wasn't good at soccer.
It's teamwork.
What do you think will
happen to Detective Suk?
He's wanted as a prime suspect
in a murder.
He's pretty much done-for,
socially speaking.
Even if he turns himself in,
how will he prove his innocence?
How will he prove
that there was
a blonde woman leaving
the crime scene?
Suk is in the same situation as you.
Except for one thing.
This is goodbye, Doctor Tenma.
Huh?
There's only one person who knows the
details about the latest string of events.
He's right here.
What do you think of sending
this to the police?
What's this?
It's a letter from
the serial killer...
I reveal in detail secrets that
only the murderer would know.
B-But if you send this
to the police, you'll be...
Grimmer will suddenly
return to Germany.
The police will cast a dragnet,
but Grimmer will get away.
That's because he used to
be a skilled spy.
But you'll be a suspect and be forced
to run away for the rest of your life!
That's all right.
Because the person known as
Grimmer never existed to begin with.
Someone just gave
that role to me.
Even if Grimmer is a suspect for the
rest of his life, I'll be completely fine!
Just kidding.
What do you think of
this method, Dr. Tenma?
Oh. No.
That's all right.
You're going to the Rose Mansion,
aren't you?
Y-Yes.
You might be close
to your goal.
No. I don't know that.
I'd tell you to not do anything rash,
but you won't listen.
But please don't die.
Mr. Grimmer...
That promise we made when
we crossed the Czech border...
When we meet again,
let's have a picnic.
We'll fish for trout in surrounded
by wonderful scenery.
We'll have good wine
and cheese.
Until we meet again!
From now on I have to live
in fear of that sound.
It hurts!
What's wrong?
Let me take a look at that!
It's just a scratch.
I'll just apply some antiseptic.
O-Owowow!
You're a boy, aren't you?
Bear with it!
Good. You're a strong boy.
You're Kenzo Tenma,
aren't you?
We're the police !
Come with us to the station.