Are you crying?
This letter from my friend...
My best friend...
When we were 15, we tried to cross
the Czech border together.
She was caught
and taken to Prague.
She says she's doing fine.
She knows me better than
my parents or my siblings.
She's a true friend.
Who knows how much trouble
she went through to get this to me,
with all the government's
harsh inspections.
She says, "Please visit me
if you have the chance."
"Cedok Bridge,
Three Frogs"...
I want to go back to Prague.
Margot...
Say...
Call me by my real name.
Just for today, I want you to
call me by my real name.
I'm Helenka Novakova.
Just for today,
I'm not Margot Langer.
I sold my stocks in Reiser-Berger
Pharmaceuticals at the right time.
Then, when I bought some stocks in
Knutter Laboratories, I hit the jackpot!
Well, it was cause
for celebration, so...
You had a drink?
Yes. Just a little.
How foolish.
It was just one drink.
I'll say it again.
For an alcoholic, drinking just a little
is the same as drinking a lot.
It doesn't seem like you've been going to
the alcohol relief group I introduced you to.
By the way. .. Umm...
Doctor, you can keep a secret,
can't you?
Actually, there's a woman
I want you to meet.
You have another mistress?
No, well...
She's also
a pretty bad alcoholic.
She's waiting outside right now.
Could you see her for a moment?
Not suddenly like this.
Make an appointment.
Just for a little while
will be fine.
I've got a house call right now.
It's for an important client.
I went to Prague
in the Czech Republic.
It's a really nice place.
Prague Castle...
Wonderful Gothic cathedrals...
It's beautiful when
the old town plaza lights up!
It's like a village
out of a fairytale.
What about Cedok Bridge?
Did you go to Cedok Bridge?
Of course!
I did as you told me to do
and I found it. Even the three frogs!
Was the woman there?
No. No one was there.
Actually, I didn't learn
anything by going there.
I couldn't find anything
on Tenma's whereabouts,
and I also couldn't find anything
on Nina and Dieter.
Take this.
It's a lucky rabbit's foot.
I want you give it to
our soon-to-be child.
Margot... No, Helenka... I ...
Thank you.
Yes?
Excuse me.
I've come from Germany
in search of a woman
whose whereabouts
are unknown.
Do you know a woman by the name of
Margot Langer–no, Helenka Novakova?
Helenka...
Anyway, Mr. Schuwald...
I heard from your son, Karl.
You haven't been able
to eat properly.
You had a petrifying experience at the
fire in the University of Munich library.
I know that the fear
still hasn't left you.
But you have Karl...
A wonderful son.
You have nothing more
to worry about!
Make sure to eat more.
The monster...
As long as that
monster exists.. .I...
Why did that monster know
so much about Margot Langer?
He knew far more than
either her son Karl or I did.
Margot's best friend, the one who knew her
better than her parents or her siblings...
The woman who Margot
exchanged letters with...
In the '80s, you searched for Margot,
who had gone missing.
You went to Prague
and met that woman.
Yes. I thought that that woman might
have heard something from Margot.
But she knew nothing.
We talked for a while
about Margot at the door.
That's when they were listening
to our conversation.
Who was?
They were quietly listening
behind that woman.
The twins...
Come in!
Sit over there.
You're the person that Mr. Thalbach
wanted me to see, aren't you?
You can't stop drinking either?
Make yourself comfortable.
Just act as if we're
going to have a little chat.
Doctor!
What's wrong, Mereth?
I'm in the middle of counseling.
On TV! Right now on TV!
It's Tenma. Dr. Tenma!
Excuse me for a second!
I repeat, the Czech police have
apprehended in Prague
the prime suspect of
the poisoning of three doctors
of Dusseldorf Germany's
Eisler Memorial Hospital,
the murders of the journalist Maurer
and the Fortner couple in Heidelberg
and the phantom killing
at Heidelberg Castle...
the Japanese Doctor Kenzo Tenma was
apprehended on the afternoon of the fifth.
We have not received
any further information.
We will continue to report the details
of how he was taken into custody when
- the police make their announcement.
- Tenma...
Don't!
This is the office.
Please wait in the consultation room,
Miss Eva Heinemann!
Kenzo...
Sorry everyone,
for coming late.
Mr. Hess, you look like you've
gotten ten years younger!
That's because I'm always
playing with my grandchild.
Huber, how are you doing?
Well, I've managed to move up
to my final academic year!
Mr. Kieffer, I hear you're
pretty busy too.
I was bragging about how
I'm friends with a scriptwriter
who's been invited
to go to Hollywood.
I just happened to catch
the eye of one of their producers.
My mind has cleared and
new ideas keep coming!
Sounds promising!
Ever since that surgery...
If my brain operation hadn't
been successful, I'd be...
I wouldn't have been able to walk
with my grandchild in the park.
That seat...
He always sat there
drinking tea by himself.
There were other cafes
where doctors gathered.
But he came to this café
behind Eisler Memorial Hospital.
When we patients
would come in...
...he'd raise his head
as he sat there...
...and smile and wave.
He was a kind doctor.
Yes.
Such a kind doctor. ..
would never do this!
This is why I've
gathered everyone here.
No, even the people who couldn't come
here today would feel the same as we do.
They were Dr. Tenma's
former patients, too.
Dr. Schumann, bad news!
Old man Merkel collapsed!
All right! I'll be right there!
But I'm busy right now.
Sorry, but wait for me there!
All right!
Dr. Tenma never
did those things.
Calm down and
listen to me, Mom!
Go to him quickly, Dear.
Yes. But, Petra...
No buts! Dr. Tenma was arrested
for a crime he didn't commit!
If he hadn't been around,
I wouldn't be alive!
Dr. Schumann, don't you care about
the man who saved your wife's life?!
What'll happen to this village?
Huh?
I'm the only doctor in this village.
What'll happen to the folks
in this town if I'm gone?
Don't blabber on.
You want to go, don't you?!
Quickly, go and save Tenma!
If there's a patient,
a doctor mustn't leave him.
That's what Dr. Tenma
would do.
Doctor, see us quickly!
Wait, I'm getting ready
right now!
How long are you going to
make us wait?!
Don't complain!
Lately, the doctor has been
going to medical school.
It's risky for her to examine
patients here illegally!
When you're in darkness,
you just sink deeper into it.
Shine some light.
You can do it!
You can become
a good doctor.
Dr. Tenma...
I'm going to start examining patients!
Whoever's first come in!
Get a lawyer.
Yes.
But we still don't know where in
Germany Tenma will be transferred to.
Retain an attorney
from each state.
Get the best criminal attorney.
Yes!
He's the only one...
He's the only man who
can erase the monster.
First off, we need to
get more allies.
Let's call Dr. Tenma's
former patients!
We may be weak as individuals,
but if we join together...
All right!
Let's ask Eisler Memorial Hospital
for help in forming a relief group.
It's impossible.
Eisler Memorial Hospital won't
help you with something like that.
I was listening to you.
It was quite a touching story.
But think hard about it.
How will you prove
Tenma's innocence?
Dr. Becker...
He has some motive,
but no alibi.
They even say that
there's physical evidence.
Even if you gather numbers
and make a lot of noise...
No, no matter how brilliant
a lawyer you hire...
No matter what, it's impossible
to prove Tenma's innocence.
How unfortunate for
such a brilliant doctor.
Truly unfortunate.
I'll ask you once more...
What's your relationship
to Tenma?
Miss Eva Heinemann...
I don't know who you are,
but I'm going to go save Tenma.
I don't want you to come with me
if you're just going to sightsee.
Eva... Heinemann...
Heinemann!
Heinemann...
Could it be that you're the daughter
of Director Heinemann,
who was killed at Eisler Hospital
in Düsseldorf?!
Dr. Tenma...
He's the man that
destroyed my life.
But I'm the only one
who can save him.
Huh?
I saw.
Saw what?
Kenzo Tenma is being
detained in Prague.
He will be deported to Germany
in a day or two.
He's being moved to Düsseldorf
where it is believed these incidents began.
After interrogation...
No way.
That's impossible.
This person is...
This doctor is...
This is Dr. Tenma.
Suk, he saved your life.
He applied first aid.
He's also been framed for
a crime he didn't commit.
He's in the same
situation you are.
Saved my life.
Same situation as me...
You're a detective
aren't you?
If you're a detective,
you must dissect everything calmly.
If you don't want to be
betrayed anymore,
doubt the people you don't
ever want to doubt.
I've got to go.
Anyway, I've got to go to
Prague station and talk to Tenma!
I've been looking for you, Suk.
Detective Bradec,
Detective Stransky...
I...
You don't have to
run away anymore.
Huh?
You must have had
a terrible time.
You've been cleared.
A letter was sent to the station.
Here's a copy.
A letter?
It's a confession that gives
the details of all the events
that only the culprit
would know.
You've been cleared
of all suspicion.
Wh-Who sent this letter?
A man who goes
by the name Grimmer.
What?
Grimmer has been put on
the wanted list as a prime suspect.
H-Hold on a second.
Relax, Suk.
Inspector Zeman's murder,
the chief's poisoning,
and the shooting of the special
investigations team have all been solved.
Where have you been,
Lunge?!
I called you
so many times!
Well, Chief,
I was doing some sightseeing.
Honestly!
Don't act dumb!
Act dumb?
What are you talking about?
Cut it out! Don't tell me you
haven't heard the news!
Oh. Are you talking about
Dr. Tenma's arrest?
Congratulations, Lunge!
Huh?
You knew that Tenma was
hiding in Prague, didn't you?
Good work, Lunge!
Your persistent investigation
has paid off.
We've finished talking
to the Czech police.
Tenma will be transferred to
Düsseldorf tomorrow afternoon.
You're in charge of this case.
Come and take direct command!
Anyway good work, Lunge!
Congratulations.
Dispatch someone
other than me.
Huh?
Prague is a nice place.
What?!
Besides,
I'm on vacation right now.
Hey Lunge!
What are you talking about?
Hey!
Let me see Dr. Tenma!
I keep telling you,
you can't see him!
Tell me why!
This country is a democracy.
Tenma is already going to
be deported to Germany.
Just let me see him
for a bit before you do!
It looks like it was
all for nothing.
We came all this way
to Prague.
Please ! Just once!
Get out.
Come this way.
When we interrogate people,
what kind of person do you think
we have the most trouble with?
People who don't change their
expression, no matter what we say.
People who don't talk.
People like that.
"Love Letter from
the Monster to the Beauty"
It's like a draft for a novel.
"I've been watching you."
"I've been watching so
I could devour you whole."
"But instead, everything about you
consumed me."
"When I was falling apart,
how did I look to you?"
the object that you gave me..."
"You left me
a beautiful jewel."
"The twins who look as if they
were blessed with eternal life."
"The most sinful deed is to
take away a person's name."
"Let's get your name back."
"I'll give you your name back."
"Your name is.. .Anna."
"Right now,
I'm just sad."
"Sad."
It exists?
Many people died
in that room.
And an incredible
monster was born.