My consciousness awakened inside
a coin locker in complete darkness.
Blue...
The blue sky...
The blue sea...
And the blue window frame...
I want to go to Tunisia.
Gunter Milch.
Arrested in '88 for robbing a Bavaria
BASF Bank cash transport vehicle.
He was placed in
Badenburg Prison.
In '91 he escaped
from that prison.
In half a year, he managed to
cut through the iron bars of his cell
with a nail that he had
fashioned into a rasp.
Three days later...
He was caught.
He was imprisoned again
in Kreiner Prison.
But in '93 he escaped through
the sewage drain pipe.
His prison clothes were found next to
a nearby river, covered in raw sewage.
He was arrested while trying to rob a
Maximillian and Co. salary delivery truck.
In '97, in Ingebork
Prison's showers...
He spent a year making a hole
with a spoon and escaped.
The smell of the toilets
here is really terrible.
I crawled through sewage pipes,
so I'm sure of it.
Be quiet and walk!
What a miserable face.
Face forward!
I believe he was called Dr. Tenma,
or something.
Get walking!
I never would've thought he'd be
such a miserable looking guy
with a face like that,
devoid of any hopes or dreams.
I'll ask you once more.
Do you deny any involvement
in the poisoning of
Eisler Memorial Hospital's
Director Heinemann,
Chief of Surgery Oppenheim,
and Dr. Boyer eight years ago?
So you plan on keeping quiet
throughout the interrogation...
Cut it out!
Dr. Tenma.. .
what do you plan to do?
You'll still be sent to trial
even if you stay silent.
You have no chance in court.
Talk! Why don't you tell us
everything and get it off your chest?
What's wrong?
What's the fuss?!
Milch is suffering from
stomach pains!
Doctor!
Dr. Duller!
Where's Dr. Duller?!
The doctor is in the examination room.
Peter swallowed the janitors' detergent!
Do you think he's
choking on vomit?
What?!
I can't breathe.
Damn it. Let's call him.
Huh?!
The doctor.
Can you take a look?
Does it hurt here?
How about here?
Get some hot water!
And some towels
and a change of clothes!
Get out of the room!
This could be contagious!
Why are you
pretending to be sick?
Be nice.
You're the first doctor who
saw through my act this quickly.
I figured that I would have more chances
to escape if I were sent to a hospital.
Do you know how I rob
cash transport trucks?
I act like I'm sick and
jump in front of the truck.
When the guards came out panicking,
my friend comes out with a gun.
I never killed anyone.
Unlike you.
How about it?
Want to escape with me?
You have such
a miserable face.
You start to look like that
when you're in here.
I hate cramped spaces like this.
My consciousness awakened inside
a coin locker in complete darkness.
My father and mother left me in there
while they went to work.
I kept waiting to go home.
"Let's go to Tunisia some day"'
my father and mother always said.
My father said, "If work goes
well today, we're going to Tunisia!"
But I waited for three days
and they never came back.
My father and mother left me
and probably went to Tunisia.
I'm also going.
I'm going to get out of
this cramped place and go to Tunisia.
What a miserable face.
Your face has no hope.
You don't have hope like I do.
What will you do
if you're caught again?
I'm going to run away again.
I'll do it over and over again.
Now then...
Are you going to
stay quiet today, too?
The truth.
As we do this,
something terrible will happen.
The truth.
You won't believe me.
You won't believe what I say.
But I must fight!
Over...and over.
I must tell the truth!
Therefore, I sentence the accused
to 20 years of imprisonment.
The day my father was found guilty,
my way of life was decided
After the war,
my father moved from Sudetenland
in Czechoslovakia to Germany.
He started a small
radio station in '49.
But in the 60s, during the Cold War,
my father was arrested for spying
and for the murder of
a federal politician's secretary.
The news caused shockwaves
in West German society.
My father stood
by his innocence.
But he was sentenced to
20 years of imprisonment.
My mother continued to fight for my
father's innocence, and, in '71 , she died.
In '72, my father also
regrettably died in jail.
In '73, when I was in the gymnasium,
my father's innocence was proven.
After I graduated
from Düsseldorf University,
I was I was invited to join
the famous Hoffmann Law Office.
In the first case I was assigned,
I proved the innocence of
the falsely accused defendant.
After that, I've continued to disprove false
allegations in the cases I was in charge of.
I, Fritz Verdemann, went from being the
son of a spy to a hero in the legal world.
Over the Rainbow...
The radio station
that my father ran
would always begin and
end everyday with that song.
Oh?
To you and my father who were in the East,
it probably symbolized the free world.
Yes.
My father died in jail fighting
for his innocence.
To clear away that regret, I want to be
involved in as many cases as possible
where the person standing trial
may be falsely accused.
Tell me more
about Dr. Tenma.
Ilsa, how was
your prenatal check-up?
I'm doing well.
The doctor said that the baby
could be born any time soon.
You passed by a man in the lobby,
didn't you?
Yes. Is he the man who
you were talking about?
Yes.
Alfred Baul...
He asked me if I wanted to
represent Dr. Tenma with him.
Didn't you turn down
Dr. Tenma's case the other day?
Yes. But that time,
the client was Hans Georg Schuwald.
I wasn't sure why that tycoon would
want me to be Dr. Tenma's lawyer.
But, this time,
a different reason became clear.
What reason?
The clients that Mr. Baul talked about were
patients whose lives Dr. Tenma had saved.
Oh.
This Dr. Tenma was definitely
a wonderful doctor.
Why don't you
take up the case?
If I win the case, I can receive
a large reward from the tycoon,
but not so from the patients.
If you did your job for the money,
you'd have a larger office right now.
Oh. It's Over the Rainbow...
Turn it off.
Huh?!
Please turn it off.
O-Okay.
Anyway, let's go get
something to eat.
You've got to eat for yourself and
the new life that's going to be born.
Our baby's moving around
because it's hungry.
Well Missus...
What restaurant shall we go to?
Well...
What about that place?
Then he disappeared
into the flames.
That was the last time
I saw Johan.
Shall I tell my story from
the beginning once more?
I will keep telling it.
I will keep telling the truth.
You're the fourth lawyer
who's come to see me.
But they all want me admit to part of
the crime and try to lighten my sentence.
That's all they talk about.
Probably.
You seem like you don't want
to prove your innocence,
but rather prove the existence
of the young man called Johan.
That's right.
Then you don't
really need a lawyer.
Dr. Tenma...
When did this really begin?
As I said, a boy with a gunshot
wound to his head was carried in.
No, didn't something
happen before that?
A Turkish woman...
Bring back my husband!
After all, people's live
aren't created equal.
People's lives are equal.
I don't know...
if what I did was the right thing.
I don't know if my patients
are good or evil.
My sin is...
My sin is saving that boy's life.
But...
Does a doctor have the right
to choose who to save
based on whether
his patient is good or evil?!
People's lives
aren't created equal.
They're equal.
I don't know.
Even now, I can't tell.
It's the same with lawyers.
You can't tell if the accused
is good or evil.
I have a list of names here of the
people who asked me to represent you.
Mr. Michail Hotter, Mr. Stephan Crump,
Mr. Franz Kieffer, Mr. Rudolf Huber...
Mr. Kieffer... Mr. Huber.. .
They are doing well, huh?
Mr. Horst Henschel,
Mr. Harmut Hess...
Even Mr. Hess. .. I see.
I wonder if he's living happily
with his grandchild.
Time's up.
I see. Thank goodness.
Dr. Tenma...
I'll take up your case.
Even lawyers can't tell
if people are good or evil.
The only thing I can do when
I defend someone is to believe.
One more.
I said, "One more !"
Well Ma'am...
When did this place
start refusing my orders?!
Hey!
You just laughed,
didn't you?!
N-No.
You laughed!
You looked at me and laughed!
I remember you!
You used to come to my house often
and bow your head,
Mr. North Rhine West Bank
assistant branch manager!
What a look!
I've finally came back...
Eva Heinemann has
come back to Düsseldorf!
Thank you for agreeing
to meet me, Dr. Reichwein.
I've been calling you
ever since I heard that
Dr. Tenma had obtained
legal representation.
I'm sorry I'm usually not home. I've
been running around investigating.
Investigating?
Yes. I've been visiting Dr. Tenma's
former patients who are supporting him.
What did they say?
It seems that Dr. Tenma
is a wonderful doctor.
So did you get any
important testimonies?
No. I'd like if I could connect a
testimony to Dr. Tenma's alibi, but...
Anyway, in order to prove
Tenma's innocence,
we need to prove
Johan's existence.
Dr. Reichwein...
Huh?
Dr. Tenma said that he was going to
shoot the young man named Johan.
I'd like to cover up
that testimony.
Huh? W-Well...
That event is the only one
that can prove Johan exists.
Tenma is innocent no matter
if Johan exists or not.
Listen, Dr. Reichwein.
This country only wants a scapegoat.
My child will be born soon.
I want true justice for my child as well!
There are judges and lawyers who will
place the guilt on an innocent person
just so that they can wrap up
their cases quickly!
This entire country must repent
for its lack of justice.
That's what's important!
Dr. Reichwein...
Y-Yeah.
I'm searching for
someone right now.
She might know
something important.
She?
Dr. Tenma's former fiancée...
Eva Heinemann.
What's wrong,
Dr. Reichwein?
She's here.
Huh?
That woman came with me
to this town.
Everyone is always laughing.
Laughing at me...
Eva, listen to me.
I'm listening.
How annoying!
I want you to meet
Tenma's lawyer.
For Tenma...
Huh?
Didn't I tell you the other day?
I tried to shoot him.
I was surprised when
you told me that.
But you didn't shoot him!
Yes. I didn't shoot him.
Do you know why?
It's problematic for me
if he dies.
I won't let the man who ruined my life
die that easily!
He's got to be put in jail for the rest
of his life and regret what he did!
Regret for the rest of his life
that he dumped me!
She fell asleep.
What's wrong?
Were you dreaming?
Three gunshots.
I didn't see him.
I.. .didn't see the blond haired man.
Eva...
Did you see Johan?
Over the Rainbow...
A song that symbolizes
the free world.
Mr. Verdemann, your wife
has gone into labor.
She's been taken to the hospital.
What?
I see!
Klinger...
Contact Mr. Baul immediately!
Okay!
I was going to
see Dr. Tenma right now,
but ask him if he can
see Dr. Tenma instead!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Baul.
I came to see you today.
How are you?
Are you getting enough sleep?
Yes.
That's good.
Whoops.
I'm actually right handed.
I just can't get used to holding
a pen with my left hand.
My right hand doesn't move.
Do you remember me?
I've lost some weight.
Well, I'm even impressed with myself
that I escaped that sea of fire.
You really shot me.
This left hand...
It's still hard using pens, but it's gotten
quite used to handling a gun.
To tell you the truth, I was thinking of killing your former fiancée... Eva Heinemann.