Tell Helene and Gustav to tape
"Detective Forster."
Huh?
It re-airs on Tuesday at 10 AM.
You've never seen it? It's amusing.
Milch, come on.
Now's not the time
to be joking around.
Do you know how much
trouble you've given our boss,
screwing up and
getting caught like that?
He retained me as your lawyer
even though you're an idiot.
At least thank him a little.
He sent you watch over me
so I don't say anything, right?
That's right.
Listen, Milch, you know what's going
to happen if you tell the truth, don't you?
Don't worry.
I'll never sell out my comrades.
All right. Just file a confession
that matches my scenario. Got it?
Anyway, has my next job
been scheduled?
Next? When do you think that'll be?
Think about it.
You think about it.
Huh?!
Who do you think I am?
I'm Gunter Milch,
the king of prison escapes.
I have no time for
your silly stories.
Listen, if you give them
the confession I made up for you,
you'll get out in five years.
Tell them.
Huh?
I said, tell Helene and Gustav
to tape "Detective Forster."
Oh. But I can't really
count on them.
While I'm here in this police station,
I guess I'll try it out once more.
Try what out?
Do you think
he's faking it again?
I-I don't know.
But there was blood in his vomit
and his body is so cold.
Don't throw up here!
Doctor!
Ah. You came just in time.
- Huh?
Come take a look.
Some young folks we brought in
were getting rowdy on the third floor.
Several people were injured.
B-But.. .he looks like
he's going to die right now.
Milch again, huh?
Let him rest in the back.
I'll take a look at him later.
Th-Then take me to a hospital.
I'll come back immediately,
so wait for me.
Honestly. People just keep
bringing patients to me today.
Give me a break.
You're giving me the bed
next to a serial killer?
Why is he here?!
Don't complain!
This man collapsed from starvation.
He's receiving an intravenous drip.
I feel even worse
being next to this guy.
Shut up and sleep!
Doctor...
How many injured are there?
I don't know.
We won't know
until we go there!
Crap.
Those kids won't
get away with this!
What we talked
about the other day...
I need your help.
I want to escape.
I'm thinking of killing
your former fiancée...Eva Heinemann.
What do you think?
Don't you think
that's a good idea?
She knows too much.
On that rainy day, she heard three gunshots
in that building that was under construction.
She saw him.
We don't need people like that.
Isn't that right?
Stop. Stop.
Don't do it!
She... Eva won't
testify about that!
She wants me to spend
the rest of my life in jail!
She just wants me to spend the rest
of my life regretting that I dumped her!
She'll only testify against me.
So... So...
So that's why I'm asking you
whether you think it's a good idea.
If she's gone,
you may not have to go to prison.
Her death is advantageous
for the both of us.
Wii you tell the police?
I wonder if they'll believe you.
Wii you tell Verdemann?
He might be one of
my comrades.
We're brilliant lawyers.
We'll find a way to clear you.
When you finally get out,
you can have a good drink.
Because, by that time, that arrogant, noisy,
ruined woman will no longer be in this world.
I want to escape.
Give me a break!
I don't want to sleep
next to this murderer!
Hey, Milch, keep to yourself!
Just keep quiet or whatever!
Milch!
I'm going to confess and
be escorted to jail in five days!
I'll be able to bid farewell
to murderers like you!
What are you
yammering on about, Milch?!
You're healthy!
Come on!
You really were faking it!
Ah... What a relief!
I just have to put up with being with
this murderer for five more days!
Cut it out!
Hey! Be quiet!
In five days...
On that rainy day, you heard three
gunshots in a building under construction.
You saw a blond young man
come down the stairs.
Is that true?
That's right.
What do you think?
Can you continue working on this
case while ignoring Johan's existence?
W-Well...
Miss Eva Heinemann...
Would you be willing to make
this important testimony in court?
I don't want to.
What in the world does Dr. Tenma
want so late at night?
What does he have to tell us?
W-Well... Anyway,
he said to call an interrogator.
What did you want to tell us,
Dr. Tenma?
Dusseldorf's Eisler Memorial
Hospital's Director Heinemann...
Chief of Surgery Dr. Oppenheim,
Dr. Boyer...
And my patient,
Adolf Junkers...
I did it.
I killed them all.
The wind blew.
The bottle fell over.
The sandwiches were
covered in dirt.
That's when...
he smiled sadly.
According to the police announcement,
on the fourth before dawn,
Kenzo Tenma, who had been
denying all accusations
of involvement in
the multiple homicides until now,
suddenly gave a complete confession
of the murders of the director and
two other doctors of Dusseldorfs
Eisler Memorial Hospital
as well as the murder
of Adolf Junkers.
N-No way.
This news just in.
- A confession? That's impossible.
- According to the police announcement,
According to the police announcement,
on the fourth before dawn,
Kenzo Tenma, who had been
denying all accusations until now,
has admitted to
the allegations.
No way.
What did you do
to Dr. Tenma?!
What kind of torture did you subject him
in order to extract this false confession?!
Could you get
your hands off of me?
Shut up!
Let me see Tenma!
I'm going to meet him in person and expose
what happened to him during interrogation!
It's no use, Dr. Reichwein.
He refused to see me
though I'm his lawyer.
It seems that his confession
really was of his own accord.
That's impossible!
I've done some research.
I know the interrogators.
They're not the kind of people
that would use torture.
It seems that Tenma confessed
willingly. Astonishingly willingly.
Mr. Verdemann, could it be that you also
believe that Tenma's confession is real?
I can't tell his motives
unless I see him.
I believe in him.
Dr. Tenma is innocent!
I believe in him!
Verdemann speaking.
Oh, Mr. Baul.
I'm sorry for calling you
at this time.
I can't meet you there because
of some urgent business.
That's all right...
How was it?
Was Dr. Tenma serious?
Oh. He refused to see me.
How troublesome.
Just as we were trying to
prove his innocence,
he gives a complete confession.
In that respect,
your father was quite admirable.
He never caved in,
no matter how harsh his interrogation.
He continued to
plead his innocence.
His innocence.
Now then...
What should we do now,
Mr. Verdemann?
Huh? O-Oh.
That woman...
What did you say her name was?
The important witness who could
prove Tenma's innocence...
Oh. Eva Heinemann.
Where is she right now?
She's at a hotel in the city.
I'd like to meet her.
No. She's a pretty difficult woman.
I'll meet with her by myself.
My father was admirable, huh?
Open up, Miss Heinemann.
I know you're in your room.
The maid said that
she couldn't make the beds
because you spent the entire day
in your room drinking.
Miss Heinemann... I know very well
that you hate Dr. Tenma.
Your life would have
continued to go well
if your relationship with Tenma
had continued
even after you had lost your father,
the hospital director.
But Dr. Tenma dumped you.
Indeed, Dr. Tenma threw
your life into disorder.
My father...
My father was jailed on
suspicions of espionage.
For a long time, I was looked upon
as the son of a spy.
My father threw
my life into disorder.
But I didn't give in. Why?
Why do you think I kept on fighting?
Because I believed,
my father was innocent.
My father is innocent.
Innocent... Innocent...
Those I believe in
must be innocent!
Prove Tenma's innocence!
Tenma must be innocent!
Just like...
Just like how my father
had to be innocent!
Here's where you can
reach my partner and me.
Please contact us when
you feel like testifying.
What?!
He's being transported to
the detention center tomorrow?
It's only been a few days
since his confession.
It's because Tenma's
confession was so willing.
Can't we do anything,
Mr. Verdemann?
The police are trying to reason
with Tenma into seeing us.
Anyway
where's Eva Heinemann?
She went out.
Huh?
She's probably
drinking at some bar.
Dusseldorf...
I know all these places.
What a wretched town.
Oh. You're here?
I've been sitting here
for five minutes.
Oh. Sorry.
I was copying down
a very interesting essay.
Sh-Shall we move elsewhere?
Oh yeah. Let's go eat!
Where would you like to go?
Italian?
How about French?
Why don't you
keep on writing.
Huh?
Just stay there
and keep writing.
Oh. Eva...
Eva!
Is that so?
That's wonderful.
Isn't that delicious?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm placing stones so the wind
doesn't blow it all away.
That's not what I mean.
Why are you laying it out here?
It's nice to have lunch out here
every once in a while.
The weather is nice.
Who's having lunch?
We are. I made sandwiches.
I hope you like them.
There are bugs.
It's all right.
What is this?
Oh.
They're all covered in dirt.
It's a complete disaster.
Do you want to
eat one too, lady?
Hey, Franz!
That's rude!
Thank you.
Is it good?
Walk.
Get in.
Oh. Hello?
Mr. Verdemann wasn't answering,
so I called you.
Oh. His wife just gave birth,
so he's probably at the hospital.
I've heard rumors about you,
Eva Heinemann.
If you like,
you can talk to me.
I was thinking of talking.
About what?
Testifying to
Tenma's innocence...
I see. That's good.
So...
What hotel are you at?
I see.
I'll be right over.