The wind blew.
The bottle fell over.
The sandwiches were
covered in dirt.
That's when...
he smiled sadly.
Do you want to
eat one too, lady?
Hey, Franz!
That's rude!
Thank you.
Is it good?
Walk.
Get in.
Oh. Hello?
Mr. Verdemann wasn't answering,
so I called you.
Oh. His wife just gave birth,
so he's probably at the hospital.
I've heard rumors about you,
Eva Heinemann.
If you like,
you can talk to me.
I was thinking of talking.
About what?
Testifying to
Tenma's innocence.
I see. That's good.
So...
What hotel are you at?
I see.
I'll be right over.
They're going to dodge and
pass me by at this timing.
The car comes.
I fall down.
It comes. I fall. It comes. I fall.
This timing will do.
It comes. I fall.
- Hey... Hey!
- It comes. I fall. It comes. I fall.
What is it?
I'm busy now.
Are you really going
to marry me today?
How many times
do I have to say it? It's true.
Truly true?
Swear to God?
Yeah. Today, I'd swear it
to anything, Helene!
Then kiss me Gustav.
Let's keep going in the car.
Huh?
Whoa ! Hey, wait. You idiot!
Now's not the time.
You took my drugs again!
That was the last of it!
I didn't do it.
I thought it was strange
you were sniffling. You bitch!
You were getting high in the car while
I'm desperately practicing for the job.
It's a pretty easy job.
You just have to
lie in the road.
Easy?! How can you say that?!
If I make a little mistake, I'm dead!
You're going to die?
Take a look!
I'll be gone just like that!
I don't want you to die.
No. It's just hypothetical.
You're going to die.
I won't die. I still have
something I have to do.
What would that be?
Make a lot of babies with you.
We're going to make
a soccer team with just our kids.
Ah. .. Wonderful...Gustav.
I'll get money once
this job is finished.
Then we'll get married.
You'll grant me my wish,
won't you, Helene?
Oh, Gustav.
I'll make them.
I'll make many many children!
I said, "Now's not the time!"
No. I want to make children!
Control yourself for now.
It's almost time for
"Detective Forster" to re-air.
The car comes.
Jump out. I fall.
Jump out. Fall.
The car comes.
Jump out.
Fall.
The car comes.
I was thinking of killing
your former fiancée...Eva Heinemann.
Stop... Stop!
Don't do it!
The weather's nice outside.
Such a fine day,
but I'm stuck riding in this truck.
And I'm with this heinous murderer.
I'm really unlucky.
Keep to yourself, Milch!
But you're lucky.
Because in this drab transport truck
headed to a miserable prison.
You get to hear about the twelve
escape stories of Günter Milch,
the king of prison breaks!
Now where should I begin.
My jailbreak at
Kreiner Prison is great.
Keep to yourself!
Why? I'm bored.
What time is it now?
I said, "What time is it now?"
9:32.
If I were free, "Detective Förster"
would be rebroadcast soon.
Do you watch that drama?
It's good.
It's almost time.
I'm going to do this job easily.
Watch me from here.
A gun.
You're not going to shoot it,
are you?
I won't shoot.
I'm just going to use it as a threat.
If we had children, It'd be awful
if their father was a murderer.
Don't shoot!
I'll even give up the drugs.
I love you Helene.
I really made up my mind !
Let's get married!
Really?
From now on,
I'll go straight.
I won't take jobs where
I wave around guns.
Really?
Yeah. Jobs where I wave
this around aren't any good.
Gustav...
Ah... This feels great!
Damn.
Helene!
What?
I love you from
the bottom of my–
W-What is it?!
What's wrong?!
I-I hit someone.
What?!
You hit him?
Milch, sit down!
Can't you understand that
I'm telling you to sit down?!
It's probably my "little bro".
Huh?
The plan has failed,
Dr. Tenma.
I taught Gustav the timing
and how to act thoroughly.
I guess there isn't anyone
who can stop a car
by collapsing in the road like
a sick person as good as I can.
He's terrible at this,
so dodge him.
What good would it do
to hit him?
I don't know what
you're saying,
but anyway, check and see if
this man is the man you know!
Gustav...
Oh. .. Gustav...
Helene...
This is bad.
D-Do you think
he's still breathing?
This is bad.
Th-That doctor
is right over there.
Hey. .. Come here a moment.
Get out.
Hey!
Gustav is dead!
H-How is he?
Is he alive?
How could I?
How could I have
screwed this up so badly?
Gustav...
I'm stumped.
Let's smooth it over
in the report.
We can't smooth over
something like this!
W-Well... But...
The key.
Give me the key
to these handcuffs!
The key.
Give me the key
to these handcuffs!
Are you waiting
for someone?
Yes.
Would you like
something to drink?
Scotch.
No.
Get me a coffee.
Next in the news...
This morning, there was a fire at
a large shopping center in Dortmund.
According to the workers, they put out
the fire, but two stores were burned down.
There aren't any reports
of anyone injured in the fire.
I was thinking of talking.
About what?
Testifying to
Tenma's innocence.
I see. I'll be right over.
Please wait
in the hotel lobby.
What will I do if
I make him innocent?
This just in.
This morning, at 10:00, in Erkrath,
a suburb of Dusseldorf,
two suspects who were being sent
to Hilden Detention Center
escaped from
the police transport.
Details have
not been released,
but the names of
the two escaped suspects are
Gunter Milch, who's suspected of
robbing a money transport vehicle,
and Kenzo Tenma,
serial murder suspect.
The police have made
an emergency deployment
to locate and apprehend
the two fugitives.
Why?
Why did he escape?
Yes, hello?
Oh, Mr. Verdemann.
Yes, I heard the news.
Why do you have to escape?
I was just about to
prove your innocence.
Why?
I don't know what's going on.
I also don't
understand his actions.
Yes. Anyway,
let's go to the police.
But actually, there's something
I have to do before that.
I see. Yes. Yes.
That's right.
That's the situation,
so we should deal with this calmly.
Yes. Yes.
I think so, too.
This voice...
Anyway, we must
find out the details. Yes.
This voice...
Exactly. As you say. Yes.
Yes. I'll try my best. Yes.
Roberto!
Your coffee...
That's not my cigarette.
This smell...
It's that man's smell.
In this room...
Roberto was just in this room.
Gustav! Gustav is dead!
Helene, he's still not dead.
But it's no use.
He's not bleeding even though
he's hit his head.
It's a cerebral hemorrhage.
Isn't that right, Doctor?
I understand your feelings,
but we're going to switch cars
in the road in the woods
up ahead as planned.
Gustav is in the way.
We're going to leave him in this car.
No!
Keep going!
Huh?
There's no time to switch cars.
Don't be silly!
The police are
looking for this car.
They'll quickly catch up to us!
There's a possibility he'll be saved if we
get him to a hospital as soon as possible!
A hospital?!
Doctor, your quick wits turned
my failed escape plot into a success.
But as a pro,
I want you to listen to me.
It's terrible, but we've got to leave
Gustav in the road in the forest up ahead.
Go straight to the hospital!
The Eisler Memorial Hospital!
They have the best facilities
and staff in Dusseldorf.
It's the hospital where
I used to work! Quickly!
Up ahead is the hospital's
front entrance.
Don't cry!
When you get to the entrance, tell someone
to give this letter to Doctor Wagner.
The details of the accident
are written in it.
Gustav won't die?
He's still alive!
Don't give up while
he's still alive!
Go quickly!
Now then...
If we hang around here, it's like
telling them to come and get us.
You've been a great help.
Huh?
What are you going to do?
Where are you going?
You should stay with me.
You're an amateur.
There's a woman I know
whose life is in danger.
I've got to get to her quickly.
A woman?
Is that why you escaped?
You can screw as many great women as
you want if you escape with me to Tunisia.
Thank you. See you later.
Doctor.
You really never killed anyone,
did you?
I shot one person.
But he was still alive.
That's not killing.
You're going to get acquitted
in your case.
But you have
a real criminal record now.
You're a fine fugitive.
From one fugitive to another,
let's meet in Tunisia some day.
It's a great place!