Eva Heinemann?
Yeah, she came.
Even though she's ruined, her attitude
is still the same as it was before.
No, it's gotten even worse.
Did she say where
she was staying?
Oh. She said she had no cash on
hand and told me to get it from her hotel.
She probably still
thinks she's rich.
Which hotel was that?
She said it was
the Steigent Hotel.
I wonder if she's really
going to pay her bill.
Staying at such
a third-rate hotel...
Huh?
You. .. Come to think of it.. .
you were engaged to her.
C-Come to think of it...
Oh. H-Hello?! Police?!
J-Just now.. .
That serial killer...
Hey!
Huh?
Do you know
where my coat is?
Huh?
I hung my coat
by the entrance.
Huh?
Hello?
Oh, is Eva.
A woman by the name of Eva
Heinemann should be staying there.
Yes. I shall connect you
to her room.
Please wait one moment.
Oh, okay.
Hurry.
Quickly.
I was thinking of killing
your former fiancée...Eva Heinemann.
Hurry!
Thank you for waiting.
We called her,
but she's not picking up.
Get me her room number.
Oh, no, umm...
I-I'd like to send her a fax,
could you tell me her room number?
Please! Tell me!
She's in room 402.
Our fax number is...
402...
It's no good. Mr. Baul isn't in his office
and isn't answering his cell phone.
Your partner won't come
no matter how long you wait.
I'm guessing that he became Tenma's
lawyer to win Tenma's innocence.
But Tenma made a complete
confession and, in the end, escaped.
He couldn't defend that,
so he's resigned as Tenma's counsel.
Are you going to quit too,
Mr. Verdemann?
I don't plan on doing that.
But it's a fact that
Tenma escaped.
Before he escaped, as his lawyer,
I wanted him to trust me.
Then do you believe in Tenma?
Do you believe what
happened in Munich?
Do you believe everything
that Tenma has said?
You don't believe any of it,
do you?
When I heard the news
that Tenma escaped,
I had the same reaction
as I did back then.
When he disappeared from us
and tried to shoot Johan...
Something's happening again.
That's why Tenma escaped.
Believe in him.
Just like the way that you believed
in your father and became a lawyer.
The telephone's just been ringing!
The media is in an uproar
about whether Verdemann,
the great lawyer,
will continue to defend Tenma.
Tell them I have no comment.
B-But that won't
calm the media.
Tell them that I'll hold a press
conference after I've reexamined the facts!
Until then, don't let
anyone into my office.
Oh, but you have a visitor.
What?
You let him in?!
I won't see anyone today!
O-Okay. I told him that
and tried to turn him away.
But he insisted that
he was going to wait here.
Who in the world is he?
W-Well, he's with the German
Federal Criminal Police Office.
The BKA?
Over the Rainbow...
Such a nice song.
I believe it was the theme song of
the radio station that your father ran.
Wh-Who are you?
My name is Lunge.
406...
405...
404.
Room 402...
That's her room.
Guten tag.
Oh. G-Guten tag.
Um...
Huh?
Where's the guest who
was staying here?
Huh?
Oh. I came to visit the guest
who was staying in this room.
Huh? Didn't this guest
check out already?
Huh?
See? There's no one
here anymore.
Eva.
Inspector Lunge...
Of all the reports on Tenma
I've seen during my investigation,
I've taken the closest
look at your report.
It's an elaborate report.
I've also heard rumors about you,
Mr. Verdemann.
You're a hero in
the legal world.
You've probably come here upon
hearing about Tenma's escape.
But unfortunately,
I have no information to give you.
Escape, huh?
No. Actually, I'm on a long
vacation at the moment.
In a way, my long vacation may
have been an escape as well.
Umm. .. Excuse me,
but I have no time for chit-chat.
Perhaps it is a long work habit, but
I can't freely travel without direction.
I end up making themes
for my travels.
The theme for this journey
is this picture book.
Sorry. I don't have time.
Please leave.
No, let me talk a little longer.
You don't have anything
to say about Tenma?
I'm not here to
talk about Tenma.
Huh?
Besides, I only heard about
Tenma's escape on the way here.
Then why are you here?
As I said, this book...
I've become intensely interested in finding
out about the writer of this picture book.
But this writer has
had many pseudonyms.
Of them,
only Klaus Poppe was German.
I was curious
and as I investigated,
I came across someone
who was Poppe's acquaintance.
Someone?
Your father.
Your father's radio station had a
program called "The World's Fables."
According to records,
Poppe's work, "Where am I?"
Was aired in the August of '66.
I've seen records
of your father's trial.
It was the espionage case that
shook post-war West Germany.
So what about it?
Your father entered
Czechoslovakia several times.
He was just meeting with
a picture book artist,
so it wasn't examined
or noticed at all.
What are you trying to say?
Well, I'm suggesting that your father
might have been old friends
with this picture book artist.
My father had many acquaintances
involved with his work.
He used to meet with countless
people to arrange programs.
So you're saying that
they weren't that close?
But according to my investigation,
Klaus Poppe usually met people
at his chief editor's house
or at his vacation home,
an old farm in the Czech suburbs.
But your father met with him
at a certain mansion.
A certain mansion?
It was called Red Rose Mansion.
Poppe never used the mansion
under the name Klaus Poppe.
When he used the mansion,
he called himself Franz Bonaparta.
He was someone with a very important
post in the Czechoslovakian Secret Police.
What are you...
What are you trying to say?!
Spy kid! Spy kid!
Son of a traitor!
Son of a coward!
Hey! If you don't like that,
prove that he's innocent!
If the father's dirty,
the son's dirty, too!
Spy kid! Spy kid! Spy kid !
Spy kid! Spy kid! Spy kid! Spy kid!
I just want to learn
about Franz Bonaparta.
I know of no such person!
In Czechoslovakia in '66,
your father met Klaus Poppe
at a certain mansion, didn't he?
A picture book artist and
the owner of a radio station.
That's all they were!
When he went by
the name Klaus Poppe,
he never used
the Red Rose Mansion.
What are you trying to say?!
When he met your father
at the Red Rose Mansion,
he wasn't meeting him as Klaus
Poppe, but as Franz Bonaparta.
As someone who was important to
the Czechoslovakian Secret Police.
That's a false charge!
I don't care whether or not
your father was a spy.
My father wasn't a spy!
Your father should have known
who Franz Bonaparta really was.
He's not involved!
Your father knew what went on in
the Red Rose Mansion, didn't he?
No!
My father is innocent! No!
Contact me when
you feel like talking.
I'll keep on saying it: I don't care if
your father was a spy or not.
I just want to learn
about Franz Bonaparta.
My father is...
Mr. Verdemann,
you have a call from your wife.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Umm... Your wife is
calling from the hospital.
Okay.
Hello?
I see. You're finally getting out, huh?
That's good.
Yeah. All right.
I'll come and
pick you up right now.
Tenma!
Drive the car!
C-Calm down.
Listen to me.
Drive the car, quickly!
Quickly!
You'll understand if we talk.
Anyway, calm down, Tenma.
Tell me what you have to say.
Where's Eva?
Huh?
Where is Eva Heinemann?!
W-What are you talking about?
What about Eva Heinemann?
Don't act dumb!
I know what you guys
are trying to do!
"You guys"?
Don't stop the car.
Look ahead and keep going!
I know that you're
both after Eva's life!
"Eva's life"?
"You guys"?
Don't play dumb!
Your partner...
You're partners
with that man, Baul!
Baul?
He's the man I shot at the library
at the University of Munich!
I won't allow any more casualties.
Answer me! Where is Eva?!
It all began when
I saved Johan's life.
He's taken many lives
since then.
Many, many lives.
I've had enough!
I won't let there
be any more victims.
Don't stop the car!
Is that true?
I said, "Move the car!"
Is it true,
what you just said?
Is it true?!
Can I trust you?!
My father...
was suspected of espionage.
Afterwards,
I proved his innocence.
But he really was a spy.
I believed in my father's innocence
and studied hard to become a lawyer.
But I found something
when I was a student.
Decisive proof that
my father was a spy...
Ever since then...
Ever since then,
I could never believe in anyone.
"The great, crusading lawyer?!"
"The hero of the legal world?!"
Don't make me laugh. A man
who doesn't believe in anyone...
I really was the son of a spy.
Ever since I found
that notebook...
Ever since I found that notebook
that my father had written in the 60's.
As I flipped through
the pages of that notebook,
everything I had believed
about my father crumbled.
There was no mistake.
My father was a spy.
The notebook had records of contact
with the Czechoslovakian Secret Police,
written in
an indecipherable code.
The mysterious people that my father
contacted included Franz Bonaparta.
Was something about the Red
Rose Mansion written in there?
How do you know about that?
So that's it.
Huh?
That man, Baul, probably got close
to you so he could get that notebook.
Where is that notebook
right now?
At my house.
This is bad.
There's no mistake.
He was after your father's notebook.
It's a letter addressed to you.
He predicted that
you would come here.
"Help me, Kenzo.
Help me, Kenzo."
"Come quickly to
the Red Rose Mansion."
Does this mean
that Eva's safe?
No.
This isn't her handwriting.
He's toying.. .
He's toying with me.
It's safe.
It's in the pile of old records.
Over the Rainbow.
This is the notebook.
Take it.
But if someone gets it,
your father will...
I don't need it anymore.
Can I trust you?
What you told me...
What you're doing...
I can't be of any help.
But can I trust you, Dr. Tenma?
You shouldn't trust anyone, who
carries one of these around, too much.
I want to believe.