June 19, my first meeting
with Franz Bonaparta.
RF-17-9.
He's a very quiet man.
He behaved elegantly
and wore a suit.
In the afternoon, he gathered
the children for a book reading.
Where do you want to go?
To the border.
Which border?
The Czech border.
Get in.
Thank you.
In the afternoon, he gathered
the children for a book reading.
A very strange mansion...
Red Rose Mansion...
P-Brevnov W..
A steeple to the left...
A weather vane
to the right...
Human dignity...
Experiment...
Amazing experiments...
Deprivation of dignity...
Where are you from?
Huh?
I said,
"What country are you from?"
Oh. I'm Japanese.
I don't know if a Japanese man
would like this, but...
Eat this.
It's leftover from my lunch.
Thank you. But...
Eat.
You look like you're
going to collapse.
My wife has been nagging me
to go on a diet.
Then I won't hesitate.
Yeah. Eat, eat!
You won't be able to last
the long journey if you don't eat!
I've got to finish this journey.
What?!
You let him go?
You just let Tenma go?!
Yes.
Why didn't you stop him?!
You know that you can't stop him.
But...
Especially since Eva Heinemann
is now missing.
It's a race against the clock.
That's why Tenma escaped.
That lawyer called Baul
is probably the same man who
tried to kill me at my clinic.
He was planning to take my father's
notebook by getting close to me.
That notebook must be
pretty important.
Let's go.
Where?
The place where
Tenma is headed...
The Red Rose Mansion...
Where is it?
My father's notebook is filled
with unintelligible descriptions.
I don't think that part is code.
Red Rose Mansion,
P-Brevnov W...
"P" stands for "Prague"
and "W' means "west."
The Prague suburbs to
the west of Brevnov.
It's somewhere you can see a steeple to
the left and a weather vane to the right.
I see.
I hope that
there's a witness
who will get us closer to solving
this case at that mansion.
But at this point...
No.
Huh?
An entry in the notebook said that children
would gather for recitals in the afternoon.
Those children are
our witnesses, huh?
Mr. Vardemann...
I scolded you for
letting Tenma go,
but had I been in the same position,
I'd have done the same thing.
Let's go.
I was here.
I lived in this town.
And...
Welcome home
Are you all right, Nina?
Yeah.
I'm all right.
I think that
you should give up.
You get lost
every time you try.
No. I'll remember.
My brother talked to me
at that time.
When he was taken from
the "Three Frogs"...
What he passed along the way
and where he was taken...
When he passed the station,
a streetcar ran along the riverside
as he watched the town to his left...
Turn right here.
Don't...
Don't keep secrets from him.
Turn right?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
What do you think?
Notice anything?
I don't know.
It's no good.
You won't be able to remember a
conversation from such a long time ago.
Nina!
A weather vane to the right...
A church steeple to the left...
Nina!
The Red Rose Mansion...
Is this it?
I don't know.
But. ..I know this place.
"I'm afraid"...
What is that?
It looks like the door just
emerged out of the wall.
There's nothing in this room.
Huh?
Nina ! Nina ! Nina!
You demon!
You demon! You demon !
The demon is dead.
How do you feel?
Welcome back, Mr. Lipsky.
Did you have an audience?
No. I was terrible, as usual.
But they're such
wonderful dolls.
The one I'm making right now
is even better.
I'd like to see it soon.
I'll show it to you
right after I finish it.
It's time to go to work.
The restaurant?
Yeah. I can't make enough
just on dolls.
I'm sorry for staying here
for so long.
No. It's all right.
Don't worry.
Mr. Lipsky,
I want to ask you something.
W-What is it?
Three months ago, you found me
unconscious and took me to the hospital.
Yeah.
Why were you
at that mansion?
Nina! Nina!
Nina!
Answer me, Nina! Nina!
What happened?
When I go to that mansion,
I get ideas for my stories.
How should I say this?
Umm...
But right now,
rather than that mansion...
No, that's all right.
Anyway, don't be shy.
You can stay here
as long as you like.
Nina...
Can I come in?
Of course.
Should you be up?
It's okay. Amazing!
So this room is where
your dolls are born.
I don't have an audience,
though.
What's your play about?
It's the story of a demon.
What's wrong, Nina?
Nothing. Continue.
A demon sets out on a journey in search
of a dragon that will destroy the world.
On the way, he nearly dies.
But a boy who's passing by
saves his life.
When the boy realizes who he's
saved, he chases after the demon.
At the end of his journey,
he finds the demon.
And with a knife in his hand,
kills the demon.
I think it's interesting,
but it isn't popular at all.
Are you all right, Nina?
I think that I would do that.
Huh?
I would do that.
But I mustn't let him do that.
Nina?
A human would...
save that demon.
You think so?
I think that he'd like this story.
"He?"
This shelf...
They're all picture books.
Jakub Farobek. .. Klaus Poppe...
Emile Scherbe.
The Nameless Monster...
You know him?
He wrote many picture books.
Jakub Farobek. .. Klaus Poppe...
Emile Scherbe...
They're all pseudonyms
for the same person.
The person called
Franz Bonaparta.
Franz. ..Bonaparta.
People can become
whatever they want to be.
I wasn't a brilliant child,
so I was thrown out of the recitals.
Recitals?
He held recitals at
the Red Rose Mansion.
I was a student there.
I knew what
he was trying to do.
"A deal. Let's make a deal"'
said the demon.
"No, never"' said the man
with the big eyes.
"Sure. Let's make a deal"'
said the man with the big mouth.
The man with the big mouth's yard
became a flower garden.
The man with the big eyes was
very hungry because he was very poor.
The man with the big mouth
had so much fun everyday.
He was very full from eating the fruit
harvested from his garden,
so he didn't realize that
his flower garden was withering.
The man with the big mouth
cried and cried
in the garden that
would never grow again.
"I shouldn't have made a deal
with that demon." he cried.
The big-eyed person
was dying of hunger.
As the tears fell,
he cried,
"I should have made
a deal with the demon"
"A deal. Let's make a deal."
the demon said.
Jakub Farobek's
Jakub Farobek's The Man with the
Big Eyes, the Man with the Big Mouth.
We'd gather every Friday
at 3 PM for the recital.
We'd gather around him and listen,
he'd read to us in a kind voice.
In a kind voice...
A very kind and gentle voice...
And once he was done
reading a story, he'd ask them...
"The meaning of this story. .."
You understand it don't you?
I-I understand.
I also understood after
reading it several times.
Then he'd take the next book.
Klaus Poppe's
The God of Peace.
Let's read this one next.
It's as if I've come here
for the first time.
Though it's taken quite some time...
all my memories have come together.
The God of Peace
was very busy.
He blew his trumpet every day. He
didn't have the time to look in the mirror.
The God of Peace's trumpet
made everyone happy.
The God of Peace was very busy.
He poured the mysterious water. He
didn't have the time to look in the mirror.
The mysterious water made
the mountains green,
made the fields grow,
and made fields of flowers.
The God of Peace was very busy.
He gave everyone names. He didn't
have the time to look in the mirror.
Your name is Otto.
Your name is Hans.
Your name is Thomas.
Your name is Johan.
In appreciation,
Johan gave the God a lovely hat.
The God was very happy.
He wanted to see what
he looked like with the hat on
and, for the first time,
he stood before a mirror.
But there was a demon
reflected in the mirror.
The demon said,
"You are me and I am you."
"What should I do?"
said the god.
"No one can live in peace
with a demon here."
"What should I do?
What should I do?"
The troubled God...
Do you know
what he did next?
I know.
Do you know?
Do you know what the God did?
I know.
We finally meet.
I'm back. Welcome home.
It's me, Mother.
Even you couldn't tell us apart,
could you, Mother?
She is me and I am her.
You are me and I am you.
I understand everything.
Where we came from
and where we're going.
The weather's nice outside,
Mother.
Everything will be in flames.
I know.
The God...
points a gun
to his forehead...
Shoot me.