Shoot me.
Are you ready?
No need to be nervous.
Your hair clip is crooked.
I'll fix it.
Smile.
That's right.
You look very cute.
Now let's hold hands.
All right. Let's go.
Mr. Liebert who fled to
the West a few days ago
appeared before the press
with his wife and children.
Mr. and Mrs. Liebert
did not appear to be tired.
And their twin son and daughter
are both wearing bright expressions.
Mr. Liebert, what do you
think of West Germany?
It's very tough.
Huh?
When I realize that I'm free to say whatever
I want, I'm unable to find any words.
I see.
Anyway, the answer to that question is in
the smiling faces of my wife and children.
Your children also seem
to be enjoying their freedom.
Yes. So it seems.
Now then, would you care to talk
about the current situation in the East?
Big brother.
What are you doing?
Big brother...
Which hand is it in?
Hmm... This one!
Correct.
Here. It's yours Anna.
Yay, an acorn!
Once more.
Which hand is it in?
Hmm... This one!
Correct again.
Here, it's yours again Anna.
Amazing!
Brother, open up
both of your hands.
What? Either one
would have been correct.
That's right.
All the acorns here
are yours anyway Anna.
Hey brother, did you see
the town on the way here?
It's completely different
from the other side.
There were lots
of pretty shops.
There were also
lots of clothes and toys.
You saw them too,
right, brother?
Yes. I saw it.
All that's yours too, Anna.
Really?
Really.
Why are they mine?
Everything is yours.
I saw you on TV, Mr. Liebert.
Anyway, just come in.
Brother... Is somebody here?
Brother...
Brother?
Brother... Did you do it?
All this time?
How Mr. Josef
and Mrs. Ciara died...
How Mr. Bedger died...
Did you do it all?
Today was special.
Did you do it brother?
Today. ..the monster came.
You killed all of them,
didn't you?!
The monster came
to take us away.
Hold out your hand.
Shoot me.
After you shoot me, wipe the gun with
a cloth and throw it out the window.
Be sure to shoot me
in the head.
After you shoot me,
run away.
Run away so the monster
can't catch you.
It's all right. Even if I die,
you are me and I am you.
That night... That rainy night.. .
Someone came.
Nina?
Someone came
to that mansion!
Nina?!
Who?! Who came?! Who?!
The monster came.
Nina!
This is pretty bad.
Why was the house on fire?
No one lived here.
They are saying it was arson.
How terrible.
Dr. Tenma...
Can you come with us
for a moment?
General Wolf
wants to see you.
General.. .Wolf?
General Wolf...
Doctor. ..Tenma...
Yes?
You were called upon too,
weren't you?
Johan wrote a letter to me saying that
he'd be waiting at the Red Rose Mansion.
But I was just barely able
to get to Prague hospital.
You've received
that letter, too?
How ironic.
Johan is now the only person who
sends letters to the man called Wolf.
You shouldn't talk too much.
I was born into a military family.
I was promised a life as one of the
chosen ones since the time I was born.
But now. .. The one who knows me
as I know myself is that monster.
I heard that the Red Rose Mansion
burned down.
They're probably revealing
themselves right about now.
Those whose names
were taken, like me.
Were you able to determine
where the fire started?
Yes. It seems it was a hall
on the second floor.
From the concentrated flames in that
area, it was probably kerosene or gasoline.
Kerosene?
I guess it was arson.
We can't be sure unless
we investigate carefully.
There are signs that a wall
in the hallway was broken down.
What does that mean?
Who knows?
U-Um...
C-Come here a moment!
What's wrong?
This is...
I dug it up when I saw something
at the base of the rose bush.
They just keep coming out.
They'll reveal themselves
after many years.
But no one knows
their names any longer.
This is terrible.
It's completely burned down.
Our only clue to find Tenma.
At this rate...
Out of the way.
Let us through!
Out of the way!
What's this?
C-Contact headquarters!
This is an emergency!
Skeletons!
Tons of human remains!
46?
Yes. That's what I've heard.
In 1981 , 46 people suddenly
vanished in that mansion.
It was among the intelligence
I had received in East Germany.
They were doing an experiment
at that mansion.
An experiment...
Move back, move back.
This is my deduction.
Turn away any onlookers!
Those children were
probably born there.
Brother... I'm cold.
I can't walk anymore.
I'm hungry.
Brother.. .
Are we going to die?
Brother... Say my name.
Say my name.
We have no names.
Say my name. My name...
Get a blanket.
Yes!
And some water to drink.
"Because Johan was
such a wonderful name."
Johan...
Those children had no names.
When I gave that child the name
Johan, something awakened inside of him.
No. There's no point in
talking about the past.
Let's talk about the future.
Though, I no longer have
a tomorrow.
That's enough,
General Wolf.
Don't talk any more.
Eva Heinemann is...
Eva Heinemann is. ..
with people from my organization.
The four of us formed
our organization.
There's Professor Geidlitz,
who was killed, and me...
Eva.. .is with the other two.
He's trying to use Eva.
They mustn't come together.
Whether I live or not,
I can no longer stop it.
He's going to go wild.
Stop him. Save us, Tenma.
Doctor Tenma...
My name is Helmut...
Helmut Wolf.
There's no longer anyone
who knows me as Helmut.
Call me. ..by my name.
It's the proof of my existence.
Helmut...
My name...
Helmut.. .
You're Helmut Wolf!
So this is what Johan saw.
A world without names...
General Wolf...
It burned down, huh?
The gate is locked.
The police probably made it off limits.
It's useless.
Mr. Lipsky...
I understand how important
this place was to you.
You went to the recitals here
when you were a child.
But...
Nina. .. It should have been
an important place for you as well.
This might have been the place that
could have brought back your memories.
That vision...
Many people piled up dead in
a large hall in this mansion.
The vision you had was true.
I was surprised when I saw the news.
They said that they found the remains
of 46 people at the Red Rose Mansion.
Was it as your brother...
as Johan said it was?
What did my brother. ..
Johan see?
Something terribly frightening?
True fear?
If I had been there at the time...
If I were there,
would I have become the monster?
Nina... It might have been a good
thing for this place to burn down.
I thought that it would
be more painful.
I thought that I couldn't live
if I lost this place.
But I just don't feel that way.
This place is just
full of sad memories.
I wasn't a superior pupil.
That was sad.
I couldn't meet his expectations.
If...If I had been able
to meet his expectations...
But that wasn't the case.
I became unwanted.
Mr. Lipsky what about
your mom and dad?
They are alive.
But.. .I've never lived with them.
Your memory...
If your memory comes back Nina,
I hope they are fun memories.
Fun memories?
Yes...fun memories.
I wonder what fun memories are?
Tenma told me...
If you don't have any fun memories,
you just have to make them.
Tenma said that we should
just start making them.
Dieter, you've got ketchup
around your mouth. It's all red.
You too, Nina!
Huh?
Nina...
I'm making a new puppet play
right now.
What's it about?
No one's ever wanted
to watch my puppet plays.
But people might like this one.
Show me your new work!
I wanna see it!
I am a girl who's
lost her memory.
I had a dream that I was
being chased by a monster.
chasing a monster.
But I like to sing.
I like to dance too.
Someday,
I'll have a wonderful dream.
that dream will come true.
Someday...
I can't figure out
what comes next.
I'd like to make this girl's story
have a happy ending.
But I still can't think of one.
I'd like to make it
a happy ending.
Thank you.
The girl made up her mind
to go on a journey.
She doesn't know what
kind of journey it will be.
is waiting for her.
But the girl will courageously
continue her journey.
The girl turns and waves her hand
again and again.
Again and again...
And she is gone.
To search for
a happy ending.
Nina!
Nina, you've come b–
I've been looking for you,
Mr. Lipsky.
You're the owner of
the Red Rose Mansion...
Franz Bonaparta's son,
aren't you?