If I had known this
was going to happen...
I never would have
taken that job.
I didn't like it
from the beginning.
It'll be all right! Relax!
Th-That wound is nothing!
We'll be at the hospital soon!
I told you it's not a hospital.
He's a doctor,
but it's not a hospital.
The Helbrau Hotel...
I-I know what
you're trying to say!
If we go to a doctor, the police will
come and you'll go to prison again!
But, unfortunately, we don't have
the time to go to that unlicensed doctor!
Go to the Helbrau. ..Hotel.
Prison or your life!
As long as you're alive, you can.
Hurry up!
The Helbrau Hotel!
This is why. ..nothing good comes
from dealing with women.
I'm begging you, hurry.
Take me to Doctor Tenma.
Don't be rude.
The person we're going to meet
usually doesn't see people like you.
In that case, I should have
brought an autograph book.
If you fool around,
I'll kill you.
Come in.
This man is Martin,
my subordinate.
You can leave now.
Huh?
I'm saying that I want to speak
with this man in private.
Oh.Yes.
If you really screw up,
I'll kill you.
May I sit here?
Go right ahead.
How long have you been
with "The Baby"?
It's been almost three years.
What about before that?
Prison, huh?
How many years?
Eight years.
Murder?
Pretty much.
Despite that,
you've gotten out pretty quickly.
I was well behaved.
You also seem to be well behaved
when it comes to your work.
I'll do anything.
Whatever job. Except...
Except?
Except any job
that involves women.
Oh?
Well, I don't choose my jobs, but I
don't want to get involved with women.
It involves a woman.
I want you to keep watch over
a certain woman for a while.
What a terrible job.
I want you to go to Düsseldorf
and bring me a certain woman.
You say that you don't want to
get involved with women?
Then this job is perfect for you.
You seem like you'll be more
professional about this job.
Ms. Eva Heinemann?
Who are you?
Martin...
Well, my name doesn't matter.
I was told to take you
to Frankfurt.
By whom?
A man with glasses
who wore a nice suit.
A man with glasses?
He's not with Roberto, is he?
I'm not too sure.
He seems to be important.
I won't force you to go
if you don't want to.
I'm not too enthusiastic
about this either.
Someone's after me right now.
Oh?
Will you be my bodyguard?
Well, that's kind of
part of my job, so...
Wait for me.
Carry this!
Let's go. This is better than
being killed by that man.
What an unpleasant woman.
The way she swings her hips.. .
The smell of her perfume...
It's annoying.
What a terrible job.
Why don't you talk?
Well... If that's what you want.
What shall we talk about?
I don't really want to talk.
Then let's be quiet.
How about a drink?
Do you have any alcohol?
Unfortunately, I don't drink.
I'm going to
check the dining car.
I see. You're traveling alone.
I'm by myself, too.
Well, if it's all right, could you
tell me where you're staying?
Oh, this is my card.
What are you doing?
W-What am I doing?
This woman told me
to give her a drink.
Don't touch her.
Why aren't you talking
while we eat?
Like I said,
I'll talk if you like.
Why haven't you
had anything to drink?
My mom was
a terrible alcoholic.
Well, I don't mind if you drink.
Your mother probably
had a good reason to drink.
You think so?
Yes. I also have
a good reason to drink.
Well, tell me about it if you don't
want to eat in silence.
It will take a while.
Please, go right ahead.
I had a fiancé.
He was a Japanese
neurosurgeon.
He was brilliant.
Then...
Then I tried to shoot
my ex-fiancé.
Aren't you surprised?
I tried to kill him!
But you didn't shoot.
It's better than my story.
What is your story?
Tell me.
I shot her.
I saw my girlfriend straddling
another man.
I shot the both of them until
I was out of bullets.
The room was filled with
the smell of her blood,
his blood and the scent of perfume.
When I came to my senses,
I was standing there by myself.
You are such a fool.
Aren't I?
What a terrible job.
My client is waiting
in this hotel.
You said you killed someone.
Don't touch me.
What room?
I'll take you to him.
Your attire. ..
doesn't match this hotel.
Wait here.
It's room 1014.
What a terrible woman.
I don't know what the man
with glasses is going to tell her,
but if she turns him down,
this terrible job will be over.
I won't have to
see her anymore.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
It wasn't such a bad proposal.
He said that I could use
this card as much as I like.
What are you doing?
We're going now.
Going? Where?
Shopping.
What a truly terrible job.
This place next.
This is a men's store.
I have to make you look
somewhat decent as well.
This is good enough for me.
I don't like it. I don't want the man
accompanying me to look unsightly.
This is good.
And for your tie...
Kenzo...
Try it on.
A tie... How awful.
How is it?
Well...
Hmm.. .
You look somewhat decent.
But.. .tie your tie properly.
Stop walking with your shoulders
slouched like a thug.
I'm walking normally.
Your idea of normal
is not normal.
From now on,
you're escorting me.
Wherever we go,
make sure you don't embarrass me.
It's your job, isn't it?
Yes.. .that's my job.
Don't put your elbows
on the table.
Fork in your left hand,
knife in the right.
Don't make sounds
when you eat.
So it's true.
What is?
What you told me.
You told me that you were the daughter
of the director of a large hospital.
Did you think I was lying?
Until I brought you
to this town, yes.
You looked like nothing more
than an alcoholic.
Were you wrong?
You thoroughly look
the part of a rich woman.
This is my true form.
Eva Heinemann has returned
to the place where she belongs.
What is that?
An invitation to a party.
A party?
Yes. It's the job I was given.
Job?
I have to attend several parties.
That's all.
Aren't you glad?
It seems like a fun job.
You're coming with me.
You must escort me as
someone worthy of me.
This job getting more
and more terrible.
What do you think?
How does it feel to be back
in your stomping grounds?
What's so funny?
What are the people gathered
here talking about?
The weather? Stocks?
I don't even know what
language they're speaking.
I'm starting to feel sick.
So there you are.
Yeah. Don't mind me.
Enjoy yourself.
We're going.
Huh?
We're leaving.
Huh? Oh. Hold on.
He's not at this party.
The job's over.
He's not here?
Who's not?
Take me away from here!
Anywhere is fine.
Just take me away from here quickly
Why was the woman's hand
trembling?
I didn't know at that time.
I managed to survive today.
What's wrong?
Didn't you return to the place
where you belong?
In the past,
I lived like that every day.
Once I entered that world, I
thought that the real me would return.
But now you only find bars
like this relaxing?
I don't belong here either!
Not here, not there!
No matter where I go,
there's no place where I belong!
I know that!
Once this job is over,
I'll probably be killed.
I thought it would be better than being killed
by Roberto in Düsseldorf in a shabby state.
I thought it would be better to be killed
as the beautifully attired Eva Heinemann.
But it's all the same
if you're dead.
I thought that
I should protect her.
My bad habit came back.
I wound up thinking that
I should protect her.
Damn. How in the world
did this happen?
Th-That's what I'm going
to go tell Dr. Tenma.
G-Get a hold of yourself!
We're close! We're almost there!
A tie... If I didn't have this,
I wouldn't have had to go there.
I wouldn't have had to
see such a terrifying thing.