What'll you have?
The usual.
What was "the usual"?
When are you going to
remember it Robby?
A hamburger, double cheese, extra
ketchup, and thick slices of tomato.
I'll kill you if you
put pickles in it.
How am I supposed to
remember that?
That Chinese or Vietnamese guy
is sniffing you out.
He's been coming here often.
He was asking who you were.
He's not Chinese
or Vietnamese.
Oh?
He's probably Japanese.
And he's a neurosurgeon.
And a brilliant one at that.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Answer me!
And you used to be engaged to
the hospital director's daughter.
What are you planning
to do with Eva?
Eva?
You're being too
familiar with her.
When are you going to stop
thinking of her as your fiancé?
From what I hear, you're no
longer a doctor, but a fugitive.
Just get in there and get out.
If you behave you might
get out one day.
Let Eva go.
Let her go?
I haven't been confining her at all.
Actually, she's been going
to parties every day.
Let me. ..see Eva.
"Let you see her"?
Hey, hey.
Don't mess up my shop.
Don't hang around
here anymore.
Get out of here.
E-Eva...
Get lost.
You saw Kenzo?
Yes, two days ago.
Thought I'd let you know, just in case.
He wanted to see you.
You didn't hit him, did you?
N-No. I wouldn't do that.
We're leaving.
Huh? Did you have
enough of today's party?
For today.
Or rather, the party is over.
I think.
Good work, Eva.
How about dinner?
Let's go.
So you dropped her off with
your client at the restaurant
and you're eating
dinner here?
The hamburgers here
are way better
than the food at those parties
and expensive restaurants.
I'm not sure whether you're
praising me or insulting me.
You sure are persistent.
Do you want to
get hurt again?
What part of "get lost"
don't you underst–
Don't move either,
Mr. Manager!
If you move, I'll shoot!
What a dangerous doctor.
Who hired you?
I know that your immediate boss
is The Baby.
But the person who ordered you
to escort Eva
is someone further up
in the organization.
Who gave you your orders?!
I don't know who he is.
But. ..I know his face.
He wears glasses.
A man with glasses?
What is he making Eva do?
I told you, didn't I?
He's just making her go to parties.
She drinks, eats, and leaves.
That's it.
That can't just be ! Eva should have
been ordered to perform a specific task!
Nothing.
Come to think of it, today...
Today...
No, it's nothing.
She pointed.
Pointed?
To a young man.
A young man...
Like this.
He was a young blond man
with a pretty face.
That was it though.
Where is Eva right now?
She's having dinner with my boss,
the man with the glasses.
W-Where?!
Tell me quickly!
Where are they?!
Eva's job is probably over!
Once this job is over,
I'll probably be killed.
The party is over.
Where is Eva?!
Wait!
W-Where is she?
I dropped her off at her hotel.
Do you have a gun?
N-No. I try not to
carry one around.
Then use this.
Kill her.
That party was the same
as it always was.
The smell of alcohol,
the smell of perfume,
meaningless laughter...
It was the same as always.
Except for that one moment.
The moment when Eva
pointed at a young man...
When she did,
the man with glasses appeared with
another well-dressed young man.
Then, those two young men
shook hands.
I didn't notice it at the time.
It seems that that's when
Eva's job was over.
I knew that you would be
the one to kill me.
Go right ahead.
The drinks are settling in nicely.
I have no lasting regrets.
Oh, that's right.
You can't shoot me in this hotel.
You told me before that
you shot your girlfriend
and found yourself in
a pool of blood, right?
Take me outside
and shoot me.
If you don't, you'll have to pay
for messing up the room.
Oh. I do have one regret...
one last thing.
But. ..it doesn't matter.
I wonder what I did today?
You saw me pointing,
didn't you?
I probably did
something terrible.
I let a terrible person and
a demon come together.
Did I bring Mephistopheles
and Faust together?
But it doesn't matter.
It looks like I don't need to
go to parties anymore.
But I still have my invitation
to the next party.
If you want, you can go and confirm
what I've done after you shoot me.
Now then. .. Finish me off.
Let's run away.
Run away with me.
You seem to be getting
the wrong idea.
Run away with you?
You're kidding, right?
When did we
become so friendly?
I can't kill people anymore.
Can't kill people? Are you saying
that you could kill a devil?
I'm a devil.
That suit and necktie
I bought for you
were the same as the ones
that Kenzo used to wear.
Understand? I was just turning you
into Kenzo Tenma.
Kill me.
Kill me quickly!
Quickly!
Kill me...quickly.
If you don't kill me quickly...
you'll be killed.
Kill a devil, huh?
Hey, wake up!
It's all right.
I'm just sobering up a bit.
No! You'll die
if you sleep here!
It's all right.
Just leave me here.
You look depressed.
I'm always depressed.
Did someone come
looking for me?
No, no one. But the Japanese man
from yesterday left this.
Helbrau Hotel, room 205.
He said to call him
if something happened.
What will you have?
The usual?
Not now. I won't feel like doing anything
if I fill myself with your crappy burgers.
Where are you going?
A party.
How strange. I can go anywhere
if I have a necktie.
With just this...
There he is.
So is he a devil?
He shook hands
with so many people.
So many that his hands
were probably swollen.
Then he left the party.
Floor six, huh?
But which room is his?
Please come in.
Right this way.
Have a seat.
Don't hesitate.
You want to meet him too,
don't you?
Him?
I'm waiting for him as well.
He'll be here soon.
Before he comes,
let's talk about something.
What should we talk about?
Oh yes.
Let's talk about
the end of the world.
The young man happily talked.
Like a child who was
telling his parents
about something fun that
happened at school that day.
That's how he talked to me.
The end of the world?
The silly talk of a fanatical young man.
That's what I thought
at the time.
What do you think?
Interesting, isn't it?
Were you amused, Martin?
How do you know my name?
Oh yeah,
let's talk about you next.
You've been with The Baby for
almost three years, haven't you?
You looked me up?
Before that,
you were in prison.
Eight years...
That must have been terrible.
You got out on good behavior, right?
You sure got out quickly, for a murder.
Was it fun living
with your girlfriend?
The girlfriend you shot.
Her name was.. .Edda.
That's in pretty bad taste, boy.
She was quite
the drug addict wasn't she?
You desperately tried
to get her clean.
That's pretty difficult to do.
Was it love?
Do you want to get hurt?
She recovered. She made dinner and
waited for you to return home each day.
Your happy life
together began.
I said, "do you want
to get punched?"
But that night...
When you returned to your room,
you saw something outrageous.
She was with her ex-boyfriend.
She had done drugs again.
Though disoriented, she saw you and
said over and over again, "I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry."
But you shot her along
with that man.
That was the story at your trial.
Why did you lie?
She killed herself, didn't she?
Your lawyer determined
that she killed herself
because there were traces
of gunpowder on her hand.
But you stuck to the story
that you shot her.
She asked you to kill her,
didn't she?
Am I right?!
I'm right, aren't I?
I thought so.
You weren't the one who shot her.
Back then, she told you
to shoot her, didn't she?
Shoot me.
Don't look at me like that!
Kill me.
Kill me!
Martin!
I didn't do it.
She shot herself!
It wasn't me!
Right? It wasn't me, right?
I thought so. Amazing.
I'm right, aren't I?
No.
You left her behind.
That's how you
granted her wish.
No.
Then what about your mother?
Your mother froze to death
when you were ten.
At that time,
you left your mother behind.
Am I right again?
Amazing, amazing. I'm surprised.
I really got it right.
Everyday, you'd carry
your alcoholic mother home.
Isn't that right?
Your mother would always tell you
to leave her where she was.
Even so, you'd carry her home
every day. But that night...
No, you can't sleep here.
It's all right. It's all right.
Leave me right here.
Wake up!
You left her there.
Isn't that right?
You left your mother there.
The next day, you were informed
that your mother had frozen to death.
But at that time,
you thought that you weren't at fault
and that you left her there
because she told you to.
That's right.
You're not at fault.
Your mother and your drug-addicted
girlfriend both wanted to die.
You were letting people who
wanted to die, do what they wanted.
You're not wrong.
You're right.
You released them
from the pain of living.
Eva also wants to die.
It was at that moment...
the devil arrived.
I passed by him,
careful not to look.
Like a child, I repeated to myself,
"Don't look, don't look. Don't dare look."