No, you can't sleep here.
It's all right. It's all right.
Leave me right here.
You left her there.
Isn't that right?
You left your mother there.
The next day, you were informed
that your mother had frozen to death.
But at that time,
you thought that you weren't at fault
and that you left her there
because she told you to.
That's right.
You're not at fault.
You were letting people who
wanted to die, do what they wanted.
You're not wrong.
You're right.
You released them
from the pain of living.
Eva also wants to die.
It was at that moment...
the devil arrived.
I passed by him,
careful not to look.
Like a child, I repeated to myself,
"Don't look, don't look."
"Don't dare look."
Eva also wants to die.
Kill me!
Leave me right here.
Kenzo...
I'm not going to do the devil's bidding.
Because nobody wants to die.
Where's the woman?
Eva's not here anymore.
Where did you let her escape?
I finished her.
Don't lie, Martin.
If you tell us now...
I'm not lying.
How pitiful.
What is?
To lose your life
over a woman.
Are you up?
Our pursuers are here.
They've parked
their car outside.
It's only a matter of time now.
I took a maid's uniform.
Wear it and escape
out the back way.
What about you?
Wandering out together would be like
telling them to come and get us.
But they'll get you
if you don't run away!
I can handle them by myself.
Go to the place that's
written on the note, on the desk.
It's Tenma's hotel.
Get dressed. Hurry!
I'll be waiting at
Frankfurt Central Station.
Let's run away together.
Cut it out.
This isn't the time for jokes.
Listen ! You'll be safe if you go
to Tenma. It's what you want.
This is an order! Go now!
I don't remember having to
take orders from you.
Just kidding.
I'm going.
Okay.
Don't get yourself killed
doing something stupid.
I don't owe you that much.
See you later.
Right.
I don't owe her anything.
I don't have to go
this far for her.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
I can't believe I'm alive.
Frankfurt Central Station, huh?
No more bullets.
I really am unlucky.
You idiot. Aim for the head.
There was a gunfight at the Reagen
Motel in Sossenheim, Frankfurt.
Four men were found dead.
The police believe it was
a gang related dispute.
The police are questioning
motel employees about the incident
- Robby. Did you hear that, Robby?
- and are tracking down the culprit.
- That's my heroic story.
- None of the employees were injured.
Robby?
In other news...
We're here, Martin.
Huh? Frankfurt Station?
Hey... Doctor.
I've done as much first aid as I can.
I can't do much more here.
Let's go to a hospital.
Stop.
I already know.
It's probably no good.
Eva...
Where is Eva?
What happened to Eva?
Didn't she come here?
Why are you laughing,
you idiot!
Don't talk anymore.
I can't do that.
Listen to me, Dr. Tenma.
Where should I begin?
I know far too much
about so many things.
The experiments at the Red Rose
Mansion are still continuing.
Do you know what I mean?
Also...the devil now
has an apprentice.
That man is trying to
create a dictator.
"That man?"
The man with glasses.
The survivor of Red Rose Mansion...
Peter.. .Čapek...
Peter. ..Čapek.
He is trying to
control the devil.
But the devil is...
The devil is far more terrifying.
Far more.
The Jahreszeit Hotel...
Room 606...
The devil's apprentice is there.
You mustn't look at the devil.
Can't do his bidding.
Nobody wants to die.
Martin!
I'm...happy...
I don't have to
look at the devil anymore.
Eva... Eva is waiting for me
at Frankfurt Central Station.
I'm sure...she bought
two tickets.
For as far as...
For as far as we can go.
Eva is waiting there?
Please protect. ..Eva.
Eva...
Don't die.
You've got to go
to the station, right?
Don't die. Don't die!
Even if you stay there, there's still
a lot of time until the first train comes.
Are you waiting for someone?
Ah, a man right? I can tell.
I've been working at
this station for a long time.
Then do you know if
he's going to come?
I don't know that.
I'm not a fortuneteller.
But having someone
to wait for is happiness.
Whether he comes or not.
Happiness?
Yes! When you get to be my age,
you don't get that feeling that often.
Happiness, huh?
Oh, could this be the person
you were waiting for?
Kenzo!
Martin is...
dead.
It seems he's not the person
she was waiting for.
He came to tell me
some important information...
with the last bit of
strength he had.
You have to leave, quickly.
Eva...
There's still time
until the first train.
Can you stay with me a bit?
Sure.
It's not alcohol,
is that all right?
That man, Martin...
didn't like alcohol.
I see.
To Martin.
It's been a while.
Yeah.
Are you eating properly?
You've gotten pretty thin.
Yeah.
It's strange. We're holding
Martin's funeral together like this.
He was a good person.
I did such a horrible thing
to such a good person.
I made him wear a suit and tie
like the one I gave you.
How horrible. I'm horrible.
Why am I still alive?
I also gave false testimony against
you and continued to pin the guilt on you.
Why am I still alive?!
Because Martin protected you.
Why did he?
Why would he protect
a woman like me?!
Nobody wants to die.
That's what Martin said.
He said he was happy that
you were waiting at the station.
He said he was
happy about that.
Munich...
Go to Munich.
I know a psychiatrist there.
Dr. Reichwein...
Do you know him?
Yes.
Anyway, stay with Dr. Reichwein.
He'll take care of you.
And go to the police.
Tell them that you're being chased by
The Baby's organization in Frankfurt.
And that Roberto's after you.
Tell them everything.
I'll tell them about you too.
You haven't killed anyone!
It was all Johan's doing!
I'll tell them everything.
So come to Munich too...
He's right in front of me.
Huh?
He's so close.
You saw him
at the party, didn't you?
Johan's right in front of me.
I've got to end this.
There can't be any more
victims like Martin.
Do you understand?
I've got to end this.
I'll send a letter to Dr. Reichwein.
I'll give him all the information I know.
Kenzo...
Now go.
But Kenzo...
The only way you can help me
is by going to Munich
and telling everything
you know.
I'm glad you helped us
find Johan.
I appreciate it.
I heard that there
was someone
who matched his description
here in Frankfurt.
That's why I had you
identify him.
Excuse me interrupting your dinner.
You have a telephone call.
Okay.
Hello? It's me.
Johan...
I see. Where is he?
An apartment on
Haldecker street.
"An apartment on
Haldecker street."
Johan...
even I can end all this.
The Jahreszeit Hotel...
Room 606...
The devil's apprentice
is there.
Are you the one
that wanted a gun?
Yes.
I have all sorts of guns.
I want the biggest one
you have.
Beginners can't handle
the big ones.
What are you
planning to shoot?
A devil.