You found a job as a waitress
and got a place to live.
But this bed is terrible.
It sinks in this far
when I get on it.
It wouldn't be able to support
your weight if you slept here.
I'll sleep on this bed.
You should sleep on that sofa.
There's no place
for you to sleep here.
Huh?
Go back to Dr. Reichwein
in Munich.
Why?
Why? Because you
have to go to school.
I don't have to go to school.
How will you learn anything?
You're teaching me.
It's not just about your studies.
You won't be able to make
any friends living like this.
I have friends. You and Tenma.
Besides, you'll be lonely without me.
Anyway, you should
go back to Munich.
No!
I'm not going to Munich.
H-Hold on, Nina.
Are you going there today, too?
Hey, wait!
You should give it up already.
You've been going to
the same place everyday!
It's always the same ! You're
not going to remember anything.
Nina!
We lived here.
Mom and I. ..and Johan.
That day, Johan was dragged
down these stairs and taken away.
No! Stop! Let go of me!
Mom ! Nina!
No. Nina is my name now.
What was I called then?
Nina? Anna?
What is my name?
The car they put Johan
into went along this road.
Don't keep secrets from him.
They gathered children here
and held what they called "recitals."
Here in the Red Rose Mansion.
The lock's broken.
They were trying to create
a "superior pupil" here.
What's a "superior pupil"?
Johan?
They also...
Who did it?
He escaped.
Johan ran away.
He went through
the rose bushes.
Ow!
Are you all right?
This pain...
Huh?
Could it be?
I.. .was waiting in this room...
for Mom to come home...
for Johan to come home...
while I was reading this picture book.
People can become
whatever they want to be.
Franz Bonaparta...
Bonaparta held the recitals
at the Red Rose Mansion...
I read one of his books as
I waited Johan to come home.
I smiled as I faced
the open door and said...
Welcome home.
Welcome home. Welcome home.
Now then, come here.
The door won't open!
The door won't open
even when I say, "Welcome home !"
It won't open!
That's because I ...
I remember! I was...
Stop it Nina!
You don't have to remember!
You don't have to remember anything!
I'm the same!
I have a lot of bad memories!
But you don't have to
remember any of that!
Fine, I'll go to Dr. Reichwein !
You too Nina, let's go back together!
Let's do as Tenma said!
We'll make fun memories
from now on.
Wait a second, Chief Detective!
All I can do is sit next to
a detective and just listen?
What's the meaning of this?!
We're trying to satisfy
your requests as best we can.
"As best you can"? In addition,
there's a thirty-minute limit per person!
Just listening to them
should be enough.
The fact that we are helping you
this much is quite extraordinary.
We went through
a lot of trouble
and were finally allowed to
question these five witnesses.
Still...
You should have taken the opportunity
to get as many testimonies...
You're naïve.
Huh?
Those "children of the recitals" probably
don't want to talk about their pasts.
Well, the large amount of human
remains that we discovered definitely
has something to do with the former
Czechoslovakian secret police.
But you know...
The truth about things like this
usually remains a mystery.
Oh. He's the detective
in charge of the case.
This is Mr. Verdemann.
He's the lawyer from Germany.
Take care of the rest.
I'm Detective Suk.
Pleased to meet you.
I prepared the questions in advance.
Please do exactly as I tell you.
You will sit with me
only as an observer.
Number 3 Cerveny Street,
a.k.a. "The Red Rose Mansion."
It's burned down.
Currently, it looks like this.
But there is no mistake
that you participated
in the "recitals" here in 1968,
right, Mr. Erno?
How about it?
Have you heard of
Franz Bonaparta?
Can you please be quiet?
We're running out of time,
aren't we?
I just want to be thorough.
Do you want to be thorough
and end up with no information?
You don't know how hard
we worked to get this far.
I don't feel sad.
I thought this mansion was
my emotional foundation.
Upon seeing this image
of it burned down,
I thought that I would
feel sadder, but...
Do you feel nostalgic about it?
Nostalgic?
Yes. This was like
a school to you, wasn't it?
Mr. Verdemann, please be quiet!
The questions that I prepared are...
I don't know.
Sadness... Nostalgia.. .
I don't know...
Emotional scars?
What do you mean?
Well, is there anything
that affects you now
because you participated
in those "recitals"?
Well... Not really.
What about your family?
You don't have to answer.
You have that right.
I'm divorced.
Well, there weren't any big problems
between my wife and me, but...
My children... My oldest son and
my second son. ..committed suicide.
We didn't really
have any problems.
But for some reason, they...
I wonder why they
committed suicide.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just saying all your questions
are "by the book."
How much have you been able to
get out of anyone so far?
You're a typical youth of today.
You probably try to ask girls out
"by the book" as well.
You're acting like a father.
I don't have a father, but I wouldn't
like to have a father like you.
Will the next person come in?
Memories of the "recitals", huh?
Anything you can recall,
no matter how trivial.
"The God of Peace
was very busy."
W-What are you?
"He blew his trumpet every day. He didn't
have the time to look in the mirror."
Klaus Poppe's The God of Peace.
You know it, don't you?
Yes. I kind of remember it.
Aside from that,
I liked the one about the Monster of
the West and the Monster of the East.
What did you like about those stories?
Hmm... How should I put it?
It felt like I was being taken
to a different world.
A different world?
Well, I guess...
crying, being happy,
and being afraid...
I suppose it felt like all of
those things just disappeared.
Why did you feel that way
about this book?
I don't know.
I didn't feel a thing.
You didn't need
your own name anymore.
That's true freedom.
That's what it felt like.
Why did you feel like that?
Franz Bonaparta taught you
to feel like that, didn't he?
Was that the name of
the person who held the recitals?
That's what you clearly remember
from the recitals, right?
Clearly remember?
No.
One day, a man came
to visit that mansion.
He said he was
from a radio station.
He said that he liked the song,
Over the Rainbow.
He told me about
The Wizard of Oz.
What kind of man was he?
Tell me! Tell me about him!
What are you thinking?!
- Tell me!
- Cut it out!
Please, anything!
What are you trying to do?!
It's like your personal emotions
are influencing the questioning!
This is personal for you, too.
You're the young detective
that was falsely being accused
for the series of crimes
committed by the secret police.
You're him, aren't you,
Detective Suk?
You're desperate to prove
your innocence. Am I wrong?
The same goes for me.
My father was imprisoned
for being an East German spy.
I continued to believe that
he was falsely accused.
But my father really was a spy.
I could no longer believe in anything
after I found out.
I no longer believe in
anything in the world.
But now, I am pursuing a case involving
a man who has been falsely accused.
And because of that, I have once again
found something that I can believe in.
The man from the radio station
that the witness talked about...
was my father.
My father might have participated
in the brainwashing experiments
that happened at
the "Red Rose Mansion."
In order to find out the real truth,
you mustn't look away.
Say, can I go home already?
No, just a little longer.
About that man I told you about.. .
He told me, "Get out of here...fast."
"There is definitely a wonderful place
over the rainbow."
"It's where your family is"'
he said.
"Dorothy from The Wizard of Oz
gets to go home in the end."
"You must get away
from here fast"' he said.
So I cut all ties
with that mansion.
Is that enough?
My wife and kids are waiting.
Y-Yeah.
We mustn't look away.
Yeah.
There are two more witnesses
left to question.
Yeah. Let's continue.
Come on, Dieter.
Stop spacing out and hold it steady!
This is your study desk.
O-Okay.
Nina doesn't want to talk about
that happened in Prague.
According to what
I heard from you,
she's probably recovered
quite a bit of her memory.
But it seems like
the brakes were hit
right before her memories fully
came back to her, thanks to you.
Did I do something wrong?
No.
Dieter, you did a good job.
Now let's finish this quickly and
have some weisswurst and beer.
We ate all the weisswurst
last night.
Oh. That's right.
Oh no!
Doctor!
We bought your favorite,
weisswurst.
How considerate of you.
Oh.
Dr. Reichwein, how are you?
- I'm sorry for not
- Nina!
- Contacting you for so long.
- Lotte!
I'm sorry for making you worry.
I'm safe.
Dr. Reichwein, to be honest,
I would like to ask you a favor.
I'm sure you know a woman by
the name of Eva Heinemann.
Right now, she's being pursued
by a certain organization.
I've sent her in your direction.
Please take care of Eva.
And please take care of
Nina and Dieter.
I'm almost finished.
I think this is the only way
to put an end to the case.
"Sincerely, Kenzo Tenma."
This letter came
three days ago.
And there's still no sign of Eva.
Where was this mailed from?
You can't see the postmark
very clearly.
Can you look it up, Karl?
Yeah. Probably.
If we do that,
we'll know where Tenma is, right?
But.. .I'm a bit worried
about this last sentence.
"I think this is the only way
to put an end to the case."
Now then,
let's finish this study desk.
I drank a beer,
so my hand might slip.
Dr. Reichwein.
I think I can almost
remember everything.
When you do remember everything...
Are you prepared for that?
Yes.
Use whatever method necessary
to bring my memories back.
Honestly, I don't want to do anything.
But if you really want to...
You're fine with this,
right, Nina?
Yes, Dr. Gillen. But...
Whatever I say under hypnotherapy.. .
might be incredibly terrifying.
Will you face it with me?
Yes. I'll be fine.
Let's face this together.
Now close your eyes.
Take a deep breath and
relax your whole body.
What was your mother like?
My mother...
My mother...she's nice...
songs. ..singing voice...
a beautiful singing voice...
The smell of pea soup.
What about your father?
My father... My father is...
a government soldier.
A government soldier?
Have you ever met him?
I've never met him.
My mother told me.
My father.. .was killed.
My mother. ..participated in
anti-government activities.
Your father was killed,
and your mother,
an activist who participated in
anti-government activities, escaped.
Who was she
running away from?
The three frogs...we hid.. . but a
man in glasses caught my brother.
Your brother was caught, right?
The Red Rose Mansion!
Many people were dead.
Did your brother see that?
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts! The rose thorns...
It hurts!
Welcome home.
Nina?
I found out where Tenma
mailed his letter.
Where is it?
Frankfurt.
Nina? You've remembered everything,
haven't you, Nina?
I'm.. .not Nina.
Then who are you?
I don't want to say.
It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Tell me.
Who are you?
I don't want to say.
It's all right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I don't want to say.
Huh?
I'm back.
I-I'm going to clap
my hands right now.
Then you're going to
wake up from your trance.
Nina!
I-It's all right.
Did I say something
terrible just now?
No.
While you were hypnotized,
you refused to talk about it.
But you remember everything now,
don't you?
Dr. Reichwein, Dieter...
Please forgive me
for leaving suddenly.
I'm going to Frankfurt,
where Tenma is.
I know everything.
Who I am. Where Johan has
come from and where he's headed.
If I go, I can end everything.
If I go, I can save Tenma.