The experiments at Red Rose Mansion are still continuing.
The devil now has
an apprentice.
The man with glasses...
The su
Peter. .. Čapek...
He...is trying to
control the devil.
Follow that car.
He got away!
Where...
Where am I?
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Oh. Well...
You're lucky.
You just sprained your ankle.
From the looks of it,
you didn't hit your head hard.
But I'm not an expert like you.
You know about me?
Dr. Tenma,
a brilliant neurosurgeon.
I saw it in the newspaper.
Who are you?
I'm a dentist here.
Milan Kolas.
I happened to see you get hit by a car.
The car took off.
You should rest more.
No. I'm troubling you.
Wandering out on those legs and
getting caught around here by the police
would trouble me even more.
"Around here?"
This is Frankfurt's
Turkish neighborhood.
Turkish neighborhood?
No. I should say that it was
the Turkish neighborhood.
Most of this area has been
cleared for redevelopment.
Most of the Turks who lived here
have moved away.
A while back, when right-wing
extremists tried to burn it down,
we all joined together
to fight them.
Is the Café Bahir gone too?
Yeah. It's long gone.
Do you know this area?
Yeah. A little.
By the way, if you can get up, would
you like to have dinner over there?
Meals taste better when
eaten together, don't you think?
Today we're having Vietnamese food.
Minh made it.
It's pho ga and cha gio tom.
Minh's Vietnamese food is
exceptional. Don't be shy. Eat.
It's delicious.
I love pork,
but the Turks forbid it.
Czech food isn't good.
That's because Milan's
terrible at cooking.
Sorry about that.
Everyone takes turns to make
the food from his or her homeland.
It's pretty extravagant to be eating
food from different countries every day,
don't you think?
Dr. Tenma, you're Japanese,
aren't you? How's Japanese food?
Japanese food, huh?
That's right.
Make some next time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well...katsudon uses pork.
And sushi... There are some
people who can't eat raw fish.
How about Oyakodon?
Oyakodon?
Yes. Chicken covered
with eggs and sauce on rice.
Why is it called an "oyakodon"?
The chicken is the parent
and the egg is the child.
And that's why it's called
a "parent-and-child bowl"?
Who knew Japanese food
had a sense of humor!
How amusing to refer to chicken
and eggs as parent and child.
What's wrong, Tenma?
It's nothing.
Is the food not to your liking?
No. It's delicious.
Such delicious food...
Such a fun meal...
It's really been
such a long time.
Good night, Tenma
Good night.
How long will it take
until I can walk?
I don't have the time to waste.
Peter. ..Čapek.
A gun?
A report of Peter Čapek's
movements?
You knew it was odd,
didn't you?
The police didn't gather here
so they could catch you.
The police were on
the look out for me.
I'm...going to kill.. .
Peter Čapek.
It's no good.
That's odd. I used to be able to
make ones that flew really well.
Milan is good at making
paper airplanes.
They fly smoothly over
to that roof there.
I see.
Milan always says to us...
He always promises us...
Soon enough, we'll go much further
than those rooftops.
We'll go to Turkey, Vietnam,
even to the Czech Republic.
We'll all go and see each other's
homelands together.
Right?
Right.
There!
It wasn't any good.
Why won't it fly?
That's odd.
I'm...going to kill Peter Čapek.
Why? Mr. Milan,
why would you do that?
That man...
That man Peter Čapek
is a devil.
In 1989, the night before the collapse
of communism in Czechoslovakia,
he escaped into this country.
Čapek settled here
in Frankfurt
and began giving lessons
as a German language teacher.
He was a quiet man.
But after a while, there was a change
in the children who attended his classes.
One by one, the children who took
his classes began to commit suicide.
Then they began to display
extremely violent behavior.
Finally, one day,
there was a massive violent eruption.
It looked like the children
were trying to kill each other.
I talked to the boy who was
the ringleader of the incident
at the place where
he was being detained.
He mumbled, "I want to go back
to the recitals immediately."
Recitals?
That night,
the boy killed himself inside his cell.
He was my son.
Čapek disappeared from
the town during the riot.
The next time he appeared in town,
he was like a different man.
He was leading an underground
organization in Frankfurt.
He had allied himself
with right-wing extremists
and he began to eject the Turks
and other foreigners from this town.
I don't know what
he's trying to do here.
But the pinnacle of
his violence was in 1996,
when he tried to burn down
the Turkish neighborhood.
You know about this incident,
don't you?
Yeah. From the news.
The people in this town formed
a neighborhood watch group
and tried to fight them.
But in just three months,
the five leaders of the neighborhood
watch died in strange ways one by one.
Who are the five who died?
Suleiman's son, Tung's father,
Minh's husband...
Mustafa's son,
and Shemel's father...
They didn't die.
They were murdered
by Peter Čapek.
I don't know why
you're watching Čapek.
But I will say this.
The one who's going
to kill Čapek...is me.
Just hold on, I think this one is
going to work much better.
It's hopeless.
No. If we try...
Even if you try hard,
impossible is still impossible.
I know. There's no way that we can
go on a trip to Turkey and Vietnam.
We don't have to go on a trip.
We can continue to live
with Milan and Tung.
I'm done.
It'll fly this time.
There.
See?
All right! It's flying!
That's amazing!
I guess it's impossible
to make one
that goes beyond that rooftop
like Mr. Milan can.
But it's flying, somewhat.
Aren't you glad
you didn't give up?
- Yeah !
- Yeah!
You can't give up.
Where's my gun?
Where did you put the gun
that was in my drawer?
I've got a chance
to shoot Čapek.
I'm going now.
Give me back my gun.
I can't let you do that.
I can't give you back your gun.
This is the gun that
was in your coat.
I want to do the job with a gun that
I've trained with and that I'm used to.
Give me my gun.
You have a family now.
You shouldn't do that.
I've been following Čapek's
movements for a long time.
There is no better chance
to go after him than now.
Please stop, Mr. Milan.
I told you not to interfere.
Even if you take your revenge now,
the dead won't return.
Furthermore...
You have to think about the future.
You have no right
to tell me that.
Mr. Milan...
We're the same, Dr. Tenma.
I looked you up.
If what you claim is true,
we're doing the same thing.
He wasn't always like this.
The man I knew...
wasn't a devil.
Peter Čapek and I are childhood
friends from the same county.
I invited him to this country!
What do you think
is across the border?
You shouldn't go there.
I know I shouldn't,
but do you know?
I heard it's a wonderful place
beyond the border.
There's a town where
it's bright all night.
Is that true, Peter?
Who did you hear that from?
Mr. Gregor.
He's an alcoholic.
They say that
across the border,
there are things that can ruin a man
just like what happened to Mr. Gregor.
Something that
ruins people, huh?
I want to see that.
You want to see
something like that?
Go!
It caught the wind!
You're really good, Milan!
It's flying! It's flying!
Amazing ! That could really
cross the border!
Look at what's on
the other side for us!
We were raised in a town on the
Czechoslovakian and Austrian border.
I was the son of a laborer.
He was the son of a bureaucrat.
But, oddly, we got along.
In 1989, when the Czechoslovakian
Communist regime collapsed,
the one who helped him defect. ..
was me.
The one that brought that devil
to this land was me.
I was worried about you during
the Soviet invasion last year.
Many people I knew were
dragged off, though.
But I'm here safe and sound.
How about you?
Me? I'm scraping by here and
there as a rookie dentist.
Milan's a dentist, huh? You were always
skillful with your hands, weren't you?
I want the kind of skills that get you
ahead in the world, like you.
Indeed, the reason I kept my position
even after the Soviets came in,
was probably because
I'm good at getting ahead.
I even had a lot of fun
during the "Prague Spring."
I even got to go to the West.
We talked about that when
we were young, didn't we?
We wondered what it was like
on the other side.
Did you get your answer?
Yes.
And?
There was nothing.
On this side or that side.
This country is wrong. But that doesn't
mean that the other side is right.
I see.
You said that I'm good at
getting ahead in the world.
But actually, there's someone
who saw something in me.
Oh?
When you meet him,
he's so wonderful that you stop
caring about your present situation.
Just when I had concluded that
there was nothing in either country.
He showed me a light
I never knew existed.
He will bring forth
something entirely new.
And? What's he
going to bring forth?
He'll bring forth? Well...
It could be something frightening.
Thinking back on it, something inside
of him might have started coming apart.
Give me back my gun.
Here. I'll give you
back your gun.
No. Mr. Milan...
you can't do this.
You can't stop me.
I'm going to kill him.
You have a family you're with,
right now!
And he's killed several members
from this family.
They were killed because
I brought him to this country.
Even my son...
After that attempt
to burn down this town...
there was one person the Turks
speak highly of, even to this day.
There was a Japanese man who
desperately tended to the wounded...
and tried his best
to put out the fires.
It's you isn't it, Dr. Tenma?
I believe in you.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're the same as me.
I'm going. It's time.
If I let this opportunity go,
I might never get another chance.
Mr. Milan!
Thank you for trying to stop me.
If I was in your shoes...
I doubt I could stop you.
What's this?!
This is delicious!
Yeah. This is really good.
Japanese Oyakodon
is really delicious!
Is your leg all right?
Shall I help you, Dr. Tenma?
No. I'll be finished with
your portion soon, Mrs. Minh.
Milan sure is late.
I think he should be home soon.
Oh. It's best to eat it
as soon as it's done.
- I'll make Mr. Milan's portion later.
- Next in the news...
- Really? Then I'll leave you to it.
- At about 11 A.M.
at the Roedelheim Convention Center
in Frankfurt,
there was an incident where a man
with a handgun, opened fire.
Police who were providing security for
the convention shot and killed the gunman.
There were
no other casualties.
But due to the large number of important
figures present at the convention center,
there was significant cause for
concern among the attendees.
The gunman's identity and
motives are still unknown.
We now turn to a clip of the incident
that happened to be caught on tape.
Everyone says it's delicious.
It's a hit!
I wish Milan would
come home soon.
And now the footage
of the incident.
That man...
He's Red Rose Mansion's...
That's...
Don't keep secrets from him.