Where's the guest list
for the reception?
I've got it.
We have a pretty good understanding
of where all the guests were
during the incident.
Was the governor
the gunman's target?
All of the guests are VIPs.
Most of them probably have enemies.
Anyway, continue checking
for any connections
the guests might have had
with the gunman.
The Frankfurt station
is in a state of chaos
over the convention center
shooting, isn't it?
Yes.
Even though we know who the culprit
is, we don't know who he was after.
Oh? You know
who the culprit is?
Yes. He's a dentist from
the redevelopment section of town.
A dentist, huh?
How terrible.
What's wrong?
Nothing... I was thinking of going
to a dentist after I retire.
I've been busy every day,
so I haven't been able to go.
I don't want a crazy dentist.
Inspector, right this way.
Okay.
I'm Inspector Visbaugh
of the Nordrhein-Westfalen
police department.
Reinhart Dinger, age 42,
occupation, taxi driver...
Suspected of killing a passenger
in Gunter Forest Park
as well as the '97 murder of
a Bilker Investment Bank employee,
the '96 Hofgarten murder,
the '95 Rhine Riverside murder...
Dinger is wanted for
all of these murders
which occurred near the
Düsseldorf metropolitan area.
Therefore,
I hereby request that
the suspect be moved to
the state of Nordrhein-Westfalen.
Hey. Are you ready?
Yes.
Get out.
All right. Shall we go?
Do you want
something to drink?
No.
Smoking's not allowed.
I said, "Smoking's prohibited
in this coach."
Huh? Yeah.
If only you lived the rest of
your life so morally...
How many people have
died at your hands?
Counting precious lives
on your fingers...
the ones you killed will
never be able to rest in peace.
This is my last job.
I'm retiring tomorrow.
It was a boring life as a detective,
but it wasn't bad.
Now I can live peacefully with
my wife and tend to my garden.
That's how life is.
I want you to regret destroying
the modest lives of others.
Even people who spit at me?
The passenger who I let off at
Adler Street spit at me as he got off.
You mean that you killed him
just for that?
Spitting at people is the most pathetic
thing you could do as a person,
don't you think?
The couple that got on at
Gerresheim Station were even worse.
They started having sex
in the back of my car.
In the back of my car!
So I killed them.
A young drunk with
a foul mouth...
A prostitute who tried to pay
the fare with her body...
An old hag with too much makeup who
kept insulting everyone around her...
All sorts of people
got into my taxi.
They were all scum.
So I killed them.
Then let me ask you
one more thing...
What about the murder of the
Bilker Investment Bank employee?
How was he scum?
He worked diligently, he had honest
relationships, he didn't even smoke.
That banker
loved his family.
Because you killed him,
a corporate bribery scandal
involving big-business conglomerates,
that he was going to blow
the whistle on, remains in the dark.
That...
left a bad aftertaste. Yeah.
Just look at that.
You talk proudly as if you are
delivering holy retribution,
but you're just trying to
justify your actions.
That one. .. I had no choice.
Did someone ask you
to kill him?
I can't tell you that.
I told you,
"Smoking is prohibited."
Don't put a cigarette
in your mouth again.
If you do,
I'll kill you.
I wonder what
made you like this.
I always have been right.
But I just got a little push.
On that day...
There was a man walking his dog.
The man kicked the dog
for just for taking a crap.
The dog was terrified.
All it did was take a crap.
I stopped the man.
Before I realized what happened,
I was being subdued by the police.
That's when a boy appeared...
And the boy told
the police officer,
"It's not his fault.
The man with the dog started it."
I wasn't arrested
because of that.
I thanked the boy and told him
that I'd give him a ride home.
But he said that he didn't
have a home to return to.
Furthermore, he brought out
his sister from the bushes.
They were twins.
Well, I didn't have a choice,
so I took them to my apartment.
Strangely, when they took off their
coats, they were both in pajamas.
It was as if they had
escaped from a hospital.
Come to think of it, the boy's head
was wrapped in bandages.
That night, we watched
the news after dinner.
I complained to myself as I usually do
about how pathetic the world is.
How pathetic people are...
I said that the scum
should all die!
And what do you think
that boy told me?
He said that I was right.
He then told me...
We don't need people like that.
That was when I was liberated.
Cut it out! Are you saying that's
when you started killing people?
Good work, Inspector.
Yeah.
Your last job went off
without a hitch.
Yeah. I just have to
clean out my desk.
Thank you very much for
your long years of service.
I'm kind of relieved.
Well, there are some
cold cases, but...
What's wrong, Inspector?
He brought his sister.
They were twins.
They were both in pajamas.
It was as if they had
escaped from a hospital.
Can you remember anything
about that night?
Anything will be fine.
Anything you can remember will do.
Your name is Anna.
Anna Liebert. isn't that right?
Come to think of it, the boy's head
was wrapped in bandages.
The twins are
nowhere to be found!
Oh. Detective?
Huh? When did I meet those kids?
Well...
It was about 11 years ago.
W-What did those
children look like?
Well, they were blond twins
with beautiful faces.
I'll be damned...
Those twins
that disappeared...
The twins who are central to
solving Doctor Tenma's case.
This is frustrating.
Just thirty hours until
my retirement...
A vampire, huh?
I see. So that's why you
killed thirteen people.
You can't live without
drinking people's blood.
And they have to
be from virgins.
I see. I want to ask you
one more thing.
The murder three months ago...
The daughter of a grocer in Frankfurt...
Frieder Schelling.
Did you drink her blood too?
No, you did indeed.
As you've said,
your victims until now were all girls.
Furthermore, you thoroughly researched
them before carrying out your attacks.
I understand how much
you need virgin blood.
But. ..Frieder Schelling...
was twenty-one.
Although she looked as if
she was still in her teens.
But that's not the issue here.
She had worked at a cafe on Zeiler
Street in Frankfurt since she was 16.
The cafe was next to
a prestigious gymnasium.
She was an idol to the boys
who attended that gymnasium.
But she had a child
when she was 17.
According to rumors, the father was
one of the students from that gymnasium.
After she gave birth,
her parents opened a grocery store.
The parents of the student
who got her pregnant were rich.
And rumor has it that her parents
received a lot of money from them
to open the store.
You knew about that, didn't you?
After all, you researched
those other girls so thoroughly.
Do you drink blood even if
it's not from a virgin?
That one...
left a bad aftertaste.
Why did you go after her?
I met the real thing.
The "real thing"?
I knew it when I met him.
I knew that I was still just a bat
that just flies around vampires.
He is none other than
the real thing.
Did that man tell you to do it?
Who is he?
Where did you meet?
In a Frankfurt suburb...
Griesheim...
There's a park there
that's just like any other.
At a sandbox in that park, he wrote
a woman's name with a tree branch.
And I got to work.
Who is he?
I told you. A real vampire.
It's strange no matter
how you think of it, isn't it?
The murder of Erich Klemperer
four months ago...
You were only receiving orders
in Lower Saxony.
So why did you go to Frankfurt
just for this man?
Did the aliens communicate
this to you as well?
Did the aliens suddenly
change their minds
and tell you to go to
Frankfurt to kill someone?
Or was there
a different reason?
Mr. Klemperer history
is pretty suspicious.
He defected from East Berlin
during the Cold War.
During the past few years,
his food commerce business
seems to have done well.
But there are rumors that
he helped smuggle children
from the East to the West.
In other words,
he sold children from the East to
wealthy childless people on the West.
I wasn't contacted.
I met him in person.
I was really excited.
I was standing before a real alien.
Where did he land his UFO?
At a park in Griesheim.
He spoke the language of the
cosmos.
So to make it easy for me to understand,
he wrote letters in the sandbox.
I wish you could feel
that excitement I felt then.
Good work,
Inspector Visbaugh.
Yeah.
You're finally counting down the
seconds until retirement, aren't you?
You're thinking of this as getting rid
of a nuisance, don't you?
That's right!
So today, we're celebrating the
riddance of a nuisance over drinks!
I get the feeling the alcohol
is going to taste bad.
Who's that man?
Oh...
It's Dr. Gillen.
A criminal psychologist.
It seems he's come to see Dinger,
the serial killer taxi driver.
Who asked him to?
Well... He said it was for
a paper or something.
He's an authority in his field,
so it seems he has connections
with important people.
When the passenger got out of the taxi
and spit at you, you ran him over.
Yeah.
I've said this over and over again
during interrogations,
but the people I killed
were all unneeded.
You just don't understand
how right I am.
"How right you are"' huh?
Then can I ask you one thing?
You're always talkative
during interrogations.
But when it comes to talking about
Mr. Oberth of Bilker Investment Bank,
you don't seem as forthcoming.
With the other murders,
it's been recorded that you express
your reasons for them.
But with the murder of Mr. Oberth,
you've never given a single clear reason.
I don't want to talk
to you anymore.
How was it, Dr. Gillen?
I'm Inspector Visbaugh.
Did Dinger say anything
of scientific interest?
No. Nothing outside of reports
until now.
Now then...
Actually, there's something
I really want to ask that man.
I'm going to retire today.
I won't feel right unless
I ask him this.
What do you think of this from
an academic standpoint?
If there was
a monster-like child...
and he grew up and revisited a man
who took care of him as a child...
A "monster-like child"?
Well... It's an absurd story.
Tell me the story in detail.
What do the two of you want?
I said that I didn't want to talk
to that researcher there.
I'm still a detective.
Until the end of the day.
This is an interrogation.
About the story you told me yesterday,
the one about the twins.
You told me that
the boy liberated you.
Suppose that child grew up
and asked you to do something...
Would you do it?
Well. .. Who knows?
The murder of Fritz Oberth from
the Bilker Investment Bank.
Did you do it
at someone's request?
A diligent man. An honest man.
That's the kind of man Mr. Oberth was.
He's far from what
you would call scum.
He was trying to
expose a bribery scandal
involving a certain
financial conglomerate.
If you call him scum, it would wreck
the reasoning behind your crimes.
I wasn't asked.
He and I don't need words.
"He"?
That bank employee
was probably trash to him.
That's what I'll believe.
Why?
Because he's right.
Who is he?
Is he the twin you talked about?
When and where
did you meet him?
In Griesheim.
At a park in that town.
In a Frankfurt suburb...
Griesheim.
At a park in Griesheim.
He wrote a name
in the sandbox...
He didn't say a word.
But I understood.
He wanted me to kill the man
whose name he had written.
We don't need words.
We understand.
That we don't need this guy!
What do you mean?
The three people
you interviewed
were asked by the same person
to commit murders?
He tried to make the three murders
lose their significance
by incorporating them into three
completely unrelated multiple homicides.
Lose their significance?
What do you mean?
Tell me in detail.
Tenma and Nina
have headed to Frankfurt.
Johan...
He's planning something...
in Frankfurt.