First came countless bouquets that
barely fit into my dressing room...
Next came the brand-name
clothes and bags...
Finally a jewel the size of which
I've never seen before...
I had no idea who was
sending them to me.
It was you.
I felt something special
when I first saw your show.
Something special?
Was it my chest or my ass?
Something that
cannot be seen.
You should have come to see me
in person in my dressing room.
Even someone like me?
Huh? What are you
talking about?
You seem like someone
who'll listen to my story.
This is delicious!
I've never had anything this delicious!
Eat all you want.
Does "The Baby"
always eat this good?
Yes. But it can be good or bad
depending on the company you're with.
I always eat by myself.
Do you eat with a group?
Yes. I pay many people
and bring them over.
Huh? Why do you do that?
I wonder why.
Now that I think of it,
no matter how many people I bring
and no matter how lively things are,
I always feel like
I'm eating by myself.
How about now?
It's very fun.
That's good!
Would you care to dine
with me from now on?
All right. But I'll get tired
if the food is always like this.
It's been odd lately.
What has?
I've never felt like this before.
I built my kingdom
here in Frankfurt.
I fought to establish
a new order.
It was my dream to become
like Der Führer, Hitler.
My dream is to
become a dancer.
What I'm doing right now
is a little different.
But everyone's fascinated
when they watch me dance.
I feel kind of good
when I dance.
I'm afraid.
Huh?
This is the first time
I've ever felt this way.
I'm afraid.
What are you trying to say?
Oh... Well... Anyway...
About the three murders that have
occurred during the past few months...
It was probably Johan's will.
Y-Yes. It's as you say.
I understand the meaning of
the murder of Fritz Oberth,
the Bilker Investment
Bank employee,
and the murder of Frieda Schilling,
the grocer's daughter.
He was hiding a scandal.
I understood what
those murders were for.
But Erich Klemperer,
the trader...
Did you know him?
No, I didn't know about it.
It's unrelated to Johan.
Is that really so?
Do we really know what
Johan is trying to achieve?
Or are you hiding
something from me?
You have no need to worry.
Anyway, were you able to find Nina?
She left a psychologist
in Munich,
and it seems that she's
headed to Frankfurt.
Don't you think our first priority
right now is capturing Nina?
I don't think you know Nina's true nature.
Don't forget that she's Johan's sister.
That look she had...
That time we tried to burn down
the Turkish district...
The look she had when
she pointed her gun at me...
It gives me chills
just thinking about it.
Why, that's splendid.
Does that come from
the program you set up?
I only helped.
My master did everything.
Everything is proceeding
according to his program.
Are things really going
according to the program?
There it is!
Over there ! It's my favorite
This time, I'm buying.
Is it good? This is the best
ice cream in Frankfurt.
Yes, it's been a long time
since I've felt relieved.
Lately, I've been on edge.
Why?
Yes. I wonder why.
There's no need to
guard me so heavily.
Still, those are
Mr. Čapek's orders.
There's no need to worry.
Even if I walk outside, there aren't
many people who know who I am.
No. Things will become troublesome if
we let you do whatever you want again.
Who did whatever
they wanted?
Three people died to
cover up your scandals.
I wonder how many people will have
to be killed before people figure it out.
Who do you think is responsible
for keeping you in your position?
The four leaders
of this organization...
Professor Geidlitz, General Wolf,
Mr. Čapek... And your late father...
You seem to think that you've
succeeded to your father's post...
but it's not that simple.
What matters is whether you are a
talented person who is worthy of that post.
Are you saying that you
should have had the post?
The scandals
surrounding you...
I know all of them.
You know what happens to people
who know about them, don't you?
You're ten years too early
to try to scare me.
I have no intentions of
making an enemy of you.
You're the great leader of
Frankfurt's right-wing group.
I had fun.
Me too.
I'm really glad that
I talked to you today.
Talk to me any time.
It's been a long time since I walked
the streets like this without bodyguards.
Are you all right?
Shall I walk you home?
You? Walk me home?
Are saying that you're
going to protect me?
I'll be all right.
My hotel's nearby.
Amazing! You live in a hotel.
Here. This isn't much, but...
I don't need any.
Huh?
Goodbye.
Oh. S-Sorry.
It's a habit of mine.
I apologize.
I always...
bought people with money...
Can I go...
up to your hotel room?
You're called "The Baby"...
But what's your real name?
My name is...
Yes.
We've located the twin sister.
I called the Baby right now,
but he's not answering...
so I'm going directly to his room.
Yes... Later...
Hello? Yes. It's me.
Th-The Baby...
The Baby...
He's been killed!
Come here.
Don't be afraid.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Are you all right? Mr. Čapek?
You look pale.
So... Forgive me for asking
such a rude question,
You weren't the one who
killed the Baby, were you?
What an absurd question.
We're just asking you
to confirm that.
By dawn, news of the Baby's death
will have spread everywhere.
With the death of the Baby,
the balance of this organization
might suddenly collapse.
Our situation from
here on is unclear.
We are bodyguards. We will carry out
the job we were assigned.
But if that was your work, guarding
you will no longer be in our interest.
Why do you think
I called you
immediately upon hearing
the news of the Baby's death?
Was it because you sensed that
you would be in danger next?
Do you have an idea of
who killed the Baby?
Do we really know what
Johan is trying to achieve?
What am I afraid of?
Everything is going
according to plan.
Everything is...
is proceeding according
to the program.
Fine then.
We'll move you to a safe location.
I have a mountain villa
in Idstein.
I haven't told
anyone about it.
We'll stay there for a while.
But first... The twin sister...
You said that you knew where
the twin sister was, didn't you?
Yes. She's come
here to Frankfurt.
She's staying at the Toulette,
a cheap hotel.
Securing this girl will
guarantee my safety for now.
We'll do it immediately
tomorrow morning.
Do it right now!
All right.
I've contacted two other guards
to head to your villa in Idstein.
Okay.
Last night, for some reason,
the Baby sent his bodyguards away.
He went out on his own
and got himself killed.
You have us.
Don't worry.
Okay.
You were also safe when
that man tried shooting you at
the convention center the other day.
You're very lucky.
Milan...
Milan, listen.
I've met a wonderful man.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Peter Čapek.
You've shown me something
wonderful. Your "recitals."
Could you tell me
more about them?
About your new...
You should read this.
All the answers are
in these books.
Oh, how beautiful.
What beautiful children.
So these children are the ones who
will lead the future of the human race,
according to your program,
Franz Bonaparta.
The car...
Stop the car.
What's wrong?
We'll be at your mountain villa once
we go up this forest path up ahead.
What did you say earlier?
Huh?
Two more guards.
Yes. At your mountain villa.. .
They should have arrived by now.
Is there any chance that those two
could let any other information slip?
Huh?
Can you assure me that they
haven't leaked the information
that I'm heading to
my mountain villa?
Yes.
They're trustworthy people.
I've decided not to go
to my mountain villa.
Huh? Hold on a second.
So where are you going?
Never mind that. I've decided that
I'm not going to my mountain villa.
But there's no point
in driving all night.
This is an order.
I know that you feel
threatened, but...
Let's just go to
your mountain villa.
A-A lighter?
H-He wasn't reaching
for his gun?
It's me. Is anybody here?
J-Johan...
At Red Rose Mansion...
many people drank that wine.
It's all right. See?
I'm drinking it too.
What happened to the bodyguards
who are supposed to be here?
Why...did you kill the Baby?
We're supposed to be allies!
Y-You were helping us.
We were going to find and
bring your sister to you.
Everything is going
as planned.
Your sister. ..
We've already captured your sister.
If something happens to me,
your sister will...
Nothing will go your way.
Got that? Everything will
go according to my plans.
What am I?
The monster inside of me.. .
wasn't inside me.
It was outside.
What are you trying to say?
Franz Bonaparta...
is alive, isn't he?