It's me.
Is anybody here?
J-Johan...
At Red Rose Mansion...
many people drank that wine.
It's all right. See?
I'm drinking it too.
What happened to the bodyguards
who are supposed to be here?
Why...did you kill the Baby?
We're supposed to be allies!
You were helping us.
We were going to find and
bring your sister to you.
Everything is going as planned.
Your sister. ..
We've already captured your sister.
If something happens to me,
your sister will...
Nothing will go your way.
Got that? Everything will
go according to my plans.
What am I?
The monster inside of me.. .
wasn't inside me.
It was outside of me.
What are you trying to say?
Franz Bonaparta...
is alive, isn't he?
I'm sorry to disturb you at this hour,
Miss Nina Fortner.
Miss Fortner?
Miss Nina Fortner?
Don't move!
Who ordered you
to come here?
I see.
As the Baby told us,
you're no ordinary girl.
The Baby...
Did the Baby
order you to get me?
No. The Baby is dead.
Dead?
Peter Čapek is the one
who told us to get you.
It seems that if we take you as
a hostage, your safety is ensured.
Čapek...
Take me.
I'll go see Peter Čapek.
This is the police.
We'll be conducting a search
of the home of Milan Kolas,
a suspect in Roedelheim
Convention Center Shooting.
Begin.
Out of the way!
Come on,
move out of the way!
Is this Kolas' room?
So it seems.
The police are going to
search this place soon.
I have to go.
Milan...
Did Milan really die?
Milan...died for us.
Čapek killed our relatives.
He died trying to
get revenge for us.
Revenge...
Let's get revenge.
Let's get revenge!
- Let's get revenge !
- Let's get revenge!
No!
You mustn't think that way.
But. .. But Milan. ..
Milan...
Milan wouldn't
want you to do that!
Revenge leads to more revenge.
It will repeat itself over and over.
Milan didn't want you
to think that way.
Someone has to stop it.
Milan tried to put an end to this.
What was Milan's true wish?
To visit each other's
homelands together.
Study hard. Someday,
that dream will come true.
Thank you for everything,
Mr. Mustafa.
Mrs. Minh...
Mrs. Suleiman...
Thank you for the delicious food.
Dr. Tenma...
You aren't going to...
There is a ton of information about
a man called Peter Čapek, isn't there?
Yeah. It seems like Milan Kolas
was after this Čapek.
Find this man immediately
and question him.
Inspector!
A man known as The Baby, the leader
of a right-wing extremist organization,
was killed at the Kaiser Hotel.
Someone has to...
I have to stop this.
It's the young man who's
come in and out of this hotel
countless times
with Peter Čapek.
Is that the "devil's apprentice"?
Follow that car.
Johan...
Are you there, Johan?
Where have you been Johan?
If I remember correctly,
you're... Eva.
Where is he?
Where is Johan right now?
Mr. Čapek...
We've brought Nina.
Peter.. .Čapek...
Come here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
H-Hey!
Wait. Stop!
Which one is it?
Is it Johan?
Or is it his sister?
At this point,
they're both the same.
Johan let me live.
Because the one that's
going to kill me...
is his sister.
Everything is
going as planned.
Whose plan? Mine?
Johan's?
Whose... Whose plan is it?
Hurry up, kill me.
Johan was...here, right?
Where did he go?
Take me to him.
Where is Johan right now?
It's pitch dark.
I'm scared.
I want to get out
of here quickly.
If we go out now...
I wonder if it's still going on.
The killing...
If I hadn't introduced you two...
at that party...
You and that devil...
If I hadn't done that...
Martin wouldn't...
...wouldn't have had to die.
All right. Hold on a second.
Where is Johan?
I don't know.
I'd like to know that, too.
Calm down...
I've been watching
this apartment for two weeks.
He never showed up.
Where else could he be?
As I said, I don't know.
Really.
My ear... My ear!
I'm serious.
It hurts. It hurts!
The next time,
it won't be just an ear.
Christof Sievernich...
I looked you up.
Though, I did know about
your late father, Ernest,
without having to
looking him up.
The Sievernich Financial Group
is quite prominent in Frankfurt...
no, in all of Germany.
Who would have thought that you
were the heir to that financial group?
What is Peter Čapek planning to do
by bringing you and Johan together?
I'm bleeding a lot.
Help me out.
What's going to happen when you
and that devil are brought together?!
No. That's wrong.
What's wrong?!
Čapek thinks that
he introduced us.
But Johan and I have known
each other for a long time.
What?
Čapek doesn't know that we were
friends in East Berlin over ten years ago.
Over ten years ago.. .
In East Berlin?
I'm the adopted son
of the Sievernich's.
Actually, I was sold to them
in secret by a smuggler.
Johan and I met in
East Berlin's 511 Kinderheim.
511 ...
We met there...and survived.
He and I survived.
I'm scared.
I'm hungry.
I really need to pee.
I wonder if the killing
has stopped.
I wonder if everyone died.
Let's go out.
- Huh?
It's all right.
It's gotten quiet outside.
It's all right. Let's take a look.
We'll go crazy if we stay here.
I-I'll go take a look.
Come back and tell us
if things are all right.
O-Okay.
I don't know why, but everyone at
511 Kinderheim went crazy that day.
It wasn't just the children.
Even the instructors
began killing each other.
He hasn't come back.
He ran away.
Huh?
He left us behind
and ran away.
How terrible.
He tried to save himself.
You think so?
Go take a look
if you think I'm lying.
He's probably happily eating
a warm meal right about now.
A warm meal!
I-I'm going to take a quick look.
You won't betray me, right?
O-Of course not.
He also didn't come back.
I'm going to keep on hiding.
Wracked with hunger and thirst,
I fell in and out of a light sleep.
Am I going to die like this?
There he stood.
It's just you and me.
I have a plan.
That was Johan?
Čapek calling it
his plan is laughable.
Johan and I talked about it constantly
when we were children.
About what?
What is his plan?
Do you want to hear it?
Well...
You can't do that.
You can't shoot my ear!
To become a politician,
a face is very important!
You can't do that.
I'm going to put the world
into motion. Right?
I'm going to team up with Johan
and make the world mine.
Right?
What are you going to
do about my ear?!
You can't interfere
with my plan.
You can't!
Drop your gun!
Kenzo?
Johan told me to tell his sister,
where he was if she came
and that his sister would
probably kill me afterwards.
Why won't you kill me?
Your memories...
Did you get them all back?
Yes.
Then why won't you kill me?
You must be overflowing
with hatred, anger and grief.
What are we?
You know, don't you?
I've heard things...
about how you twins were born.