Mom...
Don't let go of my hand, mom.
The man. ..was Czechoslovakian
of German decent.
He was the oldest son
of a family
that remained in Bohemia
after the Second World War.
He was a soldier who graduated
from a military academy.
He was an elite, someone who was
to lead the country in the future.
His name...
His name is not important.
The woman...
was the only daughter of a
Moravian elementary-school teacher.
She was a beautiful blonde-haired,
blue-eyed woman.
She went the University of Bruno.
She majored in genetic engineering.
Her teachers had
great expectations for her.
She was a talented woman.
Her name. ..
Her name...is not important.
The two met at a cafe in Prague. It
didn't take long for them to fall in love.
Not long after,
the woman became pregnant.
And the man
made a confession.
"This was a mission"' he said.
He told her that there was
an experiment being conducted
involving several dozen
couples of men and women
chosen for their race, intellect, physique,
and athletic abilities to produce children,
and that they were
one of those couples.
The man had followed
the orders as planned,
but he said that he no longer
wanted to do so anymore.
Then he said...
Let's run away.
The two of them ran away.
The man said that he wouldn't
do things as planned.
But his actions were
already a part of the plan.
The woman was isolated
in an unfamiliar room.
Let me see him.
He's been assigned
a new mission.
Let me see him.
He's been assigned
a new mission.
Let me see him.
He's been assigned
a new mission.
The woman said...
"Let me see him.
Let me see him."
She knew that he
was no longer alive.
Her unborn children grew well.
They were twins.
Turn your head this way.
The woman began to realize that
the man who came to visit often...
the man who was sketching her...
was the man responsible
for the whole experiment.
I won't forgive you.
I will never forgive you.
Even if I die, the children who are
growing inside of me will get revenge.
You say the most
interesting things.
The due date came and
the moment of birth had arrived.
When she was being moved to a different
room to calm her of her labor pains,
she finally sprang into action.
It was only a several
dozen centimeters wide...
Pregnant and wracked with labor pains,
she escaped through a ventilation duct.
She collapsed on the road several
dozen meters from the gate.
Her water broke.
How beautiful.
What beautiful children.
So these children are the ones who
will lead the future of the human race.
Wonderful.
I thought of names for them.
You don't need to think
of unnecessary things.
I thought of names for them.
You don't need
to think about that.
Names...
Give them names.
Give them...
It's all right.
They don't need names.
Franz.. .Bonaparta...
That's right.
Johan asked me about
where he was.
Is Bonaparta alive?
"I won't forgive you.
I will never forgive you."
"Even if I die, the children who are
growing inside of me will get revenge."
Franz Bonaparta is still alive,
isn't he?
You should ask Johan.
He's over there.
What a terrible doctor.
There's a hospital up ahead.
I'll take you there if you tell me
where Johan is.
At this rate,
you're going to bleed to death.
I-I don't know
what I don't know.
Tell us immediately.
What a terrible doctor.
You shoot me with a gun,
you make me bleed like this...
and you threaten me...
Where is Johan?!
What a terrible doctor.
Tell us now! Right now!
I don't know
what I don't know...
Eva...
Over there.
There's a pay phone.
Call the hospital and tell them
that there's an injured person
who's bleeding excessively
in this car.
W-What are you saying?!
He's about to tell us where Johan's-
His life will be in danger
if we stall any longer.
Hurry. Call them.
You saved again.
You're always like this.
You can't kill people.
He wants to see you.
I'll tell you where Johan is.
Kenzo, the hospital's sending
an ambulance right away.
Let's get away from here
immediately.
Where's Kenzo?!
He left.
He left a message for you...
"I can't let you get involved
any further. I've ruined your life."
"I'm very sorry.
Please find happiness"' he says.
Why are you crying?
I don't understand.
I don't understand at all.
Johan.
Welcome home.
L-It's a fire!
The Three Frogs is on fire!
Go on, eat.
If you eat that quickly,
you're going to choke.
You must have
been really hungry.
Where did you two
come from?
What are your names?
You don't talk at all,
do you?
Fine. We can talk once
your stomachs are full.
Wait!
Wait for me!
This way!
What should we do?
What do you mean?
Those children...
They don't have any parents,
do they?
Even if they did, maybe there's
a reason they don't want to go back.
We've always
wanted children, right?
Yeah.
We could take them in.
Don't be foolish!
Sorry. I didn't mean to be harsh.
Anyway, let's call the police.
What's wrong, son?
Look, look. A pretty flower.
I'm going to give it to
the man and the lady.
You don't have to.
Huh?
I told you, didn't I?
I have a good plan.
Come on.
Oh, honestly!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
We finally meet.
When I escaped from
Red Rose Mansion,
you greeted me when I got to
the room at the Three Frogs.
So this time,
I'll say it to you...
Welcome home.
A lot of time has passed since I came
for you in Heidelberg on our 20th birthday.
You came for me?
You came to kill.
The Fortners and
the Lieberts...
Everyone who had
been kind to us...
You killed them all!
Please come back to life!
Huh?
I said, "Today's a nice day,
isn't it?"
Oh. Yes.
Driver...
Yeah?
Could you hurry a little?
It's all right.
Hang in there.
Shoot me.
Kill...
I'll save you.
Are you going to shoot me
like you did then?
Yes.
I'm going to
put an end to this.
The end...
What is the end?
I've seen the end of
the world over and over.
What is the end?
This will end.
You're going to die
and I'm going to die.
You've seen it?
What did you see?!
What have you seen?!
You don't know.
I'll tell you...
a truly terrifying story.
I'm back.