It's all right.
Hang in there.
Shoot me.
Kill...
I'll save you.
Are you going to shoot me
like you did then?
Yes.
I'm going to put an end to this.
The end...
What is the end?
I've seen the end of
the world over and over.
What is the end?
This will end.
You're going to die
and I'm going to die.
You've seen?
What did you see?!
What have you seen?!
You don't know.
I'll tell you...
a truly terrifying story.
I'm back.
A truly terrifying story,
you say?
The story of
the many things I saw...
All those things I told you...
I was taken from the room
at the Three Frogs.
I was put in a pitch-black room
without any walls.
There was an odd sensation
to whatever I touched.
The room had no sense of
up or down, left or right.
But I knew that someone
was watching me.
It was a completely
soundless room.
No.
Sometimes I could hear
a voice screaming.
Meals would come
from somewhere.
I counted how many
times they came.
Five...Six... Seven...
Eleven... Twelve... Thirteen...
Twenty-one... Twenty-three...
When I started to lose count...
A man stood there.
Listen, listen well.
People can become
whatever they want to be.
Oh?
Should a small child like you
be walking around here?
Well, that child is...
So this is that child.
My, how cute.
Ah. So this is the child.
How wonderful.
What a beautiful child.
Take a look. This is the child.
So this is the child.
The result...
The result indeed.
So this is the child.
This child is...
- Ours...is. .. with the result...
- I only remember parts
- to his new...
- of the welcome speech...
This.. .for us. ..
the chosen ones...
A toast to our country's future!
- Cheers!
The first person collapsed.
The people around
rushed to him.
They also collapsed,
one by one.
Moans... Shrieks... Screams...
Fear filled the room.
The 42 people in
that room died.
Leaving only
Franz Bonaparta...
I ran to escape
from that place.
I didn't even realize that I had scratched
my arms on the roses in the garden.
I ran.
When I arrived at the Three Frogs,
you greeted me.
I continued talking.. .for days and days
about everything I experienced.
You're wrong.
You're wrong!
Nina...
Can you hear me, Nina?
Calm down, Nina.
It's me...Tenma.
You know who I am, right?
It's me...
Yes. That's right.
Calm down.
All right. That's a good girl.
It's all right. It's all right now.
You're wrong, you're wrong,
you're wrong.
It's not me.
I wasn't the one who said
"Welcome home."
The one who said it...
What. ..I said...
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Johan's wrong.
Johan just listened
to my story.
The one who was taken
to Red Rose Mansion...
The one who was taken to
Red Rose Mansion...was me!
Getting dragged down those steps
at the Three Frogs...
Being in that pitch-black room
with no walls and counting meals...
Standing, surrounded
by all those corpses...
All of it...
It was all me!
I'm scared.
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Tell me everything.
Well... well...
I talked...
for days and days.
That's enough.
I told Johan what I had experienced.
Johan thinks that my experiences...
That's enough already.
Johan thinks that my experiences
are his experiences.
Because of me, Johan...
That's enough already!
I told everything to Johan earlier.
Johan listened to my story.
It looked as if he was smiling. ..
but it also looked as if he was crying.
I've...
I've never seen
anyone look like that.
I couldn't shoot him.
But I'm sure that he's going to
destroy himself. ..just like me.
Don't...
Just like how I'm going to
destroy myself!
Don't!
Don't...
If you die...
If something happens to you...
What will I do?
If you die. ..where can I go?
Please live.
Please.. .
no matter what happens...
I beg you.
Yes. It's me.
You found a car near
the mountain villa?
Yeah.
It's at the bottom of a cliff.
Edward's inside, dead.
He was probably killed by...
Johan is probably...
going to kill Franz Bonaparta.
His son is in Prague.
I told Johan about that.
But...
will it really
end at just that?
I'm not sure his destruction
will end there.
His sister's memory...
Where something is
missing from her memory...
Johan has another
memory inside.
Just what were we trying to create,
Franz. ..Franz Bonaparta?
Live.
We will.. .find it, the place where
you should be, where we should be.
We'll find it somewhere.
Hey. I'm really glad you came.
I never thought you'd come
Come in, come in.
I was just making some tea.
I wanted you to try some of
my wonderful tea.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
It's a special herb tea.
For you to come to me...
means that you have some pretty
important business, don't you?
Ask me anything.
I'll get prepared immediately.
Who do you want me
to kill next?
Huh? Don't joke around.
Stop that.
The dream...
I woke up from it.
Are you tired or something?
What are you going to
do about your plan?
I woke up.
Hold on a second. What did I gather
all that money for anyway?
I woke up from the dream.
What did I kill all
those people for?
Many visions of the end...
But...right now,
I see a different vision.
A vision of the true end.
A memory only I have.
The real place I must go to.
Huh?
The place I must go to...
Ruhenheim...
This is it.