Ruhenheim...
This is it.
Hey, Ludwig!
Why are you barking?!
Did that bike
breakdown again?
Yeah. The chain always
comes loose.
As expected, bulky trash left at
a trash pick-up isn't any good.
It doesn't look like
bulky trash to me.
When I ride it,
everyone says,
"It's trash.
Trash is moving by."
"Trash is riding by on trash"'
they say.
That's not true. It's a wonderful
five-speed super cycle.
Let me see it.
Let's adjust it one more time.
Oh. It looks like
there's a guest.
Yes. He called earlier.
Umm... You had a reservation?
Yes. My name is Lunge.
Ah, Mr. Lunge,
thank you for coming.
I'm glad that a room was open
on such short notice.
Well, we always
have openings.
Is it still the off-season?
It's like an off-season
all year round.
The only guests staying here
right now are that couple over there.
The man's legs are bad.
And it seems like they've had
a rough time on their trip.
I'll take his bags.
I leave it to you Wim.
It's room 302.
How's the view
from that room?
I've given you the room
with the best view.
I'll leave your bags here,
okay?
I don't think it looks
like trash, either.
Huh?
I think it's a pretty
wonderful bike.
Inspector Lunge of the BKA?
Why are you here at
this rural police station?
Well, I was wondering how many more
officers I could gather for backup here.
Backup? More officers?
Well, If you asked
the state police,
they could supply you with quite
a few officers in under an hour.
But I don't think that a situation like
that would happen in a rural town like this.
Right now, you should start checking
everyone who comes into town.
Huh?
Before something
terrible happens...
That's good ! Just like that!
It's running well!
Speeding up!
Changing gears!
Ow!
What happened, trash?
Can the trash still move?
It's an eyesore!
Trash!
Stop.
Stop it!
Trash, trash!
Are you all right?
Are you alone?
Are you traveling
by yourself?
Yes.
Is this for work?
No, it's private.
Oh. Aren't you lonely
by yourself?
No. I'm used to it.
What about your family?
I have family.
My daughter had a son.
Oh? You have a grandchild?
Grandchildren are nice.
Our grandchild always
thinks about us.
See, I'm writing them
a postcard now.
Letters are nice.
You can write things that you would
never be able to say in person.
How about it?
Care to write one, too?
A letter to my grandson...
What should I write?
Anything is fine.
If I could only draw...
Umm, excuse me.
Can I stay here for the night?
Yes. Of course.
You saved me.
I was enjoying a relaxing picnic.
But I got lost along the way,
and when I finally reached this town,
it was already late.
You're a lifesaver.
No one got off at
this town, huh?
A gunshot?
It didn't sound like a gunshot.
No. It definitely sounded
like a gunshot.
No one in this town has a gun.
Even if they did,
it's probably that drunk out back.
It would make a larger sound
if it were out back.
Besides, that drunk
wouldn't hit anything.
Wouldn't hit...
Honestly!
I lost again because of
your unlucky talk!
Honestly!
Shut up! It's not my fault!
Stop playing the lottery!
Ludwig...
My Ludwig isn't anywhere!
There was something that
sounded like a gunshot earlier!
Could it be that
my Ludwig was...
My baby was...
Calm down, Mrs. Hillman.
There was no gunshot.
Calm down.
What's the matter?
Oh. Well, this woman's dog
has gone missing.
Oh my...
That's worrying.
Anyway,
let's inform the police.
I've already gone
to the police!
But that man's no good.
He's an officer,
but I can't count on him at all.
He's an officer
who hates dogs.
Shall I look for him?
Huh? Are you sure,
Mr. Newmeyer?
Yes. I was going to stroll
around town anyway.
Yes, I know Mrs. Hillman's dog.
It's that stupid dog
that barks a lot, right?
He's gone missing.
Did you see him?
No, I haven't.
I see. Thank you.
By the way, have you seen any
suspicious strangers around town?
I have.
Oh?
You.
A dog?
What's this? I thought that you
were going to stay over here.
Sorry. I'm staying at
the Versteck Hotel.
What's with that? They're stealing
everyone's customers.
Which means that...
the guests you have now...
I don't have any. Thankfully,
it's quiet because of that.
So if that dog barks as much as it did
when it was nearby, I'd know immediately.
Did you hear barking today?
No, I didn't.
Maybe...
I heard something that
sounded like a gunshot earlier.
Perhaps some weirdo got angry at
the dog for being noisy and shot it.
Oh. Good day. Umm...
It's Lunge, Mr. Newmeyer.
Oh, Mr. Lunge,
where are you going?
I'm looking for a dog.
Oh, I see.
Have you found any leads?
No.
Then let's continue
our search.
A drink. .. Give me a drink!
No. Dad, you shouldn't
drink anymore!
Go and buy me a drink already!
A drink!
I don't have any money!
You have the money you earned
from working at that hotel!
I wonder if I could buy one.
Wim, it's all right.
That's the money you've earned.
You got beaten
pretty badly today.
Come on.
Let's go to my hotel.
This is delicious!
It's unusual to see someone
eat as eagerly as you do.
Really? It's really delicious.
But they're just
regular sausages.
This is the face I make
when things are delicious.
Huh?
This is a nice town.
It's quiet and there's good food.
You think so? I want to get out of
this boring town as quickly as possible.
I wonder if there's someone wonderful
who can take me away from this place.
Has someone wonderful
come recently?
Not at all.
Everyday, it's the same faces.
I'm sick of it.
By the way, about the dog...
Oh, I've walked
that dog before.
Walked it?
When Mrs. Hillman had a cold,
I walked him for her.
When I let him have some Eisbein
from my deli, he wouldn't let go.
He pulled it away
with incredible force.
Where did he go?
Inspector Lunge!
As you've said, something
terrible has happened.
It's a dog.
A dog has gone missing.
Did you hear the gunshot?
Oh, that wasn't a gunshot.
A car broke down by the highway.
That was probably the sound
of the car backfiring.
You won't hear a gunshot
in this town.
Later.
Things will get bad
if you frighten me.
There he is.
Ludwig...
You troublemaker.
You remembered that
you buried that bone here.
Hey, nice to see you,
Mr. Lunge.
It seems like different clues
led us to the same place.
What are you doing in this town?
And yourself?
You're a detective,
aren't you?
I had a hunch.
You have the air of a detective.
I'm on vacation.
You don't look as if
you're on vacation.
I was in Prague
not too long ago.
There I heard information about
someone involved in a certain case.
He was a tall man with a big bag.
He had a friendly, gentle smile.
His hair color...
You completely match the data
I have on this man, Mr. Newmeyer.
No. Mr. Grimmer.
Why did you come
to this town?
It seems we really were led to the
same place through different clues.
Am I wrong?
Do you think that
you can stop
the terrible massacre that's
about to happen in this town?
Hey. Are you matching
lottery numbers again?
Your husband's going to
sweat away at work.
Don't talk so big.
You make so little.
What?!
Our future will be bleak
unless we win the lottery.
If you don't like that,
then earn more money.
Dear!
Shut up. What is it?
Dear...
What is it?!
I've won.
Won what?
Th-The lottery.
Give it back!
Where did you put my bike?!
Shut up!
We don't know about
your bike, do we?
We threw away
some trash, though.
You threw it away?
Yeah.
We tossed it in the Vampire's House
in the West Hills.
Vampire...
Go by yourself if
you want to get it back.
We don't know what'll
happen to you if you do.
You trash!
D-Dear...
Did anyone come?
N-No.
Be sure to put the chain on.
Say...
Y-Yes?
You're sure this is
the number, right?
I-I've checked it many times.
I-I really won.
20 million marks, huh?
What should we do, dear?
I went to the neighboring town.
D-Dear! This...
It's just in case. It's dangerous to be
carrying that much money unarmed.
Well, you don't need it if we
make sure no one knows about it.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong?
No one knows the number of
the lottery ticket you bought, right?
A-Actually,
when I bought that ticket...
The usual.
Here you go.
You just don't win,
do you, Mrs. Henich?
Oh. Hello, Mr. Conrad.
Your husband was grumbling
about your lotto obsession.
You can use my birthday.
March 2, 1945. It wins pretty often.
I've hit the jackpot twice
at the horse races.
All right. Thank you.
I-It can't be...
You used Conrad's birthday?
If he sees the number
in the newspaper...
B-But he doesn't know what
numbers you wrote, right?
I don't know. Rumors about it might
be spreading through town now.
C-Come to think of it...
W-What?!
On the way home, I stopped at the
general store to buy some cigarettes.
When I did, the girl from
the sausage shop was looking at me.
Oh! That's got to be it!
Me, too!
When I was throwing away the garbage,
the drunk in the back was staring at me!
Who knows what that drunk would do
if he heard about the money!
Calm down!
- But.. .
- Listen.
We've got to
protect ourselves.
The Vampire's House...
I-It's dead.
Someone's here!
From the looks of it...
No one's come here recently.
Everything's uncompleted.
Did he stop drawing?
Or could he not draw?
Hey. Why it's Wim.
Mr. Newmeyer...
Mr. Lunge...
What are you doing here?
U-Umm... My bike... My friends said
that they dumped my bike here.
Ah. Your friends tricked you.
Your bike was in a bush at
the bottom of the mountain path.
Anyway...
It seems like that cat was shot
with a submachine gun.
They've already...
Yes. They're nearby.
Look.
A drawing of the twins...
Yes.
And this...
They're about ten-years old.
Those twins were about ten when
I was in charge of Tenma's case.
These are pictures drawn
around that time.
How many other pictures
like this one are there?
No matter how many times he
drew it... he was never satisfied.
My, my...
Looks like there're going to
be a lot of vines this year.
I'm worried about this year's
lingonberry crop.
Hey. I haven't seen you before.