This jam is really delicious.
Thank you very much.
It's homemade lingonberry jam.
My, homemade!
I was asked to show this to
customers who particularly enjoy it.
This is the maker of the jam.
Oh, this person?
His name is Conrad.
There's a place on the southern hill
where a lot of lingonberries grow.
Before we knew it,
that whole area was his.
But no one complained because
he made such good jam?
Yes. He's a very pleasant man.
He's one of my few friends.
It was his idea to
show his picture.
It's his way of saying, please continue to
enjoy the Conrad-brand lingonberry jam.
That means that I have to
come back here for this jam.
That's right.
He'd be pleased
you said that.
Is there really going to be
an attack on this peaceful town?
An attack...
There are other methods.
There was a case in which a
single gun annihilated an entire town.
1958, in Zweifelstadt.
There was a string of
serial murders in Lower Saxony.
The residents thought that
their neighbors might be serial killers
and were paranoid over
ordinary everyday occurrences.
Amidst the mass hysteria,
one of the residents obtained a gun
for self-defense and shot his neighbor.
No one could control
what followed.
A fire started in the town and
everyone held weapons by their side.
All of the residents killed each other.
There were no survivors.
Don't tell me that's going to
happen to this town.
We've got to stop it.. .
before that happens.
No.
It may have already begun.
Come on, give us your money!
You have some. Give it to us.
No, that money is for...
It's probably money for
your drunken dad's alcohol, right?
Drinking too much
isn't good for the body.
We're helping him.
Helping.
Hey, let's go eat
at the usual place.
All right.
Sounds good.
Boy...
You hate them, don't you?
You hate them so much that
you want to kill them, don't you?
Where are you going, dear?
I'm going to talk to Conrad.
Talk to him? How?
When we passed the cafe,
didn't you notice that Ralph, the owner,
and the customers were smiling at us?
That's because it was unusual
for them to see us together, right?
No. If they knew that we won
20 million marks on a lottery,
who knows what they'd do?
O-Oh no!
So I think it's better to talk to him than
to continue to be suspicious of him!
Well, Mr. Conrad might
know that I won the lottery.
Even so,
what are you going to do?
I'll pay him any amount
of money to keep him quiet.
But Conrad is greedy.
What if he keeps on asking
for money afterwards?
W-When that happens...
What'll we do
when that happens?!
I-I don't know.
Was this the area where
he gathers lingonberries?
Dear...
Mr. Conrad's not such
a bad person, right dear?
Y-Yeah.
He's not the sort of person who would
ruin the luck we managed to seize, right?
Right, dear?
What's wrong?
D-D-Dear, did you...
It wasn't me.
Doing something
so irrevocable...
I said that it wasn't me!
Then who did this?!
H-How would I know?! I've
never fired my gun since I bought it!
Shut up.
That dog sure is annoying.
Yeah.
It's getting on my nerves.
You seem in
high spirits today.
Did something good
happen to you?
He finally appeared.
What finally appeared?
The wonderful person who will
take me away from this town.
A drink...
Crap...
The townspeople...
They ridicule me...
It's not funny at all.
A drink...
The thing that you want...
Could it be this?
Your son has
already taken one.
A gunshot.
The dog stopped barking.
That sure was interesting.
Mr. Lipsky.
You're Franz Bonaparta's son,
right?
Tell me where your father is.
There's not a moment to lose.
Something terrible will happen
if I don't hurry.
You know where your father is,
don't you, Mr. Lipsky?
That puppet is modeled
on Nina, isn't it?
Nina told me that
you were here.
Nina told you?
The curtain...
Please keep it open.
Okay.
How long have I
been like this?
Don't worry about that.
You should continue to rest.
Thank you. I get the feeling
that you stayed by my side.
Don't worry about me. I'm all right.
I won't try to kill myself.
Dr. Reichwein and Dieter
should be coming soon.
What about you?
I've got to go.
Where to?
"Where to"' huh?
You've gathered a lot of material and
have been looking at it here, right?
Did you find something?
I'm okay, so tell me.
I've been having former
secret police in Prague
and General Wolf's subordinates
gather whatever information they could.
About Franz Bonaparta?
Yeah. He was a very mysterious person,
but little by little, I learned who he was.
He was a Czechoslovakian
of German decent.
Franz Bonaparta
is also an alias.
After World War Two,
despite the fact that many
Czechoslovakians of German descent
were driven out of
their homeland, Bohemia.
His family remained
within the country.
It's not clear
what post he held
in the government in
Communist Czechoslovakia.
We know that he was once married to
a Czech woman and they had a child.
It seems that that child participated
in the early stages of his "recitals"
during the mid-sixties.
"Bonaparta has
a son in Prague."
I think that Peter Capek's
last words refer to this son.
I managed to
get a hold of this.
It's a copy of an old photograph
that shows the children
who participated in the "recitals"
in the mid-sixties.
It seems that the boy
to the far left...
Wasn't a superior pupil...
Huh?
He wasn't a superior pupil. ..
so he was expelled from the recitals.
You know him?
He became of no use
to Bonaparta.
He's probably the man
I know in Prague.
Do you think that this man knows
where his father.. .where Bonaparta is?
I don't know.
But he's our only lead.
If you don't hurry,
something terrible will happen.
Something terrible?
I know what Johan
is going to do.
What is he going to do?
A perfect suicide.
True solitude.
The only expression of love.
If you don't hurry,
many innocent people will die.
Your bookshelf...
It's filled with picture books that were
written under Bonaparta's pseudonyms.
I've also obtained and
read most of them.
After reading several,
I realized something.
For some reason, the characters in
his books have German names.
Even in Klaus Poppe's
The God of Peace...
But the issue is the pen name,
"Klaus Poppe."
Franz Bonaparta and his other
pen names are all Czech names...
But only this name is German.
Could it be that Klaus Poppe is your
German-born Czech father's real name?
There was a detective who
made the same deduction–
that it was my father's
real name.
A detective?
An Inspector Lunge
of the BKA.
Lunge?! He's here?
He left several weeks ago.
Left?
He also figured it out.
No, Inspector Lunge
becomes the person
rather than
making deductions.
"I am Klaus Poppe."
"I have no place
to go home to."
"In order to regain
my peace of mind"'
"I must return to my hometown
in my mind"' he said.
The German-born Czechs
were chased out of Bohemia
and lost their homeland
after the Germans lost.
Where in Germany were
his ancestors from?
I don't know the details.
But when I was a child,
my father told me that our home
was a town surrounded
by mountains in southern Germany.
I didn't need that anymore,
so I gave it to Inspector Lunge.
A postcard that was sent to me
three or four years ago.
It was unsigned and
it has a hand-drawn picture
depicting a town
as seen from a mountain.
It was signed "K. P.".
K. P...
Klaus.. .Poppe.
That is all I know.
Southern Germany...
A town surrounded by mountains...
My father...
Is my father
going to be killed?
I don't know.
But it won't end there.
Where's Nina?
Nina is safe, right?
I...
I want this puppet show
to have a happy ending.
Please protect Nina.
Okay.
What in the world
is going to happen?
He's...
Johan is trying to recreate the atrocity
of the Red Rose Mansion...
the 511 Kinderheim Massacre.
Please...
No matter what happens,
come back alive, Tenma.
You saved me.
So you must, too.
It's begun to rain.
A drink...
Give me a drink.
Crap...
How was it? Did the police
find Conrad's body yet?
No. They're still investigating
his disappearance.
We really shouldn't have
hidden him in the forest!
We should have informed
the police at that time.
What are you saying now?!
You're the one who thought
that I shot him!
Honestly. This happened
because you won the lottery.
Even so, you didn't have to
buy these things.
No matter how long you wait,
the train won't come.
All this rain flooded the railway bridge
over the Elgar River!
And the roads are closed
because of the river flooding.
An isolated island.. .
This is the worst situation.
Klaus Poppe, huh?
You know of him?
Jakub Farobek,
Emile Scherbe...
I think they're
the same person as Poppe.
The drawing and literary styles
are different, though.
When you become an enthusiast
like me, you sort of know.
I don't know why he used
so many pen names, though.
His drawings are amusing.
But I can never like his pieces.
There are tons of picture books
in the world with dark content.
But his books are
a little different.
How are they different?
Hmm...
They're filled with malice.. .
I suppose.
Now, about that.
A picture book by Helmut Voss
was published in '89.
There were very few printed,
so you'll seldom see it.
But from what I can see, he's also
the same person as Klaus Poppe.
How do you know?
As I said, when you become like me,
you just know.
No matter how much
he changes his drawing style,
there's always a certain
idiosyncrasy that remains.
The story is completely
different from the rest.
A thief flees to a town nestled
in the mountains.
The thief plans to make
some money in that town,
but as he interacts with the people
in the town, he forgets how to steal.
And he begins to work for the people
of the town and lives peacefully.
It's titled,
The Peaceful House.
The malice I used to get from
his books is completely gone.
But the art is no good at all.
It's odd. His story got better,
but he can't draw anymore.
It's as if he
lost sight of his goal.
A Peaceful Home. ..
A town nestled in the mountains...
Our home was a town surrounded
by mountains in southern Germany.
A map...
Do you have a map
of southern Germany?
What are you looking for?
A town nestled in the mountains
in southern Germany...
I found it.
Ruhenheim...
Honestly. It sure is raining.
Oh, how did it go? Did you find out
where Conrad went?
No. We don't have any idea.
My partners are searching
for him right now.
But with this rain...
I hear that
the train tracks and roads
aren't any good
because the river's flooded.
As his friend,
I'm sure you must be worried.
Honestly, what's going on?
It was such a peaceful town.
It started with Conrad going missing,
then Mrs. Hillman's dog was shot...
Poor Mrs. Hillman was
overcome with grief.
I heard that Mr. Kemnar was attacked
as he was leaving the pub.
I heard that he was
in serious condition.
We still don't know who hit him.
If Mr. Kemnar died, it would have
been the first murder in this town.
Though the situation is what it is,
back up won't come because of the rain.
What are we to do
with such few people?!
It's got to be an outsider!
There were never any crimes
in this town before!
It's the work of an outsider!
We're outsiders, too.
Well, you're...
It sure is raining.
I can't go outside in this rain
in a wheelchair.
Now then, I'm going to pick up
my partners and patrol once more.
Be careful.
Your husband's shoes.. .
they're pretty dirty.
It's as if he walked
around in the rain.
I'm going to borrow
your phone.
It's that drunk.
He's not the sort
to do anything.
What's wrong?
Did you run out of gas?
Or are you out of oil?
I'll call a repair shop.
Another gunshot...
The phone's dead.
Is it too late to stop it?