I don't want to do this to elderly
people... But you're important witnesses.
It would be bad if
you died or ran away.
The back entrance and
most of the windows
have been barricaded
with furniture.
But if someone really wanted to,
they could easily break through.
It's better than nothing.
Let's go to the first floor.
Do you know how to shoot?
Y-Yeah. Probably.
I'm going, too.
I have to go, too.
It would be bad if something
were to happen to you.
You need to survive and
tell the world the truth.
Wim, stay in the room.
If something
happens to you...
It's all right. There's no need to worry.
A strong ally is coming to save us.
Really?
Yeah, really.
He comes to save us
whenever we're in danger.
He never let's evil go unpunished.
He's the Magnificent Steiner.
Now! Run!
Take the path through
the woods to the north!
I'm pretty sure most of
the children have escaped now.
You go quickly, too!
I still haven't looked around
the center of the town.
Leave the rest to me.
You lead everyone to safety.
A-All right.
Oh. There's just one thing
I'd like to ask you...
Do you know Bonaparta.. .
no.. .Klaus Poppe?
Poppe?
Ah. He's the owner
of the Hotel Versteck.
What are you doing there?
Relax. I'm on your side
I ran away in a panic.
But the town is full of corpses.
I don't know where
I should run to.
Where did you run from?
H-He's giving orders
from his room.
I heard.
He?
Roberto!
I thought it was strange that he kept
coming and going from his room!
Each time, he'd change
his clothes and take a shower.
Where is this Roberto?
A room on the fourth floor
of the Hotel Bergbach.
I ...didn't know he was
that sort of person. I...
Listen. Everyone's hiding
in Hotel Versteck.
Can you get there
by yourself?
B-By myself? I'm scared.
Now, get up.
I-I'm scared.
Dr. Tenma...
Inspector Lunge...
My journey into delusion...
has finally become reality.
The emergence of you marks the end of
following what I thought were delusions.
My duty as a police officer
begins from this point on.
I'm finally going back to work.
Take this girl to the Hotel Versteck.
The person you're after is there.
Franz.. .Bonaparta...
Inspector Lunge,
where are you going?
I told you, didn't I?
To work...
Let's talk when I get back.
There're a lot of things
I want to ask you about.
Dr. Tenma...
I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Nina?
My memory...
is trying to come out.
My deepest memory...
Your deepest memory?
I...
don't want to remember it.
This memory... Johan.. .
If Johan remembers this...
Come out.
D-Don't shoot.
I-I'm from this town.
Don't shoot me.
Where's is the man
who's giving you orders?
Huh?
I said, "Where's Roberto?"
Stand up. Walk.
I can't take it anymore.
There are dead bodies everywhere.
I'll go crazy here.
Then we've got to get to
Hotel Versteck as soon as possible.
No!
Open your eyes, Erika.
Please... Erika...
She's your wife?
Unfortunately. ..
Your wife is already...
I'm on your side. It's dangerous here.
Get to somewhere safe immediately.
Give me your gun ! I'm going to
gun down the guy who shot Erika!
Give me the gun right now!
He destroyed our happiness.
I'm going to...
Your wife.. .
wouldn't want you to do that.
Your wife wants that child to be safe.
Am I wrong?
I'll take you to a path through the
woods to the north, where you can escape.
You should go towards the path
instead of the hotel as well.
No. I won't go anywhere.
All right. I'll be right back.
Don't move from this spot.
Got it?!
It sure is quiet.
Say... They're really not after
the lottery prize we won, are they?
Yeah.
Honestly. I didn't feel like I was living
for the past few days.
There really was
something wrong with me.
Because of that money,
I ended up buying a bunch of guns.
Normal's what's best of all.
Normal, huh?
I've got to let my wife know
that we're not at fault.
Hey, can you hear me, dear?
Mr. Henich!
M-My wife...
Ma'am!
I-It hurts.
Quickly, this way!
They're shooting at us from
the building across the street.
Does this hotel
have a basement?
There's a storehouse
under the kitchen.
How are your injuries?
What about you?
Dad's doing this.
Dad is going crazy because
he can't get a drink.
No he's not, Wim.
Dad's... Just like when he
hits me every day, Dad's...
Do you think that your dad is the sort
of person to do this sort of thing?
I...
This will end if I go out.
Don't make me repeat it.
I won't let you die.
I'm going to tie you down here
if you keep saying that.
Stay here. I'll deal with it.
Mr. Grimmer...
I told you, didn't I?
When things get tough,
the Magnificent Steiner will appear.
Long ago...
I've seen cases like that
during my experiments.
By imposing an excessive amount
of stress from anger or sadness,
a child will manifest
a different personality.
Those children were
exceptionally violent.
Most of them
committed suicide.
I'm surprised you've lived
as long as you have.
Look. I'm unarmed.
Listen to what I have to say,
even for just a little while.
Why are you doing this?
Who gave you your orders?
It doesn't matter if you're people
from the old East Germany
or if you're former
secret police.
It doesn't matter who you are!
I'm nobody from nowhere.
Are you listening?
Listen to me. Don't just follow orders,
but think with your heart.
Think with your heart
about what you're doing.
Can you do that?
You can...
What are you doing?
I was so scared!
I came all this way by myself.
I'm so glad that you're here.
Huh?
The Magnificent Steiner!
Hey everyone!
I watched it so fervently each day,
sitting so close to the TV...
But I have no memory of
watching the last episode.
Call out my name!
Come on. Let's go.
N-No.
No. No.
No!
I wonder if the main character,
the weak young man,
realized that he turned into the
Magnificent Steiner when he got angry.
I wonder if that young man
found happiness.
That young man...
That young man
becomes happy.
It's just a little further.
Just a little further and
we'll be out of the forest.
You're from Ruhenheim,
aren't you?
Who are you?
Something's happening
in the town, right?
People came into
the town with weapons.
Everyone in town began
killing each other.
Are you with them?
Calm down.
We're on your side.
Did you see an Asian man...
a Japanese man with long hair?
Do you know him?
So you do know him!
Y-Yeah. He was desperately trying
to help these children get away.
Right now, he's staying in
the town trying to save people.
When we split up,
he mentioned the Hotel Versteck.
Oh, Nina!
I left my car right outside
the path through the woods.
Use that car to transport
the injured and the sick.
And contact the police
as soon as possible.
A-Are you planning on
going to the town?
You shouldn't do that.
You'll get killed!
Tenma's...
that Asian man is my friend.
I'm going to save him.
Contact the police immediately!
Hotel Versteck...
Mr. Grimmer...
Hey. I knew you'd come,
Dr. Tenma.
Two in the neighboring building...
one on the floor below this one...
and one here.
I got a total of four of them.
The Magnificent Steiner appeared,
didn't he?
No. He didn't come.
I did it on my own.
I did it in a fit of anger.
Anyway, those wounds...
Oh yeah...
So I don't forget...
Here. It's a letter.
I got it from Inspector Lunge.
He found it in
the Red Rose Mansion.
Help him. He headed to
the Hotel Bergbach by himself.
Before I do that, you...
I'm fine.
Let me rest.. .for a while.
Let me introduce you.
This is. ..Franz Bonaparta.
Mr. Grimmer...
It's all right, Wim.
It's been raining a lot.
This area is nice when it's sunny. ..
don't you think, Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
When it gets sunny again,
let's have a picnic with Wim here.
Yeah.
We'll have good wine...
and good cheese.
Yeah.
I'm sad.
I'm not sad
because I'm going to die.
Right now,
I'm sad because my son died.
You can't make
people's feelings go away.
My emotions were
lost somewhere.
It's as if I had received a letter that
had been sent to me decades ago.
So this is true sadness...
So this is happiness...
The last episode of
The Magnificent Steiner...
He probably turned back
into a human.
Mr. Grimmer?
Mr. Grimmer!
I...