So...
you're Roberto.
I have no name.
That's unfortunate.
As a police officer,
I'd prefer to know the name of
the criminal who's going to kill me.
Oh. This is terrible.
He was such a good person.
He risked his life for us.
Mr. Grimmer...
Dr. Tenma,
where are you going?
I can't waste any time.
You're going to where
Inspector Lunge is, aren't you?
I'm going, too. I have a gun.
This letter...
This letter that Inspector Lunge
gave to Mr. Grimmer...
It seems that Inspector Lunge
found it at Red Rose Mansion.
"I've been watching you."
"I've been watching
so I could devour you whole."
"But instead,
everything about you consumed me."
"When I was falling apart,
how did I look to you?"
the object that you gave me.. ."
"You left me a beautiful jewel."
"The twins who look as if they
were blessed with eternal life."
"The most sinful deed is to
take away a person's name."
"Let's get your name back."
"I'll give you your name back."
"Your name is Anna."
"Right now, I'm just sad."
"Sad."
You wrote this, didn't you?
I. ..fell in love with
the mother of the twins.
My mind changed in an instant.
So...
The people who knew about her. ..
about the twins...
and about the experiment...
I killed them all.
That's all.
Answer me. Who are you?
If you don't get that wound treated,
it'll kill you.
Answer me if you
want to be saved.
Where is Johan?
Why do you go
so far for Johan?
What's your relationship
with him?
You've fallen quite far in the world,
haven't you, Inspector Lunge?
The BKA's best investigator is in
this rural village all by himself...
You went sightseeing
without a badge.
You investigated too deep into a
scandal involving a parliament member
and lost work.
Chasing Tenma became
your only reason for living.
That's right. I'm impressed
you researched that.
Your wife.. .
Is living with another man.
She looks so happy.
And your grandson thinks
that man is his grandfather.
He can speak now...
And he calls him
"Grandpa, Grandpa."
Shut up.
You want to see him,
don't you?
Shut up.
Your grandson is
growing up beautifully.
Shut up.
You want to see him,
don't you?
Shut up!
You've fallen.
The old Inspector Lunge
wasn't like this.
"Who am I?"
"What's my relationship
with Johan?"
I have no name. I have no country.
I have no memories.
Before I realized it, I was out
of the orphanage and working.
One day,
Johan appeared before me.
He awakened
one of my memories.
Just one memory.
What is his real name?
He said that he didn't know.
His own name?
Yeah.
He said that he was
from an orphanage.
He said that he had
forgotten everyone else,
but he remembered
his friend's name.
He forgot his name,
but remembered his friend's?
Yeah. His friend liked
drawing and bugs.
But he didn't like killing bugs,
so he let them go from their cages.
I believe his name was...
Adolph Reinhardt.
He loved the hot cocoa that was
given to them once each week.
Johan came to me. ..
and handed me a cup.
I remembered the thing I looked
forward to each week in that orphanage.
I loved that hot cocoa.
It would be nice if the rain
would wash everything away.
Fear, hate, and sadness...
But it's quite the opposite.
Everything gets worse.
Even on that day,
it was raining like this.
Mr. Liebert, former head of
the East German Trade Commission,
who fled to the West from
East Germany just the other day
appeared before the media
with his wife and children.
The Lieberts didn't appear
to be exhausted.
And their two children have
bright expressions on their faces.
Are you a refugee as well?
Yes. From Czechoslovakia...
You say that you
know the children?
Please let me see them.
Just one look.
Even just their
sleeping faces.
A tragedy occurred
that night...
One girl is confirmed
to be alive!
A man and a woman
are dead!
The boy is in serious condition
but he has a pulse!
Where's the patient?!
Blood pressure, 72/50...
Pulse, 138!
The bullet went in
through his forehead?!
Kill...
I didn't know what in the world
had happened.
No. I knew.
I knew everything,
but I ran away.
I stopped thinking about
anything and ran away.
I tried to draw.
Pictures of those ideal twins...
Of them surrounded by love...
But. ..no matter how many I drew,
I couldn't draw it.
Because I knew that
it didn't exist.
Inspector Lunge is at Hotel Bergbach.
That's just up ahead, right?
Yes.
Let's go. Be careful.
We don't know where
they're coming from.
I...
I created a monster.
I brought that monster
back to life.
This won't kill you, will it?
I don't have much grip
in my right hand.
Dr. Tenma shot me
in a library in Munich.
It would have been easy
to kill him there.
But I can't kill him.
Dr. Tenma is the one
who's to be left.
He'll be the one left in the end. ..
all alone.
He's going to die
alone and sad.
Without a name.
This is part of Johan's plan.
Dr. Tenma will be allowed to
see the sight Johan has seen.
I want to see that sight, too.
I want to see it.
Inspector Lunge...
you won't see it.
You're going to die.
This is also part of...
Johan's plan.
Plans?
The computer in my head tells me
that doesn't add up.
Answer me.
Where is Johan?!
This is terrible.
It's like a battlefield.
Johan is not here.
How do you know?
He's watching this
from somewhere.
As if he were watching
a line of ants...
Anyway, let's look inside.
Tenma was headed here.
Someone! Is anyone here?!
I'll look on the second floor.
A child?
Don't come near me!
It's all right. We're on your side.
We've come to help.
Look. I'm not holding anything.
Okay? It's all right, right?
Oh.
The woman in the picture...
"The woman in the picture"?
There were lots of pictures.
You look exactly like the girl
in those pictures.
"Lots of pictures"?
There's a boy with the same face.
They were pictures of twins.
Where did you
see those pictures?!
Where did you see them?!
Th-The hill to the south...
At the "Vampire's House."
Hey. Does anybody know?
Do you know where my son is?
Hey...
Wim, where did you go?!
Everyone's dead.
It's the devil.
The devil has come
to this town!
There's no one here
anymore.
Johan was here just
a moment ago doing that.
Is that what you're saying?
They're all attempts at
drawing the two of you.
But they were left unfinished.
All the pictures look like
they're smiling affectionately...
But did Franz Bonaparta
draw these pictures?
What did Johan do upon
seeing these pictures?
...home.
I'm back. Welcome home.
Nina...
I saw something
very frightening.
Something really,
really frightening...
Many people died.
Red Rose Mansion...
Everyone drank alcohol.
And when they did...
When they did...
Everyone suffered and collapsed on
top of each other right before my eyes!
Where's my mom?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
That time...
The two of you
have to keep on living.
The two of you, keep on living.
Why are you crying?
Why are you crying?!
Don't cry!
Nina!
Nina?
He.. .was crying.
Nina...
In this room...
Just until a while ago,
in this room, by himself.
He cried just like
he did back then.
That rainy night...
If I hadn't shot him...
If I had forgiven him,
this wouldn't have continued.
All these people
wouldn't have died.
It may be too late.
But this time...
Where is Johan now?
He went into town...
in order to end all of this.