Everyone's dead.
The devil...
The devil has
come to this town!
Listen. I'm going in first.
You back me up from behind.
Our first priority is to
save Inspector Lunge.
Okay.
Dr. Tenma...
Wim ! Why did
you come here?!
A woman came to see you.
A woman?
She went to
the Vampire's house.
She looked like the twins
in the pictures there.
Twins in the pictures?
Nina?!
So she's called Nina...
She's called Nina now, huh?
Yes. Nina Fortner.
Such a good name.
Cherish your name.
That's what you always told me,
Mr. Poppe.
Say, have you seen my dad?
I've looked everywhere,
but I can't find him.
All right. Right now, I have important
business to attend to here.
Once I'm finished,
let's look for your father.
Dad hasn't killed anyone,
has he?
No, Wim. Your father
isn't that sort of person.
All right. Now hide in
that grocer's over there.
Take Wim and hide, quickly!
We finally meet, Dr. Tenma.
Let's die.
You and me together.
Wait, Nina!
I'm going to look for him...
Franz Bonaparta!
That time at Red Rose Mansion. ..
He told me...
All right? Listen carefully.
Forget everything
you've just seen.
Run far away.
As far as you can...
People. .. can become
whatever they want to be.
You two are beautiful jewels.
And that's why you
mustn't become monsters.
That's what he told me!
That's why I'm...
That's why...
Mr. Poppe!
Mr. Poppe?! Mr. Poppe?!
Franz.. .Bonaparta...
Roberto!
Wim! Run away!
Show it to me.
The "scenery for
a doomsday."
You...
can't see it.
Wim...
Step back.
Dr. Tenma...
For you, all lives are equal.
That's why I
came back to life.
But you've realized it,
haven't you?
The only thing equal
for everyone...
is death.
You can see it.
My scenery for a doomsday.
No!
Dr. Tenma,
you mustn't shoot him!
Don't shoot.
I...
I forgive you.
Even if we're the last
two people in the world.
I forgive you.
That's my...
From me to you...
No.
There are things that
can't be taken back.
There's no going back.
Dr. Tenma is
going to shoot me.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Isn't that right?
Stop!
The devil...
The devil has come to this town
and killed everyone in it.
Wim...
S-Stop. My son... Sto...
W-What is that?!
A-A monster...
What is this?!
Stop! Get away!
Get away from my Wim!
This is D-KMIF!
We've landed in
the west side of Ruhenheim!
We've confirmed that
the east side is safe!
Assist the residents
immediately!
This is terrible.
Are there any survivors?
Our DNN reporting team,
have finally entered the town through
the southern hills after much difficulty.
We have never heard
of such an event!
It appears that a massacre
nearly wiped out a whole town!
What happened in this quiet town
in Southern Germany?
Yes. Right now, we are holding
only one person as a suspect.
Herbert Knaup, 38 years old,
unemployed.
Dad...
Yes. He's confessed to a crime.
The shooting of a young man...
Dad shot him to save me!
It seems he is
a severe alcoholic.
He claims he shot because
there was a seven-headed monster
with many horns attacking his son.
- He was talking nonsense.
- Dad...
Dad...
Could you respond?
Damn it. I got cut off again.
It's as we told you.
Well... It doesn't make sense.
A young man named Johan
tried to annihilate this town
so that he could
commit suicide.
Dr. Gillen. ..could you explain it to us
in a way that we can understand?
It'll take a while
to tell you everything.
No, even if I did,
you still may not understand.
We've taken in an injured
police officer at the Hotel Versteck!
How is he?
His life is not in danger,
but he's only half conscious...
Crap! Isn't there a single officer
who can explain the situation to us?!
Right here.
I know everything.
Who are you?
Inspector Lunge of the BKA...
I don't have any identification on me
right now, but contact the BKA.
Roberto... He died huh?
He's the perpetrator who's
responsible for this incident.
I tried to stop him,
but he lost consciousness.
I moved away from him and
headed towards the stairs.
When I did, I heard his voice.
In the next instant, I took a blow to
the back of my head and passed out.
He said then...
"I still can't see
the end of the world."
Anyway, we'll discuss the details
after you get treated.
Don't cry.
It's all right now.
Excuse me.
I need to confirm your identity.
Henich of Erft Street.
This is my wife, Franca.
Do you have anything that
can prove your identities?
Yeah.
Huh?
What? What's wrong?
Well...
The lottery ticket's gone.
Huh?
I-I'm sure I left it
in my pocket.
I'm going to look for it!
D-Dear...
I dropped it somewhere !
Somewhere!
Its all right, dear!
We don't need it.
It's more than enough
that we're still alive.
Umm... Your identification.
You can present it
to me afterwards.
Umm.. .
The remaining survivors...
Oh... There they are.
Excuse me...
I need to confirm your identity.
Go around to each house!
There still may be
survivors inside!
U-Umm...
What is it?
Actually...
What?!
Johan... He's still alive.
Well. ..
with that head wound...
Even if he had
the best neurosurgeon...
No. There is one.
Call him.
There's something
I'd like to ask you.
Could it be that you're...
There's no mistake.
You're the wanted–
Dr. Tenma!
You're Dr. Tenma,
aren't you?
Could you come with us?
Hey, wait a second!
Inspector Lunge of the BKA
is asking for you.
Huh?!
He wanted us to tell you that
there's a patient who needs your help.
My dad isn't a murderer!
Listen little boy, we need to
ask your father a few questions.
Dad... Dad tried to save me!
All right, c'mon.
Dad!
I want to forgive him.
I want to forgive.
Tenma, you aren't wrong.
What you did then...
and what you're going to do...
My dad isn't...
My dad isn't a murderer!
Let's begin the operation.