"When Zeus commanded"'
"the people who lived on the land
learned to plant seeds and till the soil."
Karl, your pronunciation
is wrong again.
Sorry, I'm trying to be careful.
But you've gotten better.
When you first came here, I thought
that you were a terrible student.
Y-Yes.
What happened to him?
What happened to
that Japanese doctor?
I hear he's traveling
around the world.
I see.
I'd like to see him once more.
Yes.
You've started working?
That's good.
So what kind of work is it?
I'm an interior decorator.
I see ! You probably have
quite a good eye for furniture.
It's interiors, but it's a little
different from that.
I'm a kitchen designer.
Oh?
It's funny, isn't it? I've never even
stood in a kitchen before.
Then could you do
my kitchen sometime?
Sure.
But your kitchens
must fetch quite a price.
Just a little.
You haven't been drinking,
have you?
No, not a single drop.
Good.
Let's take our time.
Even if we rush, the day will pass and
tomorrow will come in the same way.
That's what happiness is, right?
Are you tired of hearing that?
Happiness, huh?
He said he was happy just because
I was waiting for him at the station.
That man called Martin?
People are strange.
Their sadness slowly fades and
leaves only the fun memories.
People sure are
designed conveniently.
That's why we can
keep on living.
Let me introduce you.
This is Verdemann, the lawyer.
He's the person who cleared
your name, Mr. Grimmer...
I looked up as much
as I could about you.
You graduated from
511 Kinderheim.
You were a secret agent
for East Germany and
traveled around the world
posing as a freelance journalist.
Afterwards, you investigated
human rights violations
as a freelance journalist.
The mountain of data in your big bag
was evidence of that.
But the only thing we never learned
was your real name.
Wolfgang Grimmer.
Not only his name...
He left without
telling us anything.
Inspector Lunge...
I'm no longer an inspector,
Detective Suk.
I heard that you became
a professor at a police academy.
I converse regularly
with my daughter now.
I say converse,
but it's by email.
We spent our lives as parent and child
without telling each other anything.
We both lived our lives not knowing
anything about each other.
How many things can
people say in a lifetime?
He probably had a lot he wanted
to talk about over a good beer.
You're going back
to Düsseldorf?
Yes. The company I'm under
contract with is over there.
I see.
Are you all right?
A lot happened to you there.
"It's pointless to run away."
"What's important is to
face the truth and move on."
Right?
Yes.
Could you dispose of this
when you have the chance?
See you later.
Okay. Take care.
Tell me if anything happens.
Dr. Gillen and
I will always help you.
Dieter and "him", too.
Give him my regards.
Okay.
"Questioning continues for Dr. Tenma.
The case in its entirety is still unclear."
"Inspector Lunge's
testimony begins."
"Could this possibly be the worst
serial murder case in European history?"
"Dr. Tenma
completely innocent."
"The police formally
apologize to Dr. Tenma."
"A motive for the case
still has not been found."
"Who is the mysterious young man
who is the supposed real criminal?"
"The University Münster's
medical department"
"invites Dr. Tenma to
become a professor."
"Dr. Tenma declines firmly."
"Dr. Tenma joins
Doctors Without Borders."
The articles get
smaller and smaller.
People are designed
conveniently, huh?
Hey, Dieter, you've gotten bigger
since the last time I saw you.
Mr. Heckel, it looks like you've
gotten sneakier since I last saw you.
You're still a chatty brat, huh?
Sorry, but I can't hang around.
I've got soccer practice.
Hey, wait a second.
Did Tenma come back?
Damn it.
He joined Doctors Without Borders,
or something.
He's trying to look good by doing
something that doesn't make any money!
I can't get a hold of him.
What are you going to do
if he is back?
With all the expenses
I incurred and
the labor I put into that job
he gave me a little while back,
I don't think he
compensated me enough.
Tenma gave you a job?
He said that he was
just looking for someone,
but it was a lot of work!
I even had to steal confidential
information from the police!
Who knows what'll happen
if they catch me...
Hey.
Give Tenma this bill!
If he can't pay it I'm going to make him
become an underground doctor again.
Tell him to be ready!
We've been waiting for you.
You haven't come for a while.
Well, I've been overseas.
Please, share this with everyone.
Oh, my, my...
The weather is nice.
Many leaves are photosynthesizing.
Life. .. Countless genes...
Do you know of Mendel?
Yes, he discovered
the rules of genes.
I went to the same university
as Mendel.
Bruno University.
It's in a city in Moravia, the Czech
Republic's southeastern region.
It's a nice place.
I'll go there some time.
Thank you...
for coming by so many times.
I've enjoyed the times
we spent together.
It's nothing.
I'm in a good mood today.
I feel like I can
tell you anything.
No matter how terrifying...
You have something you
want to ask me, don't you?
You're...
the mother of the twins,
aren't you?
Yes.
I loved him.
That man killed him.
That was that
man's experiment.
I will never forgive that man.
Even if I die, these children growing
inside me will definitely punish him.
My hand...
Don't let go of my hand.
Who is the real monster?
Those children are still alive,
aren't they?
Yes. They're well.
I just remembered.
What is it?
I may never
remember it again.
I have to say it now.
I gave those children names.
Their names are...
Come in.
Tardy, as usual.
You're ten minutes late
for our appointment.
Sorry, Professor Kronecker...
Its fine. You know why
I called you in today, don't you?
It's about
your graduation thesis...
Come forward.
Y-Yes.
I know that a lot
has happened to you.
It must be pretty difficult to catch up
after your absence from school.
But that isn't an excuse
for my grades.
That's right.
Now about your thesis...
It's the best.
This is the best thesis I have
received from any of my students.
You did well.
I'm proud of you.
Th-Thank you very much.
What do you want to become?
Yes! A lawyer!
I pray that you will be able to
save many people.
You may go.
Yes!
But...
You won't be allowed to be late
for court, Fräulein Nina Fortner.
Yes!
Yes? Hello?
Oh, Dieter?
Well, are you graduating?
I'll be here with you even if you aren't.
Oh, how reliable you are!
I'll have you cheer me up
the next time we meet.
I can tell from your voice
that you're just acting.
You did it.
Congratulations!
Thank you. Things will get
tougher from this point on.
Let's celebrate.
Come home quickly!
I can't right now.
I have a part-time job.
I also have a lot planned
with my friends.
What are you talking about?!
Tenma's coming back!
I just got a call.
But he's immediately
going back overseas
with Doctors Without Borders
afterwards.
When's he coming?!
He said he's coming back tomorrow.
So come back quickly Nina!
Oh, Nina,
about our plans tomorrow...
Sorry. I can't go anymore!
Tenma... I can see Tenma.
Oh, hello.
Thank you for your efforts.
You've been
sleeping ever since...
Can you hear me?
I talked to your mother.
She loves you.
She told me your real name.
You had a name.
Dr. Tenma. .. There's something
I want only you to hear.
That time when the monster
appeared before me...
Stop!
Don't touch these children!
No!
Don't come near us!
This is an experiment.
One must be left behind,
one must be taken away.
This is an experiment.
Now, which one
will be taken away?
Don't let go.
Mom...
Don't let go of my hand.
This one.
No...
This one!
No!
Did Mother try to save me?
Or did she mistake me
for my sister?
Which is it?
Which one of us
wasn't wanted?
I'll be going now.