Your mom deserted you!
She threw out you
and your alcoholic dad like garbage!
So don't you crawl out
of that garbage heap ever again!
The Town of Slaughter
I'm sorry, but I want you out of here.
If you want a drink,
then pay your tab first.
If you want money…
I've got it. This is enough for one drink.
We don't sell liquor to people who pay
with their kid's hard-earned money.
What did you say?
Now get out!
It was probably him.
Do you mean that thing with Mr. Conrad?
He also could've killed
Mrs. Hillman's dog.
That dope doesn't have the guts
to ever shoot a gun.
That's for sure.
He's just a cowardly alcoholic.
How can I find anything in this rain?
Hey Merkel! Let's pack it in and go back!
Hey! Merkel!
It's him! I found him!
Merkel! Mer--
Merkel?
Laufer here! Please respond!
Someone! Someone answer!
I'll take your gun as well.
That dope doesn't have the guts
to ever shoot a gun.
That's for sure.
He's just a cowardly alcoholic.
Corpses… all over town.
It's like a battlefield.
Wim!
What's happened, Wim?
It's all right. Calm down.
It's me.
I…
Calm down. Now, let go of the gun.
I don't remember, but I shot them, right?
They're always bullying me, so I…
Wim. You…
It's all right. Calm down.
It's all right now. Don't be afraid.
Calm down and try to remember.
Who gave you this gun?
Hang in there!
How in the world
did you get here on that leg, Laufer?
Call… the station.
The phone lines are down.
My… gun was taken.
Was it someone from this town?
No. I don't know him.
He was an outsider I'd never seen.
Anyway,
we've got to get you some first aid!
Is he a friend of yours?
What are you talking about?
How many of your friends
have come to this town?
What are you getting at?
You must have handed out
a heck of a lot of guns.
I mean, you even gave this boy a gun.
Wim! A gun? Don't tell me you've…
"You're not trash.
Don't hang around with those boys."
"There's a reason why you were born."
It seems you told this boy
those things to give him strength.
He didn't fire that gun.
It's still fully loaded.
Wim stuck to the things you taught him.
You did the right thing, Wim.
It's all right now, Wim.
However, there are corpses all over town.
How many did you hand out?
How many guns did you give to this town?
How many people took guns from you?
You'd better not get me any angrier!
Get me angry, and there'll be hell to pay!
He looked… just like our grandson!
What?
He looked just like our dead grandson.
"He"?
He knew a lot about us.
He was like our real grandson.
Who is "he"?
You wrote letters
to your deceased grandson.
But you were sending him intelligence,
weren't you?
Who is "he?"
I must be the target.
His target is me.
Yes.
That's exactly right, Mr. Poppe.
Or should we say, Franz Bonaparta?
The heavy rains continue to fall
in southern Germany
causing extensive damage
along rivers in Bavaria.
You know what? You smoke way too much.
I need to. I've quit drinking.
You should quit smoking too.
Dieter, what is that you've been drawing?
So, does it look like him?
Like who?
Tenma! Can't you tell?
Maybe I'll give that
to the police the next time.
They still don't believe
in the critical part.
Here's what I'll tell them next time.
"This is the man I'm talking about."
"This man has gone all alone
to kill the monster."
Tenma will come back, won't he?
Here are more details on the damage
throughout the region.
Due to flooding of the Elgar River,
several roads are closed
and all rail lines are blocked.
Power outages throughout the region
also mean that phone lines are out.
This email arrived three days ago.
Dr. Gillen and I discussed it
and decided that we must show it to you.
Thank you.
"Dear Nina.'
"I'm waiting for you in Ruhenheim."
It's Johan.
Do you think so too?
This is how you described
what you think Johan is trying to do.
"The perfect suicide."
You also said
many innocent people would die.
Ruhenheim.
There is a countryside town
by that name in southern Germany.
Tenma may be headed there.
We must go there!
Please allow me to go there.
This is a very bizarre feeling I have.
I initially assumed
that you were nothing more than
a figment of one man's imagination.
You seemed more like
a character in one of your picture books.
For many years,
I have investigated this case
by objectively collecting data on it.
But this time,
I completely ignored that data
and traveled around
following that man's fantasies.
I was only halfway seriously
following the leads
when I met a young man
in the Czech Republic
who often visited the Red Rose Mansion.
It was your son.
This is a postcard delivered to him.
It's signed with "K.P."
which is your real name, Klaus Poppe.
After tracking down this landscape
and coming face-to-face with you,
it still feels quite odd.
It's as if you are a character
who escaped from a picture book.
But this is real.
On the list of people who defected
from Czechoslovakia I got from
a group that helped them,
I found the name "Klaus Poppe."
Just after the fall of the Berlin Wall,
you escaped here.
What were you running from?
From people like me?
Kinderheim 511,
which was founded by East Germany
based on your ideas…
That was where I was created.
Were you running from people like me?
He's predictable.
I can tell what that young man,
Johan, is trying to do.
I also know that right now,
it's happening right here in this town.
Was that another gunshot?
I saw a lot of dead people
on the way over here.
Something's happened to this town!
Hey! Hurry up and get me out of this town!
No can do.
All ways out are closed off.
Darn it all. What are you up to anyway?
You keep going in and out
and you shower every time you come back.
The town smells of gunpowder and blood.
It's disgusting.
Now, just calm down.
I ordered you some hot tea
from the front desk.
It will be just fine.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Once it stops raining,
everything will disappear.
Disappear? What will?
All the memories.
I'll only let you go
under a few conditions.
Firstly, you must go with Dr. Gillen.
And second, there's no way
we're letting you carry a gun.
I don't need a gun.
I'll get ready to leave.
Also, start taking care of the things
that I told you about.
Get Deiter, Eva and you, Dr. Reichwein,
Mr. Schuwald, Karl and Lotte,
and anyone else who knows Johan,
and make sure they're in hiding.
Johan is trying to erase
all memories of himself.
Come on, before Dieter notices you!
Memories of Dieter.
Memories of Dr. Reichwein.
Memories of Lotte and Karl.
Memories of Mr. and Mrs. Fortner.
Memories of Tenma.
I have memories I don't want to forget.
No matter how much I may
want to erase some memories…
What about Johan?
What about your memories of Johan?
I will never lose them.
A police officer…
His gun's been taken.
You! Don't move!
Save… the town…
Who shot you?
There's shooting everywhere in town.
First, several armed men… came into town.
Then suddenly, everyone in town had guns…
and was shooting each other.
I've got to go… and get help…
We must at least save… the children…
Help them…
Johan…
The first time I heard that name
was in the statement of a certain
neurosurgeon in 1995.
Dr. Tenma.
So, you admit that there was a flaw
in your theory about this case.
No. To me, he is still a possible suspect.
Johan is still an imaginary person to me.
Imaginary person…
Those words captivated me
during this vacation.
How can a real person
become an imaginary one?
The answer is simple.
Eliminate everyone who knows that person
and everyone who knows their past.
Ultimately, it will wind up like the end
of your picture book, Mr. Bonaparta.
"At last, he had found a name,
but there was no longer
anyone around to call him by it."
"Such a shame,
because Johan was such a wonderful name."
That could be
what's happening now in this town.
If I were Johan, that's what I would do.
You see, I'm an imaginary person too.
I'm not the person Neumaier
that's written in your guestbook,
and I'm not the person
Wolfgang Grimmer is either.
I'm not anyone.
I may as well disappear with them too.
The people who stole my memories
and stole my name.
I've been waiting.
I've simply been waiting here
for judgment to come down on me.
I'm not afraid of dying.
But, I don't know how to atone.
I just waited here
ready to accept whatever would come.
"I've been waiting," you say?
"I'm not afraid of dying," you say?
Don't you have any idea
how awful your crimes were?
Don't you know what it means to destroy
a person's sense of right and wrong?
Don't you know what will happen
when you awaken the monster in a person?
People…
People need to know what it's like
to enjoy good food.
We need to know
how to look forward to a weekend picnic.
the joy of having a beer after work.
People…
need to know how to grieve
from the depths of their hearts
when their child dies.
I won't let you die.
I'll remove you safely from this town
and expose everything.
I'll let the whole world know
who the beast you awakened is!
Before I can do that, I will protect you!
Where is Johan?
I don't know…
Then someone must be
leading this massacre.
Where is that person?
I don't know!
Where are they?
Another gunshot.
Is someone in there?
Can you see? I'm not carrying a weapon.
It's all right. Don't be afraid.
I've come to help you. It will be okay.
It's dangerous here. Understand?
You must get out of town.
Don't cry!
I'll lead you to the forest path.
You can run, right?
There's a man
at the Bergbach Hotel giving orders.
I see.
But all I've got is this one gun.
I found these two outside.
We're very sorry.
It feels like this all happened
because I won the lottery.
I should have told the police right away
when I found Conrad's body.
Then maybe the town
wouldn't have gone mad like this.
Did you buy these?
I haven't shot them even once!
I swear it!
Let me borrow this one and this one.
You protect this hotel.
What will you do?
Even ordinary people are carrying guns.
I'm a police officer.
I can tell the difference.
By the way, Mr. Grimmer.
When we're done here,
allow me to buy you a beer.
Sure, I'd be glad to share
a good beer with you.
Now!
Run! You must survive!
The Magnificent Steiner's Rage