I don't like having to do this
to elderly people,
but you're very important witnesses.
We can't have you dying
or running away from us.
I've barricaded the back door
and most of the windows with furniture.
But I'm sure if someone wanted to,
they could easily get through them.
It's better than nothing.
Why don't the two of us
get downstairs now?
You know how to shoot a gun, right?
I think I do.
I'll go with you.
I must go with you.
I can't have anything happen to you.
You will survive this
and expose the whole truth to the world.
Wim, you stay in here, okay?
But what if something
happens to you, Mr. Grimmer?
It will be all right. I've got
a powerful friend who will help us.
You do?
Yes, you can be assured of that.
Whenever I'm in a pinch,
he comes and helps me
no matter where I am.
He never lets any evil deed go unpunished.
He's the invincible Magnificent Steiner.
The Magnificent Steiner's Rage
Now! Run!
Take the trail north!
I think we've gotten
most of the children out now.
You go too! Now!
I still haven't looked
around the center of town.
Leave that to me.
I want you to guide everyone.
All right…
I have one question!
Do you know a man named Bonaparta…
I mean, Klaus Poppe?
Poppe?
Yes, he owns the Hotel Versteck.
What are you doing there?
Don't be frightened. I'm on your side.
I tried to escape as fast as I could…
but the town is filled with bodies!
I don't know where to run to.
Where did you escape from?
He's… giving orders from his room.
I heard him talking.
"He"?
Roberto!
It was weird because
he kept going in and out of the room.
He showered and changed
every time he came back.
Where is this Roberto now?
A room on the fourth floor
of Hotel Bergbach.
I didn't think he was that kind of guy. I…
Listen. Some people are hiding
at the other hotel, Hotel Versteck.
You can get there alone, right?
Alone? I'm too scared!
Come on. Stand up.
I'm scared!
Dr. Tenma.
Inspector Lunge.
This trip of fantasy
has become one of reality at last.
Now that the real person
that is you has arrived,
my vacation of tracking this thread
of fantasy has come to an end.
From here on,
I'm working as a police officer.
It's good to get back on the job.
Take this girl with you.
The person you're after is
at Hotel Versteck.
Franz Bonaparta.
Inspector Lunge, where are you going?
Like I said, to work.
Let's talk when I get back.
I have plenty of questions for you.
Dr. Tenma…
I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Nina?
My memories… They're becoming clearer.
The ones that were most deeply hidden.
Your most deeply hidden memories?
The ones I never wanted to remember.
If these memories…
If Johan remembers these same things…
Show yourself!
Don't shoot!
I'm from this town. Please don't shoot.
Where's the man giving orders?
I asked you, where's Roberto?
You have to stand up and walk.
I can't take it anymore!
There are dead people everywhere!
I'll lose my mind if I stay here!
That's why you have to go
to Hotel Versteck as soon as possible.
No!
Open your eyes, Erika.
Please, Erika!
Your wife… Right?
I'm sorry, but your wife is dead.
I'm on your side.
It's dangerous here.
You've got to get somewhere safe.
Give me your gun!
I'll kill whoever it was who killed Erika!
Hurry up and give me your gun!
I'll kill whoever it was
who destroyed our happy life!
That isn't what your wife
would have wanted.
Your wife would've wanted
your child to be safe.
Isn't that right?
I'll take you to the trail.
You can escape to the north on it.
You'll come with us.
Forget about going to the hotel.
No. I don't want to go anywhere.
Fine. I'll be back soon. Stay right there.
Understand?
It sure is quiet.
So, it's not me and my wife
these people are after
because we won the lottery, right?
That's right.
Damn. These last few days have
felt like a living hell.
I'd lost my mind.
I can't believe I bought all these guns
because of all that money.
Normal life is best.
Normal, eh?
I have to tell my wife
this wasn't our fault.
Honey! Can you hear me?
Mr. Heinich!
My… wife…
Mrs. Heinich!
It hurts…
Hurry! Come with me!
They're shooting
from the building across the way.
Does this hotel have a basement?
There's a storage room under the kitchen.
Are you hanging in there?
Me? What about you, honey?
My dad's doing this.
Dad's out of liquor,
so he lost his mind and is doing this.
No, he's not, Wim.
Dad's gone crazy like he does
when he hits me every day. Dad's…
Do you really think your dad's
the kind of person who'd do this?
If I... if I went out there,
surely this would all end…
If I…
Don't make me say it again.
There's no way in hell
I'm letting you die.
If you keep talking like that,
I'll tie you up here.
You stay here. I'll handle this.
Mr. Grimmer…
Remember what I said?
When in a real bind, the invincible
Magnificent Steiner shows up.
I saw examples of that
in my experiments long ago.
When faced with the massive stress
of overwhelming anger or sadness,
the children would manifest
a different personality.
Those children would be
excessively violent,
and most of them would kill themselves.
I'm surprised you've survived so long.
Look! I'm unarmed!
Just listen to me for a minute!
Why are you doing this?
Who ordered you to do this?
It doesn't matter to me if you're people
from the former Eastern Bloc,
or if you're ex-secret police,
or whatever!
Look, I'm just a nobody from nowhere.
Are you listening?
Listen to me carefully!
Don't listen to someone's orders!
Listen to your own heart!
Think long and hard
about what you're doing now!
You can do that, right?
You can do it!
What are you doing?
I was so afraid, but I made it here alone.
Thank goodness you're here!
The Magnificent Steiner!
Hey, kids!
I used to be glued to the TV
watching it every single day,
but I have no memory of the final episode.
…just call my name.
Okay, let's go.
No!
I wonder if the young man
who was the weakling main character
realized that he transformed
into the Magnificent Steiner
when overcome with anger.
I wonder if the young man found happiness.
That young man…
Did that young man ever find it?
Only a little farther.
A little more
and we'll be out of the woods.
You're people from Ruhenheim, aren't you?
Who are you?
Something is happening in town,
isn't there?
Some people with guns entered
and started a massacre around town.
You're not part of them, are you?
Calm down. We're on your side.
Was there an Asian?
Did you see a Japanese man with long hair?
Are you friends of his?
Have you seen him?
Yes. He did everything he could
to get these children out of there.
He's still there now
trying to help the townspeople.
When I left him,
he was headed to Hotel Versteck.
Nina!
My car is at the end of the trail.
Use it to take the injured
and sick to a hospital.
And contact the police
as soon as possible!
Are you two going to town?
You shouldn't! You'll be killed!
Tenma… The Asian man, he's my friend.
I have to save him.
Now hurry and contact the police!
Hotel Versteck.
Mr. Grimmer…
Hi… I thought you'd come, Dr. Tenma.
Two in the building next door…
One downstairs… and one in here…
I killed four in total.
So, the Magnificent Steiner showed up.
No, he never showed.
I did this myself.
I let my anger take over
and did it myself.
I have to check that wound.
That's right.
Before I forget… Here, a letter.
Inspector Lunge gave it to me.
He said he found it
at the Red Rose Mansion.
Help him.
He's gone to Hotel Bergbach alone.
Before that, you need--
Forget about me.
Let me… relax here for a while.
I'll introduce you.
That's Franz Bonaparta.
Mr. Grimmer…
It's all right, Wim.
It sure is raining a lot.
It's so much nicer
around here when it's sunny.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
It is.
When the weather clears up,
let's take Wim here with us for a picnic.
Yes.
We'll bring along
some delicious wine and delicious cheese.
Yes.
I'm sad.
I'm not sad because I'm going to die.
Because my child died…
I'm sad now.
People cannot lose their emotions.
My emotions… got lost somewhere inside me.
They're like a letter I sent to myself…
that took decades to finally arrive.
Is this how true sadness feels…
or is this… happiness?
In the final episode…
of The Magnificent Steiner…
he probably…
turned back... into a human being.
Mr. Grimmer…
Mr. Grimmer!
What…
What have I…
A Man Without a Name