They're… all dead…
A devil…
A devil has come to this town!
Are you ready? I'll go in first.
You cover me from behind.
What's important here
is to rescue Inspector Lunge.
Right.
Dr. Tenma!
Wim! What did you come here for?
A woman's here looking for you, Dr. Tenma.
A woman?
She looks just like the girl
in the drawings of twins
at the vampire's house.
Drawings of twins… Nina!
So, she's called "Nina."
She's called "Nina" now, is she?
Yes. Nina Fortner.
Such a nice name.
Mr. Poppe, you've always told me,
"It's important to cherish your name."
Did you see my dad?
I've looked everywhere,
but can't find him.
All right. But we have something
important to do here first.
Once we're done,
we'll look for your father right away.
My dad didn't kill anyone, did he?
That's right, Wim.
Your father isn't that kind of person.
Yeah.
Okay. You go and hide
in that store over there.
Take cover with Wim now!
We meet at last, Dr. Tenma.
Let's die.
Let us die…
together.
The Scenery of The End
Wait, Nina!
I have to find him! Franz Bonaparta!
Way back then,
at the Red Rose Mansion, he told me…
Now, listen well.
You will forget everything you just saw.
You will run far away.
As far as you possibly can.
People can become
whatever they want to be.
You are both beautiful gems.
That's why you mustn't become monsters.
That's what he said to me!
That's why I…
Mr. Poppe!
Franz Bonaparta…
Roberto…
Run, Wim!
Show me…
the scenery of the end…
You…
cannot see it.
Wim! Get away from there!
Dr. Tenma,
to you, all lives are equal.
That's why I returned to life.
But you understand now, don't you?
The only thing that's equal for all…
is death.
You can see…
the scenery of the end.
Don't!
Dr. Tenma, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
I…
I forgive you.
Even if only you
and I were left in this world,
I'd forgive you.
That's what I can do for you.
It's too late.
Some things cannot be undone.
There is no going back.
Dr. Tenma will shoot me.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Isn't that right?
Don't!
A devil…
A devil has come to this town…
and massacred everyone in it.
Wim…
No… Not my son…
Don't…
What… the hell is that?
A monster…
What the hell is that?
Stop! Get away from him!
Get away from my Wim!
This is rescue chopper F. We've arrived
at the west side of Ruhenheim.
The east side of town
has also been secured.
Get everyone to safety immediately!
This is a nightmare.
Do you think anyone's left alive?
After great effort, our DNN news crew
was finally able to enter the town
through the hills in the south.
This is an unprecedented incident.
Nearly the entire town has been
wiped out in a massacre.
What in heaven's name happened
in this tranquil town in southern Germany?
Right. As I said, there's only one man
that we've arrested as a suspect.
He's Herbert Knaup. Age 38, unemployed.
Dad!
Yes. He's admitted to the murder.
He shot one young man.
Dad shot him to save me!
The thing is,
he's a pretty serious alcoholic.
His said reason for doing it was,
"A seven-headed monster
with lots of horns was attacking my son."
He keeps talking nonsense like that.
-Dad…
-Please respond.
Dammit. It went out again.
It's just like I already told you.
Right, but you see,
that doesn't make any sense at all.
Why would this young man, Johan, wipe out
this town so he could kill himself?
Dr. Gillen, could you please explain this
in a way we can understand?
It's a very long story.
Even if I told you everything,
you may not understand it.
At the Versteck Hotel,
we've found one injured police officer.
His condition?
His life doesn't appear to be in danger,
but he's only barely conscious.
Dammit! Isn't there a single officer here
who can explain what happened?
I can.
I know eveything about it.
Who are you?
Inspector Lunge of the BKA.
I don't have my ID with me though.
Contact BKA to confirm who I am.
Roberto… Dead, huh?
He is essentially the one
behind this incident.
I tried to put an end to him,
but he only lost consciousness.
When I left him and went downstairs,
I heard him behind me.
The next instant,
I was hit on the head and blacked out.
When he did it, he said,
"I still can't see
the scenery of the end."
Anyway, get patched up first,
then we'll talk more.
Quit crying. It's all right now.
Excuse me. I need your names.
I'm Henning Heinich from Elft Street.
This is my wife, Franka.
Do you have any IDs?
I do.
What?
What is it? What's wrong?
Well…
It's gone, the lottery ticket.
What?
I had it in my pocket, but…
-I'll go look for it!
-Honey!
I must have dropped it somewhere!
Honey, forget about it!
We don't need that thing.
Just you and me being alive like this…
that's enough.
Excuse me. Can I see your IDs?
Make sure you show me later.
Let's see. Any other survivors?
There are two.
Excuse me. Can I have your names?
Check every house!
There could be survivors inside.
-Excuse me.
-What is it?
That man…
You're kidding!
Johan…
Is he alive?
Well, he's got a pretty bad head wound.
If we had a top neurosurgeon,
he might survive.
Actually, you do.
Who?
Get him.
Can I bother you for a moment?
You wouldn't happen to be…
No doubt about it.
You're that wanted man…
Dr. Tenma!
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
Can you come with us?
Hey! Hold on here!
Inspector Lunge
of the BKA wants to see you.
What?
He told me to tell you,
"There's a patient who needs you."
My dad's no murderer!
Now listen, kid. We've got to ask
your dad some questions.
My dad was just trying to save me!
Enough of that.
Dad!
I want to… forgive him.
I want to forgive him.
Tenma, what you did wasn't wrong.
You weren't wrong then…
and you won't be now either.
My dad--
My dad's no murderer!
Let's begin the surgery.
OPERATION ROOM
The Real Monster