Thank you for watching!
Outstanding.
Yes, his skills are truly unmatched.
The aneurysm was in such a delicate location, yet he clipped it off so effortlessly.
Indeed. Another perfect operation by the peerless Dr. Tenma.
I was finally able to observe the genius surgeon at work for myself.
No, I couldn't have done it without your help. Thank you all very much.
It's not midday already, is it?
Well, you know that surgery did go on for almost six straight hours
We don't have any more patients today
You should go rest
Mommy, where's Daddy?
What happened to Daddy?
Oh, my God.
We'll be right back.
To be continued...
Wake up, sleepyhead.
It's time to wake up, Dr. Tenma.
Looks like roles have been reversed.
It should be a princess like me who's awoken with a gentle kiss.
Ava, when did you get here?
his family to the west well i guess you did forget about our date didn't you kenzo i'm here in
düsseldorf where the east german trade i didn't forget fled to the west appeared before the press
yesterday along with his family mr and mrs liebert appeared to be in fine spirits along with their
fraternal twins the family will remain in düsseldorf for an unknown period of time before
moving to a home provided by local government authorities we'll be following this story with
great interest i feel like i'm still so exhausted hey wake up look at the tv they're talking about
you but seems to be recovering well after undergoing surgery dr heinemann director of
eisler memorial hospital where the surgery was performed is holding a press conference now we
take you there live. Mr. Rosenbach's diagnosis showed a ruptured aneurysm in his cranial artery.
The operation went smoothly, including the successful clipping of the patient's cerebral
hemorrhage. Mr. Rosenbach has quite a large following. What are his chances of a full
recovery? Yes, well, we will certainly do whatever is necessary for him to be able to sing again.
Dr. Heinemann's surgical team has completed many difficult surgeries, including Mr. Rosenbach's.
however with this latest success they have affirmed our country's status in
the medical world isn't that wonderful Kenzo it wasn't even about me it was all
about your father well that may be true but it's only because you did such a
wonderful job last night working as part of father's team I'm sure he appreciates
all your hard work since you're the one responsible for raising the hospital's
reputation. No, I'm the one who should be grateful. I mean, after all, it is thanks to your father that
I'm actually able to work here in Germany. Hang in there, Kenzo. If you stick with father, your
future is guaranteed. It won't be long before father becomes chairman of the board. Soon after
that, you'll become chief of surgery, and then chief director. Which means I'll be the director's
wife you better make me happy kenzo because hardship doesn't suit me
you still want to go out on that date or should we just
blood pressure 128 over 64. spatula
i will now scrape the pyramus
Whoa.
As usual, you did a magnificent job, Dr. Tenlo.
Thank you very much.
But it seems to me that your talents extend beyond the OR.
Well, you're the head of neurosurgery at such a young age.
You've become the golden boy for both the director and the chief of surgery.
And on top of that, you've even captured the heart of the director's daughter.
What exactly are you trying to say, doctor?
Ah, sorry. I'm not suggesting you've done anything wrong here.
After all, hospitals are ruled by politics.
Come on, you do realize that you're being used by the director now, don't you, Dr. Tenma?
I mean, take that amazing surgery you performed on that opera singer.
He acted like he performed it himself, even holding a televised press conference.
Well, if he is using you, then it must mean that you are gifted.
When you do become successful, don't forget about good old Becker.
I'll buy you a drink next time, eh, Tenma?
may I help you are you dr. tenma I am give me back my husband
Huh?
Give me back my husband!
Tell me, just tell me, why didn't you operate on my husband?
Who are you?
My husband was dying and he was brought to this emergency room first!
He came in long before that stupid opera singer was here!
But you made him wait to be operated on!
Everyone says you're supposed to be the best surgeon in this entire hospital!
Why? Why? Why?
I remember now.
I was about to start surgery on a Turkish man injured in a construction accident.
Dr. Tenma!
Yes, sir?
You shouldn't be here right now, Doctor. Get over to OR-1 immediately.
These are the Director's orders, Doctor, so please hurry.
Why? If you had operated on him, he would have survived!
What? What?
Bring him back to me!
Bring him back!
And then my friend and I started fighting over that dress.
It was the only one they had in that size.
Can you believe that?
But don't worry about it.
Of course, it was mine in the end.
Hey, are you listening?
Huh?
Yeah.
Is there something wrong?
You seem distracted.
I checked the records and the surgeon who operated on the Turkish man was dr.
Becker why are you still talking about that if you look back over the charts
they clearly show what happened Becker took too long to treat that man
I don't know but I think if I had performed the surgery on him I might
have been able to save his life do we have to talk about this at dinner but
what does she want from me anyway I was just following orders from the director
when I perform surgery on that opera singer.
I'm not responsible.
Well, am I?
- Well, of course not.
After all, people's lives aren't created equal.
Bring him back! Give me back my husband! Bring him back!
Is that the house?
Yes. One of the neighbors called in.
How many shots were fired?
Five or six, sir.
Who lives in this house?
well it seems it seems to be the residents of the Liebert family who
recently fled here from East Germany this is gonna turn into a big mess
we'll charge in there at the count of three one two three
This is bad.
What happened here?
Someone's there!
There appears to be one survivor. A girl. A man and a woman are dead.
A boy is in critical condition. I repeat, one boy is in critical condition.
An emergency.
A bullet to the head. Is that boy the only patient?
Yes. His parents were DOA. It seems to have been a robbery.
All right, then. I'm about five minutes out.
I should be there shortly.
Oh, Father.
Evening, Dr. Heinemann.
I'm terribly sorry for keeping your precious daughter out so late.
What are you talking about, Tenma?
It's all right. Ava is your fiancée, isn't she?
Now, what are we all doing standing here?
Come in, have some tea.
so tell me something have you notified your parents in japan about your wedding date yet
uh yes sir but my father runs a small hospital back home so i'm not sure if he'll be able to
take the time and come all the way out here to germany well wouldn't it be a good opportunity
for him to take some time off and enjoy a leisure trip overseas yes they should come we're taking
care of the expenses anyway thank you very much sir i'm completely indebted to you for everything
you've done for me did i ever tell you that when you first arrived here in germany i thought you
were a high school student and now you're the best young doctor at eisler memorial hospital
by the way kenzo i want to talk to you about your current research on cerebrovascular spasms
and subarachnoid hemorrhages oh good i've been creating a model of a subarachnoid hemorrhage
in a dog i'm sorry but i'm going to have to cancel the project but sir i have been asked
to speak at the next european medical convention and of course that means preparing a sharp
presentation that's why i want to have you compile my manuscript well sir my research is very close
to being completed i'm almost finished by the way ava did i tell you what happened earlier today
no father you didn't what happened a suspicious group of civilians forced their way into the
hospital they were protesting the operation we performed on the opera singer they claimed we
pushed back the case of a Turkish man who'd arrived at the ER first they got
the whole thing wrong that's not how it happened that Turkish man was operated
on first there was not a thing wrong with our procedures right Tenma yes
apparently they think we're some kind of charity or something our priority is to
to progress as medical scholars before we save lives.
Don't you agree?
In any case, I do want you to work on my manuscript.
I have great expectations of you, Dr. Tenma.
- I appreciate that, sir.
Where's the patient?
They just brought him in.
How's he holding up?
Blood pressure 72 over 50.
his pulse is at 137 the bullet entered through his forehead we need x-rays
immediately yes doctor Oh dr. tenma
who's this she's the twin sister of the little boy we just brought in any
injuries no but she seems to have sustained a serious psychological shock
Yes, what is it?
Dr.. Tenma
The boys x-rays and CT scans are ready. I understand. I'll be there shortly
It entered the front of the head and stopped deep in the center of the brain
Yes
This one is definitely going to be difficult, huh? The bullet is touching the left side of the middle cerebral artery here
Will you look at that?
Dr. Tenma is absolutely right. This one won't be easy
If you jostle the bullet even the slightest bit then the artery could rupture and cause a massive hemorrhage
Hey, I'm late
Dr. Becker you're supposed to be on duty. I don't understand how you could be so late
We'll do a full frontal craniotomy and remove the bone fragments and contaminated brain matter.
Then we'll remove the bullet very carefully, and lastly repair the arterial wall.
But with a little hard work and some luck, I'm certain that we can pull it off.
Blood pressure 120/80, pulse 92. He's looking good.
The anesthesia's taking effect.
oh there you are doctor yes you shouldn't be here you're needed in operating room one
immediately it's critically urgent mayor roediger has suffered a cerebral blood clot
he's being transported here by helicopter they're scheduled to arrive in 10 minutes
then i think the best thing is to contact dr boyer there's a chance his carotid artery is blocked
If that's the case, we want you to operate on him.
But, sir, I can't do that. I was just about to begin surgery on that young boy.
Here.
It's an order from the director.
Hello, this is Tenma.
Hello, Tenma. Take care of the mayor, will you?
I've contacted Dr. Eisen and Dr. Boyer.
It'll be good to have that extra support in case you need it, but dr. Heinemann. I was about to start another operation right now
I forget it. Just let dr. Becker take over that one
With all due respect sir
The patient I am about to operate on has a bullet up against his left middle cerebral artery
And it could turn into a very complex surgery, but I am confident I can save him director
So I'm going to let dr. Boyer take care of the mayor
I'm the only one who can perform this surgery on that boy
Tenma I'm expecting you to do everything in your power to save the mayor
You need to understand something very important in the next review of medical facilities
The mayor has promised our hospital a very generous increase in funds. We can't have him die just yet
Do you understand I'm expecting you will do this. I'm counting on you. Dr. Tenma
Yes, sir
The mayor has just arrived on the heliport doctor
After the CT scans are done do the angiogram. We need to confirm where the arteries blocked
About time to get ready dr. Tenma. Yeah, we're all counting on those brilliant skills of yours
Apparently, they think we're some kind of charity or something.
Our priority is to progress as medical scholars before we save lives.
Tenma, don't you agree?
But what does she want from me anyway?
I was just following orders from the director when I performed surgery on that opera singer.
I'm not responsible.
Well, am I?
After all, people's lives aren't created equal.
bring him back if you had operated on him you would have survived
why bring him back to me bring him back bring him back
hmm well is something the matter dr tenma
I have...
I have a surgery to perform in the other room.
Hey, where are you going, Dr. Tenma?
But this is an order from the director.
The mayor is having a CT scan done on him now.
Doctors, please report to the reading room.
On my way.
Dr. Tenma!
Hang in there, kid.
I'll save you, no matter what.
G-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g
© transcript Emily Beynon
© BF-WATCH TV 2021