Blood pressure 120 over 80 pulse 92. I will begin extracting the bullet.
bullet is extracted removal process is completed it's a little early to be
relieved we must still reinforce the walls of the damaged blood vessels Oh
right eight zero proline yes sir
We'll be right back.
♪♪
His current blood pressure is 128 over 72, and his pulse is 88.
It looks like he's still under the effects of the anesthesia.
Live on, kid.
Survive and have a good life.
Oh, Dr. Boyer, how did everything go?
It looks like the procedure went smoothly on your side.
Yes, the surgery went well at least.
The mayor wasn't so lucky.
Really, is that so?
That's very unfortunate news.
You act as though his dying has nothing to do with you.
The truth is, doctor, that you're the one who abandoned our team.
Just before surgery, too.
No, but wait, that child was brought in before the mayor.
What does it matter? Who the hell cares who came in first?
The problem is, you selfishly left us a man short.
We had to scramble to cover for you at the last minute, and somebody died.
Now, wait a minute. Just listen to me. I was...
You upset the teamwork, Dr. Tenma.
You are aware that I followed the director's orders,
and I clearly instructed you to perform that surgery on the mayor, did I not?
However, you chose to ignore that order.
But, doctor, you have to understand, at that time, I...
The process of a surgery depends on the trust among the entire staff.
It's a team effort, and yet you decided to act on your own.
I've already given my report to the director.
He deeply regrets this incident.
This will greatly affect our hospital's reputation.
You have only yourself to blame.
Sir, wait! Please, wait!
Dr. Tenma, things are looking very good.
At the moment, the boy's blood pressure is 114 over 82, pulse 84.
Overall, sir, the boy's vitals are very stable.
I see. Well, that's good to hear.
Um, I just want to say, sir, the operation was amazing.
After collapsing on a holiday retreat,
Mayor Roediger passed away at the hospital where he was being treated.
As soon as his sudden death was made public,
people began flocking to City Hall with flowers,
many reminiscing on the life of the mayor.
A press conference has been held at Eisler Memorial Hospital
where the mayor was taken.
Mayor Roediger's cause of death was a cerebral infarction
caused by severe infarcts of the inner carotid artery.
We certainly did everything we could for him,
but the condition caused intense swelling of the brain and it resulted in the mayor's untimely
death. As for naming a successor, a city official explained that concrete steps will be taken to
ensure a new mayor is chosen. I've got to get some sleep. We now move on to the murder of Mr. and
Mrs. Liebert, which took place late last night. Judging from clues from the crime scene, police
believe this might have either been a robbery or a politically motivated terrorist act against the
couple who had recently fled here from the east a full investigation is currently underway
tragically one of the couple's twin children a young boy suffered a gunshot wound to the head
although the surgery was successful the boy has not yet regained consciousness and is still in
critical condition now the weather the whole country is in for a clear it's a shame i wonder
what'll end up happening to the boy in a way i'm just like him now
Mrs. Reinhardt in ICU is complaining that she's having a hard time sleeping.
That said, do you think we can give her something to help her sleep?
Dr. Tenma, are you listening to me?
Oh, I'm sorry. Yes, in that case, give her one Halcyon tablet, please.
That should help her get some sleep.
What is with him today? He's been spacing out all day long.
Hey.
Dr. Becker, it's you.
Looks like you're going through a bit of a tough time there.
Come on, fess up. Have you heard anything from the director yet?
Hmm?
I did try to warn you, didn't I?
I told you the hospital is ruled by politics.
I knew what I was talking about.
And if you had played your cards right, I'm sure your future would have been smooth sailing.
Oh, well, I guess what this means is you and I are on the same boat now, my young friend.
Oh, come on, Tenma, don't be so depressed.
I know you'll get a chance to redeem yourself sooner or later.
What do you say we go get some drinks? That'll put a smile on your face.
hold on a second nurse excuse me i still need to get a statement from the girl would i be able to
go in and question her now i'm sorry detective this is not a good time huh that girl has
disappeared from her room what did you say
seems like she's always slipping out of her room and wandering all over the hospital
Kill.
And so, the reason that Eisler Memorial Hospital has proven to be the nation's leading medical facility is, first and foremost,
because we're blessed to have excellent personnel such as yourselves.
And I'd like to take this opportunity to thank every single one of you for that.
Unfortunately, as you all know, just yesterday, the mayor passed away in our hospital.
Of course, as always, we did our utmost to save his life.
And because of that, this hospital's reputation remains intact.
In appreciation, let's have a round of applause for Dr. Boyer and Dr. Eisen,
who strive to the very end to try and save the mayor's life.
Thank you.
I looked over your thesis, young man.
You did an excellent job.
Please keep up the good work, all right?
Excuse me.
hmm I I'm so sorry I apologize for what happened sir now now don't worry my boy
what's done is done director you did what you thought was best you followed
your heart why don't we just leave it at that
thank you sir ladies and gentlemen may I have your attention please now a word
from the head of neurosurgery please excuse me it looks like I'm being called
up there no you're not tenma allow me to introduce the newly appointed dr boyer please make your way
to the microphone but sir what does this mean if you wish to remain at this hospital you may do so
but you'd better give up any dreams of furthering your status it's not possible for irresponsible
people such as yourself i recognize your skill as a surgeon but that is it and you
can forget about presenting any research papers at future conferences but sir
please listen to me you decide to transfer to another hospital I have no
intention of recommending you in other words it's useless for you to harbor any
ambitions you have successfully tied the noose around your own neck tenma
Successful surgery requires teamwork.
It's only with everyone's help and cooperation that we can hope to save lives.
Ava.
Ava, please, you have to talk to your father for me.
Make him see I haven't done anything wrong. All I did was operate on an emergency patient who was brought in first nothing else
Wait is that the engagement ring I gave you spare me Kenzo. You're such a fool
Ava, why?
Dr. Norton, you're looking very handsome this evening.
Oh, thank you.
You're looking especially beautiful tonight yourself, Ava.
It's quite ironic, really.
I came to Germany after I discovered one of Director Heinemann's papers,
and as soon as I get here, he takes me under his wing.
So now it all makes sense.
That paper I was so impressed with,
it was probably written by someone else.
Someone he was grooming, just like he'd been doing with me this whole time.
I knew that he was really just using me.
But I was hoping that when I'd reached a certain status,
I'd be able to make my own choices with what I wanted to work on.
Our priority is to progress as medical scholars before we save lives.
Don't you agree?
That's not true! A doctor's priority is to save whoever he can!
After all, people's lives are not created equal.
Everyone's lives are equal! I don't care what they say!
I am not wrong. He is!
He tells me there's a flaw in my character.
Well, what about him?
He says he's a doctor, but he's just a greedy bastard!
Bastard! Bastard!
He'd be better off dead!
I have to thank you.
I have to thank you because you helped me open up my eyes as a doctor.
So survive and live a good life.
After all, I did throw away everything in order to save you.
That's how far I went to give you your life back, and I would do it again.
You know your name, don't you?
Your name is Anna Liebert, isn't that right?
I did try to warn you that all this was a bit too soon for her, Detective.
Isn't there anything we can do, Doctor?
She saw her parents get shot to death.
She's fine physically, and I think her trauma-induced amnesia is natural, given the circumstances.
Is there any chance you might be able to wait to get a statement from her after she gets better?
Not really. This is a very difficult case.
One of the victims was a former East German diplomat.
If we're not able to solve this quickly, the BKA will be all over our backs.
Those guys always come here after the fact and try and steal the show from us.
I haven't got time to take things easy.
Oh, what if we do this? Yeah, we let her see her brother,
and then she'll probably be so relieved to see him that it might help her regain her memory.
I cannot possibly agree to such a risky proposition. That's completely out of the question.
Besides, I'm sure Dr. Tenma would never permit such a thing.
Tenma?
He's in charge of Johan, her twin brother.
Yeah, sure feels like I'm getting a run around.
Hey, Dr. Tenma. You seem a little bit out of it.
You all right?
I mean, you are looking awfully tired this morning.
I've been so busy with emergency surgeries.
Wow, it seems like they've been working you to the bone.
Well, ever since you were demoted from chief.
Well, I don't mind, really.
It actually makes me feel better.
Hmm. How are you really doing, doctor?
I'm sorry.
I've just been paged. I need to go.
Are you so sure it's a good idea to keep on going like this?
Hard work won't get you anywhere.
Look at this, Dr. Heinemann.
Look at all the gifts and letters of encouragement.
Yes, there are mountains of them in his sister's room as well.
The media keeps reporting on the twins' heartbreaking saga after losing their parents
and how they're now on their own.
And this is what we get.
As far as this hospital is concerned, with no one alive to pay their medical expenses, they're nothing but an inconvenience.
Now, now. So their story is a pitiful one. That works for us.
Huh?
It only means this hospital is garnering attention.
Think about it a moment, Doctor. These kids are very valuable to us.
Am I right or aren't I?
Uh, yes, sir.
Why don't we do this? We'll give the media a photo of the siblings together.
They'll probably be thrilled to have something like that.
Yes, that's something the media's been requesting for some time now, but the thing is...
Just do it. Don't be naive.
It'll be a picture of the orphaned siblings struggling bravely to survive under the warm-hearted care of our hospital staff.
However, sir, the boy's attending physician says it is still too early to allow them to see each other.
Who's on this case?
It's Dr. Tenma.
Not anymore.
What's that?
There's no need to leave him in a position that's getting so much attention
Just take Dr. Tenma off the case
Yes, sir
This is a heartfelt gift from the citizens
Here, why don't you have one?
Thank you
You're looking well, Mrs. Hankel
How do you feel?
I'm feeling quite well, Doctor.
And I owe it all to you.
Thank you.
We'll be removing your stitches very soon,
so it won't be long until you're released.
You mean I'll be able to go home soon?
That's right.
Just make sure you follow my instructions.
All you have to do is rest.
Of course I will, Doctor.
She'll need regular doses of anticonvulsants
and antihypertensives, okay?
Ah!
Anna, wake up!
What happened to her?
Dr. Tenma, we brought her in to see her brother and then she just, she just started screaming and...
Why did you do that?
Look, Dr. Tenma
Take her back to her room
Yes, sir
Dr. Boyer, mind telling me what this is about?
And why the camera?
Oh, this?
Well, we wanted to commemorate the emotional meeting of the twins
And then release a picture to the media
Who allowed you to do such a thing?
I should have been consulted
I'm the boy's doctor, damn it
You've been dismissed as the boy's attending physician.
As of today, he's my patient, so I made my own judgment
that it would be fine for the twins to see each other.
Those children!
You can't turn them into a media circus!
We were just following the director's orders,
and I think it would be best for you not to fight him!
I saved this boy's life.
It's my duty to protect him until he fully recovers!
Well, in that case, just take a look.
as soon as he saw his sister he reached out to her and began to cry you see he's regained
consciousness and is reacting normally to stimuli which means the surgery was a great success
so good job your work is done here now get back to your post that's an order
damn it such idiotic clowns so it was the director's orders don't make me laugh what
gives a damn about what the chief says bunch of greedy morons their only motivation is their
Well, that's for power and money.
Screw them!
I'm not wrong, no matter what those bastards think of me.
Hello? Father, I'm home.
Father? Are you in your room?
Huh?
Excuse me, Dr. Boyer. Are you still in a meeting at this time of night?
Hello, Father. Are you sleeping already?
I'm coming in.
That bastard would...
That bastard would be better off dead.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
© transcript Emily Beynon