Sorry to bother you at this hour.
We're here on official police business.
Would you happen to be Dr. Tenma?
Can I help you?
Pardon my asking, but were you home all last night?
What?
No, I...
I was out drinking until dawn.
Why do you ask?
Well, sir, Eisler Memorial Hospital's Director Heinemann, Chief of Surgery Dr. Oppenheim,
and Dr. Boyer...
[GROANING]
(dramatic music)
- No one except the police are allowed
But you're interfering with the operation of this hospital.
Press is not allowed inside.
We can't have patients in this kind of chaos.
Can you tell us, please?
Was it an accident or was it murder?
Three people died at the same time.
Of course it was murder.
Are you part of the hospital staff?
Tell us. Would you happen to know anything about this incident?
Out of my way. Let me through.
Hey, no one's allowed in.
I work here. I'm Dr. Kenzo Tenma.
Come on, step back.
So, did you see anyone suspicious earlier tonight?
- I don't think this is the time to be--
- Oh, Dr. Tenma.
Dr. Tenma, the director and the others.
- Calm down, everyone.
Is the emergency room running smoothly?
- Well, actually, we're swamped
with emergency cases right now, doctor.
Two patients are waiting to be operated on.
- All right then, I'll see what I can do.
- Can you take care of the car accident victim
with the brain contusion?
- First, I'll go look over the x-rays.
How about the other case?
- The patient collapsed with a stroke.
- Ah, doctor, I'd like to ask you a couple of questions.
I understand, but this initial investigation is vital.
Do you know of anyone who could have possibly held a grudge against the Director and the others?
A grudge?
You have successfully tied the noose around your own neck, Tenma.
Doctor? Did someone come to mind?
No. Sorry.
Doctor Tenma! We have a problem!
Those kids! The twins! The boy and the girl!
They're gone, sir! We can't find them anywhere!
And is the little girl's bed empty as well, nurse?
I already checked, but they're both just gone.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
In his mercy, he lent a hand to many who were ill and suffering.
We will always remember his great accomplishments.
Farewell, Dr. Heinemann.
May you rest in peace.
Amen.
Father!
(crying)
- Ava, Ava, I know it's difficult,
but please, try to hold yourself.
- Don't touch me!
Give me my father back!
I want him back!
- This whole funeral business is just too sad, Dr. Tenma.
- Yeah.
- Up until now, she was fed with a silver spoon
as the director's daughter.
But now suddenly, she's just another ordinary person.
That's gotta be quite a big shock.
- How can you say that right now?
- Sorry about that.
- Dr. Tenma?
I am Inspector Weisbaugh
of the Nordheim-Westfalen Police Department.
- Thank you for your efforts.
- This was such a tragedy.
- Yes.
- Let me introduce you.
Dr. Tenma?
- I am Inspector Lunge.
I've heard about your amazing abilities, Doctor.
No, I... I still have a long ways to go.
Um, do you have any leads at all to the children's whereabouts?
No, but we have determined the cause of death for the Director and the other two doctors.
We have discovered traces of nitrate inside all three of their bodies.
So there were traces of nitrate? That's a muscle relaxant.
or not a doctor for nothing.
- How could something like that end up in--
- It was candy.
- Huh, candy?
- It turns out the same candy wrapper
was found beside each of the bodies.
The same substance was also found in each of their stomachs.
Tell me, would you have any idea
where they might have gotten this candy
or something else of that sort?
- I wouldn't know where they got it from.
If you don't mind me asking,
how is the search for the twins going?
"The BKA has taken over jurisdiction on this particular case from the local authorities.
Please don't worry."
"Hmm."
"As it stands, after investigating certain events, we believe all this could be tied
back to the moment the twins' parents were shot to death.
First their parents defect from East Germany and are murdered soon after that.
Then staff from the hospital where the children were treated are also murdered.
Political terrorism may be a possibility.
Those children might hold a major key to this whole mystery."
Please do your best to find them, Inspector.
We certainly will.
Excuse us.
Interesting.
A Japanese doctor demoted by the director
and then his engagement with the director's daughter
broken right before the incident.
But the man was in the bar drinking
at the time the crime was committed.
It checks out.
Um, mind if I ask you something?
move like that oh oh this i was just typing i'm inputting all the information onto the hard drive
in my head and if i access the information no i i still have a long ways to go dr tenma was
actually quite modest about it when i commented on his well-recognized talents earlier
Hmm...
The police, huh?
What, are they thinking you're a suspect?
There's enough evidence to implicate me.
Nothing I can do about it.
Ah, don't worry about it.
They were persistent when they questioned me, too.
God, I'm so exhausted.
Once this whole thing gets settled,
I think I'm gonna go back to Japan.
Huh?
I came to Germany to do research,
but with everything that's happened,
The most important thing for a doctor is to save lives.
Come on, don't get all depressed on me now.
I'm just tired. So, so tired.
Mr. Buchner, you're making great progress.
Thank you so very much, Dr. Tenma. I'm glad to hear it.
Do you think I'll be able to work like I used to?
Yes, of course.
Good. Because if I'm not there, I'll have no choice but to close shop.
However, you mustn't overdo it.
I'll stop by your restaurant for a drink after you're released.
And that's just to make sure that you're not overworking.
Say, Dr. Tenma.
Yes?
I heard that you were leaving this hospital.
Is it true, Doctor?
Don't quit. Please don't quit.
Good doctors like you are so hard to find.
Please stay. Please don't say you're quitting.
Please.
Mr. Buchner...
Dr. Tenma, the chairman is asking for you.
Right now he's in a meeting with the board discussing how to fill the open positions.
Until now, most of these posts were held by Dr. Heinemann's followers.
It seems like there are going to be major changes.
For example, the rumor is Dr. Eckner is being transferred to a small hospital in Bavaria.
Dr. Tenma, hold on.
No matter what the chairman says, please don't give up.
I want you to know we're all behind you.
So please, don't leave the hospital.
Let me say this again.
I'm performance-oriented, and that's the reason
I'm making you chief of surgery.
What a life.
I went against the director's orders and lost my position as chief, and my engagement to
Ava is broken, and then as soon as I decide to work as a regular doctor without hope of
ever being promoted...
Oh, God, what a life this is.
I'm sorry for calling you out of the blue, but I'd heard you'd been appointed Chief
of Surgery.
I'm truly happy for you.
- Thank you, Ava.
- Kenzo, that day at my father's funeral,
I remember you were trying to comfort me, weren't you?
- Uh, well...
- It made me happy.
A lot of things happened between us,
but I'd like to start over.
- [gasps]
Kenzo?
Kenzo!
Listen, please!
Forgive me!
I was wrong!
Let's start over!
Kenzo?
Kenzo!
A patient is hospitalized for a spinal cord tumor.
His paralysis has accelerated.
I understand. I'll do the operation myself.
Excellent, Doctor. I'm glad to hear that.
Make the arrangements for the procedure.
Right!
I've had it with this damn flood.
I thought the world would change when the Berlin Wall came down six years ago.
And it did. For the worse.
It's true.
They talk about a unified Europe, but we just keep getting dumped with the bad.
Yeah. The rate of unsolved crimes is definitely on the rise.
Inspector! We have arrived, sir!
Both victims had their throats slit. It isn't pretty.
Their identities?
Mr. and Mrs. Reichman from Stitch Drive. They were murdered in their home.
We believe they were hidden away in a closet, but were washed out into the open because of the rising floodwaters.
Another middle-aged couple murdered for greed.
In the past two years, there have been four other similar cases across the country.
All murdered the same way. Probably the same thief.
No. It's too premature to call these simple robberies.
Judging from the data, for some reason none of these couples seem to have had any children.
Well, this couple didn't seem to have any children either.
Don't you think there are too many factors in common here
to make the assumption this is just a simple robbery?
Well, sir, I'm just going by the fact that money and goods were taken from all the victims' homes.
It was, all of it totaling a small amount.
Although this would make sense if it were the work of a single perpetrator.
Hold on. You're suggesting there's more than one?
Two of the homes in question had extremely strong locks and sophisticated alarm systems.
But the perpetrator bypassed them and was able to enter without any trouble.
Also, none of the couple showed any signs of struggle before they were killed,
and the neighbors did not hear a single sound at the time the incident took place.
Don't you think these were orchestrated all too well for just one suspect?
Yeah, maybe.
Do you know this man?
No.
Adolf Junkers, 32 years old.
He's been arrested twice for larceny.
In a robbery, he's the one who gets you through the front door.
In other words, a lockpick.
It turns out, he was spotted near the area in three of those four double murder cases.
Then he's gotta be the man, right?
Or not. It's too early.
Well, in any case, detective, your job here is done.
The BKA will take it from here.
Uh, sure.
Well, it didn't fly after all. Sorry about that. I've never flown a kite before in my life. It was good
You almost did it. Well doctor do tell how was your date last night? Oh
She seemed like a nice girl. Come on, dr. Tenma. Don't be coy. She's the daughter of a director
Don't tell me you just had dinner and saw her home
Well, actually there was an emergency call during dinner. So I had to come back to the hospital. Hold on you did what?
Ah, you'd better rethink that all work and no play doctrine.
You're gonna lose a great catch and regret it someday, do you hear me?
Hey, are you listening to a word I'm saying?
Oh, a kite, eh?
Good morning, Doctor. How are you?
Is this yours, Carl?
My grandpa gave it to me.
But it won't fly. I think it's broken.
Maybe the alignment needs to be adjusted.
Well, Doctor, do you know how to fly a kite?
When I was a kid back in Japan, I used to do this a lot.
Hold it up in the air now. All right, you ready?
How like this that a boy?
Now here we go
It's flying
All right.
Oh, man.
If I were as smooth as that,
I'd have at least five lovers.
Hell, maybe even ten. Seriously.
That's so awesome, Dr. Tenma.
Get better soon, Carl,
so that next time you can fly it yourself, okay?
Yeah.
Today's surgery is a paracellar meningioma.
extirpation we'll proceed with a right tyrion approach yes everyone watch
closely the chief of surgery himself is heading up this one brilliant operation
just look at that he's hardly retracted the brain at all he is truly a surgical
genius new residents should learn to treat the brain with such care
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
This is terrible! An ambulance! Someone call an ambulance!
I didn't do it! This wasn't my fault!
This guy ran into the street all of a sudden out of nowhere!
Is this the patient?
Yes.
How is he?
Well, we... we tried. But there isn't much we can do.
This man is a material witness in a case.
It's important that we get his testimony since it may help us solve a string of serial murders doctor
We can't have him die on us
But inspector this patient is in very critical condition
Really? There's nothing else we can do for him here
However, there's a top-notch neurosurgeon at Eisler Memorial Hospital if he comes here. He might be able to do something
neurosurgeon
That would be dr. Tenma
Thanks for coming all the way out here, Dr. Tenma.
What's his condition right now?
He is conscious, but a bit delirious.
Also, one of his pupils is dilated.
It's been a while, hasn't it, Dr. Tenma?
Uh, sorry, but do I know you from somewhere, sir?
It was nine years ago. The director's funeral, remember?
Oh, yes, you were from the BKA.
Inspector Lungay, please do be sure to perform a successful operation for the sake of the BKA.
The thing is, Doctor, this patient has to survive. He holds the key to solving a very important case.
Well, Inspector, I don't operate for the sake of the police. I do it for the sake of the patient.
Fair enough, Doctor.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have an operation.
I hear you've become the Chief of Surgery. Well now, Doctor.
You've certainly become very successful.
Yes, and what about it?
Nothing. At your age, it's quite an accomplishment.
Aren't you next in line to become the director?
No. I still have a long way to go.
Those murders years ago at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
Due to a lack of evidence, that investigation has seen very little progress.
The only clue we found was the poisoned candy.
This suggests it was a calculated act on the part of the killer.
In that kind of crime, the killer always has something to gain from the victim's death.
What are you getting at, Inspector?
Nothing. Forgive me.
In my line of work, the mind doesn't stop. I'm always thinking like this.
In any case, rest assured, of all the cases I've ever handled throughout my career, not one has gone unsolved.
No, not a single one.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
We'll perform a craniotomy to remove the hematoma.
If we don't hurry, the brain hernia will worsen.
After the Eisler Memorial Hospital murders, no matter which way I looked at it, one person
had everything to gain from the incident.
And that is you, Dr. Tenma.
Thank you again for going to all this trouble, driving all this way.
No, don't worry. How is the patient responding?
Well, he is still conscious, but his right pupil does remain dilated.
He's also got paralysis on the left side.
But he has already started rehab, hasn't he?
The paralysis should go away. He's on the right track listen
I think the police want to interrogate him as soon as possible, but that's out of the question
But doctor that detective Lungay is a very persistent man right now the patient's recovery is all I'm worried about
How are you feeling Mr.. Yonkers everything okay?
So, tell me, Mr. Junkers, are you able to recognize me?
Do you see this finger I'm holding up?
How about it?
Can you talk to me today?
What's that?
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
- The monster is coming.
- Coming?
Mr. Junkers, what's coming?
- The monster is coming.
The monster is coming.
- The monster?
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)