How are you feeling, Mr. Junkers? Everything okay?
So, tell me, Mr. Junkers, are you able to recognize me?
Do you see this finger I'm holding up?
How about it? Can you talk to me today?
What's that?
I'm sorry. What did you say?
The monster is coming.
Coming? Mr. Junkers, what's coming?
The monster?
♪
♪ He is risen ♪
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]
Junkers. I know you're able to speak. You have been identified at the scene of the
crime of four murderers involving middle-aged couples in the past two
years. There's no point denying it. What do you say? Well, speak up, Mr. Junkers.
Hmm. All right, okay. I guess we'd better tell you that we already know that you
is strictly undoing locks.
You couldn't have possibly slit their throats in one single slash with such cold-blooded
grace-yunkers.
No, that wasn't your work.
No, that means there had to be other accomplices involved.
And I'm thinking there would have had to have been at least three of you in order to do
both, open a strong lock, and murder a middle-aged couple without resistance.
That sound about right?
We're almost through compiling a list of suspects
who we already know are skillful with knives.
It's only a matter of time before we're able
to narrow it down to one name,
whether you decide to cooperate with us or not.
However, I must confess that's not really
what I wanted to ask you about.
What I would really like to know, Mr. Junkers,
is why four couples from across Germany
and every one of the couples middle-aged
and without children,
but we know the amounts were too small to justify murdering for a mere third of it.
All right. So tell me, are you up for some negotiation?
If you confess now, we'll dismiss all charges against you.
So tell me, who was the person who hired you to do this?
Mr. Junkers, it's alright! It's alright! That's it! This interrogation is over right now!
I don't think so. We're almost there.
Get out of here! As a doctor, I'm ordering you!
Very well, but I'll be coming back at a later time.
And just to make sure he isn't poisoned or that he doesn't disappear, I will assign a guard to watch him closely.
That shouldn't strike you as odd.
There always seems to be so much trouble happening all around you, Dr. Tenma.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Oh, nothing really.
Well then, we'll keep in touch.
Hey, hold on! Where are you going?
Just going out for a walk.
He's not supposed to leave the room without permission.
Patients need to get fresh air every so often.
We're just going out into the garden.
You're welcome to come with us if you like, officer.
It's nice and warm out here today.
You are able to talk, aren't you?
It's afternoons like this one that make you happy to be alive, you know?
If it weren't for times like today, I don't think I'd be able to go on.
Especially when you're here constantly seeing people having to fight for their lives.
That's why it's easier for some doctors to think about their money, their research, or getting promoted.
I used to be one of those guys myself.
I wanted to get promoted and do my own research.
I was positive that being successful in surgery was the way to the top.
But after performing a surgery on a certain little boy, everything changed for me.
He was the older of twin siblings.
He'd been shot in the head.
Saving his life reminded me why I had become a doctor in the first place.
It reminded me that all human lives should be regarded as equal and that a doctor's job is to save those lives.
Thank you.
People start over all the time. It's never too late, believe me.
Doctor, you know something?
You and I are very close in age, but you're almost like a father to me.
Doctor, you saved my life and you've protected me.
That's why it almost feels like you're my father.
Well, it looks like I landed myself one big kid, huh?
Doctor, this one time when I was a little boy, I wanted this clock.
You know, I'm sure you've seen those before.
the kind that have a little Nutcracker figurine popping out of it every hour.
I would stare at it for a long time,
pressing my face against that display window at the store every afternoon.
So I guess it's no surprise, Doctor, that was the first lock I ever picked in my life.
But I was caught in the act, and I never got that clock.
However, ever since that day, picking locks sort of became my job.
and it all started just because I wanted that stupid clock.
All I wanted was that stupid clock.
I just...
- You should just tell them everything.
Tell the police everything you know
and just make a fresh start of it.
- They're dead.
Oh, my friends, they were all killed.
Who did it?
Is it this monster, the one that you mentioned before?
Do me a favor, don't screw it up this time.
I went out of my way to set this one up for you.
You know, she's the daughter of a state legislator.
She is beautiful and intelligent all in one package in other words perfection
Well, we'll see about that
But you know what all kidding aside you're right. It is time for me to find someone
Of course i'm right. The thing is that someone in your position without a wife just seems like uh, hey
I'm sure you've seen those before, the kind that have a little nutcracker figurine popping
out of it every hour.
This is it.
Excuse me.
About the clock in the window.
Hey, what's going on?
You're already late for your date.
What are you doing?
[music]
People start over all the time.
It's never too late, believe me.
Officer?
Excuse me, officer, are you out there?
Hello?
I'm ready to confess, but I'd prefer if Dr. Tenma were present.
Where'd he could have gone?
Hey, officer, I wanted to...
Listen, I know it's late, but can I go see one of my patients?
Yes, but of course, Dr. Tenma. What is it you have there?
I found something special.
Hey, what's the matter? Are you alright?
He's dead.
Candy?
Mr. Junkers!
It's the same as last time.
I'm Candy. My patient's disappearing, just like nine years ago.
Mr. Junkers!
It's me, Dr. Tenma.
Doctor!
Stay away, Doctor!
Let's go back to the hospital, Mr. Junkers.
Everything will be alright.
Don't, Doctor!
Don't come any closer!
I'm begging you, please, don't look at him!
At who?
He's the one who killed my friends, and he'll kill you, too!
Who are you?
Oh, God, just run!
Run away!
Please!
It's me.
It's been a long time, Doctor. It's me.
Nine years ago, you saved my life.
Nine years ago?
Have you forgotten already, Doctor? About the twins?
Yohan...
That's right. That twin. You remember.
Run! Don't look at his face! He'll kill you!
What do you think you're doing here? Mr. Junkers is my patient! Let him go!
What am I doing?
(gun cocks)
- An execution.
(Run screams)
- Don't do it!
- Dr. Run, he killed my friends!
Run while you can, just get out of here!
We were hired by him.
He'd call us each time.
A large amount would be wired to our accounts
after each job.
That way it seemed as if we had taken the money
and split it.
He had it all figured out!
- It can't be.
So the murder of those four middle-aged couples
was ordered by, it was you.
The police started suspecting me and following me, so he... he wanted to get rid of us!
Listen to me! The other two, Fritz the Slayer and Big Boy Boris, have already been killed!
Fritz said to me just before he died that we had...
Oh my God, that we had been hired by a monster!
He doesn't even blink at killing someone. It means nothing to him.
Run, Doctor! He'll kill you where you stand, just run!
You talk too much, Junkers.
Johann! Don't do this!
Mr. Junkers doesn't know your identity, but I do!
I was your attending physician!
You are Johann Liebert, the elder of fraternal twins.
You are the son of Michael Liebert, former advisor of commerce,
who fled East Germany in 1986 as a political refugee to the West.
If we know this much about you, you can't possibly escape.
Don't add to your crimes, Johan.
Johan, huh?
Yes, there was a time when I went by that name.
But you know something, Doctor?
Johan isn't my real name.
Wh-what are you talking about?
You must never know about my past.
Not about those four couples.
Nor the Lieberts.
But you're different, Doctor.
You cared for me and you restored me to life.
So I feel as though you're like a father to me.
Like a... a father?
The truth is, if it weren't for you, I wouldn't be standing here right now.
Stop it! You can't just go around killing!
Why not?
Why not? Because...
A human life is precious, don't you see that?
Rescuing you opened my eyes. I was able to go back to being the doctor I should have always been!
Saving your life made me realize that the weight of each life is equal! No one's better than anyone else!
That's why no one has the right to take another person's life!
As a doctor, I lived by those beliefs for the last nine years because of you!
What are you laughing at?!
Doctor, I heard you were promoted to Chief of Surgery soon after that incident.
Huh?
I'm really happy, Doctor, that you were promoted to that position.
What are you trying to tell me?
You are where you are today because the Director and the others died, right?
I'm so glad I was able to help. That was a good thing.
Did you? Oh my god!
Isn't that what you wanted, Doctor? That's what you said anyway. Right after I regained consciousness, that's what you told me.
That you hated them so much, you wished they were dead.
I am not wrong, he is!
Bastard! Bastard!
He'd be better off dead!
All that I did was grant you your wish, Doctor.
Oh, God! I'm afraid! Oh, God!
Save me, Doctor! I don't wanna die!
I don't want to die!
I can't!
I was supposed to die that night you're the one who resurrected me
Hey, Doctor.
What a miserable downpour.
I despise the wet weather.
All it does is wash away the crime scene evidence when you need it the most.
Well wouldn't you agree, Dr. Tenma?
All right. To summarize what you've told me so far, just to make sure that we piece it
all together. Back in 1986, Liebert, a high government official, escaped from East Germany
with his wife and two children. Right after they arrived, the Liebert family was attacked,
the couple was killed, and the twin brothers suffered a critical gunshot wound to the head.
in charge of his operation,
and subsequently save the boy's life.
But to everyone's surprise, as fate would have it,
the boy kills the director, the chief of surgery,
and the head of neurosurgery with poison candy,
and then disappears.
And last night, after nine long years,
out of the clear blue, the Liebert boy reappears
and kills a state police officer
with poison candy yet again.
And right in front of your eyes,
he shoots Adolf Junkers, your patient.
He is none other than the very man that hired Junkers
and two others to murder the four middle-aged couples
across Germany.
And his name is Johann Liebert.
I believe that's the entire story, isn't it?
(clears throat)
- Yes, sir.
- I think we're finished with the doctor.
He can go.
I don't think that someone with Dr. Tenma's credentials, or in his position, could be responsible for such a crime.
He has an alibi for the time the policeman was killed, and we didn't find any gunpowder residue on his hands.
So much for key evidence. There go all of our leads to solving those murders of the four middle-aged couples.
Inspector Lunge, should we get started on this Johann Liebert for the time being?
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC]