Now, class, I want you to tell me what was the basis for the ruling the judge made in
regards to the 1968 Stuttgart case.
Oh, boy, what is this silence?
Are we some kind of a monastery?
Mr. Imer, I'd like to hear your answer if you have one.
Uh, well, sir, that is to say, I, uh...
Anyone. Is there anyone in this room who can break this silence?
So the chronic latecomer is here at last.
13 minutes tardy.
Seems your part-time pizza delivery job
kept you awfully busy today.
- I'm sorry, Professor Kronecker.
- Well, let me ask you a question before you sit down.
Do you have enough strength left to tell me the basis
for the ruling in the 1968 Stuttgart case?
- Um, oh yes.
Well, the defense claimed that the kidnapping was a sham,
death had been due to poisoning. After an investigation into the crime scene, it was
found that the victim's death had been accidental, and that there was no motive. So, since the
crime couldn't be proven to be an intentional murder, I believe a sentence of 15 years was
handed down." "Hmm. Very good. You can take your seat,
Nina Fortuna.
Yes, Professor.
(dramatic music)
Wow, good job, Nina.
If no one had been able to give him the answer, I have no doubt that Kronika would have probably
I'll have to treat our savior, Nina, to something to eat.
What do you say, Nina? A nice meal, just the two of us?
Oh, I'm sorry, Peter, but I have a club meeting today.
Well, bye.
Aw.
She turned you down again.
Hey, Peter, how many times was that?
Come on, shut up.
As if one of you losers could actually score a date with her.
(Grunting)
(grunting)
- Thank you.
- Oh my gosh, if I'm late with my deliveries,
the manager's gonna be furious.
(laughing)
- Hey!
- Hi!
Hi, I'm home.
Boy, am I hungry.
Oh, my, the neighbors can probably hear you.
You are such a child.
Go and wash your hands, dear.
Yes, ma'am.
Huh?
Hey, Mom, you dyed your hair.
What do you think?
At your age?
I don't think you should be dyeing your hair
such a bright color.
I don't agree with you, Dad.
I think Mom looks great.
Looks like she's going to some costume parade.
It's nice to know Mom is still young.
Right, hi dad. Oh
And that reminds me speaking of costumes I saw some kids dressed up from head to toe today
Oh, yes. Today's supposed to be the st. Hadrian costume parade
Oh, I wish I had dressed up like that when I was a little girl. They were so adorable
Huh, yeah, you did dress up in a costume once isn't that right dear? That's right. I'd completely forgotten
it's around here oh look here it is you were so cute
guess I did you were so excited and made such a fuss isn't that right dear huh
Yeah, I remember
Costume parade
Distant spring I forlornly wait for a spring that will never come
Will you get over your break-up already?
I shall send you the most beautiful flowers.
I was born to smother you with flowers.
That's so beautiful.
Wow! I wonder who sent this.
I'm very impressed with you, Peter.
So, how have you been, Nina?
Well, I've been very well lately, Dr. Geidel.
That's good to hear.
But of course, I could tell just by the look on your face
when you came into this session that you were doing well.
So, tell me, are you still having that nightmare?
The one about the monster emerging from the darkness?
No. I've been sleeping very well.
I've been so busy, I don't have time to dream.
I wonder why I was plagued by such a dream night after night.
It's common for students to feel fear and anxiety.
Expectations of the future mix up with other insecurities.
People end up confused, losing sight of who they are.
But who you are is something you can spend your whole life trying to grasp
and never figure out completely.
We're always projecting and trying to look into the future.
We spend our whole lives looking for the answers and we do the best we can.
Right, and that's what I'm doing.
I want to become a federal prosecutor.
That's very good.
All right, I think that brings us to the end of our session.
Bye, and thank you, Doctor.
Mm-hmm.
Nina Fortner. Such a cheerful girl.
But I can't help thinking that she's overcompensating
or running from something.
Something overwhelmingly dark.
Huh?
What do you mean, "what"?
innocent what in the world are you going on about i was born to smother you with flowers
i would never have guessed in a million years you had such talent for writing poetry i don't know
what you're talking about i wouldn't be able to come up with frilly stuff like that even if i
stood on my head then who was it i only give my email address to friends and no one else beats
Damn it. What this means is some suave poetry guy is honing in on my girl.
Who then? Who could it be?
This was a bizarre murder that took place in Munich.
After shooting the parents to death, the perpetrator strangled their two children with a rope.
Grizzly, really?
Now, I would like you to explain the verdict.
using the records from all of the hearings.
Nina Fortner.
What, do you not understand the question?
- Um, no.
Well, the trial was focused mainly
on the cold-blooded murder of an entire family.
The evidence.
- Oh, so not even Nina has all the answers,
Nina? What's wrong Nina? Nina?
Are you alright? You want to go see the nurse?
I... I'm alright. I just felt a little ill, that's all. I was just listening to the professor
and I...
about that murdered family?
Don't say that!
Is that it?
I thought you were awfully brave,
but I guess you're pretty sensitive too.
Did you watch a horror movie
that totally scared you when you were a kid or something?
I know exactly what that counselor,
Dr. Geidel, would say.
If you get back to the root of it,
I think that you'll find it was nothing significant.
Now go back to your childhood.
Am I right?
That's it.
Hmm, I have no memories, huh? I remember nothing before the age of 10
"Memories"
Where are my memories?
My childhood memories...
Yes, those two were indeed a very nice couple.
To think that they died in such a way.
Huh?
Children.
Oh.
Now that you mention it, yes, there was a son.
His name was Michael, I do believe.
He was there for a year or two.
Let's see, a boy.
Do you remember if there was a boy?
wasn't his name Michael he was 14 give or take Michael you say yeah I think I
remember him but why who are you the police yes Michael Reitman I remember
him vaguely but he was a student in my classroom but he he didn't leave much of
an impression I'm embarrassed to say it but honestly I don't remember him very
well. I'm not sure if he had any friends. You see, there are no records left from then.
Everything went up in a fire about six years ago now.
There definitely was a boy named Michael living here in Koln until six years ago. And Michael's
His real name is...
Johan, huh?
Yes, there was a time when I went by that name.
Who are you?
What does it matter? What's the use?
He's a serial killer. The elder of twin siblings.
That's all there is to it. Nothing else.
What am I doing?
Twins? His sister? Where did his twin sister go?
I will pick you up very soon. Who is this?
He'll be picking me up very soon? But what does that mean?
A child. Oh, yes. There was a boy about seven or eight years ago.
So, Mr. and Mrs. Haina had taken a boy in before they were killed.
And what was he like?
What was he like?
That was quite a long time ago.
And I think he only really lived with them for about a year or so.
I honestly don't remember anything about him.
Wait, do you remember if this boy had a sister?
No, only the boy.
Listen, I just want to forget about what happened to that poor couple.
After all those horrible things happened, I almost moved away.
I remember that boy very well.
Why don't you come up?
I was about to have some tea.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Uh, yes.
Thank you.
Um, I was wondering...
Just have a seat.
Go ahead, have some tea.
Thank you, sir
You're a doctor right that boy was the one who told me you are dr. Tenma
He's coming to pick you up who is he I have no idea who he is it was just an anonymous email oh
Aw, you look so happy.
You're not thinking this is Prince Charming on a white charger
or a knight in shining armor coming for you, are you?
Why are you jealous?
There you go, Nina, daydreaming again.
It said I was born to smother you with flowers.
Come on, that's so corny.
How many boys do you know who write like that?
Oh, hold on, wait.
There is a new guy in our class.
You know who I'm talking about?
Oh, I've seen him.
in that legendary seat in room 12 where you're bound to be called by the
instructor but strangely enough he's never called on that's right and you
want to know what else he is always staring at Nina the entire class he's
the one what do you mean come on you know it's charming who else
all I know is that boy was extremely grateful to you yes dr. Tenma he told me
You saved his life. You meant more to him than his parents.
What name did he go by then?
Franz. But he did tell me it wasn't his real name.
If he opened up enough to tell you that much, it means he must have really trusted you.
He just showed up one day out of nowhere, really.
Mr. and Mrs. Heine, who lived across the hall, took him in.
He lived with them for about a year.
No. Actually, it was 14 months, to be precise, from March 1987 to April 1988.
Then one day, out of the blue, he suddenly vanished.
He really was very bright, that boy, and very well-mannered.
Did he visit you in your apartment very often?
Every day. I live alone, so I always welcome the company.
He sat in that chair and would spend most of his time studying.
He was able to master the English and French that I taught him in no time.
By the time he disappeared, he was completely fluent in both languages.
He was only twelve years old.
Can you tell me if there's anything else you remember about him? Anything?
He was always interested in listening to my stories.
What stories do you think he liked best? Go on, take a wild guess.
I...
He liked my war stories.
War stories?
During World War II, I was on the crew of a U-boat.
The boy's favorite story was about the time we were attacked by a destroyer of the Allied forces.
We were at a depth of a hundred and twenty meters.
That's when we were attacked by the enemy.
We had suffered a mortal blow, but we just kept going.
We all waited in terror inside that creaking boat,
enduring hour after hour.
We had to endure that hell for a day and a half.
Any ordinary child would have probably looked at this
as another adventure story, but that boy was different.
What he was most interested in was my description
of ultimate fear.
Yes, ultimate fear.
That reaction of people on the verge of death fascinated him.
That was all he was interested in.
He toyed with fear.
So what...
What was the expression on his face as he listened?
He probably had a gleam in his eye and a smile, I imagine.
Imagine?
Well, I cannot see, Dr. Tenma.
So, no. I don't know the boy's real name, nor obviously do I have any idea what he looks
like for that matter. Earlier, you suggested the boy trusted me because he told me France
wasn't his real name. I can assure you that he doesn't trust anyone. There's only one
person that boy's trusted in his life, and that's his sister.
Listen, I need your help. I'm looking for that sister.
- He said he would go get her when she turned 20.
- Where is she?
- In Heidelberg.
- [gasps]
- See you later.
- Be careful on your scooter, honey.
- I will.
Bye. See you later, Daddy.
- Bye. And drive safely, okay?
- See you later.
[chuckles]
(birds chirping)
- The time has come, hasn't it?
- I know.
- We made an agreement.
We said we'd tell her on her 20th birthday
that she isn't our real daughter.
(Ruby whimpering)
- Hold on a second, I'm not sure I can do this.
- What are you talking about?
You wanted to meet him.
Here, it's better you didn't know.
- Don't mess it up.
You're about to meet Prince Charming.
Later.
Wait, Clara, wait for me!
How could they do this behind my back?
It's him!
Here we go!
Hi, how do you do? You're Nina Fortuner, right?
Uh, yes.
Oh, good. Yeah.
My name's Otto Huberman.
Oh. Uh, hello.
Who? Who are you? I've seen that face... somewhere before.
Who? Who are you?
(eerie music)
(thudding)
- Nina!
- Oh, Nina!
- Nina, what's wrong?
- Nina, can you hear me?
- Wake up, come on, Nina.
- Nina, wake up, please.
- What happened?
- Nina, come on.
You're okay.
Nina.
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)