Mr. Maurer, you haven't bathed in days, have you?
And you've been wearing that same shirt for half a week.
You promised you'd shower every other day.
Quit nagging me, will ya?
You have a visitor in the reception area.
Alright, I'm going home.
Listen, you're gonna have to make your own coffee, okay?
A visitor? At this time of night?
Yeah, he hasn't had a bath either.
You'll like him, he smells almost as bad as you do.
Give it a rest.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Whose fault is it that I haven't been able to take a bath anyway?
She's completely oblivious to the fact that it's 'cause of me that we all still have work,
even though this paper has no future.
How hard is that to figure out?
Jeez.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello, my name is Tenma, sir.
And I've come here to ask you for your help.
He certainly looks filthy.
I see. So you're a doctor, huh?
Well, you don't look like one.
Let me get this straight.
I just want to make sure that we're on the same page here.
So what you're saying is that the infamous serial killer
who's been executing middle-aged couples throughout Germany
has his next target in Heidelberg?
This particular couple have an adopted daughter,
and you're saying that when that girl turns 20,
the killer will come to take her away.
are going to be killed, and you have no idea who that girl or her parents are, but you
want to save them.
If that's not delusional, I don't know what is.
I'm not joking about this.
You have to believe me.
What a load of hooey.
Not even a third-rate tabloid would buy that story.
Look, I didn't come here to sell you a story.
After the twins escaped, they disappeared.
was at least six months that went by
before the brother was seen in Munich.
- So what's your point, huh?
- I believe that after leaving the hospital,
those children must have come here, to Heidelberg, together.
- You know, this is just your theory.
- And then the two of them were raised
by the twin sister's current foster parents.
But the brother ran away from home after a short period,
leaving the sister behind.
- Why don't you write a novel?
Probably won't sell, though.
- Wait, maybe the couple reported
Or there might be a newspaper article about it from nine years ago.
All I'm asking is to look through your archives from the past nine years!
I'm begging you!
Wait, please!
There mustn't be any more victims! The killing has to stop!
Listen to me!
The boss is allergic to technology.
Reduced versions as well as the original archives from nine years ago.
And the rest of these are the articles that never did make it to print.
Thank you very much.
So, is that some sort of Japanese bow?
Well, domo arigato.
Let me say this.
This doesn't mean that I believe you.
and show yourself out when you're done looking, you got that?
God, why do I always have to deal with the weirdos?
- Please, please, let me find it.
(choral music)
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
- Good morning, Nina.
- Good morning.
- You're looking much better.
I'm so glad.
really scared when you fainted like that, you know?
- I guess you really didn't like the boy
we hooked you up with, huh?
- No, that's not it at all.
I just felt sick all of a sudden.
I need to apologize to him.
- Oh, never mind.
You don't have to worry about him.
Trust me.
- Huh?
- Well, it turns out when I talked to Otto,
I found out he wasn't your Prince Charming
on a white horse after all.
- Yeah, we asked and he said he didn't know anything
at all about those email messages.
- Oh, really?
So you're saying that you fainted right after you saw this particular boy at your campus, huh?
Yes.
Well, what did this fellow look like?
I only saw him for a second, so I'm not really sure.
And do you remember exactly what you felt at the moment when you saw him?
I remember I felt nostalgic.
Hmm.
But maybe not. I don't know how to explain it.
Go on.
(Gasp)
(Gunshot)
Just take it easy. Don't force yourself.
Absolute evil.
Hmm?
I don't know how to put it, but...
Yes, it felt just like when I used to have that nightmare.
Absolute evil, eh?
It sounds more like it has to do with your religious beliefs.
I don't think so. I'm not really one to go to church regularly.
But I think if I see this young man again, it might help to clarify things for me.
You're thinking this might help you recover your memory, is that it?
Yes.
I suppose that's one way to go about it.
But I don't think you should allow this to disturb the peace you now have.
It's important you continue to focus on your future and the road ahead.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Just work up a sweat doing your Aikido
and your anxiety should disappear.
Hey, Maurer.
So, did you pull another all-nighter?
Yeah.
By the way,
I'm just wondering,
were you the one who told that person
he could use the file room?
That weird guy?
Yeah.
I asked him what he was doing there
and he said you had given him permission
to look through the archives.
Why? You mean he's still in there?
Hey, you! Time to hit the road!
Hey! Are you alright?
Hey!
Come on, eat up.
Thank you.
Good, isn't it?
I always come here for breakfast.
So don't you ever eat at home, then?
What about your family?
Haven't got one.
My wife walked out on me a while ago.
Huh?
I was always too busy with the work.
And before I knew it, my wife left with our daughter and moved back with her parents.
Do you ever think about trying to patch things up with her?
Why would I do that?
She's the one who walked out on me.
Why should I have to be the one to go after her?
Well, it just seemed like you regretted spending so much time at work.
That's complete nonsense.
Work is priority number one, you hear?
Any woman who can't understand such a simple fact is welcome to leave whenever she wants.
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to pry.
That's right.
None of your business.
- Oh, another thing, please do forgive me,
but you smoke too much.
As a doctor, I recommend you cut back.
- I told you already, it's none of your business.
You're beginning to sound just like that wife of mine.
- Well, what's so bad about that?
It means she cares about your health.
- Just mind your own damn business.
- Is that Nina's birthday present?
She's finally able to finish it.
Goodness, I remember when her sweaters used to be this tiny.
Honey, do we really have to tell her?
Does she have to know that she's not our real daughter?
Why not just leave it alone?
You're right. There's no point in telling her that now.
Nina's our daughter. That's all there is to it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I am so hungry.
All I have to do is focus on my future.
Yeah, maybe Dr. Geidel is right after all.
See you tomorrow at 7 p.m. at Heidelberg Castle for your birthday.
Tomorrow? At Heidelberg Castle?
I'm a very busy man. I've been staring at newspaper clippings with you for two days.
I admire your gumption, but don't you think it's about time you gave up?
If, and I say if, I were to ask my wife to come home again, do you really think she would
give it another go?
Yeah, if you kick the habit one day.
What is it?
Found it.
11-year-old boy goes missing.
There's a possibility the child has been abducted, but there have been no ransom demands made as of yet.
Address 16 Necker Street.
Someone named Fortner filed a missing person report that day.
There should be some more information in here somewhere.
- Here it is.
Oh, man.
- What is it?
What did you find?
- Hey, Doc, you said that killer would come
to take his sister away the day she turned 20.
Isn't that right?
If the boy in this article is her twin brother,
well, see for yourself.
His birth date is printed on it.
Those twins are turning 20 today.
Um, hi, Dad. It's me. I just finished up at work.
I'm going to be meeting up with a friend, and then I'll be coming home.
Uh-huh. Yeah, at Heidelberg Castle.
Really? Your mom is making a birthday cake, so don't stay out too late.
Was that Nina, dear?
Yeah. She's meeting a friend before coming home. I'm wondering who this friend is.
Nina's a big girl now.
Maybe this will help me to remember things.
I want to know who I really am.
So Doc, what are you going to do if this girl is at the Fortuner's residence?
Whatever's going on, one thing's for sure, they're in danger.
So I'll call the police and see if they can send over a car.
And you think the police are just going to show up?
Yeah, doctor, but if we wait till then it'll be too late. Look nothing's gonna happen. Come on. This is all in your head
Hey doc, listen up, I know what I'm talking about. I actually went to the crime scene of the fourth middle-aged couple murdered in Cone
There was something unusual about those crimes
No motive. No vengeance. Oh bitterness nothing
Yeah, it just seemed like whoever did this wanted to kill for killing's sake
I've been a reporter for a long time.
Something tells me you're way off base this time around, Doc.
Honestly, do you really think a 20-year-old kid could be such a cold-blooded killer?
There's no way a kid would do something like that.
It's something a whole lot worse.
How could it be any worse?
Hell, that's just it.
I have a hard time finding the words to describe that case.
Whenever I tried to describe it, the whole thing just sounds so corny, but the truth
is, that was the devil's work.
One thing's for certain, Doc, if I had half a chance, I'd snuff that guy in a heartbeat.
16 Necker Street.
Good evening, sorry to bother you so late.
Yes?
I'm sorry to bother you, sir.
My name is Maurer.
I'm from the Heidelberg Post.
So you're a newspaper reporter?
Yeah, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
What about?
Well...
The missing persons report that you filed for your son in 1986...
I've got nothing to tell you!
I'm sorry, sir, but you need to talk to us. Please listen!
We know that you have a girl living with you.
The twin sister of the boy who disappeared nine years ago!
This is important. Please answer me!
(knocking)
- Son of a gun.
I saw a cake.
I just saw the mother in there.
She was holding a birthday cake.
- Nine years ago, you took in a set of twins
and the sister is still living with you both.
Well, isn't she?
- Please leave.
Nina is our daughter.
We are a family.
It's that simple.
Please don't cause us any unnecessary trouble.
Just leave us alone, please.
You took in a pair of twins nine years ago.
The little boy had surgical scars on his head.
The girl had amnesia, and the boy disappeared.
Isn't that right?
Mr. Fortner, listen to me.
You've got to call the police now.
All your lives are in danger, your daughters and your own.
Mr. Maurer.
What? What are you talking about? What do you mean?
- Look, it's very important we talk to your daughter.
- Well, she isn't home at the moment.
She's out.
- Huh?
- Where?
Where did she go?
- She's gone to Heidelberg Castle.
She said she was going to meet a friend there.
- Please, let me borrow your car.
- No, wait.
We gotta call the police station first.
- We don't have time to waste
explaining things to the police.
Give me the keys quickly.
- All right.
You go on and I'll call them myself.
- Thank you.
Hey, Doc, listen.
Be careful.
Like I told you before, this guy's the devil.
Don't die on me.
You got that?
Mr. Mauler, I...
You better come back alive.
Do you hear me?
I promise.
I'll follow your advice and I'll finally quit smoking, so get back here quick.
Your wife will be glad to hear that.
Huh.
Oh, boy.
How am I supposed to explain this to the police?
Our daughter!
is our daughter all right what is it what's happened don't worry she'll be
fine but I need to use your phone what has happened to our daughter please tell
us just tell us already calm down lady hmm
what in the hell's this it's dead the phone lines been cut
Please, Anna.
Just hang in there.
Hold on.
It's getting pretty late.
He's probably not coming.
Well, I guess that message must have been a prank after all.
I'm going home.
You can't do that.
You can't go.
You have to wait here.
Who are you?
He told me.
I'm supposed to make sure you wait right here.
I just told you to wait. Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Wait!
I'm supposed to keep you right here, lady!
It's my job to keep you here!
Anna!
I guess that they're calling you Nina now.
Do you remember me? I'm Dr. Tenma.
Thank God you're okay.
Anna... Dr. Tenma...
Let's go. Back to your house.
Are you... my Prince Charming?
Who the hell are you?
Don't interfere. You can't interfere in this.
She needs to stay here. That's all there is to it.
If she doesn't, I won't.
I won't.
I won't get paid, you bastard!
He said no one else was supposed to show up!
Hey, are you alright?
Yeah, but how on earth did you...
I need something to tie him up with, quick!
Oh, uh...
Tell me, who put you up to this?
I don't know, okay?
Well, when is he coming back here? What did he say?
Look, I don't know. All he said was he would be back as soon as it was done
was something very important he had to take care of.
Oh, God. He's at your house.
Come on, we have to get back to your house right away.
Why? What's going on?
I'll explain it all later. We have got to hurry, Anna.
Anna...
Let's go!
You have to untie me!
(sobbing)
- Please tell me, who on earth are you, Dr. Tenma?
You got it wrong, my name's not Anna.
I'm Nina.
- Now, but that wasn't your name
back when you were brought into my hospital.
You were Anna, and your brother,
your brother's name was Johan.
- My brother.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]