Please tell me! Who on earth are you, Dr. Tenma? You got it wrong, my name's not Anna!
I'm Nina!
Now, but that wasn't your name back when you were brought into my hospital.
You were Anna, and your brother... your brother's name was Johan.
My brother...
Yohan...
Anna...
My brother...
Mr. Fortuner!
Mr. Maurer!
Mr. Moura! Mr. Fortuner! It's me, Dr. Tenma! Anna, I mean Nina, is safe! She's here with
me! Mr. Moura!
All right, you go on and I'll call them myself.
It doesn't look like the police ever came.
Oh, my God.
[Door creaks open]
[Door creaks closed]
[Footsteps approach]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
(eerie music)
Liv, please, come back.
You must live.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Mr. Maurer, you don't have to quit smoking anymore, all right?
(sobbing)
- Mr. Maurer!
- I killed him.
Back then.
I killed him, but now he's...
[eerie music]
Kill?
I know. I killed him.
I did. I killed him.
I know.
On that day, I know, I'm sure, I killed my brother!
It was me, I was the one who brought your brother back to life.
It's dead.
The phone line has been cut.
We're getting out of here.
He'll be coming back for you.
(suspenseful music)
- You okay in there?
- We're with the police.
Someone called earlier.
Is there any trouble?
- If you don't mind, sir,
we're just gonna have a quick look around.
- Good Lord.
You two alright? Are you injured? You hurt?
Well, that's a relief. Backups should arrive very soon.
They'll take care of the crime scene, and we'll take you over to headquarters for questioning so we can file a report on this.
So, are you the daughter of the victims?
I'm sorry for your loss.
I'm assuming neither of you saw the intruder then?
To think something like that could happen in such a peaceful town.
Pardon my asking, sir, but where do you come from?
Are you Chinese?
No, sir.
I'm Japanese.
My name is Kenzo Tenma.
Okay.
You're Japanese.
Yeah.
well seems to me you're quite a ways from home then aren't you you're all
right now it's gonna be okay
sorry but can you tell me where we're headed officer the police station
remember but wait I don't understand the Heidelberg police station is in town
Yeah, but we're from the station in Mannheim, the next town over.
Why? Why are they taking us so far?
Yeah, we're almost there. Just another 15 minutes or so.
Uh, okay.
He said they got a call. They came because they got a call.
But who could have called?
The phone was dead.
There were no sirens when they first came.
And they took us away before making sure that backup arrived at the scene.
But those badges...
Those badges did look real.
Blood!
It... no way...
It can't be...
Could these men have...
Uh, excuse me.
Huh?
A police checkpoint.
Thank goodness.
We're searching for a hit-and-run suspect, so please be alert.
Uh, excuse me.
It's you.
Well, if it isn't Detective Messner and Detective Mueller.
Good evening to you, gentlemen.
Are you two on your way back to the station?
Wow, you've got a new car.
What's going on?
Really nice.
I'm sure we'll get it banged up soon enough.
Yeah, we really give our rides a workout.
Excuse me, detective.
Uh, she's not feeling so well back here.
Can she get some fresh air for a minute?
Oh, uh, sure. You go ahead.
Say, detective, what's up?
Are these two in some kind of trouble?
Trouble? Not at all. It's nothing. Don't worry.
They seem like real detectives, but what about that blood?
Who could have called them?
Their sirens weren't even on.
What should we do?
What?
Hey, what's wrong, Dr. Tenma?
Are you two okay?
How?
How do you know who I am?
I gave you my name but I never told you not once that I was a doctor.
Tell me, how did you know that?
I found a grocery store nearby I also got you some dry clothes there's bread
I filled this thermos up with hot coffee, too.
You probably don't have much of an appetite, but you really should eat.
You're shivering. You should change out of those wet clothes.
(birds chirping)
- A lot of people were dead.
My brother and I were walking.
It was like we were all alone in the world.
Where were you when all of this happened?
Can you remember anything else?
We crossed the border.
Uncle and auntie helped us.
They were so kind to us.
Then my brother said,
"I have a good plan."
Soon after that,
my uncle and my dear auntie were both dead.
Anyone who was ever good to us died, without fail, all of them.
But then one day, one day, I discovered the reason why.
That rainy day.
You're talking about the incident with Mr. and Mrs. Liebert?
My brother did it. He shot them.
My brother, he... he murdered them.
He's the one who did all this.
My brother murdered them all.
So I picked up the gun with both my hands,
and then I aimed it right at my brother.
And that's when he said it.
He was smiling.
"After you shoot me,
make sure that you throw the gun out the window."
And he told me to aim for his head.
So I... I shot him like he said... I aimed for his head like he told me... Why did you
save him?
If you hadn't saved him, Mom and Dad would still be alive! You wouldn't have killed them!
Why did you have to save him?
Stay here. I'm going to the police.
If those detectives last night were real,
it means that some members of the police force are linked to Johan.
If so, we can't just wait here like this.
"Nina, I need you to listen to me.
I know that Johan is going to come after you.
If anyone comes looking for you, just hide.
Why don't you have some food, drink some hot coffee, and then try to get a couple hours
of rest.
One step at a time, that's how we'll get through all this.
You're alive.
You must think about the future, your future.
Were there any clues left by the killer?
Is there any connection to the serial murders throughout Germany?
Chief, Chief, one question.
Like I said, we're doing everything we can to investigate this case,
but I can't make any comments or talk about details.
Chief, we've learned that the 14-year-old had a daughter.
Are you able to tell us where she is at this time, or is she presumed dead as well?
We're trying to figure out her whereabouts.
reporter with them. Mr. Mauer. Chief, one question. And who was that Japanese man who
is said to have been with him? One more question, sir. Japanese? Who is he? He sounds suspicious.
Quick question, Chief. Is this murder at all related to the one that took place
at Heidelberg Castle around the same time? Heidelberg Castle?
So he was killed, too. Chief, we gotta have something. One more.
That's all for now. We'll release additional details in due time.
Please let me through
Excuse me, sir, of course, we appreciate all the support we're getting from Mannheim like detectives Messner and Mueller
Thank you both for coming out this afternoon
We're at your disposal to aid in the investigation anything we can do to help
So, how are things coming along sir?
Please come inside that way. We'll be able to speak freely
Chief, can you tell me...
Could you give me an interview?
Chief, just one more question, really quick.
One more question.
They're real.
Those guys were with the police.
They're actual cops.
What should I do?
Hello, Heidelberg Post.
What?
I can't hear you.
We're really busy in here.
Just buy that Japanese guy.
Who did you say you were?
He was with Maurer.
He's the key.
I'm bringing an important witness to your office at five o'clock, but you must not tell the police
If I can't trust the police then the newspaper is my only option only they can help me now
Mr. Maurer.
I'm sorry, but you just can't come in here without permission.
He's right. Besides, the BKA is only working on the serial murders of the middle-aged couples.
All that you're going to find in this room is material for the murder at the castle, Inspector Lungay.
Uh, sir?
Please forgive me. I was just a bit curious.
But the crime you're investigating and this one happened at the same time, detective.
I mean, it couldn't have been the same murderer.
So, I see. It appears that this man had been tied up.
You didn't happen to find a rope or anything nearby, did you?
No. Seems the body had already been untied by the time the police arrived on the scene.
I see. Yes.
There are four possible routes of escape from the scene.
He also had to stay well out of sight.
How crowded was the area where he'd come out?
And how much light was there?
Huh?
Here it is.
- Nina, it's me, Tenma, I'm back.
Nina, you can come out now, it's all right.
Hey, Nina?
Oh, no.
Nina!
Where are you?
He came for you, didn't he, Nina?
I never should have left you here all alone.
Dr. Tenma, I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore.
You did what you had to do as a doctor.
It wasn't your fault.
Please eat the sandwiches...
and get some rest, too.
Please live on...
and continue to save as many people as you are able to.
Nina Fortner.
[sobbing]
Nina, what are you planning to do?
Are you going to kill your brother a second time?
I did it.
I brought him back to life.
That monster.
It was me.
[roaring]
I brought him back to life.
(dramatic music)
(gentle music)