Dr. Tenma, I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore.
You did what you had to do as a doctor.
It wasn't your fault.
Please eat the sandwiches, and get some rest, too.
Please live on, and continue to save as many people as you are able to.
Nina Fortner.
Nina, what are you planning to do?
Are you going to kill your brother a second time?
I did it. I brought him back to life.
That monster. It was me.
I brought him back to life.
(dramatic music)
There are a lot of blood vessels in this arterial venous malformation.
Cutting all arteries.
And now the veins.
Extraction of the nidus is complete.
That went very well.
Yes, as usual. He's remarkably quick with the clipping.
An amazing operation.
Dr. Tenma, how is it possible that even after a long break,
A genius like you only gets better and better.
It's over.
Never mind. It isn't important.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GROANING]
Isn't that wonderful, Kenzo?
It wasn't even about me.
It was all about your father.
That may be true, but it's only because you did such a wonderful job last night working as part of father's team
I'm sure he appreciates all your hard work since you're the one responsible for raising the hospital's reputation
No, I'm the one who should be grateful. I mean after all it is
Thanks to your father that I'm actually able to work here in Germany
Hang in there Kenzo if you stick with father your future is guaranteed
It won't be long before father becomes chairman of the board
You'll become Chief of Surgery, and then Chief Director.
Which means I'll be the Director's wife.
You better make me happy, Kenzo, 'cause hardship doesn't suit me.
Still wanna go out on that date?
Or should we just...
(birds chirping)
(moaning)
- Uh, please, sir, madame is resting at the moment.
- I won't need much of her time.
This shouldn't take long.
But sir, you really need to make an appointment with madame.
What's all the racket?
Um, I'm terribly sorry to bother you, madame,
but there's a police officer here.
The police?
Miss Eva Heinemann. It's been a while, hasn't it?
And who are you supposed to be?
I worked on your father's case exactly nine years ago.
I'm Inspector Lunge of the BKA.
Lunge. Oh, I see. You may leave us, Hulse.
Yes, Madame.
I do remember you all too well.
You were that good-for-nothing detective who couldn't even close my father's case.
So tell me, what on earth do you want from me now?
I'm quite impressed.
You've been able to maintain this residence exactly the same
Actually, it appears that the decor might have gotten even more extravagant than before.
So then, have you come to see how much money I've made from the inheritance my father left me in all my divorce settlements?
As you can see, detective, I live in absolute comfort.
If you see anything you like, please feel free to take it with you.
As long as I have my liquor by my side, I'm fine.
I've come today because there is something I'd like to show you.
Here, take a look at this necktie.
A necktie?
Does it look familiar?
Perhaps you don't remember.
It's a design from nine years ago.
It has a very simple print, but if you look at it carefully,
it's a wonderful piece with an extremely elaborate weave.
So what? What about it?
it back was quite a task after all it was purchased nine years ago. But luckily this
was a limited edition offering specially made for a particular store's higher-end clients.
And your name was on that list, Miss Eva Heinemann.
So what exactly is your point?
You see, I was wondering if you might have purchased this and given it to someone as
a gift. This necktie is a key piece of evidence in another murder case.
Murder?
Who knows?
I've given gifts to so many men,
I couldn't possibly keep track of them all now, could I?
They're not interested in me anyway.
The only thing they're after is my money.
- Please, try to remember.
- I told you, I don't remember.
These men are all after my money.
There isn't a single person
who truly loves me for who I am.
That's why I always stick it to them when it's time for the divorce settlement.
I did that to all three of them.
Ha! Damn bastards!
Do you want something, too?
You want something? Just tell me.
But you'll pay a high price for it.
I'll be back, ma'am.
If you remember anything, please give me a call.
Next time you stop by, detective, be sure to bring me something to drink.
(liquid pouring)
Excuse me.
(moaning)
(gulping)
(sighing)
(soft music)
- Ava.
Ava, please, you have to talk to your father for me.
Make him see I haven't done anything wrong.
All I did was operate on an emergency patient
You're the worst, nothing else!
Wait, is that the ring that I gave to you?
Spare me, Kenzo. You're such a fool.
Ava, why?
Dr. Norton, you're looking very handsome this evening.
Oh, thank you.
You're looking especially beautiful tonight yourself, Eva.
Hulse, have my car ready.
Well, Mr. Hess, you're certainly looking better today.
At this rate, I'm guessing you should be able to go home sometime later this week, all right?
Thank you very much, Dr. Tenma. You did a great job.
By the way, my daughter is getting married next month.
Do you think I'll be able to attend her wedding?
Yes, that should be fine.
You just have to promise me that you won't get too wild at the reception.
Thanks, Doctor. I had resigned myself to not going, but thanks to you...
you toughed it out. With you looking after me, I feel as though I'll even live to see
my grandchildren get married. You truly are a wonderful doctor. I really hope they keep
you at this hospital forever. Excuse me, Dr. Temma, you have a visitor. Oh, I'm doing my
rounds right now. Tell them I'm too busy at the moment, would you please? Okay, but...
Ava?
It's been a while, hasn't it, Kenzo?
It has.
Both of us have gone through so much.
Hello, Father. Are you sleeping already?
I'm coming in.
(Crying)
Father!
(crying)
Ava, Ava, I know it's difficult, but please,
try to hold yourself--
Don't touch me!
Give me my father back!
I want him back!
(crying)
Kenzo!
Listen, please, forgive me!
I was wrong!
Kenzo?
You look worn out.
You're much thinner.
I guess.
I hear that you took some vacation time.
Well, I think that's great.
You should take a break every once in a while.
You always were such a workaholic.
Seems like you've lost a little weight yourself.
I've had a rough couple of years.
I'm sure you've heard all the rumors.
I've heard a few.
It's spring. You remember?
Almost ten years ago, how the two of us would often go out for a drive.
It was this time of the year when you tried to swim in that river.
I panicked and tried to stop you.
But you insisted and you just...
Look, I'm sorry.
Look, Eva, I can't deal with this now.
Kenzo, I...
I want to start over.
After three failed marriages,
I realized that the only one who ever truly loved me was you.
It was you, Kenzo.
That was a long time ago.
Kenzo!
Please, Kenzo!
I want you to know that I'm very flattered, Eva.
But there's no going back. Goodbye.
Wait, Kenzo! I kept quiet! I didn't say a word!
The police came to my house and asked about your tie!
It seems to me that necktie of yours has gotten you in some kind of trouble.
I'm absolutely positive that's the one I gave you as a gift when we were together.
If you do as I say, I'll keep quiet about it, I promise you!
There's something very important that only I can accomplish.
I'll tell the police about your tie.
I'll tell them everything.
What's she going on about?
Do you hear me?
I'll tell them how you killed my father nine years ago.
You killed him, Kenzo.
- I don't believe it.
- Oh, I see.
Let's bring Dr. Tenma in for an interrogation right away.
- But sir, there's not enough evidence to tie Dr. Tenma
to what happened with Mr. Maurer and the Fortners.
- That's not what I'm referring to.
I'm talking about the killing at Heidelberg Castle.
- Right away.
Yes, sir.
- Thank you very much for your cooperation.
This could prove to be very helpful
solving several of our open cases resignation but what is the meaning of
this dr. tenma I'm very sorry director but I've already made up my mind about
this there have been various odd rumors going around about you recently but I
want to be clear I don't believe any of it please think this over you have hey
Wait! Dr. Tenma!
Yes, speaking.
Excuse me, the police?
Huh? Dr. Tenma is a murder suspect?
close off all the exits don't forget the back doors yes sir where is dr tenma i don't know
Why are you just standing there?
Search the place, officers.
Oh, but Inspector, sir, uh...
What is it?
Hey!
Get out of the way!
You people are interfering with the police!
Like hell!
Dr. Tenma would never be capable of killing anyone!
That's right!
that what he does is save people's lives?
- Dr. Tenma is an innocent man.
- Go away! - Now forget about it!
- He's never done anything wrong.
- We're not gonna talk to you.
He's a great doctor.
- Go away!
- He would never do anything like that.
- This is none of your business.
- Wow, I wonder what's going on in the front.
- See those police cars over there, Dr. Tenma?
Man, ain't that a sight.
- Is that right?
Anyway, can you drop me off at the station?
No problem.
Hey, Doctor, are you always this busy?
I have...
I have a surgery to perform in the other room.
Dr. Tenma!
Wait!
Hang in there, kid.
I'll save you, no matter what.
I am not wrong.
He is.
He tells me there's a flaw in my character.
Well, what about him?
He says he's a doctor, but he's just a greedy bastard.
Bastard.
He'd be better off dead.
They're gone, sir.
We can't find them anywhere.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
It's been a long time, Doctor.
It's me.
Have you forgotten already, Doctor?
About the twins?
Johan...
Save me, Doctor!
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
I was supposed to die that night.
You're the one who resurrected me, Doctor.
(birds chirping)
(engine rumbling)
- It looks like another scorcher today.
Hey, why are you all bundled up
on a hot summer day like this?
Aren't you broiling, huh?
You're reading an old paper. That one's at least three days old.
Yeah, a couple in Verden got themselves murdered.
They say a doctor did it, if you can believe that.
Hey, buddy, you said you were headed for Verden, wasn't that right?
What, you know somebody over there?
Yeah, I do. I'm not even sure if he'll still be there now.
But I have to try and find him.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)