That looks like another scorcher today.
Hey, why are you all bundled up on a hot summer day like this?
Aren't you broiling? Huh?
You're reading an old paper. That one's at least three days old.
Yeah, a couple in Verdon got themselves murdered.
They say a doctor did it, if you can believe that.
Hey, buddy, you said you were headed for Verdun, wasn't that right?
What, you know somebody over there?
Yeah, I do.
I'm not even sure if he'll still be there now.
But I have to try and find him.
We'll be right back.
Formerly served in the French Foreign Legion,
Then went freelance and fought in Nicaragua in 1979.
From 1981 to 1984, assisted the guerrilla rebels in Afghanistan.
Then in 1987, you played a key role in the assassination of radical Islamic leaders
in a top secret Mossad operation.
It's quite an impressive resume, I must admit.
Isn't it, Mr. Hugo Bernhardt?
I have no doubt that a mercenary of your caliber must be quite a teacher,
and I'm sure a number of distinguished men must have been under your instruction.
It might be a good idea to send some of our own officers to attend your seminar
and have you whip them into shape.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Incidentally, was this man here a good student by any chance?
I believe he showed up at your training grounds about five months ago.
we know that he is a genius with a scalpel what I'm wondering about is whether he has any talent
with a gun I don't divulge information about my pupils to anyone period of course you don't
So, have you ever trained with a gun before?
Uh, no.
I guess that means that you're self-taught, then.
Actually, I've never shot a gun before.
What? You mean not even once?
Right. I know I'm asking for the impossible.
That said, you're my only hope right now.
It makes no difference.
I make all my students forget everything they learned before they got here.
But this...
This is the first time I'll be teaching someone who's never shot a gun before.
I don't know.
Jump rope. Regardless of your experience or lack of, this is where everyone starts.
Now jump like that child over there.
Don't just stand there. Well, get started.
Yes, sir.
Faster now.
Hurry it up.
I said faster.
Balance.
It's all about balance.
Come on, faster.
I said faster!
Well, obviously I can't jump rope nearly as well as you do
Tell me something is this what you do, you know always supervising student training like this
All right, I understand you don't have to keep on staring at me like that I'll do it I
Know what I have to do
Hey, it's a brambling.
I wonder if it's looking for food for its chicks.
♪♪♪
What's wrong? Are you too tired to eat?
Uh, yes.
You can't train if you pass out.
Yes, sir.
She your daughter? Or your granddaughter, maybe?
Neither.
That little girl is the daughter of a woman I killed.
shot her down right before her very eyes
back in Myanmar
on mission in the jungle
I ran into a hut for shelter
and there she was with her mother
her mother was holding a gun
If I'd have been a fraction of a second slower, it would have been me that died that day.
I brought the child back here with me. I couldn't just leave her.
From that moment on, she hasn't smiled once.
That's why she'll probably hate me for the rest of her life.
That's the sort of thing that happens when you have a gun.
Now, if you can't handle that, then I'd suggest you don't carry one.
♪
♪♪♪
what's that what a pleasant scent that is it smells just like daphne blossoms
Thanks.
All right, that's enough of that.
Huh? So then...
Time for some more running. Go.
Oh, yes, sir. Right away, then.
When you're done running, come to the bottom of the hill in the back.
What's down there?
The firing range.
The firing range?
Remember, two shots.
You have to make sure that whenever you fire your gun, you always pull the trigger twice.
If you can do that instinctively, it betters your chances of taking out your objective.
If you can't do that, then you're as good as dead. It's all over.
What's this about?
You're always preparing meals for me, so I thought I would cook for you today.
It's a Japanese stew of meat and potatoes.
It's called Nikujaga. Go on, dig in. I think you'll both enjoy it.
Those are chopsticks. They're carved out of wood.
I made them. I thought it would make our dining experience more authentic.
Wow. You're really good at using chopsticks, aren't you?
♪
again faster aim do it again aim
What's wrong?
it's a baby brambling I guess it fell out of its nest no wait you have to put
it back and that chick is going to die it's very difficult to raise them like
They rarely survive for that long outside of the nest.
Let's put it back. Back with its mother, okay?
Three seconds.
That's all the time you've got.
Find your target and pull the trigger,
because one mistake is the slightest bit of hesitation and you're dead.
Tell me, how well did he perform over those five months he was there training with you?
Technically speaking, he was a perfect student.
He built up the necessary stamina, and his concentration while firing was extraordinary.
However...
However?
Being able to actually shoot a person is another story.
Really?
Whether or not he is successful on his first kill.
That's what it all comes down to.
Either he's got what it takes, or he doesn't.
Yes, I see.
I wonder which road this man will choose.
Well, it matters not.
Tell me, do you have any idea where he might have gone?
Because if you do know where, I would really like for you to tell me.
Thanks for all you've done for me over the past five months.
Here's the remaining tuition I owe.
And please, help yourself to the Nikujaga.
Again, thank you for everything.
Damn it.
Damn it all.
She's laughing.
So how about it?
You do know where this man was heading, don't you?
That I can't tell you.
That's fine. You can go now.
This way, sir.
♪♪♪
♪♪
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
© transcript Emily Beynon