One Manhattan have a ball wait a second. Where's the cherry, huh? It's not a Manhattan without the cherry
Yeah, my mistake
I'll let it slide this time
Business always goes well when I'm sucking on one of these
A lucky charm is a lucky charm.
(dramatic music)
Come to papa, I just hope there's still something of value we're taking.
Well well well, lookie what we've got here.
Five-finger free-for-all.
Wonder if there's anything valuable enough
for a connoisseur like Otto Heckel.
Heh, you never know what's gonna happen.
First, you're a shoo-in candidate for governor.
Next thing, you and your wife get shot.
Oh well, down to business.
I'm guessing this is where they kept the safe.
(ominous music)
Why am I getting the chills? This is creepy as hell. I've never felt anything like this.
Could... could somebody be in there?
As if. What am I so scared about? It ain't like me to be a chicken.
Don't move. Put your hands behind your head.
Oh man, I can't believe this.
He forgot the cherry I said put your hands up. All right. All right. All right
Give me a break on this one officer. I haven't taken anything yet. I promise I'm not a cop
No, so you're robbing the place too, huh? Well in that case, why don't you just put that thing away?
We'll have ourselves behind your head now
Jeez, what's with this guy? He's a bigger boy scout than the friggin cops
You gotta be kidding me. Thanks for nothing, buddy
Don't follow me!
Someone like you just gets in the way!
You'll slow me down! Damn it all!
I told you to stop following me!
Damn, damn, today just ain't my day!
That's right! I thought I recognized you.
You're all over the papers.
You're the doctor wanted for questioning
in connection with Councilman Springer's murder.
And you, are you a thief?
That I am. But I got something called morals.
You wouldn't know anything about the murders that happened in that house, would you?
No idea, so get out of my face, will ya?
Later.
Hey, Doctor.
You're some sort of top-notch surgeon, aren't ya?
My brilliant brain just came up with a fantastic idea.
Do you think that people meet by chance, Doctor?
They don't.
Believe me, I know.
I believe in fate.
I think people meet for a reason.
My gut tells me you and I were destined to become partners.
Huh?
Call me crazy, but I think a lot of folks in the underground community need someone like you.
You know, guys who need to hide out so they can't go to regular doctors for help.
Listen, you leave the management to old heckle here.
I'll make you the world's best underground doctor in no time.
I'm telling you, Doc, you're gonna make a lot of money.
You'll be a millionaire before you know it.
Eh?
Hey, hey, Doctor, where do you think you're going?
There's something I have to do and it can't wait
Well, I'd hold my horses if I were you you want to know about the murders in that house, don't you?
Well, I guess he'd like to hear that I saw the killer am I right what did you say
Are you telling me the truth you want to know what did he look like?
I need to know what's the killer blonde and about 20 years of age. What are you on about?
Never mind. You just tell me about who you saw there team up with me and I'd be happy to doctor
He's on the third floor.
So how did you come to know all of this, anyway?
I spent a month checking out the councilman's house, casing the joint.
I do my homework.
Just when I'm ready to make a move, the killer beats me to it.
Fifteen minutes later, I look in the window and they're dead.
Worm food.
And, well, I figured I might be able to blackmail the murderer, so I followed him here.
This is all you really need to prove your innocence, Doc.
Know what I'm saying?
All you have to do is call the police and tell him after that
We should go somewhere sit down relax talk over a drink about our future together as partners
Hey
Stop what are you doing? What do you want to talk to him for what?
Did you miss the part where he murders people man? What is he thinking looking for trouble like that? I'm out of here
However, a cash cow like him is a rare opportunity.
Damn, I usually make it a rule not to stick my neck out, but...
(ominous music)
- Hey.
Another hot afternoon, isn't it?
- I, I'm actually looking for someone.
- Hey, Doc, you alive in there?
- Doctor?
What are you doing?
He's got a gun, dummy.
- Mother and I,
We often used to go walking together.
On summer afternoons, a lot like this one,
there was a long road we took,
and alongside it a field of sunflowers,
but Mother's dead now.
This is important, so I need you to listen.
Did someone ask you to use that gun?
Tell me, was it a man?
Was it a man? It was.
One day, this young man came up to me at a local bar.
And was he about 20 years old, with blonde hair?
- Huh?
- He was, and he had a big, bright, beautiful smile.
Called himself Eric.
- So he's going by Eric now.
- We met a few times,
and we eventually became very close friends.
He invited me over to the place where he was staying.
It was the estate of Councilman Springer.
- Did he live in that mansion until recently?
- Yes, he did, for a year, in fact.
He said they took good care of him.
He was like a son to them.
- Wait a minute, I had my eye on that house for a month
I never saw anyone who looked like that.
They were a wonderful family.
I have a picture.
The councilman, his wife, and me.
However, there was something I couldn't forgive them for.
There was a beautiful area on their property,
a bed of sunflowers in their yard.
But one day the councilman cleared it all up
in order to build a bigger driveway.
So when I mentioned to my young friend
that I thought it was awful,
I was delighted to discover he agreed.
Are you saying you actually killed them because of some flowers?
Hardly. There was more to it.
He also told me Councilman Springer had a mistress.
That's when my friend looked at me and said,
"I've decided I no longer wish to live with or be a member of the Springer household.
From now on, I'm not a part of that family anymore."
Then he proceeded to request of me that I erase the family.
Having a mistress is so inexcusable.
My mother was someone's mistress, too.
She was a kept woman, you know.
Listen, listen. Don't think about all that stuff.
By the way, do you know where the safe is in that house?
I believe on the second floor in the library.
All right, then.
Doctor, you probably shouldn't stick around here.
You can erase your past. Did you know that?
If you don't like it, you can erase everything.
You can erase all of it.
You can reset your entire life if you want.
Sorry, I don't agree with that at all.
You may try to forget, but no one can simply erase their past like that.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Huh?
I wonder why I thought that.
It doesn't make any sense to me now.
Why did I think I could erase the past by pulling the trigger?
I did what he asked me.
I think you should go now.
Our talk is over.
I have nothing more to say.
Oh, that's right.
Your name is Dr. Tenma, isn't it?
He left a message behind for you.
Do make sure you take a good look at it.
You'll find it in the councilman's library.
He predicted that you would come here and he was correct about that.
Eric also mentioned to me, your fate has already been decided for you.
So has mine.
Doctor!
I told you, didn't I?
Did you actually shoot this guy?
Oh, suicide. I gotcha.
What the hell?
What's the use in dying?
Everything's over when you're dead. It makes no sense.
Hey, Doc, there's nothing like living, am I right?
You know, I think I actually agree with you for a change.
Hey, what exactly do you mean for a change?
Anyway, so you're after this killer named Johan or whatever?
I don't get it. I really don't know why you'd do that.
Hey, why don't you forget about this nonsense and team up with me?
Oh, by the way, I don't know why,
but when I tried to open the door to this room before,
it kind of gave me the creeps.
Hmm?
What the...?
What's the matter? You're shaking like a leaf, Doc.
Look at me. Look at me. The monster inside me is getting bigger.
Johan, this... this is all just a game to you, isn't it?
Hey, Doc, wait up!
Oh, come on, wait! Listen to me! Hey, Doc, I'm talking to you!
Oh, for crying out loud!
I've got some really good news to tell you. You're gonna thank me for this.
You'll keep your promise and team up with me, right?
I never said I'd team up with you.
Hey!
I just thought you might need some money to run from the cops, but I guess I was wrong.
Just get in the car.
This is our first client.
The nice man will escort you to your patient, Doc.
I'll hang on to your things for now.
If you want them back, you'd better do your job, get paid the rest, and meet up with me
at Frank's Tavern on Graston Street.
So long.
Now, get out there and earn your keep!
Now, that's what I call a profitable business.
Since I already got an advance, I suppose it's time to go and have a drink.
Hey, Counselor. I brought back a doctor for you.
Thank you for coming, Doctor.
Hurry. Please stop the bleeding.
It appears your auxiliary artery has been damaged.
Did you get hit by a shotgun?
Yeah.
Hey, the doctor is empty handed.
Did you get the surgical equipment?
No.
It was too dangerous in the city.
I couldn't get that far.
I couldn't operate on you here even if I had the proper equipment.
He needs to be taken to a fully equipped hospital.
I already would have done that if I'd been able to.
Save him already!
About how long ago was he wounded?
Four hours ago, huh?
Were you involved in the terrorist attack this morning?
And what does it matter if it were?
I won't do it.
What the hell'd you say?
I'm not helping people who took others' lives indiscriminately.
You shut your mouth!
Do you realize the situation you're in right now?
Either you help 'em or you die!
Calm down, Carl.
Our friends will be coming to help us soon, so it's simple all you need to do is stop the bleeding to buy me some time
What the hell do you think you're doing do you want to die I already told you to calm down yeah, but
Counselor no you listen to me very carefully my life is in this doctor's hands right now
if I die
Then you can shoot him
Oh, yeah
We're not running a charity, you know, you owe us so you got to pay back the
250,000 marks we lent you simple as that Otto heckle, but mr. Gloss. I want to pay you back, sir. That's nice
I'm glad you feel that way. I'll consider it
Now go on ahead and break both his arms
That's a good boy, I just need you to give me one more month
- Break both his legs, too. - Ah-ha-ha!
Witnesses have helped police identify the main suspects.
They are Max Steindorf and Carl Blum.
- Oh, please, please wait! - The G.W.E. is offering 300,000 marks
for any information leading to the arrest of the terrorists.
- Wait a minute, it's them. - Huh?
I can pay you back that money. I know where those guys are.
I really do. And that'll take care of what I owe you.
This had better be the truth.
Otherwise, I'm gonna break your scrouny neck.
Hey, would I lie oh
Man that's right. I forgot time is still with those guys. Oh, well, who cares?
You called me a murderer who goes around killing people indiscriminately
Well, you're wrong doctor what I did had meaning there was a good reason for what I did
Now that the president of G.W.E. is dead, I can finally die in peace.
I really don't mind. I achieved what I set out to do.
Counselor...
I used to be a lawyer in East Germany, and my friend here was a political secretary.
And when the wall came down, we lost our jobs.
Doctor, do you have any idea what it is like for us?
After the wall fell, G.W.E. came to the east with their big funding.
They barged in and built these factories on our land.
One after another.
That was our country, our land.
They had no right to do that.
They stepped all over our pride.
Well, I'm proud to have shot that bastard.
I'm glad that I did it.
- Counselor... - It's cold. I'm cold.
Hang on. Just hang on. Our friends will be here soon.
They won't come.
I have a feeling that our friends won't be joining us.
Stop the bleeding! Now, Doctor!
Hurry or I'll shoot you!
Don't do it!
I don't want to die.
Are you afraid? Are you afraid of dying?
Well, now you know what they all felt like.
The twelve people you killed, that's how they died.
This is what they went through.
Now do you know what it means to kill someone?
Get scissors and disinfectant.
Is that too much to ask?
Arterial bleeding's pretty bad.
He's in a state of shock from low blood pressure.
I can keep my hand pressed against the wound to stop the bleeding.
I'm gonna have to suture the open flesh here.
Needle and thread.
We don't have that.
Fine, then a stapler will do.
What? A stapler?
Just go and get it!
Yes, sir!
(eerie music)
- All right.
- What, what do you think you're doing?
- I've done what I can.
He needs to get to a hospital.
- What, a hospital?
If you don't put him down right now, I'll kill you
Pull the trigger if you want, but if you kill me know this you're gonna have to carry him to the hospital yourself
put me down right here just save yourself i just realized i've seen your face somewhere
You're the doctor wanted in connection with those serial murders, aren't you?
Put me down, damn it!
What I did this morning was not an indiscriminate attack.
The men I killed were the president of G.W.E., his lackeys, and his bodyguards.
And they all had it coming.
So you're telling me there were no innocent victims in that shooting?
You're talking about that girl at the newsstand.
You already knew about her then.
You knew you shot that girl, didn't you?
Why did you bother saving a man like me?
It wasn't because you were afraid to get shot.
You weren't afraid to die.
I could tell by the look in your eyes.
So why did you do it?
Why save a terrorist like me?
Why would you even bother?
Because I believe in you. I have faith in your humanity
You should get going the police will be here soon you hang in there
You too, you are truly a great doctor
And the money? What happened to the money? Hey, Doc, don't tell me you fixed him and
just left without getting paid.
...responsible for the Erfurt Station attack were apprehended by police earlier this morning.
Why don't you say something? Come on!
The two alleged suspects surrendered to authorities quietly and without incident.
Hey! We ain't operating no charity outfit here, Doc!
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)