Well, well, you certainly have found an excellent piece of property.
It's only a 20-minute drive to the center of Berlin, perfectly situated in a convenient and lovely neighborhood.
It's rare to find a unique property of such caliber, especially on the east side.
I can only imagine. If I'm not mistaken, wasn't this the residence of Mr. Liebert, the former head of commerce of East Germany?
What? You're not a buyer. You just came to investigate Mr. Liebert. Is that all?
Please forgive me, but I just need some information.
I don't know anything about an official who died almost ten years ago.
Apparently, Mr. Liebert and his wife adopted fraternal twins during the time that they were here.
I told you, I don't know anything.
Well, who owns the property? Can you direct me to them?
A lot of the property in former East Germany used to be owned by Jews who had to flee during the Nazi regime.
In some cases, the government ended up borrowing land from people on the West Side or in other countries.
The owner of this property is overseas.
Besides, my company is a West Side real estate firm that entered the Eastern Market after the Wall fell.
We don't know anything about the past.
Now, if you could please hurry and leave, I'm locking up.
Isn't there anyone who might remember?
Could there possibly be someone who knew the Lieberts?
Like I already told you, this was a residential area where many high-ranking officials lived.
Most of them fled soon after the wall came down.
Especially the official from the Ministry of the Interior.
Come to think of it, an ex-official from the East German Department of Commerce lives about ten houses away.
Yeah, I remember Mr. Liebert.
I'll never understand why he decided to take such a risk if only he'd waited just a little longer until East Germany collapsed
It makes you wonder why he went to a free country only to be killed in the end. It's a damn shame
Really? Do you remember if mr. Liebert had children twins perhaps? Did he have twins you say hmm? Oh
Yes, that's right
Mr. Liebert adopted those twins from the orphanage. Are you sure that's right
Those two were such cute kids.
Mr. Liebert always did talk about wanting children.
- Which orphanage was it?
- Which one was it?
Hmm.
511?
Yes, that's right.
I believe they came from 511 Kinderheim.
- I'm sorry.
511 Kinderheim?
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
(birds squawking)
They're planning on turning this old orphanage into a supermarket sometime soon.
About time.
Thank goodness they're finally going to destroy this creepy building.
Excuse me, ma'am.
By any chance, do you know anyone from this place?
The orphanage?
Everyone from there is long since gone.
Remember not to talk about it. It was such a tragedy.
Uh, but I...
If you want to find out more about it,
there's a former official from the old Ministry of Welfare named Hartmann over on 47th Street.
Hello there. Do you know if a man named Hartmann lives around here?
Wait, what's wrong? You're injured? Let me take a look.
Don't be afraid. I'm not going to hurt you.
You re-injured an old wound. It's infected, but this should help.
Atta boy. I know this stings, but it'll help you get better.
There you go, all done.
Be careful, okay?
You might get hurt again.
Hartmann.
After the fall of East Germany,
I became the foster parent to all those kids you see photographed up on the wall.
Foster parent?
Yes, well, it just means that I took care of them until they were adopted or eventually able to go off on their own.
The boy in the middle was adopted by the president of an accessories company,
and the last one on the left is enlisted in the army.
I still have one left in my care right now.
It must be hard work for you.
To tell the truth, I wouldn't call it work.
As the district official for the Ministry of Welfare,
I worked for many years dealing with orphans,
and I was adamantly against the way the government handled them.
After the fall of socialism, I thought I'd try doing things my own way.
I couldn't do any worse.
Of course, it isn't easy, and I don't have many resources,
but it's far better than the way they were living in that orphanage,
if you can call it that.
The Ministry of the Interior and the Ministry of Welfare ran 511 Kinderheim as a special orphanage.
Well, all these German orphanages were pretty severe places to be.
But these special orphanages were particularly notorious.
It wasn't just an institution for children with nowhere to go.
It was the place where children of criminals and political prisoners or suspected dissidents were sent.
humane cruelty were part of everyday life for the children there. Those poor
unfortunates were defenseless and couldn't do anything about their
situation. Ironically, it was a contradictory clash between socialism
and totalitarianism. The government claimed they were re-educating them to
be good citizens, but in actuality, behind closed doors and away from the public
eye, those helpless children were treated like criminals, even worse than
and instructors were absolutely terrible.
The worst of the bunch would confiscate care packages
sent to the children and sell them for their own profit.
Who then were the real criminals, I ask you?
Fear and violence ruled the daily lives
of those poor children in those special orphanages.
You can't raise normal people that way.
And then one day, that incident happened.
- Incident?
What exactly do you mean by that?
You said that you wanted to ask me about the twins, didn't you?
Yes, that's right. Can you tell me anything at all about them?
I don't know much about the girl, except that she was left at an orphanage in a different district.
But the boy... I'll always remember the brother, Johan.
Johan? Yes, please, tell me whatever there is to know!
What happened? They kept everyone from finding out?
The East German government placed a strict gag order on it.
Well, it is in the past now, so I suppose it's all right.
I guess there's no harm in talking to you about the incident.
Sir, what are you talking about?
I need to know.
What'd Johan do?
He led an uprising.
I'm home.
Dieter, we have company. Come here and say hello to him, why don't you?
Oh.
Dieter, where are your manners? Well, are you going to greet the man or not?
Oh, it's okay. We already met earlier out in front of the building. Remember?
Please, continue, Mr. Hartmann. I'd like to hear more.
No, I'm sorry, I can't. Not in front of the child.
Uh, understood.
Well, it's late. Can we continue this another time?
Dieter.
Maybe you'd like to stay and have dinner with us?
Sure, if you don't mind.
"Mr. Tenma, you say that you're a freelance journalist.
Does that mean you're going to write an article about the things we've been talking about?"
"Eventually."
"When you do write your article, please be sure to emphasize this.
The moral development of a child all depends on the adult that raises him.
It is essential that we encourage every child to follow the proper path.
If we do, they'll be able to achieve their dreams and have a happy life.
Dreams, huh?
Hey Dieter, what are your dreams?
A soccer ball.
Huh?
I want a soccer ball.
I see.
Thank you for dinner.
I was hoping we could continue our conversation another time.
Of course. I am sorry we couldn't finish it up tonight, Mr. Tenma.
I'll be back. Perhaps I can come by tomorrow.
Well, Dieter...
(eerie music)
- Hey.
Hello, I'm sorry.
May I still make a purchase?
Mr. Hartman? It's me, Tenma.
Mr. Hartman?
Mr. Hartman! Mr. Hartman, what's wrong? Please, open up!
Mr. Hartman, I...
Mr. Tenma!
Dieter! What happened to him?
He was playing. He was standing on a chair and he fell.
Oh, my dear Dieter.
It hurts. Oh, it really hurts.
Where, Dieter? Where does it hurt?
It hurts everywhere.
Mr. Hartmann, call an ambulance, quick!
All right.
Dieter, let me take a look.
Look! My God!
What are all these bruises?
Does this hurt?
What about here?
Two of your ribs are fractured.
And also, your shoulder is dislocated.
How did you get this injury from falling off a chair?
The ambulance is on the way and should be here soon,
so everything's going to be all right.
Good. But where'd these bruises come from?
Everything's alright. You can leave now, Mr. Tenma.
But...
Your hands just now, it was like you were examining him.
It's as if you were a doctor.
Uh, well...
Tenma, I thought I heard that name somewhere before.
You are a doctor, aren't you?
The one wanted for murder.
These bruises...
Just how did he get these bruises all over his body, huh?
You shouldn't worry about the boy.
You've got your own problems, don't you?
The police are on their way, along with the ambulance.
Mr. Hartman, what really happened to Dieter?
How did he get all of these injuries?
What's it matter to you?
I mean, you're the one who's wanted for murder, Doctor.
You're very short-tempered.
Just like a fugitive.
You did this to him, didn't you?
What do you mean?
You're the one who's been abusing Dieter all this time, aren't you?
Abusing? Why, I'd never do such a thing to an innocent child.
Right, Dieter?
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm taking Dieter to the hospital.
First murder, and now kidnapping, too?
Don't move!
The police will catch you, eventually.
It's okay, Dieter. We'll be at the hospital soon.
I'm scared. I'm scared of the hospital.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
The doctors will take good care of you.
But Mr. Harmon is always the one who took care of me
every time I got hurt before.
What?
What are you telling me?
You're completely covered in scars and bruises
and you've never been to a hospital?
I'm scared.
"The world is full of bad things. That's why I have to become stronger."
"If I'm gonna fight all the bad things, I have to become stronger."
"Is that what Heartmon told you?"
"The world is dark. The future is bleak."
"That isn't true."
"The world's not a dark place. That's a lie."
"Really?"
"Yes, really."
I almost forgot this soccer ball is for you tomorrow will be a good day I promise
I'm sorry for coming so late thank you nurse it's all right but the ER is pretty busy at
the moment it might end up being a while before we can treat him can't you move him up at all
There was a very big accident
So we need to ask the truck driver about the circumstances of the accident he broke both his legs, but he can still talk any
We have to treat him first
You can question him after we're done. All right, then we'll wait right here until he's ready. I see
I'll be back in two hours. What please just do what you can to take care of the boy
and
Whatever you do, please be sure not to let anyone else take him away
I will be coming back to get him. I owe you one.
Uh, but sir...
Is the accident site cleaned up yet?
No, traffic's still backed up.
Okay, what should I do now?
First, what to do with Dieter?
Even if I call the police, I can't go with him.
I don't know much about the girl,
except that she was left at an orphanage in a different district.
A different orphanage. Wait, that's it!
There's a child that you want me to take in?
Well, are you the child's parent?
What are you doing coming here at this hour?
I'm sorry, I know it's a strange request, but this child needs you.
Look, I understand that the child is being abused,
If you don't know who you are, then how can I...
Well, I... I just...
I can't take in a child from a suspicious person who won't even identify himself.
Wait! Did Anna Liebert live here with you at this orphanage by any chance?
Hold on a second.
Are you saying that you know Anna Liebert?
That's right. So you do remember Anna?
Yes, of course I do.
How is Anna? Is she doing well for herself?
Yes. She's currently taking classes at Heidelberg University.
Really? Then I guess she's doing very well.
Anna was such a nice girl.
I heard she was adopted by Mr. Liebert of the Commerce Ministry,
along with her twin brother... Oh, dear.
What was his name again?
Johan.
That was it. His name was Johan.
They were truly very close.
I felt so sorry for them when they had to be separated,
but they had to be placed in different orphanages.
Before the two of them arrived here, they only had each other.
They were truly alone in this world.
They were found walking hand in hand near the border of Czechoslovakia.
Just the two of them, shivering all alone in the cold.
At first, Mr. Liebert was only going to adopt Johann,
but Johann wouldn't go anywhere without his sister.
There was no separating them.
Thankfully, Anna was able to live a happy life because of her brother.
I heard that the conditions in the orphanages in East Germany were pretty terrible.
Not all orphanages were like 5-1-1 Kinderheim.
Inga, dear, the bathroom is the other way.
Down the hall, okay?
It's all right, it's all right. There's nothing to be afraid of.
Now you can go to the bathroom by yourself, can't you?
These poor children have never really felt the love of a parent.
In order to develop as a person, the only thing you need is love.
The orphanages of the East Side were truly horrible places for the children to grow up in.
Everything was so impersonal, even this place was only known by the number 47.
You'd better believe we did everything we could do within our power,
so that we wouldn't be controlled by the government.
We weren't going to be another 5-1-1 Kinderheim.
It was a special orphanage controlled by the Ministry of Welfare and the Ministry of the Interior.
Do you know what that means?
Uh, no.
The reality was, it was the Ministry of the Interior's pet project.
East Germany was using that place for experimentation...
on the children.
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]
you