Petra! You're going in for a check-up, and that's final!
I told you to stop wasting your time coming here!
Yeah, well, if you'd open the damn door right now, it wouldn't be a waste of my time!
Nobody asked you to butt in!
You're as stubborn as an old mule, you know that?!
Look who's talking, you quack!
I've never been to a doctor in my entire life, and I'm a healthy woman!
A very healthy woman, as a matter of fact!
Now, leave me alone!
Oh, no!
by you? Doctor! We got a problem! Dr. Schumann! Yes, what is it? It's a drunk, think! He
got hit by a car out on the highway! What? When you left him, was he still awake? I'm
not sure, but some guy was treating him when I left. Huh? Somebody who just happened to
be passing by, I guess. Some passerby?
So, mind telling me what happened here?
I told him you were out doing house calls,
but that man insisted.
Oh, he insisted, did he?
I'm so sorry.
I tried to stop him,
but he said he needed to take emergency measures
because the patient might choke to death.
Hmm.
Well, who did he say he was?
I don't know.
He never did tell me his name.
Oh, he did write something on the chart, though.
Hmm the patient kept pleading with me not to bring him to this clinic because he said he had no money to pay for a
doctor
Please take this to cover any medical expenses
Bastard, who does he think he is?
Doctor, where are you going? This fellow? What did he look like?
He was an Asian man, and he had a little boy with him
Doctor what about mr. Fink? There's nothing more I can do for him
But that man only took emergency measures to prevent choking.
Yeah, emergency measures my eyes.
That stranger patched him up perfectly.
[MUSIC]
Listen, Dieter, you can't keep following me around like this.
It isn't going to work.
I can never stay in just one place.
And you can't go to school like this.
You won't make any friends.
I have a friend.
And who is that?
It's you.
That isn't what I meant.
Was it you?
Huh?
Well, were you the one showing me up in my own clinic?
Keep your damn money. Maybe I'm just a country doctor, but I take care of my own
I would never stoop so low as to charge that poor drunkard for treatment
Sir, I just you're probably some big-city doctor out on vacation
I bet you're pleased as punch. You got to go show us yokel some charity
Hey, how's it going? Come on Dieter? Let's go
Don't you know it wait up?
- I'm not finished with you yet.
- I'm terribly sorry.
We're in a hurry, we have to get going now.
- Hmm, Fink got injured in a hit and run.
- Oh, you mean that guy who drinks too much?
- Yeah.
We're looking for any witnesses.
- Yikes, good luck with that one.
- Oh, hey there, Dr. Shuman.
So how's Fink doing?
- Looks like he's going to pull through.
I'm more worried about the bottle doing him in.
- Hmm.
- Uh, who am I? - Hmm?
- Dr. Chan.
We're alumni from the same medical school.
He figured he'd drop by the village while he's on vacation.
- Dr. Chan, huh?
Have you and I met somewhere before?
- He took care of Fink, actually,
since I was out making house calls.
Good thing he was here, yes, sir.
Speaking of house calls, guess where I went again today?
- Where? - Heinz, isn't it obvious?
I'm talking about your mother, Petra.
my mother you need to tell her to come down to the clinic right away there's no
telling what may be wrong with her without a checkup there's no way she's
too stubborn come on you know that woman won't listen to anybody she's your
mother stop acting so flip don't worry doc trust me mom's not gonna die that
easily what besides she raised me so what's left to do when it's time she
won't have any regrets what did you say bite your tongue Petra has plenty of
(car door slams)
- Why did you lie to him?
- Hmm?
Because I never would have made it to Fink in time.
No, he'd be dead right now
if you hadn't stepped in like you did.
- Thank you very much, sir.
- You turned white as a sheet when you saw Heinz.
How come?
Nevermind.
Least now I know you're not some hotshot doctor
from the city.
I'm in your debt, sir. I really do mean it. I don't know how I can ever pay you back
Is that so hop in the car? I've got an idea
Your splint is misaligned I'll straighten it this may hurt a bit but just hang in there
There you go, that should do the trick
Don't let me catch you not wearing that in the next two weeks.
Hey, Doc, I made some smooth apple wine, how about we drink to my new cast?
I think that's an awful idea, but I'll have a drink with you when the cast comes off.
You should be fine.
Five days and you can go back to the fields.
Good news, huh, Mr. Shono?
Doctor, why don't you take some potatoes?
We had a good crop this year.
I'll remember that offer when I come back some afternoon with a truck.
[laughing]
Thanks for the help.
My specialty's internal medicine,
but I have to be a jack of all trades out here.
I'm all the doctoring these folks get, and there's only one of me.
It's wonderful.
Yeah, tranquility's the one thing this place has in spades.
No, I didn't mean the land.
I mean how much you love all the people in this village.
how much they all seem to love you back.
Hmm. Love, huh?
That ship sailed a long time ago.
This is my job, and that's why I do it.
Well, one last stop, and you're a free man.
I saved the best for last.
You just don't quit, do you?
Quit? I don't even know the meaning of the word.
And it'll be the same thing no matter how many times you come back.
you quack like I'm talking to a mule Petra's the mother of that officer who
had you spooked she collapsed three days ago working in the fields I talked her
into coming down to the clinic but she changed her mind on the way over she's
been holed up in there ever since that is worrisome not to butt in but do you
mind if I try talking to her it's not gonna make a lick of difference I'll
Doctor, please, you have to calm down.
She'll never come out if you keep yelling at her like that.
You're getting a check-up and that's final!
I'm not going to stand the possibility of losing you!
Huh?
What I mean is, I wouldn't have anyone to fight with anymore.
Also, I wouldn't be able to eat that goulash of hers if that stubborn old thing passed on.
Hey, mister, how come your face is red?
What did you say, you little brat?
Please, Miss Petra, open the door.
Another doctor? Are you kidding me?
What did I say? It's a waste of time.
So tell me, why do you hate doctors?
Why do I hate doctors?
I'll tell you why.
You play God with people's lives. That's why.
God? Don't I wish.
Sometimes I think it would be great if we were.
We try our best, but we make mistakes, too.
Wouldn't it be great if doctors could be perfect like God and just heal people?
When I see my patients, it's always the same.
On the inside, I'm trembling like a leaf.
Please, Miss Petra, let me at least see you.
Huh?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hmm? What is it I'm smelling?
You're cooking up some goulash in here, aren't you?
Why are you asking? You like goulash or something?
I do, but it seems that Dr. Shuman is a particularly big fan of it.
At least, that's what he told me, anyway.
Well, that's news to me.
I always make it for him and he eats it, but he never says a word.
He's very shy.
This looks really delicious.
My goodness, my shoulders are so stiff
and I still have a lot of food to prepare for tonight's dinner.
Stiff shoulders.
Miss Petra, can you touch your chin down to your chest?
Of course I can. It's easy enough to do. Watch.
Oh.
Let me just check something, ma'am.
Four fingers wide.
So what was that all about?
Oh, uh, nothing.
how is she it isn't good a subarachnoid hemorrhage wait what did you say hey
Heinz the facts came in for a murder suspect make some copies is your mom
okay I heard that she had a fainting spell three days ago oh she's all right
yeah that tough old lady's gonna outlive all of us
The first stroke occurred less than three days ago.
We can still make it, but we need to operate immediately.
Can we get a helicopter here in time?
Can you do it?
Please.
If you can perform this operation, then do it.
If you can't, then my failings will have lost me the woman I love for a second time.
Are you sure that it's Kenzo Tenma?
Positive.
All right, he probably hasn't gone far.
Set up checkpoints along the highway.
If we catch this guy, it'll be big, Hines.
Yes, sir.
Prepare for emergency deployment.
This is great.
If things go well, I'll get promoted.
Hey, Hines, you have a call.
This is Hines speaking.
Oh?
The nurse from the clinic?
What?
Are you kidding me? My mother collapsed again?
God, why didn't I drag her into town?
If they had checked her at the state hospital, it wouldn't have come to this!
Dr. Tenma, you're the only one who can save her.
Just as I suspected.
It's an aneurysm of the middle cerebral artery.
Damn it.
We don't even have a surgical microscope or a craniotome here.
I can still do it, as long as I have an aneurysm clip.
No, it's too difficult.
We've got no other option here.
If the aneurysm ruptures, I'm afraid she's not going to survive the night.
It's my fault this is happening again.
What are you talking about, Dr. Shuman?
Those aren't the words of a man who's single-handedly taken care of this entire town.
I don't know what happened in the past, but you have to do the best job you can do right now.
That's all we as doctors can do.
Yeah.
(grunting)
- Hey kid, Dr. Shuman's inside, isn't he?
- Mm-hmm, he's operating right now.
- What do you mean he's operating?
Why are they doing it here at this clinic
instead of taking her to the hospital in town?
- Hey, don't worry, Tenma's in there helping.
- Tenma's in there?
- How's her blood pressure and pulse?
- Blood pressure holding steady at 126 over 84.
Amazing. He's so fast and efficient, even without the benefit of a craniotome.
Huh? What the hell are you doing?
We're operating on your mother. Isn't that obvious? What are you doing with that gun?
Put your hands up, Tenma! Do it!
If he stops now, she'll die. Is that what you want?
He's the one trying to kill her! Tenma is wanted for murder! He's a suspect in several killings!
he killed a man in Heidelberg and he's the prime suspect in the serial murders
of those couples who would have thought that I'd find you here leave it to good
old mom always looking for new ways to help out her boy now put your hands up
tenma if you don't I'll shoot like hell you will this is a sterile operating
room or it was until you came barging in do you want your mother to die of
meningitis because it's very likely to happen if you keep standing there then
She's going to die, Heinz. Don't you get it?
There's a subarachnoid hemorrhage in your mother's brain,
and she's had it for three entire days.
If we don't save her now, she dies.
Now get out of here, Heinz!
No way! I'm onto you, Tenma!
You're just planning on using my mom as a hostage so you can run away from here!
All right, nurse. Aneurysm clip and forceps, please.
Aneurysm clip and forceps, now!
Yes, that's my mother on that table. I won't let anyone hurt her. Yes Petra's your mother and you're her son
But what kind of son have you been to her these past five years? I know you didn't visit her once since you left for the
city
She sacrificed a lot for you. And what have you done for her in return anything?
Listen, son, the folks we love can be gone in an instant
Do you remember what your mother's goulash tastes like?
Even now, years later, Petra sets out a dish for you.
I should know. I'm the one who eats it.
Remember how delicious it is?
Dr. Tenma is fighting to save your mother.
He's giving it everything he's got.
So if you ever want to taste that goulash again,
you'll get out of here now!
See? Tenma's there.
It's okay.
Blood pressure 140 over 86, pulse 82.
Good. Her vital signs have stabilized.
Why don't you get some rest, Miss Pionier?
Doctor, you've been up all day.
What? Like you haven't? I'll be just fine.
Yes, sir.
You did well today.
Dr. Tanma, you should get some rest, too.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
You're fine. That was a grueling operation. You must be dead on your feet
I want to stay and make sure she pulls through that way when miss Petra has recovered enough
You can go ahead and finally propose to her
What do you mean propose?
Huh? Hey, I thought you were supposed to be asleep
I'm not sleeping not until I take him down to this station
What's he talking about? Anyway, you're not thinking about marrying my mom. Are you of course not?
me stupid. Even if I did, I'm not the kind of man who's worthy of proposing to anyone.
I used to work at the university hospital. Didn't give a damn about any of my patients.
All I cared about was moving up the ladder faster than the next guy. I got in good with
the director and ended up writing all his research papers for him. Would you believe
it? Even married the boss's daughter. What a cliché. Oh, I moved up that damn ladder
and ignored her like the wrong she was.
If only I had been a real doctor
or shown her the least bit of attention,
I'd have known in a moment.
- Huh?
- My wife came down with a simple cold.
At least that's what I wrote it off as.
If only I had looked at her, I would have seen it.
An intern would have seen it.
Severe liver failure.
Before she died, she said,
- I finally have your undivided attention.
I don't deserve to love anybody after what I did to that poor woman.
That's not true.
You have been paying attention, Doctor.
You've been watching over the people of this village.
Petra is going to survive this, because you were watching.
Do you still plan on taking this man to jail?
He did everything in his power last night to save your mother's life.
What kind of murderer would do that?
Heinz!
This is Heinz.
Get me the chief.
Chief, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
We should cancel this search.
The man I saw before was not Tenma.
He was another doctor by the name of Chan.
I thought it was him because he was Asian.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, sir, I'm very sorry.
The doctor from the state hospital sure did seem surprised.
Well, of course he did.
He probably never expected to see such amazing results
from a little clinic in the boonies.
Shuman! Are you really going to let that young doctor leave?
I was making him something to eat, but he packed his bags and left with the kid!
Tenma!
Don't go! This town is safe for you! There's no need to run away!
Dr. Shuman, what are you...
Dieter! This is a nice village, isn't it?
a very good place for a boy like Dieter here.
Yes, but not only for him.
You could stop running.
You'll be off the radar if you stay.
The folks in this village need more than I can give them on my own.
Together there's no end to the good we could do.
I can't.
I'm sorry, but I really have to be moving on.
But why?
Take care of Dieter.
He's better off here.
Tenma, wait!
I'm going with you!
Wait, Dr. Tenma!
Please!
save if you stay what's more important than that save countless lives before I
do that there's a man whose life I have to end what what are you
you can't mean that no dammit you're a good man tenma you fought like hell to
Why? You're not a killer!
It's no use.
Tenma's gonna go no matter what you say to him.
Go take care of him, Teeter.
If you stay with Tenma,
maybe you can keep him from going down the wrong path.
Go with him and look after him.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)