How many times do you plan on coming here?
You can ask me until you're blue in the face.
I'm always going to tell you the same thing.
Look, Councilman Boltzmann didn't have sex with that woman, that prostitute.
This had better be your last visit.
I would hate to have to take action against you.
Take action? Are you going to sue for defamation?
No, you wouldn't dare.
You're his secretary.
You wouldn't want Councilman Boltzmann's name to come up in a case like this.
uh inspector are you threatening me no of course not i simply want to know the truth of the matter
that's all
We'll be right back.
We'll see you next time.
I know he works for a hotshot politician, but man, that guy's not going to give an inch.
No, he'll come around.
Boltzmann's got a pretty good thing going here.
Why risk it all on some random prostitute?
The victim was no ordinary prostitute.
The names of countless politicians and businessmen were traced back to her.
Well, yeah, but there's only one person who claims to have seen them both at the same hotel.
Just because they stayed at the same hotel doesn't make them a John.
Have you decoded her client list for me?
Actually, we're still working on cracking that code. It's a lot tougher than we thought.
I'll do it myself. Just give me the disk.
Great. But don't you already have a bunch of other cases on your plate?
It doesn't matter. Give it to me.
Um, there's something I've been meaning to ask you for a while.
What is it?
Well, how do you find the time to sleep?
What does that have to do with the case?
Huh?
It's an irrelevant question, Detective.
Well, have you gotten the chance to talk to him?
It doesn't really matter when we tell him.
He doesn't listen. He stopped listening to me a long time ago.
I know. But the sooner you tell him, the better.
Keep it down. You're being too loud.
He's here, you know, working in his office.
Yeah? I wonder why.
Damn it!
Are you still trying to connect Councilman Boltzmann to the murder of that prostitute, Lungay?
Is there a problem with that, Chief?
Yes, there's a problem with that.
I'm getting all sorts of grief from the Ministry of the Interior.
You're just going to have to smooth things out like you usually do.
No! I can't unburn any more bridges for you. It's too big.
Do whatever you can, Chief.
Give me a break here, Lungay.
You're good, but you're only human. Sometimes you're gonna be wrong.
Are you gonna risk your entire career on a dead hooker?
Come on, do you need another feather in your cap?
Oh, God. Don't tell me you're doing this for the principle of the thing.
fame justice I'm not interested in either all I know is a woman was
murdered in cold blood I'm just interested in finding the killer nothing
else matters to me long day excuse me inspector you have a visitor got it huh I
I managed to figure out the encryption that she was using.
Use this formula to get all the names on her client list.
Oh. Um, that woman is here again, sir.
You know the one, Ava Heinemann?
Hey, you can't just come back here. We've been over this before.
When will Tenma be arrested? You have all you need.
It seems like you've been drinking quite a bit this morning.
Well, of course I've been drinking.
Just so you know, I've already figured out the case regarding Dr. Tenma.
Huh?
He insists that everything is the work of a man called Johan.
But this Johan is just another personality within Tenma's mind.
If you think about it, with this hypothesis, what seemed illogical now makes sense.
All we have to do at this point is just wait for the police to capture him.
So that means it's not your problem once you've got an arrest warrant. Is that what you're saying?
There are a lot of things I would like to ask him when we finally meet.
Dr. Tenma. What an interesting individual he is.
However, I have so many other cases piling up on my desk as we speak.
If you'll excuse me.
Don't you people ever let up?
I told you, Councilman Boltzmann has an alibi for that night.
An alibi? Of course he did.
The murder was a professional.
I'm sorry.
Are you honestly suggesting that my employer hired a hitman to kill that girl?
Ridiculous.
I've cracked the code on the list of clients of the woman who was killed.
Councilman Boltzmann's name was on that list.
You know, even if that were the case,
it still doesn't prove that he had her killed.
Right. Come to think of it, that's as far as we've gotten.
I'm sure you'll be in touch. Now leave.
We're dead in the water without a smoking gun, wouldn't you say?
Are you familiar with a publishing house called Shellhorn?
They're not a major company, but they stay in business by publishing tell-all books on famous people, like politicians.
They're known to play very dirty.
They hire unscrupulous women to build relationships with famous men in order to create scandals to write about.
If I were you, I'd watch out for people like that.
Check and mate. You should have seen it.
It was great. Boltzmann's guy just stared at him like,
What? Lungay is unbelievable.
Near as I can tell, all he does is work.
He's a robot, I'm telling you.
Man, I hear you.
The guy barely seems human to me.
Huh?
Oh, right.
Speaking of checkmate, there it is.
What the hell?
Hey, don't butt into our game, buddy.
You shouldn't waste your time with mind-numbing games.
It seems after a simple little threat,
the president of the publishing company chose to confess.
Write a report.
Right away.
Yes, sir.
here what do you think you're looking at it's that call girl's notebook it records the date
and time and other details of encounters with a certain client i can't really tell you the man's
name he's only referred to here by the initial b not to mention shellhorn publishing also made
arrangements with the woman to release her autobiography interesting don't you think
Oh, by the way, have you ever been in contact with a man named Yanker?
You may be aware that he is a professional hitman.
I want you to leave.
You get the hell out of here now!
We're moving out, both of us, right now.
level with me you never even noticed i was pregnant not even now did you are you going
to the man who fathered your child what do you care i bet you didn't even notice that
i was having an affair with another man did you
yes inspector it's me mintok baltimore secretary look i'll tell you everything
but you need to get over here right now please
Understood.
I have to go. We can talk about this later.
Inspector!
What just happened here?
The secretary! He committed suicide!
Councilman Boltzmann's an innocent man.
Not much of a suicide note, but that's all we got.
Lungay, I'm handing this one over to Inspector Kaminsky.
I'm giving him the Reichner Park and Gallen murder cases, too.
Given what happened, I think it's for the best.
So then, what am I supposed to do now?
Get your head together.
Then we'll talk about work.
Well, Dr. Tenma, it seems there's nothing left to distract me.
Uh, sorry, Inspector. You have a visitor? It's Eva Heinemann. I could tell her to come
back another day if, you know...
No, show her in.
I had a great time Eva how long until next time not sure babe maybe when I
return for my next business trip oh I don't want to give you back to your wife
come on stay all right I'll give you a call
No, you won't be coming back.
Not after getting in trouble for that perfumed handkerchief that I carefully placed in your suitcase.
You stupid bastard.
You were eavesdropping again, weren't you?
You must see all the different men I'm with, isn't that right?
Uh, no.
Well, what then? You want to join in the fun, is that it?
No, of course not.
You pervert.
You're wrong. I mean, I just...
I forget how nice it is.
It's beautiful. I really love this garden.
Looking at all this greenery helps me forget about the distasteful things out there.
Well, I'm so glad that you like it.
I'm going to plant some mimosas here.
And over there, I'm planning to put up an arch for your roses.
When summer gets here, it's going to be beautiful.
I'm wondering if maybe someone like you could be up to the task.
so what do you think do you think you can make me happy dad hey dad are you
listening to me dad huh oh how is my cooking today am I getting any better
you haven't heard a single word I said have you dad how come you're always
daydreaming I bet you that's why mom ran off with another man oh I'm sorry it's
- It's fine, really.
Actually, Coletta?
- Yeah?
- If Daddy found someone he really liked.
- Huh?
- Um, no, forget it, it's nothing.
My cooking is pretty awful, right?
Come on, tell the truth.
- It's not so bad.
- I see, not bad, huh?
Sorry for the trouble. You're a gardener, but I'm asking you to do all these odd jobs.
No problem.
My handyman kept asking for time off and then quit.
I'll do everything I can to help.
So, how about dinner tonight?
Oh, well, okay.
Why are you nervous?
Well, I'm not used to expensive restaurants like this.
If you want to be a man worthy of my company, you must be confident wherever you go.
Just pretend you're working in my garden right now.
Um, yes, that's right.
I do feel pretty confident when I'm out there working on something new in the yard.
I feel so satisfied when a garden turns out the way I envisioned it.
I just love being out there, you know?
People who like gardens can't be all that bad.
And you did say you liked that garden the other day.
Are you trying to say that I'm a good person?
Yeah, of course.
But you...
Well, go on.
You seem, you know, kind of lonely.
I'm not the only one.
I'm guessing that you're lonely, too.
Um, I'm sorry.
My daughter's probably worried about me, so I should get going.
Mm, Kenzo.
Kenzo.
It's almost Christmas, Coletta.
You should tell Santa he doesn't have to come this year.
Hey, come on, sweetie. Don't say things like that.
Dad, celebrating Christmas just the two of us sounds lonely.
Let's not do anything, okay?
Yeah, well, it might not just be the two of us
Celebrating this year, you know
The man you're looking at in those photographs ruined my life
Sorry, I was just cleaning up. His name is Kenzo tenma. He's my ex-fiancee
You're drinking again at this time of day. Well, of course I've been drinking
I just went to see Inspector Lungay of the BKA.
Can you believe that useless, incompetent inspector sent me away?
All I want to know is when they're going to arrest Tenma.
The BKA? Arrest?
He killed my father and then ran away!
Oh, he says he's innocent, but he's not fooling anybody.
My future should have been gilded in gold as the daughter of the director of a large hospital.
My three divorces? Everything is his fault.
And he blames the murders on Johan this is Johan with my father. Do you think that this child could kill anyone?
Is that really what tenma told you? It's utter nonsense
Have you ever shown this photograph to the police? Of course not. Why would I well, I don't know
It could be important evidence. Maybe tenma's the one who did it like Lungay says he has a split personality damn it
Then tell me, why do you still keep framed pictures of him like this around the house years later?
I figure deep down, you think Tenma is innocent.
You still have feelings for him.
You watch too many soap operas.
Out of all the men I've ever met, Kenzo satisfied the most of my requirements.
His position suited me.
He was an elite neurosurgeon who many considered a genius.
Besides, he spoiled me.
And best of all, he never contradicted me.
He just listened to my every single request.
Yes, yes, yes!
He was the man who always said yes to me!
That man could have made me the happiest person in the world!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Do you think I would ever be able to fill his shoes?
I'd be willing to tend your gardens for the rest of my life.
If that would help to ease your pain, Annie.
Don't flatter yourself just because I slept with you once.
You were just something to pass the time.
I was bored, that's all.
I was playing with you, and you fell for it.
You fool.
Who do you think you are?
Ava, you are truly a sad and lonely person
So are you
On Christmas Day, I'm having a party at my house with my daughter
You're welcome to join us
Wow, Dad, everything looks delicious.
Did you really make this all by yourself?
Yep, but I can't guarantee it'll be good.
But isn't this way too much for the two of us?
Do you think so?
Hmm?
Mom's coming home for Christmas, huh?
I'm right, aren't I?
-Well, aren't I, Dad? -Coletta.
It's Mom! She's home!
Char... Charlotta.
Mommy!
I'm so sorry, dear. I'm sorry.
♪♪
Who cares about mimosas
Or about roses
Or beautiful gardens
Or this whole damn estate
None of it means anything to me now
Just let it burn
Welcome back.
So, Inspector Lungay, you finally decided to listen to me.
I had some time open up, that's all.
This man was my only hope.
I must see to it that his life is ruined.
Or I can never be happy again.
© transcript Emily Beynon
© BF-WATCH TV 2021