[HORN HONKING]
[ALARM BUZZING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CHATTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
You're an unfamiliar face.
Get yourself a permit if you're looking to do business here.
Last thing I need is an unlicensed hooker.
Can't make as much cash when you're legal.
Yeah, good luck with that.
I just need permission from him, don't I?
Let me meet him.
I got no idea who you mean I'll keep coming back until I meet him
Until I meet the baby
That's all? Who leaves a kid with someone like me?
Gah! No way in hell!
Thanks a lot, Tem. I have to babysit?
I hate kids!
First he drops off the face of the earth,
and then he saddles me with some random brat!
Me and him had an agreement.
Doesn't that mean nothing anymore?
What the hell kind of doctor doesn't want to make some easy money?
- Here! - Huh?
Hey, nice header!
Son of a...
Did I look like I was ready to you?
Hey, remember what I said. You can't use your hands. That's a yellow card
I'm throwing this into traffic. If you mention the rules one more time, you keep talking like that. You'll get a red card
Why the hell are you so late?
Hurry up and give me the stuff!
Give me the stuff now!
Long time no see, Detective Messner.
Dr. Tenma, but...
That's right.
That's exactly what you called me back when we first met, before I even got around to
telling you what my occupation was.
But that was a long time ago.
My days in medicine are over.
But I suppose you're no longer a detective.
Detectives suspended on narcotics charges.
is. This article really came as a shock when I read it six months ago. Don't even think
about running away. I have a gun trained on you under my jacket.
All right, what do you want with me? I need answers. What happened in Heidelberg
almost a year ago? And who was behind it all? Who ordered you to do such a terrible thing?
I... I don't know anything.
You killed the Fordners and Mr. Mauer from the post.
It wasn't me that did it. I was hired as the lookout, that's all.
My partner Mueller, he did it. He killed all of them.
Detective Mueller also left the force soon after the murders.
Yeah, he did. I hear that he's very well off.
Turns out he's doing good with his money.
You, on the other hand, ended up wasting all of your money on your drug habit.
That sound about right?
He was the one who took on the job, and he was the one who committed the murders!
He ended up getting the largest portion of the reward!
They even tried to get rid of me!
They tried to kill me to make sure I didn't go to the cops!
I'm surprised you're still breathing.
It was the Organization that helped me.
Organization?
Enough! I already told her too much as it is!
"Told her?"
"Her who?"
"Ah!
Leave me alone already!
I can't...
I can't deal with you right now!"
"Looks like you're going through withdrawal.
And with me sitting here, no dealer would come within 20 feet of you, so I suggest you
start talking."
"Ah...
I...
I was...
I was saved by the baby!"
"The baby?"
"Go to a pub called Candy.
You can find him there."
"Where?"
Wait, who's this baby you're talking about?
He's a right-wing extremist.
He's also a high official in two of their major political parties.
After the Wall fell,
the baby tried to create a town of only pure-blooded Germans,
but his plan failed and now he's come back.
But why'd he do it?
Why'd he bother saving you?
The darkness.
After the Berlin Wall fell,
a great darkness was created a
monster a
monster was born a
Monster now leave me alone. I've already said everything to that girl. You understand what girl Messner?
She came for revenge and pointed a gun at me. She's the daughter of that older couple. We murdered you're saying Anna
Nina Fortner came to see you then
He said to me that I...that I was to send that girl to him if I ever saw her, or if she ever showed up around these parts.
He said that...that she's important to use as bait.
He's using her...as bait?
You don't give up, do you?
You're getting to be a regular coming back all the time.
How about I rent you for an hour or two so the night ain't a total waste?
You're the one who said I'd get in trouble if I did business without the baby's permission.
Well, we got ourselves a mouthy one!
Yeah, not so clever now, are ya?
Is this the girl who keeps asking to see the baby?
Uh, yes, sir.
It seems you're getting your wish.
Don't keep him waiting.
(crowd chattering)
- Please wait right here, miss.
Stand on that eye motif, if you'd be so kind.
[footsteps]
Directly over the iris, please.
Yes, much better.
[footsteps]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GASPS]
Now tell me, Nina Fortner, doesn't this song resonate with you right down to the soles
of your feet I have to dance the baby told me the day another Hitler is born
to us our country will be saved the girl will be the perfect bait for him
(panting)
- Nina!
- How is it that you know my name?
- That's the least of what I know.
You've also entered to the name of Anna Liebert,
but the former is just as false as the latter.
A rose by any other name does smell as sweet,
but they call me the baby, so I'm biased.
Come on, let's cut the rug a bit.
- Is it true that you know where my brother is right now?
- Ah, Johan, right?
Yes, you know don't you what are you going to do when you finally have your little family reunion?
I'm going to take him down
You shouldn't rip that out willy-nilly miss someone's liable to get hurt
Patience dear why I'm sure Johan is searching for you even as we speak
I lived around here when I was your age.
Know this place like the back of my hand.
There's a fella who buys antiques.
Gonna sell him this rug I stumbled across.
What do you mean? Don't you have any money left, Mr. Heckle?
Shut your yap already.
I'm hawking this rug so I can get the two of us something to eat.
I don't want to hear you coming up with...
Huh?
Son of a...
neighborhood mr. heckle what's wrong Turks this whole area is full of Turks
now hmm your so-called heirloom is a fake huh what are you talking about feel it
hand-woven silk you can't pick this kind of quality it's synthetic tell you what
I'll give you a hundred marks for it out of sheer sympathy ha more like sheer
Chicanery the German guy who had this place would have given me ten grand. Well, you can take it or leave it. Yeah
Don't you come crying to me when you realize my rug is the real deal
That one hanging on the wall is the real deal. Yeah, it's a genuine headache a rug
There's your hand woven silk. Look at the detail there in the patterns. It's perfect
150,000 marks
Yeah, you sure got took for a ride. If you really can't tell the good stuff from that crap. I feel sorry for you
We're out of here Dieter
Hey, I'm getting kind of hungry that rugs real, huh
It's a Hanukkah. Just like he said only a hundred and fifty grand
I could get eight hundred thousand for a rug as fancy as that. Come on
Shut up! If I can get my hands on that rug, we'll be able to eat anything we want.
How are you going to do that? What are you talking about?
I'm sure I'll think of something. Huh?
Don't give me that look. You're hungry, ain't you?
Whatever, thief!
What? Put a sock in it, you little brat! Jeez!
hold on a second where do you think you're going sorry but I'm not looking to buy that's
not what I meant are you crazy an Asian like you is gonna get killed if you walk into a
place like that they don't take kindly to foreigners in there but you're Turkish aren't
you is it all right for you to be doing business around here what are you stupid I wouldn't
Yes. A friend of mine was just abducted by a bunch of guys who are regulars there.
What?
It seems like she found out a secret of theirs.
A secret?
I don't know what it's all about, but I have to find her before something bad happens.
Who knows what they're going to do to her.
A woman I know is in there too. I have to get her out.
Who is she? What does this woman look like? Does she have long blonde hair?
Don't know. I couldn't tell you what she looks like now.
Because they just took a young blonde girl away in a car.
Where'd they take her?
Hey, how should I know?
But the baby was with them, so they probably went to his mansion.
The baby? What kind of car? What color was it?
It was big and red. I don't know.
All right, then. I've got to track down that red car before it's too late.
Wait. You have to do something to help my friend, too.
Please help her. She has a small baby.
If something happens to her...
Please!
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GROANING]
You're still alive?
This is my lucky day.
This way, please.
Without your gun, on this point, I'm afraid I must insist.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Go ahead and sit wherever you like.
So the baby brought you in, eh?
Eyes forward.
Let me see your face.
Goodness, but I should have known you'd be quite a beauty.
After all, you are Johan's twin sister.
My name is Professor Giedlitz,
and the man standing next to Johan
in the picture is General Wulf.
We created this organization along with a pair of other like-minded individuals.
Where are my manners? Would you care for some fruit?
No, thank you. I want to see Johan.
And see him you will.
Once he knows that you're here, no force on Earth could keep him away.
The boy suffers mightily in your absence.
You people don't know where Johan is either, do you?
We need him. His country needs him.
The four shall help him fulfill his destiny.
Do you have any idea how Hitler became possessed
of such power?
It's because he saw the three things a person
would have to do to gain control of a country.
Manipulate the banks, feed the war machine,
and take command of the military.
I'm sure Johann's working on one of those things
Or two. Really, it's a question of if, not when.
What exactly do you plan to do with Johan?
Think of it. Hitler bent a weakened nation to his will using nothing but raw charisma.
All that from a man who only made corporal.
A man whom art school wouldn't deign to let in.
His charisma appeared after he hit his thirties.
Not so with your brother, Johan.
He was a leader of men even as a mere boy.
Charisma of messianic proportions.
But even Jesus Christ had help.
Consider the three magi and John the Baptist
who heralded the Savior's arrival into the world,
how they readied the way for His glory.
Likewise, the four of us have been keeping track
of Johan's talents ever since he was a little boy.
Exciting, wouldn't you say?
What is it that you want with me?
Please, accept our hospitality.
Until Johan comes looking for you, at the very least.
Actually, I'm afraid I must insist.
You know too much for us to let you walk away now.
Don't worry about that.
I came here of my own volition.
I will wait here for Johan.
Then we agree.
Now then, you should at least try the fruit.
Good, you're finally awake.
Don't look so worried.
We're not going to hurt you.
Not right away, at least.
So what brings you to my little slice of the world, Dr. Tenma?
Wait, how do you already know what my name is?
Why don't you leave the questions to me?
Now all you have to do is answer.
were you snooping around I know you're looking for Johan but I can't figure out
why where are you keeping Nina I told you to leave the questions to me did I
not what are you gonna do with her why do you insist on me Nina is our guest
whereas you are just a meddlesome piece of trash to be disposed of so is she
- At the moment, but that'll change soon enough.
She's determined to kill Johan,
and we simply can't have that.
Always a shame when a pretty girl dies before her time.
- You're just using Nina as bait to draw out Johan?
What are you planning on doing?
Who the hell are you, pig--
- That is enough!
A person of impure race has no right to ask those questions!
Lesser races never know their place,
Which is why we're putting the Turkish Quarter to the torch!
The whole quarter?
Indeed.
The night sky tomorrow will be a thing of beauty,
a fiery cleansing.
If I stay here, then I'll find Johan.
[soft piano music]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[door creaks]
(footsteps)
- Please, help.
Help me.
- Who, who are you?
- Please, I beg of you.
- Okay, where are you right now?
- The third floor.
- It sounds like you're speaking with an accent.
Where are you from?
- I'm Turkish.
please I've got to escape they're going to kill me have you been taken prisoner
by the people here help me please I can't they're watching me closely I've
got to stay in here please help me escape I have to warn the others or my
baby will die too
tomorrow night we celebrate in honor of Johan's homecoming only the members of
of the pure master race like us deserve to survive.
Everything else should just burn away.
- I overheard them talking.
They're going to burn it all down tomorrow night.
They're going to destroy the Turkish part of town.
Help me.
Please help me.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]