Please help me escape I have to warn the others or my baby will die too I overheard them talking
they're going to burn it all down tomorrow night they're going to destroy the Turkish
part of town help me please help me they're all going to die if I don't warn them
(sobbing)
(choral music)
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- Hey, kid, where the hell are you going?
Come on. Give me a break leaving that rug in this town is a complete waste that guy doesn't know what it's worth
How many times do I got to tell you stop looking at me like that slimeball
Yeah, see if I care don't come crying to me when you're starving and I'm living like a king
And if you tell anybody about this you're gonna pay for you got that
Who would want to be friends with a dirty thief like him anyway, I don't need him
I'm so hungry right now.
There, there.
Don't cry.
Be a good boy.
Mommy's coming back soon.
I promise.
What's wrong?
Doesn't he have a mom?
Huh?
Of course he does.
What about you?
What are you doing sitting here alone?
You should go home to your mom.
Huh?
What's wrong?
- Wait a sec, you don't have a mom to go home to.
Hey, I'm sorry if what I said hurt your feelings, kid.
- It's all right, I've got Tenma.
- Tenma?
(Tenma growling)
Eat as much as you want, it's nothing special,
but don't feel like you gotta hold back.
So you were just sitting on those steps
waiting for that Tenma guy to come back and get you, huh?
That little guy's waiting, too.
Where's his mom? Why'd she leave? Where'd she go?
A bunch of bad guys came and took her away.
We gotta save her!
It's just so dangerous out there.
An Asian man I met said he was gonna try and help her,
but then he got hit by a car right in front of me.
An Asian man?
Wait, you said Tenma was Japanese, didn't you?
But there's no way it could be the same person, could it?
Where are they I've got to help them
The man who hired me he was a right-wing fanatic cool and sadistic
After he beat me I left but I forgot my scarf so I had to go back
That's when I heard him talking on the phone. I heard him say that I'm going to burn the entire town tomorrow
I ran away as fast as I could to warn everyone about the fire, but they caught me
Please you must help me
My baby! I don't want my baby to die!
Please, you must help me!
Who is it?
Professor Giedlitz has asked me to bring you some fruit.
Thank you very much.
The professor also asked me to deliver a message.
General Wolf will be here shortly and would like to meet with you.
You mean the man in the photograph with my brother?
That's right. General Wolf is the person who knows Johan better than anyone, probably even more than you do, even though you're his twin sister.
That's what Professor Giedlitz said.
Now don't go dying on me just yet. General Wolf's going to be here any minute.
And I want him to see what a wonderful job I've done of capturing you alive.
Wolf, you say?
That's general to you, do you understand?
You should search out a General Wolf.
He's the one who first discovered Johan and his abilities.
Receiving praise from General Wolf is an absolute dream come true for anyone.
Excuse me, sir. We've assembled our members and the arson teams ready to set fire to the Turkish quarter.
Shall we continue with the plan as scheduled?
I'm looking forward to dinner with a view of a beautiful crimson sky.
Be sure everything stays on schedule, otherwise my perfect dinner will be ruined.
And tell them that if anything goes wrong, forgiveness will come at a very high price.
Yes, sir.
He won't do it. Yohan isn't going to lead you.
You'll never be able to convince Yohan to lead your organization. Are you out of your mind?
"Yohan doesn't share your simple-minded views on racial purity.
He's not just an ignorant bigot like all of you.
He's different, don't you see?
He looks down on all humanity."
"SILENCE!"
"Well, well, what do we have here?
and a drink on me, I'm thinking the usual.
- Right away.
(laughing)
- Damn.
- Wow.
- Damn kid.
- Not bad for a little guy.
There's going to be serious trouble when he grows up.
That was disgusting. How can they drink that stuff?
This is Tenma's jacket.
Tenma?
Tenma, where are you?
(footsteps)
- Tenma?
Everything will be all right.
Just calm down.
I want to help you get out of here,
but I can't really do anything right now.
I'm going to sneak out of here,
and I'll warn everybody in your neighborhood.
I promise you.
- Oh, thank you.
- Tell me, what's the name of the street?
- Calvin Street.
And what's your name?
- My name?
It is Aishe.
I don't want you to worry about anything. Okay, I promise you your baby is going to be just fine. I'm gonna save you, too
Hang in there
Bless you. Oh
I forgot to ask your name Nina and when this is over. I hope we get to know each other better
Nina
I've had so many bad things happen to me since I came to Germany. You are the first good person. I've met
We are friends, isn't that right?
Mm-hmm.
Aishe, I forgot to ask you.
What's your baby's name?
Hey, Aishe.
Are you there?
What's happening?
Leave her alone!
Aishe...
(eerie music)
(gasps)
(panting)
(eerie music)
Tell me, is the man sitting in that chair Dr. Tenma?
Yes, it is.
And I captured him with my very own hands.
So, where is General Wolfe?
General Wolfe is waiting.
We'll be taking the doctor to him.
Huh?
What?
No, wait.
What do you mean?
But I wanted to show General Wolfe my prize catch and then finish him off myself.
What do you want me to do with this kid?
I found him walking around downstairs looking for Tenma.
Is this a friend of yours?
No, of course not. That child has nothing to do with this. Just let him go.
You don't really expect me to take a filthy street urchin like this to General Wolf, do you?
Dispose of him.
He's just a boy!
You heard me. Finish him off. Go ahead.
Got the little brat already. He bothers me.
Yes, sir.
Stop! No!
It was one of my men!
My apologies, Doctor. Please forgive us for the rude treatment you've received.
It's very important to General Wolfe that you be treated as his guest.
Poor Aishe...
Please, help me escape, I have to warn the others or my baby will die too.
We are friends, isn't that right?
Yes, we are, Aishe.
We are friends.
What happened here?
Professor Kievlitz...
Everybody's... everybody's dead...
We should be arriving at General Wolfe's mansion momentarily, Dr. Tenma.
Tell me, is Nina going to be there?
Yes, you can rest assured.
She is also considered to be a special guest of General Wolfe.
What about the Turkish lady, the baby's mom?
I don't know. We don't know anything at all.
We simply follow orders and nothing else.
We gotta go back to town.
Calvin Street is going to burn tonight. We gotta go back.
The lady who gave me dinner last night and the baby are going to die!
They're all going to die!
Be that as it may, young man, I can't let you go.
We must take you to General Wolf's mansion.
Pull over now.
All right!
Think you can make it to the Turkish quarter on your own?
I'll be there soon, but right now it's important that I go with these men.
But I...
You can do it. I know you can.
able to save everyone on Calvin Street. Go on, hurry! From here you should be able to
get to the city in thirty minutes. I apologize, but I had to do that. I had no choice. Now
I know you trusted me enough to give me back my gun, and I may have just broken that trust,
but it didn't seem like you were going to stop otherwise. It's fine. I'm sure General
General Wolfe will be pleased to know that you don't just carry your gun around for show
and that you're not afraid to use it when needed.
If you would please follow me.
Where's Nina?
I want to see her.
She is here, isn't she?
Patience.
Before we do anything else, we must see General Wolfe and Professor Giedlitz.
I just need to know for myself that she's safe.
Professor Giedlitz is dead.
And it's not just Giedlitz.
All of his men have also been killed.
We've disposed of the bodies.
Everything's been taken care of.
What about Nina?
When we first arrived with General Wolfe,
we searched the entire mansion.
She was nowhere to be found.
You're Dr. Tenma, correct?
Wait, do I know you?
You wouldn't recognize me, even if you saw my face.
I don't recognize me, but people call me Wolf.
Wolf? That means that you...
You don't look anything like the picture from ten years ago.
That's because...
Fear has aged me.
Sir, please hurry. Can't you go any faster?
You're crazy. I'm pushing 200 here.
There's no way. That speedometer must be broken.
There's no way I'm going to make it in time.
I think people's names are very interesting, mysterious even.
All the places I've been throughout my life,
Everybody has referred to me as "Wulff".
On the other hand, every time I encounter someone new,
I must tell them that my name is "Wulff".
I wonder, how can they really know that is me?
What's there to prove that I really am "Wulff"?
You're the one who found Johan and his sister, isn't that right?
I did. It happened twelve years ago.
And that's when he was sent to 5-1-1 Kinderheim.
They were going to turn him into a super soldier, weren't they?
But you had bigger plans for him.
That's correct.
He was supposed to become our country's savior before its downfall.
And now you're trying to make sure he becomes the next Adolf Hitler
so that he can lead the ultra-nationalists.
Isn't that your plan?
At the moment, I'm only part of this organization because it benefits me.
I did hear that the others are trying to make him into another Hitler.
I think it's a stupid idea.
Imagine, if a man like Hitler was able to take things as far as he did,
Johan could do more.
Yes, I was the one who gave him the name Johan.
We found the twins wandering near the Czech border.
They had managed to evade the heavy security patrol somehow.
They were dead on their feet,
malnourished and almost frozen to death.
When we finally arrived, the two of them simply collapsed.
They both would have perished
if we hadn't found them when we did.
I, too, know what it's like to have saved Johan's life.
When he regained consciousness, I asked him a simple question.
"How do you feel?" I asked.
And do you know what his reply was?
He said, "You will know very soon."
And now there's no more proof I really am Wolf.
All the people who knew me have disappeared.
My wife, children, siblings, relatives, friends.
Everybody from my life is dead.
All of them died, one by one.
The money I brought with me back from East Germany
is the only proof I have that my name is Wolf.
Because of Johann, I am a stranger to all.
You will know very soon.
Now I understand what he meant.
Loneliness.
Take a look at this.
Come to the abandoned warehouse of Hilden and Engel's company in Rombach.
Johan was here this morning.
He came here to slaughter Gielitz and his men.
Yet another person who knew me has been murdered.
I imagine Nina must have seen this and gone there to look for him.
Please kill him. I beg of you.
Calm down, kid. What are you talking about?
Calvin Street is going to burn tonight!
We have to hurry and tell everyone!
I can't believe this!
This is amazing! It must be my lucky day!
This is great!
Now I can grab that rug during the fire!
What a score!
How can you think that way?
Keep it down, you little brat!
about this I swear oh hey let me go listen kid I'm not just talking about
all those Turks okay if any of the right-wingers find out what we know
we're dead what you didn't notice all the guys with their freaking swastika
tattoos around here
I said...
One more question.
Was a Turkish woman being held hostage in there?
We found a dead woman on the third floor.
Based on what we saw, I don't think Johann killed her.
Looked like it was the work of Professor Giedlitz's men.
Well, General Worf, do you really think he'll be able to kill Johan?
I don't know. However, he still has time he may be able to.
What is this supposed to mean?
(dramatic music)
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]