She has a baby back there, and the Neo-Nazis are planning to burn the town!
A Turkish woman was found dead up on the third floor.
We're approaching the meeting place where Johan will be expecting you
I'm not sure what'll happen there
You do know how to use that gun, right?
Calvin Street, Frankfurt, now
Our plans have changed
Why the sudden change of heart?
What about killing Johan?
I'll deal with him later, now do as I say
General Wolf will be disappointed to hear this news
He personally requested that you kill Johan
He believed you were the man for the job.
I don't care. I don't take requests from anyone.
I'm gonna kill Johan of my own accord. Now hurry up and get to Calvin Street.
We'll be right back.
All ignition points are ready to go, sir. Awaiting your orders to proceed.
Well done. Time to celebrate our superiority with a little firepower.
Hyle!
Now.
What are we going to do with them?
These two are an insult to our race.
Unfortunately, these types do exist among us.
One is a thief, and the brat was trying to save the Turks.
They're both filthy scum. Purify them.
It's time to teach him a lesson.
This place is gonna burn anyway. Leave them for the flames.
Oh, come on, little one. Don't cry.
Your mama's coming back real soon.
I can't believe you're still alive
How'd you find me?
It's all thanks to Dieter
He told me that you lived in this building
Did you say Dieter?
So then it's true, you're that Tenma guy
He was talking to me about the other day
Where is Dieter?
Didn't he come by?
Uh, no
Then where'd he go?
Hey, have you seen Aishe?
This baby is Aishe's little boy.
He needs her. He misses his mom a lot.
It can't be.
No, it's not possible. I don't believe it.
What about this poor little child?
He's too young to be without a mother.
What am I going to do? What do I do?
She's the last.
There mustn't be any more victims.
I need to see the leaders of the Turkish quarter now.
So what does everyone think?
Set the town on fire, huh? Not likely.
We hear rumors about the right-wing extremists all the time.
We can't overreact every time they threaten us.
What's even more suspicious to me is this Japanese guy waltzing in here,
even though he says his life is in danger.
What's the matter with all of you?
Ayşe is dead. Don't you get it?
She was killed because she tried to warn all of us about this danger.
I wonder about that.
She was a prostitute like you, right?
You women go off with Germans all the time and end up missing.
That's nothing new.
You make all us Turks look bad.
How do we really know whose kid that is anyway?
You all know how hard it is to make a living.
You should know better than to act like this.
If you want to live, then you've got to listen to me.
Forget it! Do what you want!
You can burn and go to hell for all I care!
Now wait just one second.
Are you suggesting patrol groups?
Maybe we should do as this Japanese man says.
We have nothing to lose.
Mr. Denny's, are you really going to listen to some Asian we don't know?
He might be suspicious,
but there are certainly plenty of trustworthy Japanese people in the world.
General Nogi, for example.
General Nogi? Who's he?
You mean you don't know about him?
General Nogi was a brave Japanese man
who saved the Turkish Navy when they were lost in the Pacific years ago.
Oh.
Go ahead and gather all our men immediately.
It looks so delicious.
Let's dig in, shall we?
No need to be in such a hurry, ladies. Take your time.
We wouldn't want to finish eating before the entertainment.
I planned it so by the time the main course comes around, the show will be reaching its climax.
In the meantime, let's enjoy this 76 Chateau Latour I saved especially for this night.
the first dish we will indulge in is my favorite raw flounder with caviar
and as the feast begins oh voila the first fire what a wonderful start but like i told you that's
still just an appetizer where is the main course remember what i said don't be impatient
If you savor your dinner, my show will be something you'll truly enjoy.
Tell me where the main course is.
If that's an appetizer, then what are you going to burn for the main course?
We need more fire extinguishers!
We need to spread out. The rest of you men, come with me!
It's just as I thought. The flames started upwind.
This whole place could go up. Three groups, save the women and children!
My goodness, what a lovely surprise and what do we owe this honor don't even try it or kiss your boss
Goodbye put that dangerous thing away
Why don't we enjoy this meal together?
Unfortunately, it seems your appetizer is fizzling out
Don't worry that was just the beginning
This is your favorite, right
sorry about that don't be so contrary my dear you see after all this is a great celebration
in honor of johan listen to me johan doesn't want any of this oh and tell me how can you be so
certain i saw it with my own eyes i followed his messages i know what he wants johan doesn't care
about your plans so what exactly did you see you know he doesn't want any of this
don't you understand you're right okay relax calm down just take it easy I say
is dead because of you I won't let anybody else die tonight so where's the
main course what part of town are you going to set on fire
Take the injured to the shelters. I'll be right there.
Tenma!
Well, have you had any luck finding Dieter?
Someone told me they saw a kid who looked like him near the park around noon.
Dieter, my God.
Hey!
Shouldn't we go after her and try and bring her back?
No.
Let's just continue with my dinner as planned.
That girl sure is something.
I suppose it must run in the family.
Huh?
The look she had in her eyes.
She was really going to kill me.
It's a good thing she didn't realize how close I was to giving her the actual location of the main course.
Well, shall we bring out the next dish, sir?
No.
Well, get me some underwear first.
Scary girl, isn't she?
Hang on! I'll put it out!
You made it. You're going to be just fine.
Everything's okay, all right?
I got no idea who you are, lady, but thanks for getting us out of there.
How did the two of you end up here anyway?
Well, I...
You want to know what happened, lady?
This brat almost got me killed.
Forget this. I'm getting the hell out of here.
If that was the smallest fire those skinheads set, I wouldn't be a bit surprised.
I grew up in this neighborhood. I know the place like the back of my hand.
If I wanted to burn down the town, this wouldn't be the spot, believe you me.
This town ain't out of the woods just yet.
there were three other fires upwind that were also put out we can't thank you enough for your help
right everyone yeah if it weren't for you this all could have been a whole lot worse
our next step is to take care of the injured no i won't have any more victims not one more
wait what are you talking about well the wind's gonna change direction it always happens every
night around this time the wind just stops and it starts blowing towards town
from where the river is
the wind it stopped and now time for the main course to be served
Okay. That should take care of it.
Thanks for patching me up, Doctor. Let me buy you a drink.
What are you talking about? You have to take it easy for a while.
Oh, come on. Loosen up, Doctor. Right?
That's right. It's thanks to you we were able to put out those fires and save the neighborhood.
I bet those neo-Nazis are scratching their heads right now wondering what the hell happened.
No doubt they are. That'll teach them. Never underestimate the Turks.
Where are they tending to all of the other injured people?
The mosque by the river.
Hey, Dr. Tenma, take a break and relax.
Come on, why don't you have a drink with us?
Not until everyone's taken care of.
If all of the fires up until now were just diversions,
where do you think they're going to light the real fire?
How the hell would I know?
Who cares about this stupid town anyway?
Besides, there's something much more important on my mind
that I gotta take care of.
Wait, I need you to tell me, and I need you to tell me now.
Where would you start the real fire get your hands off of me like I already told you the winds gonna come from the river
The abandoned factory down there would be a perfect place for a fire
If I'm not mistaken, there should still be a bunch of chemicals in the warehouse
At long last something I can sink my teeth into
Yes, this is going to be delicious
We're right on schedule.
The celebration of the Master Race is about to begin.
It's you.
Why did you follow me?
Because I have to put out the fire. I made a promise to Tenma.
Tenma?
This is it. It's the warehouse.
Thank goodness. Looks like they haven't found this place yet.
These are all filled with chemicals?
If all of this were to go up, it'd be hopeless. There'd be nothing left of the town.
I'll protect this place no matter what. I'm not going to let those horrible people burn it down.
Are you okay?
I slipped. What the heck is this?
It smells like gasoline.
it looks like someone's there it's all right i'm fine i can walk on my own let's get you to
a shelter so i can have a closer look at it i twisted my ankle it probably happened when i
was trying to get away from the fire now that i finally got this rug who gives a damn about this
stinking town. I bet I can
probably get 800,000 marks for this
baby. No, a million!
Heckle!
What happened to Dieter?
Couldn't say. He's probably...
Where is he? Where'd he go? What happened to him?
Last I saw, he was
going to the abandoned warehouse by the river.
Why there?
The wind's gonna blow in from the river soon.
So if the chemicals in that warehouse
or set on fire it's all over for this town this is what I was talking about
tell everyone to evacuate from the riverside shelters right away go you're
going to take me there
who is it who's back there
Freeze! Don't move!
Can it be true? Are you really Johan's sister?
Put the lighter down now!
Once I set this trail of gasoline on fire, this warehouse is going to go up in an instant.
I'm going to shoot you in the head before that happens.
I can fire quicker than you can flick that lighter, and I'm not afraid to do it!
And what if you miss?
I haven't skipped a day of training in six months straight.
So I know I can hit you from here.
You don't frighten me.
Don't you know this is a celebration of the Master Race?
This is our big welcome for Johan.
But Johan doesn't want any of the things you want!
Yes, it's true that he was recently seen here in Frankfurt.
But the only reason he came was to kill one of your leaders and all of his subordinates.
He left a message behind, you know.
What message?
Listen to me. Johan is not the person you think he is.
The truth is much more complex than that.
What are you trying to say?
It's worse. It must be terrifying for him.
He's suffering. He's in anguish and teetering on the edge of despair.
you know i'm not so sure it's such a good idea to be making enemies of these guys
which way to the warehouse i didn't sign on for all of this
i'm gonna call it a day see ya where the hell do you think you're going are you just going to let
dieter die like that tell me where the warehouse is all right i'll tell you i'll tell you just let
me go you're choking me you told me about your friend you said that his name is tenma right
Would you believe that I know a man whose name is Tenma also?
For real? Is your Tenma really brave too?
Yes, but he must never fire a gun, not if I can do it for him
I don't want him to kill anyone, he's a good man
Killing people is always wrong, you understand?
Even if they're the bad guys?
Right, don't ever do what I'm about to do
Close your eyes, don't look!
Don't shoot!
Tenma!
Quick, Hekko! Put out the fire!
Use the rock! Hurry!
No! No!
NOT THE ROCK! NOT THE ROCK!
One million marks...
Gone...
Nina...
Tenma...
Damn it all, the cops are coming!
Get out! Go! I'll take care of things here. There's a boat over by the river.
Please, Tenma, you have to leave now!
My main course. It got cold.
Thank you for all your cooperation, young lady.
We'd appreciate it if you'd come down to the station.
Wait one second, okay? I'll be right back.
Hey, hold on!
Tenma!
Nina!
You have to promise me something, Nina!
Swear to me you won't kill anyone!
I saw it! I saw Johan's message!
I saw it, too! I'm heading there now!
Ten years ago, the night I shot my brother,
I finally know what he meant when he told me to shoot him in the head!
Now I understand!
Johan, he's... he's not alone!
There are two of him inside!
That's why, Dr. Tenma, it wasn't your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I must do it.
I have no other choice.
I have to shoot Johan again.
hey wait up what the hell are we doing here anyway come on let's get out of here
i give up there's no use with this guy i guess i'll be starving and broke forever
if only i still had that rug damn it
huh the hell's that supposed to be
"It's...a message...help...the monster inside me...is about to explode...what is this supposed
to mean?
He has a split personality?"
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
© transcript Emily Beynon