Hey, wait up! What the hell are we doing here, anyway? Come on, let's get out of here!
I give up. There's no use with this guy. I guess I'll be starving in Bro forever.
If only I still had that rug. Dammit.
Huh? The hell's that supposed to be?
"It's...a message...help...the monster inside me...is about to explode...what is
this supposed to mean?
He has a split personality?"
♪ I've got to be in this place ♪
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
Let's see if I got this straight.
So you told us when you arrived at the warehouse, you witnessed the Asian man and the arsonist
engaging in a verbal argument.
According to your statement, Anna, as soon as the Asian man saw you there, he quickly
fled.
So, Miss Liebert, is that exactly how you saw it?
Yes, sir.
Well, it's good that firebug ended up turning himself in.
He's a right-wing extremist, said he was celebrating his people when he lit the fire.
Anyway, Miss Liebert, your record's clean, so that's all we need from you today.
We do appreciate your cooperation.
So then you're saying that I can go home now, detective?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, hold on.
There's one thing I forgot to ask about.
The townsfolk refer to the Asian man you mentioned as Dr. Tenma.
Miss Liebert, you wouldn't happen to know anything else about this guy, would you?
No, I don't know anything about him.
Tell me, what are you thinking?
I'd say from the way Miss Liebert was dressed, she might just be a high-class call girl.
That isn't what I meant.
Huh?
I'm talking about Dr. Tenma.
When we first spoke to the Turks from that district,
all of them referred to our Asian guy as Dr. Tenma.
But as soon as we told them the doctor was under investigation
and suspected to be a serial killer,
they got real tight-lipped.
All of the sudden, none of them knew who he was.
They told me I'm responsible for you now.
Yana, it's so great to see you. I was worried about you.
When you left town, it was just so sudden.
Now that's more like it.
There. Now you look more like the Yana I've always known.
I like you better in casual clothes come on sit down and eat. I ordered what you like enjoy
Mr.. Rosso aren't you going to eat? No. Thanks dear. I've already eaten. I'll just have me some coffee
Go on dig in thank you. I am pretty hungry
What's so funny?
You haven't changed. You still take five sugars in your coffee.
Well, that's what tastes best.
I say coffee isn't any good at all if it isn't sweet.
It's good to see you can smile.
I know you're in the middle of a big job interview and up to now, you've looked quite serious.
But you smiled when you saw me put all that sugar in my coffee.
Your name's Anna...
Right. My name is Anna Liebert.
So, uh...
Well, Miss Liebert, the job's yours.
You'll start today.
Having a young lady like you waiting tables in my cafe might give my business quite a boost.
Except...
Do me a favor. Show off that smile a little more, alright?
When you smile, it'll make everyone feel good.
Thank you so much for the job. I'll work very hard, really.
Chances are you may not have to.
This is an Italian restaurant in a small town.
Two tables of folks is as busy as it gets.
- Anna, come stand over here. - Sure.
I'll place all the orders here on the bar,
and you'll take them from here to the customer's tables.
All used plates go on that side of the counter,
the wine is right here, and the glassware is back here.
You'll find more bottles of wine above this shelf,
on these little hooks.
So more wine is above the shelf and glassware is back there.
This is for water.
Got it.
Morning, Rosso.
So, how are you today?
Good morning and welcome.
I'm starving.
Nice to meet you, sir.
My name's Anna.
It's not possible.
There's no way someone as pretty as you could be a waitress in a place like this.
Huh?
Well, you're awake, and my place is classier than you thought.
Introducing Anna, our new waitress. She'll be serving here from now on.
Like I said, I'm pleased to meet you.
You really mean it?
(gulps)
- Huh.
(laughs)
- Hey, Anna, how about a nice plate of carbonara?
- Hey, Anna, I think I'll have a bolognese.
Can you get me some more water when you have a chance?
Uh-huh, right away.
Order up. One bolognese and one carbonara.
Coming right up.
All right, here you go, sir.
You're a gem, Anna.
Vongole and rigatoni.
And table three's fettuccine order is up.
Okay.
Hey, Rosso.
Come on, you gotta tell us how you tricked this cutie
into working here for you.
I didn't have to trick her.
Guess I was just my charming self.
Hey, Anna, if you're free tonight,
how about you let me take you out to a real restaurant?
Come on, it'll be fun.
Hold on.
Just forget about trying to make time with my Anna.
I'd hate to have to hurt you.
Oh, boy, listen to the crybaby Rosso, everybody.
Suddenly acting all tough.
Hey, way to get a load of this.
Last week, he was at my house, watching a TV movie,
falling like a baby.
[grunting]
Hey.
[laughing]
Another order of squid ink risotto!
Ah! Summertime is playing across the street.
Huh?
That old movie house is screening Summertime. See there?
What a city! Frankfurt has so many great old movie theaters.
That movie was on TV just last week.
That one really brings me to tears.
Have you ever seen "Summertime"?
- Mm-mm.
- It's touching.
The whole thing takes place in Italy,
actually in the city of Venice.
Folks don't know the history of Venice.
It was a port city back in medieval days
and everyone called it the city of water.
The entire city of Venice was originally built on a lagoon.
There were these canals
I'd really like to go see it with you some day.
It's just beautiful.
It sounds to me like you've been there before.
I have.
The film's soundtrack is great music.
It's very well composed.
I bet you've heard its theme song.
I'd say most folks have heard it.
It was a popular, very well-known song.
Tell me, how does it go?
Let's see.
[humming]
Hmm?
Hey, I know. Let's go across the street and see it right now.
We've missed some, but they'll still let us in.
Oh, it's just... well, I...
Some other time. It is kind of late, and you're still eating.
Sorry.
[music stops]
[birds chirping]
[leaves rustling]
[children laughing]
Well, I'm back.
Great! So, how was your break?
Oh, can I scrub that for you?
No, thanks. I can handle it.
I appreciate you letting me take off a few hours from work every afternoon.
Ah, it's no problem. It's always slow around this time of the day.
Anna, I don't want to be nosy, but...
Where do you go every day?
Hey, forget I asked. It's your private time. It's none of my business where you go.
I've been learning how to shoot a gun.
Oh, learning to shoot.
That's right. At Mr. Venkel's firing range.
You're learning at Vinkle's place, huh?
He's good people.
Tell me, Mr. Oso, have you ever shot a gun before?
Me, shooting guns? No way!
Honestly, I get all nervous just looking at them.
[Gunshot]
[Gunshots]
(gentle music)
- Here you go, sir.
Enjoy.
- Thank you very much.
(gentle music)
(laughing)
How'd I do this time?
Take a taste.
No, you should try it.
Let's try it.
Tell me, what's it taste like?
Like there's some garlic, olive oil, parsley, and not much else.
So the flavors of the other things you put in there are gone, right?
Mm-hmm.
That just means you haven't learned how to make it proper.
This cooking's tough stuff.
Anything worth learning takes practice.
I'm all done with the bathroom, Mr. Oso. I'm heading for bed now, so...
When I was younger, I never realized that movies like this existed.
(crickets chirping)
- Mr. Rosso, movies have always affected you deeply.
- That's true.
When I was younger, I always wanted to watch movies,
but with work, I never had the time to.
Back then, I ate a lot of fabulous meals,
but to be really honest,
I never felt any of them had any taste or flavor.
I didn't even appreciate the taste of sugar then.
- Really?
Is that the truth?
You know my past. Isn't that right, Anna?
Well, after you left, I checked up on you. And I know what happened.
You're really Nina Fortner. And you disappeared two years ago, after your parents were murdered.
"Exactly what were you looking for me to do?
Were you looking for me to do a hit?
Or did you want me to teach you to kill?"
"I guess I wanted to learn from you.
That was it."
"So how did you find out about me and what I did?"
"From one of my professors at law school.
He had done research on you and all the cases you were involved in the Ristorante Nino case
the Sacco Milano case the Sabatini murder case
You were called into court to testify in all three of those murder cases and in each of those cases
All charges were dropped due to a complete lack of evidence
However, my professor came up with a theory about it that made sense there was only one conclusion a
A world-class hitman committed all three of the murders and he said that you were that
man.
I
suppose you want to know how many people I killed.
To be honest with you, I can't even remember.
I was never a good kid, and before I knew what was what I was in way over my head.
Robbery, blackmail, if you can name it, then I did it.
And eventually I became a hitman.
I rewarded myself by eating very well.
I never had any feelings about it.
It was just my job.
This one day, I was doing what I always did.
some faceless guy.
It was sunny, and he was alone.
I'd been doing it so long I was numb.
I didn't know how many I'd killed or who was next.
I had him as good as dead.
He had ordered a coffee, and as I watched,
he started putting sugar in it.
One spoonful.
Two spoonfuls.
And three.
And four.
After the fifth spoonful, he stopped.
That moment started me finally tasting the coffee I drank.
When I saw how he was enjoying that coffee,
I couldn't do it.
- That was the day I put my gun down for good.
That part of my life is done.
I know I can't kill people and steal their simple pleasures.
After all the time we've spent together, I don't get it.
You never asked me to teach you how to kill someone.
I decided I decided that getting you involved wouldn't be right
Do you really have to go, Nina?
Goodbye.
Thank you for everything, Mr. Rosso.
You should know killing is easier than you think.
You just have to forget how sweet the sugar is.
[GASPING]
[MUSIC]
[CRYING]
(upbeat music)