my wife and I divorced about three years ago no that's uh she divorced me three years ago she
said that I stopped listening to her and I suppose she was right about that this was the only thing I
did really listen to by that point my wife said I was broken she said it was a voyeur peeking
through the window at people's innermost thoughts. Crazy. Doctor, you're abnormal.
Maybe you're right about that. I became transfixed, obsessively gazing into the abyss of the human
heart. I suppose it's possible the abyss gazes back into me. The depths of the human mind are
filled with treacherous landscapes. Your fourth victim was an 18-year-old girl in Munich, I
believe I'm curious did you experience any form of sexual arousal when you cut
her up I don't want to talk about her today doctor I want to talk about my
12th victim fair enough then that would be mrs. Hana Kemp from Krupp house 52
years old at that time I was in wait I'm not prepared to talk about her I promise
we will eventually get to mrs. Kemp but for the moment I would really like to
to focus on victim number 11.
Is that all right?
- Now then, the peak of your arousal,
does that come before or after you commit a murder?
We'll be right back.
♪♪♪
the victims were all girls with long hair ages 16 to 18 it's clear these murders should all
be categorized as acts of sexual homicide.
But then he confesses to the murder
of his 12th victim, Mrs. Kemp.
Mrs. Kemp was 52 and showed no signs of sexual assault.
He claims to have killed Mrs. Kemp as a favor for a friend,
an obvious and desperate last-ditch attempt
to disrupt the investigation.
Who is it?
Who is it? I know that you're in there.
It's me, Rudy.
Huh?
Tenma?
Well, this is a surprise.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry for barging in on you like this, Rudy.
You've heard about my situation.
That's putting it mildly.
Well, do you think I'm a serial killer?
I don't know.
But from what I've heard,
both the newspapers and our old classmates think you're as guilty as sin.
So the question is, what are you doing here?
Why come to me?
We were never exactly what you'd call close.
I know for a fact you despised me.
I could tell from the way you looked at me.
I saw the contempt burning behind your eyes.
Uh-huh, that's what this is all about.
You've come to collect what you think I owe you.
Is that it?
It's not like that at all.
You've become a noted specialist in criminal psychology.
I have something I'd like you to take a look at.
My dear Dr. Tenma, look at me.
Look at me.
the monster inside me is getting bigger help the monster inside me is about to
explode what on earth is this quite a story so ten years ago you saved a boy's
life who went on to kill the hospital director some staff and his foster
parents then he's gone leaving no trace other than a series of cryptic messages
addressed to you which is why it's so urgent that I find out where he is now
Because you think by finding him, you'll also find something that might prove your innocence.
Twenty years ago, there was a young man attending a prestigious medical school.
He was driven to be top of his class.
One day, a Japanese transfer student came and changed everything.
This new student was charming, quickly gaining the respect of peers and teachers alike.
He had a brilliant mind as well, claiming his position as the top of his class within his first semester.
Much to the man's dismay.
By the next semester, he had become obsessed with regaining his title.
He had managed to earn full marks in all his classes so far.
However, his last test was in his weakest subject: medical law.
If he failed this test, then all of his efforts would go to waste.
So he resorted to desperate measures.
Measures he thought would put him back on top.
But he was caught.
The Japanese student never told anyone about what he had seen.
As a result, the man regained his throne.
So is there anything you can tell me about this man based on the contents of these letters?
You think it may be multiple personality disorder.
And you've come to the conclusion that one of the personalities is committing these murders
while the other personality is trying to get caught.
Yes, instances of serial killers leaving these sorts of notes are not unheard of.
Just as often, these notes are fabricated as legal proof of their insanity.
Separating the pretender from the genuine article is the art of the criminal psychologist.
And believe you me, this is no easy task.
The introverted, shifty-eyed serial killer is more or less a Hollywood fabrication.
Many killers are highly intelligent, intuitive, and extremely charming.
They are adaptive and skillful liars.
So that's it? You think he might be toying with me?
Well, let's not add to the mounting pile of conjecture just yet.
Why don't you tell me a little bit more about this, Johan?
My wife and I got divorced about three years ago.
What I mean to say is my wife divorced me three years ago.
Thank you, Rudy.
Don't mention it, Timma. This is a very fascinating case you brought me.
I need to do some research. Give me a call next week, all right?
Do you have an opinion about this person?
Seems like my kind of guy.
Hmm. Can you elaborate on that?
The monster. I get all that.
That's interesting. You get the monster.
Makes sense, of course. There's a monster inside both of you.
To be fair, there's even a monster inside of me.
Shut your mouth.
Huh?
That's nothing but textbook garbage.
Why is that?
What I'm telling you, Doctor, is that a real monster does exist.
What do you think you're doing?
Just stop looking at me like that.
Don't you dare look at me with such contempt!
What are you doing?
I'm calling the guards!
Well, are you scared yet? Are you scared?
Because there are things out there that will turn your blood to ice, Doctor.
I'm going to tell you a secret.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're really still convinced that Tenma's going to try and contact you again?
I'm sure of it.
And when he does, I'll notify you immediately.
However...
Well, go on.
After his arrest, I would like to get permission to use him and his case in my research.
Dr. Tenma would make a compelling subject.
He has a complex criminal mind.
I'm going to tell you a secret.
Go to Ms. Hana Kemp's house in Krupp House.
Make your way to the basement.
You're going to find all of your answers down there.
Down there you'll find proof.
Proof the monster really does exist.
This is Rudy.
Ah, Tenma.
I've been waiting for your call yeah all right excellent I'll see you there
officer Cole Tim I just called we've arranged for a meeting tonight
Oh dare Park tonight at 8:00 by the fountain that's right
goodbye then I'm currently retracing Jurgen steps on the day of his 12th
confessed murder. According to our interviews, he broke into the basement and stayed hidden
there for several hours. Later, when Mrs. Kemp returned home, he made his way into the
upstairs bedroom and murdered her there. There's nothing out of the ordinary, except there
framed photos all over the basement they're all pictures of mrs. Kemp
just a doll almost gave me a heart attack evidence of this so-called
monster Jurgen sent me to find clearly isn't here the supports my theory that
Juergens committed the twelfth murder to confuse investigators his first
explanation was that he committed the murder as a favor for a friend one he
associates with a primal monster archetype he
When I was a kid, my mother would beat me every day.
What she would do, she would take me into the basement.
It was dark, and she had this big doll down there, a doll with long hair.
Sometimes when she beat me, I would cry to the doll for help,
and it would just sit there and smirk and watch.
The basement was filled with pictures of my mother.
Wherever I tried to look,
mother, mother, mother, mother, always watching.
No escape.
But what does it mean?
Exact in every detail.
Is it possible?
Did Juergens actually recreate the basement from his childhood?
The boy next to Mrs. Kemp is Juergens.
It can't be.
There's no evidence connecting young Juergens to Mrs. Kemp.
Huh?
Something is not right here.
It seems that Jürgens' face was pasted into the photograph
This one
And this one
And another
All of these
Mrs. Kemp never had any children
so who is this boy who are you down there you'll find proof proof the monster really does exist
i followed all of the instructions and my friend left me in the letter perfectly
friend who was he just listen the first letter came in a blank envelope without a name or return
address you have to say he understood me sympathize with me crap like that I was
annoyed angry at first but then another one came and then another the next day
and again and so on he's a letter freak
but before I knew it I started to expect the letters even enjoy them a bit then I
I thought maybe it's possible he might actually be a friend to me and then one
day one of his letters asked me for something he asked me to go down to the
basement of this house and did the basement belong to mrs. camp I still
don't know how he could have known there's no way he could possibly have
known what happened to me down there when I was a kid but somehow he got
everything right down to the smallest detail how do you do that I just got so
confused was mrs. Kemp my mother the next thing I knew I was upstairs and
mrs. Kemp was dead he's a letter freak a friend of his must have sent letters to
mrs. Kemp as well
What is this?
Another?
And this?
Another one?
Look at me.
The monster inside me is getting bigger.
Help me.
The monster inside of me is about to explode.
These are the messages that Johan left me.
They're the same.
Juergens' friend. And Johan. He's real.
Anything yet? It's way past eight already.
Inspector Cole, hold on.
Target in sight.
Asian male. Long hair.
I appreciate you making time for this, Rudy.
I want you to know I did research what you gave me.
But I thought you were making it up.
I thought that Johan was just a ruse.
A scapegoat you created to buy you time once you were caught.
You've got to believe me
Rudy
I've been conducting research on a serial killer named Juergens
And something he said caught my attention
One of his victims is off pattern
Showing no connection to profile or ritual
It doesn't matter, Rudy
Please just listen to me
Okay, listen up, everyone
We're finished for today
We'll see you tomorrow
Seems like the carnival is wrapping up
Everyone in position
Make sure they're ready to move in on my mark
Yes, sir
I want every detail of their conversation.
Tenma, you hated me, didn't you?
Huh?
You've hated me ever since you caught me cheating on that exam in college.
I can feel your disdain.
Go ahead, say it.
Inspector Cole, this doesn't look good.
Dr. Guillen and Tenma are headed toward the west exit.
Damn, we'll lose them in that crowd that's leaving.
You'd be well within your right.
A man like me doesn't deserve your respect.
- Rudy, this isn't the time to reminisce.
- Listen to me.
Now then, I looked up the answers
and wrote them all down on a cheat sheet.
A sheet just like this one.
- Run, we're surrounded by the police.
- Don't look, just walk.
- Is Dr. Tenma threatening Gillen?
- I'm not sure, sir.
There's too much background noise for me to hear.
- Hey, it's my turn.
Juergens recently confessed to me that he had killed Mrs. Kemp at the request of a friend.
Rudy, what is this?
Something I found in Mrs. Kemp's basement.
But Mrs. Kemp never had any children.
I have found compelling evidence to suggest that Juergens' friend and your Johan are both one and the same.
They've passed through the west exit. Should we move in?
Tell everyone to hold their positions. He may be armed.
I found a letter from Johan in Mrs. Kemp's house.
It was almost identical to the one you brought me.
I believe that Johan had been in the care of Mrs. Kemp at some point in his life.
That would explain his motivation for orchestrating her death.
You're an innocent man, Tenma.
I'm sorry I can't give you as much detail as perhaps you'd like,
but here's what I've worked out on Johan so far.
I don't know how he does it, but Johan can somehow identify other killers.
He finds them, worms his way in, beguiles them, then manipulates them.
It is worth noting that, to the best of our knowledge,
he hasn't killed the foster parents who cared for him as a teenager.
Probably because by the time he reached that age, he no longer found himself dependent on anyone.
Perhaps. But I have another theory.
What if Johan found himself his ideal family?
and then became a part of it.
But why work so hard to erase his past?
Was there an ulterior motive?
If that is indeed the case,
did he make his way into the family for a specific purpose?
And what would that purpose be?
Well, we're at the bus terminal.
Yes, confirm which bus Tenma's getting on!
Then get a car over to the terminal and have him followed!
Yes, sir.
Here. The least I can do is buy you a bus ticket.
You know, there's still time for you to turn yourself in and prove your innocence, Tenma.
I promise I can help you.
The truth is, I'm not chasing after Johan just so I can prove my innocence.
Hmm?
Thank you for all your help, Rudy.
Tenma! You don't have to become him to end this.
That reminds me.
I really didn't despise you back in college, Rudy.
I mean it.
I thought you were brilliant, and it was a shame we never had a chance to talk.
I'm glad that I can finally count you as a friend.
But I know you caught me cheating on that medical law exam.
There's no doubt about it.
I saw you looking directly at me and my cheat sheet.
Well, yeah, I cheated on the medical law exam, too.
He got away!
All five buses left at the same time?
Be careful, Tenma.
© transcript Emily Beynon