Here. The least I can do is buy you a bus ticket.
You know, there's still time for you to turn yourself in and prove your innocence, Tenma.
I promise I can help you.
The truth is, I'm not chasing after Johan just so I can prove my innocence.
Hmm?
Thank you for all your help, Rudy.
Tenma! You don't have to become him to end this.
That reminds me. I really didn't despise you back in college, Rudy.
I thought you were brilliant, and it was a shame we never had a chance to talk.
I'm glad that I can finally count you as a friend.
But I know you caught me cheating on that medical law exam in Professor Hesse's class.
Well, yeah, I cheated on the medical law exam, too.
Be careful, Temma.
What did that sign back there say?
Oh, sorry, dear. I missed it.
I've been trying to figure out this map is it this way or that way I'm not quite
sure we're headed in the right direction really where'd you find that map lying
in the street you know me better than that you were right beside me when I
picked it up at the car rental place I don't remember you picking anything up
you must have grabbed it when I went off to use the facilities they put in so
many place names with such small print at my age it's almost impossible to read
You could do it if you hadn't left your glasses at the airport.
There's Wippenhausen and Ampertshausen and here's Gartelhausen.
That's quite a mouthful, dear. These German names all sound alike, don't they?
They are amusing. I wonder if Germans think that about our towns when they read British maps.
Maybe, but right now we need to know when the next crossroad's coming up.
Hmm.
Look, there's a pedestrian.
Let's ask him for directions.
Let's not bother him. We can work it out ourselves.
Oh, the poor fellow. He's hitchhiking.
Let's give him a ride.
If you ask me, we're looking for trouble giving a ride to a complete stranger.
Maybe so.
Oh, wait a minute. He's travelling with a small child.
I feel sorry for them. Let's pick them up, all right?
Fine.
Hey, look, Tenma. Those people just stopped for us.
You're right.
We'll be right back.
We'll see you next time.
To be continued...
traveling to. Oh, well, all right. We're around this area now, so it's just a bit further
south from here. Oh, that's splendid. We're headed in the same direction, aren't we, dear?
I suppose. Right then, it's settled. You two, hop in. Dankeschön.
you're quite an odd couple aren't you huh i mean i don't believe you're his father
you appear to be asian and the boy is clearly german caucasian ah yes in fact he's my best
friend's son and by all appearances i dare say you're some sort of well-educated professional man
It's the way you talk and carry yourself
I really must interrupt
That's quite enough, dear
It's that rude habit of yours
I must apologize for him
Sorry, it's not personal
He just enjoys observing people
Now that he's retired from the police force
What did she say?
Nothing
She just said that he used to be a cop
let's get out of here tenma easy so uh i've been thinking i'll bet this is the first real
vacation the two of you have taken since your husband retired yes you're right my husband was
such a workaholic i never truly believed we'd be able to take a big trip together but here we both
are sir i'm sorry we're imposing on this time you plan to spend with your wife we'd be happy to
catch another ride if we're being a nuisance here so far the biggest nuisance
has been getting lost because we can't read directions not to mention the
trouble we've been having ordering food it might help us immensely to have
someone like you traveling with us if only to interpret the bloody language
- Well, what shall we do now, dear?
- I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
- I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
well what should we do now dear hmm there's nothing we can do I'm afraid
except find a gas station and bring some back look here comes a truck hey what's
wrong we're out of gas that's kind of a problem out here in the middle of no
man's land huh hmm well I've got room for two of you in my cab is that okay
somebody should take the chap up on his offer don't worry about us we'll be all
right we'll work something out listen as soon as I see a gas station I'll get
them to send somebody out here with a can of gas for you thank you that would
That would be most helpful, and we'd really appreciate it.
This is great.
Thank goodness, right, Tenma?
Everything worked out perfectly.
Yeah.
How long do you think it will be before we come to a gas station?
Don't remember there being any around.
it's been quite a while now indeed it has my dear with that nice young man lets them know
that was stranded out here on the motorway the petrol station will send someone out won't they
there is another possibility hmm he might just have left us and forgotten about us I don't
believe it he's not that kind of person he struck me as a very caring man maybe
not
what a beautiful sky I'm not really in the mood to enjoy a sunset tonight see
one you've seen them all oh i'm not talking about the sunset the sun's already disappeared
but just look at the lovely pastel colors the sun has left behind
it's like a watercolor painting in the sky
i wonder if robert's watching it now we'd be seeing it together
My goodness. Is that... I think it is.
Dear, you'd better take a look. My eyes might be deceiving me.
Someone's coming this way.
It's getting bright and closer.
It must be him. I just knew it.
I couldn't find a gas station.
I borrowed the gas and a lamp from a farmer.
Oh, my.
See, I told you.
Hmm.
Oh, that was a delicious meal, wasn't it, dear?
Thanks to your excellent translation of the German menu,
we were actually able to order something we could enjoy tonight.
Right?
Especially that wine.
Oh, it was four-star Ungeheuer.
It's from the Palatinate region.
That liver dish was just scrumptious.
The liver canoodle?
That's how it's pronounced.
It melted in my mouth.
If you hadn't been with us, we'd have passed all these wonderful places
without a clue as to what we were missing.
I want to thank you for treating us to dinner.
You're almost finished.
Would you like some more to take with you?
Thanks, but if he has any more, he'll burst.
Do you think this bloke looks like a criminal?
This chap here, he's on trial for murdering his wife
and there's a big picture of him in the paper.
See for yourself.
What's your opinion?
Do you think he did it?
Well, um, who can tell, really?
Before I retired from the force,
I was a detective with quite a long list of criminals
that I'd put behind bars.
Oh.
Come on, dear, we're enjoying the evening.
It's really not appropriate to brag about all your past exploits.
Well, I would look at a person's face
and I'd know if he'd done the crime.
I possessed an uncanny knack for spotting the guilt that a person tries
to hide I see let's talk about something else now dear I think you've had a
little too much wine however after years on the job I couldn't tell anymore
was one person good and another bad was he guilty or innocent I couldn't spot
the difference that had once seemed so clear it probably means I wasn't such a
hot-shot detective after all
enough said maybe I did have a little too much to drink and tell me once more
what was the name of that wine it was forced rolling Goyer Oh excellent bouquet
♪♪
How cute. They each have a friend.
When this trip is over, Dieter, and you move to a new place,
I hope you make lots of friends.
Oh, sure. That'd be great.
Everyone should have a happy childhood.
They should enjoy every minute.
It goes by so fast.
Yes.
Huh?
Oops, sorry.
It should be somewhere right around here.
What are you looking for?
Here's the address, dear.
Hmm. Almost there. Sorry, but we have to make a stop before continuing.
That's fine.
Oh, here we are.
Hmm?
The police.
We won't be very long.
If you don't mind, you might as well wait in the car.
What should we do, Tenma?
Tenma, let's run away.
What's wrong?
Someone's parked in one of the officer's only spaces again.
He looks foreign. Guess I should report him.
Eh, don't worry about it.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
♪♪
mr. Jones we want to get to fry home and I don't know if you're aware of it but
you're heading in the opposite direction hmm that's right it's just a brief
detail I want to stop at Steinbach Castle for a bit but dear Steinbach
Castle was something I want to see for myself
How are you doing? Are you all right?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Our son wrote us a letter about Steinbach.
He said the view from this castle is truly breathtaking.
He wanted to bring us here so we could both see it.
Oh, does your son live in Germany now?
We're on our way to see him.
It's just that we have a few detours to make along the way.
This is the view he saw on that fateful day.
My son.
My own flesh and blood killed a man.
We came to this country to visit him
because he'll never leave.
- Well, we'll be okay from here.
Thank you so much for everything.
- Thank you for your kindness
and the pleasure of your company.
Cheerio, then.
Look after yourself.
such a nice young man yes isn't he it's hard to believe that he's wanted as the prime suspect in
a series of murders that can't be you must be mistaken no i'm not it's him he's on the wanted
suspects list impossible i'm afraid so and when we were at the station to speak to the detective
who arrested Robert,
Tenma's photo was prominently posted on the wall.
Unbelievable.
There's so much good in him.
I know.
I thought so too,
and yet everyone seems convinced that he's guilty.
But my instincts keep telling me
he's an innocent man.
The good in him outweighs the bad,
I'm sure of it.
Hmm.
It was unbelievable to think
that Robert had committed murder but he did and the fact that I couldn't sense
what was going on with my own son made me realize it was time for me to turn in
my badge but you know something dear I just want to be able to trust my
instincts again Robert may have committed a crime true but I know he's a
He's a good boy at heart.
Come on.
Let's go in and see our son.
Our dear Robert.
© transcript Emily Beynon
Copyright © 2020 Mooji Media Ltd. All Rights Reserved.