Hey, honey, can I interest you in this Moscow mule?
Oh, thank you, Michael.
My pleasure.
And for you, a big glass of juice on the rocks.
Come on, Fritz, now be polite and thank your father.
Thanks, Mr. Mueller.
Stop it, Fritz.
Leave him be, Barbara. Rome wasn't built in a day, you know.
Well, it's the same deal with my new antique business.
Rough start, then smooth sailing.
Well, for me, everything has really happened so quickly.
I suddenly get to live in this gorgeous house,
and I have a wonderful and caring husband
who makes me great cocktails.
[laughing]
Hmm?
Hey, honey, did you see something just then?
There, in the window.
I have a feeling sometimes like... like we're being watched.
What? Honey, that house has been empty for a while.
Yeah, I know. It's odd.
Actually, I talked to Mrs. Daughtry from across the street.
What about?
She said that 20 years ago, a couple was brutally murdered in that house.
Anyone who moves in never stays for long.
They say the place is haunted.
Michael, dear, what's the matter?
Wait a minute. Now, don't tell me that you believe in ghosts, too, do you, darling?
Of course not. What do you take me for?
Are you going out, sir?
Yeah. I'll get the car.
Not this time. I thought it might be a nice change of pace to go out, just the three of us.
Don't worry. No one's gonna try anything.
I get it. Unless I'm mistaken, you're wanting a little father-son time with the boy.
You're a smart bodyguard, you know that?
have a good time all right off we go
(dramatic music)
- So, Detective, what all did you dig up?
- Regarding Dr. Tenma,
everything checked out exactly as you told me.
He's the main suspect in the murder
of the Fortner couple,
but the police have no idea where he is at the moment.
Here's a transcript of Tenma's statement.
during that first questioning.
He operated on a boy at Eisler Memorial Hospital
10 years ago, saved his life.
Kid went on to kill the hospital director
and two other doctors.
The boy's name was Johan.
He was already a young man
the next time Tenma encountered him.
Turns out Johan executed a patient in his care.
Next up, Nina Fortner.
She was the murdered couple's foster daughter.
No one's seen her since the night they were killed either.
Messner was a tougher nut to crack,
but I did finally track him down in Frankfurt.
- Well, then, what'd you find?
- A grave with his name on it.
Turns out he was stabbed to death about two months ago.
The official police version is that he was
on the wrong side of a drug deal gone bad.
- Back when I was a detective on the force,
Messner was my partner.
- Sorry for your loss.
They caught Messner with confiscated narcotics
and booted him off the force.
After that, he got some help from a man called the Baby.
Ring any bells?
He's the spokesman for some nationalist group in Frankfurt.
- How is this relevant?
- You remember hearing those news reports
about how its Turkish quarter
almost burned down last winter, right?
Word on the street is the whole thing
was the Baby's brainchild,
and the Turks credit an Asian stranger
with having saved their neighborhood.
Turns out that stranger's name was Tenma.
What are the odds?
I'm thinking it was the doctor and what's more people are saying the baby had those fires set to commemorate the introduction of a
new leader into their group
Some wonder can they were all really excited about he was gonna change everything. Who is this guy? I've already told you
What was the name of that boy? Dr. Tenma saved a decade ago
Johan
Well, that young man who was supposed to take the reins of the baby's organization in Frankfurt,
He was Johan, too.
Oh, I should have seen that one coming.
Call me crazy, Roberto, but I feel like one of the pawns
on this chessboard, waiting for the axe to fall.
Goodness.
What's got you looking so pensive all of a sudden?
Thinking about the past.
Everything was going straight to hell for me at the time.
But after that phone call, the change was like night and day.
Back then, my partner Messner and I were selling drugs,
whatever we confiscated off of the dealers we busted.
The voice on the other end knew everything.
He said it would be our little secret if we did him a favor.
Kill some couple in Heidelberg, the Fortuners.
I didn't know 'em from Adam.
But there was another guy there that night,
a newspaper reporter or something.
We killed all three of 'em, no choice.
After that, somebody wired money to the both of us.
When I left the police force, the syndicate
I was waiting with a great offer.
They gave me a plum job and the pay was top notch.
I had everything I wanted out of life, or so I thought.
- That's when you met your wife and decided to go straight,
or so I would wager.
- Yeah, but I still can't figure out
why they let me just walk away.
Who was it?
Who called me that day?
I gotta know.
Who transferred all that money over to us?
Who the hell is manipulating my life?
Who, damn it?
Roberto, I want to be sure that you know, I really appreciate your help.
Well, if that's how you feel, take back that last move.
Sorry, my friend, no can do.
Ouch, now you're being harsh.
All right, honey, we're leaving.
Okay.
We're gonna buy toys, right? Lots of 'em!
Maybe. But first, say goodbye to your father, Fritz.
Leave him be, honey. He's got toys on the brain.
Bye-bye, Daddy!
Huh?
Bye!
Roberto, were there any calls from the detective?
He should have come by now.
Roberto?
Roberto!
Get up!
Up here! It's the detective! Oh, God, he's...
You... But you're...
Yes, I'm the daughter of the Fortiners, the couple you murdered.
You shot him in cold blood. Roberto!
I was watching from next door. Your bodyguard's the one who killed him.
Roberto?
That's right. I saw it all through the window.
No, he couldn't have. I know Roberto. I trust that man with my life.
You came here for revenge and he got in the way, right?
Damn you.
Roberto! Help me!
I'm taking this bag.
Stay here or run for it. I don't give a damn.
Just don't be surprised if you're the next person who dies here, you bastard.
Was that you shouting just now, Mr. Mueller?
Is everything all right?
You've been watching me all this time from the house next door, Will, isn't that right?
me now I hate you from the bottom of my heart give me one good reason not to shoot you but
he knew we had to do whatever he said if we didn't kill your folks like he asked he was
gonna tell the cops about the drugs we were selling on the side don't you get it we had to do it
we didn't have any other choice
Didn't have any other choice?
You didn't have any other choice?
Stop the car!
Stop the car, goddammit!
My parents were wonderful people.
The kindest couple I'll ever know.
Mom and Dad loved me. They loved me with all their heart and soul.
Wait! Please don't do this!
It didn't even matter to them that I wasn't their real daughter.
They loved me all the same.
My mom and dad were angels. They were angels!
I'm sorry! Please don't shoot!
Angels! And they were murdered by a bastard like you!
(sobbing)
- Barbara.
Oh God.
Fritz.
- Look at me.
- Oh, well done, Fritz.
- Is that it?
- Up we go.
(sobbing)
- You're crying for your family?
What about mine?
- So this is what it feels like,
right before somebody kills you.
Fritz, he called me daddy today, for the first time.
Don't take that from me.
Please, please let me live.
I finally found someone worth living for.
My Barbara and Fritz.
I met them at half-past eight in the morning at a cafe in Dusseldorf.
I'd quit the force and joined the syndicate.
My boss told me to act like a businessman, made for a nice cover.
Every morning, this woman and her little boy would walk by.
They were my daily reminder of the regular, honest life I'd given up.
Hey, so, uh, how you doing?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Tell me something. What did you hire that detective for?
I was hoping he could find you and Tenma and my former partner.
I wanted to know what he was up to.
Messner's dead, for whatever it's worth.
When I heard about that, I asked the detective to find out more information last night. I got a phone call from him
I've been digging around. It's strange. What do you mean strange? Think about it Messner was a junkie, right?
Why would the organization go out of its way to help some doped-out ex-cop?
Also, the man who killed him wasn't from the Frankfurt group. No as it turns out he was from Dusseldorf from Dusseldorf. Yeah
I'll give you all the details when I see you in person. Here it is
the report. Messner's killer. Who is, who is Roberto? Look at this. Do you know what
this means? Yes, hello? Hey boss, I need that bag. Roberto! Apropos of nothing, your wife
and Fritz are already home what what are you saying if you hurt them I'll be
hurrying right back about now if I were you a lot of accidents happen at home
Give me your gun.
Look, there's something I gotta do.
Remember, that model's intended for close-range work.
You only got four shots, so make 'em count.
Don't worry about me. I was an officer once upon a time.
Just be careful.
You can't have me dying before you take me to the police and have me confess to killing your parents.
Is that it?
That's right.
So don't even think of dying on me.
I'll cover you from the empty house next door.
Good luck!
- Hi, Daddy! - Oh, Fritz, hey.
- Daddy, look! It's a fishing pole!
- Fritz just kept on insisting he had to go fishing with his daddy.
- Barbara, thank God.
Well, where's Roberto?
- Oh, that reminds me.
The gentlemen from his security team are here.
He said something happened while we were out.
- His team?
- There's no need to worry.
He said everything's fine and no one was hurt. Oh
Roberto look Michael's come home
Everything's alright. It was nothing important. Just a broken window
Probably just a kid from the neighborhood. Nothing to worry about nothing at all
Where's the body
What have you done with him damn it a body what are you talking about?
What's going on Roberto
Who the hell are you Fritz and the little wife here heading inside?
Don't be stupid hand over the bag
now
There you go
All right, gentlemen, nothing ever happened here understood just another boring day in paradise, right?
Like yesterday, and tomorrow.
Nina!
Nina?
She is such a beautiful girl.
What?
What did you do to her?
Don't look at me like that. Nina's fine.
My employer considers her a very important guest.
Your employer?
Well, that young man, he was Johan, too.
Johan! Johan! Johan! Everywhere I look, Johan is there!
Who the hell is he? Who the hell are you? Talk!
You want to live happily ever after with Barbara and Fritz, don't you?
Go back to your fairy tale.
Trust me. Leave it alone.
As employers go, you weren't too bad.
But this is where we say goodbye.
What are you going to do with Nina? Is she going to die?
You take care now.
Hey, Daddy, can you and me go fishing sometime soon?
Oh, yeah. If it's sunny, how about tomorrow?
All right!
"It's over. I don't see ghosts anymore."
"You have very nice eyes. You're definitely Yohan's sister."
"So, when do I get to see Yohan?"
"I let you take me in without a fight because you promised I'd get to see him."
looking forward to catching up with you well then where is he right now if you
must know he's living happily in Munich he's in Munich you know you really have
very nice eyes such a pity I just can't bring myself to do it
Now then, what's next?
Ah yes, Dr. Tenma.
[GASPING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
But why? Why did you come?
It's like I told you. For better or for worse, I did used to be a cop.
Don't worry, you're almost home.
I know.
I told Fritz that we'd go fishing tomorrow.
I promised.
Good.
I hope it's sunny.
"I'm sure...it will be."
[Music]
[MUSIC]