Excuse me, officer.
Sir, sir, just a couple of questions, please.
Stay there! Stay right there! Hold it!
Back off! You're interfering with a crime scene!
Do we have any leads?
Can you please tell us what the police are thinking?
What are your views on this situation?
Do you believe the case is linked to the serial murders?
Mr. and Mrs. Yope were quite wealthy and have no children, right?
No matter how you look at it, it's obvious this incident is exactly like the other cases of murdered middle-aged couples across Germany.
No comment at this time.
I've heard that the BKA is sending an agent to look into this. Is that true?
Does that mean there's a connection to the serial murders?
No comment.
Aw, man.
I think I'd have better luck talking to a BKA suit directly than trying to get this guy to give me anything.
Just trust me, alright?
I promise you will be the first ones with a story. Just make sure you leave plenty of space on the front page.
Just do it. I gotta go.
Excuse me, sir. My name is Kipper. I'm with the Hamburg Tog.
You've been sent here by the BKA to investigate this murder.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
I was wondering, is this case somehow connected to the other serial murders?
Well, Kipper of the Hamburg Tog, you're right on both counts.
Get your pen ready.
Because here's my statement.
A middle-aged couple was murdered and it appears to be another serial slaying.
I knew it! And it's the suspect, that Japanese doctor?
Yes, I just saw the report. It's his M.O. The murders were carried out the same way.
Thank you for the scoop.
Gotta run.
Oh, one more thing.
Huh?
I'm aware the Hamburg Tag is the leading local newspaper, but I expect you to make sure your story gets published in every major newspaper in the country as well.
Hey, consider it done. Thanks again for all your help, friend.
♪♪♪
We'll be right back.
I have become the killer.
I think to myself as I approach, what's the best way to get into their house?
Should I knock?
I don't want to startle the Yopes by walking in on them.
such a friendly couple they greet me and show me to the living room these folks aren't the
least bit suspicious as they lead me in the husband's chair naturally I sit on the sofa
facing him a few minutes later the husband will die on the floor over there
but I haven't made that move yet so I have to decide when to eliminate him
I'll do it when the wife leaves the room where did she go to the kitchen to make
us some tea she has stabbed in the back before she even has a chance to serve it
Obviously then I need to make my move on the husband while she's occupied in the
kitchen. I reach in, pull out the knife. The husband sees this, panics, tries to
stand up. I stab him, but I miss and end up slashing him. The husband runs off
with blood dripping from his wounded left hand. So I try to get him again. I
swing the knife. This time I only puncture his right shoulder. I'm such a clumsy
amateur. Desperately the husband yells his wife's name, only she can't hear him
from out in the kitchen recently she's developed a hearing problem yes turns
out I knew about that didn't I go on shout all you want I can take my time to
kill you and then your wife you're trapped there's your left hand print on
the wall you can't get away from me I've got you pinned against this table
you're finished but then something prevents me from completing the task
It's five meters from this point to where the husband dies.
How come? Why not just eliminate him here and be done with it?
Why wait?
I've never seen him.
Do you suspect he's the one who broke in and murdered my neighbors?
For the moment I can only say he's a person of interest,
but I'm asking everybody in the neighborhood
for their cooperation in this matter.
If you see this man, just act normal.
I don't want him to become suspicious.
Then get in touch with me as soon as you possibly can.
That would be all I need for you to do.
I personally assure you, you won't be in any danger.
Hard to imagine such a tragic event like this happening here.
It's such a pleasant, quiet neighborhood.
It really is.
And the Yopes were such nice people, just the best.
the best when I call out to her from my doorstep mrs. yo pay would always greet
me cheerfully that's very interesting I've been told mrs. yo pay lost her
hearing about a year ago and refused a hearing aid huh are you sure it was in
her medical record if I had to guess she really couldn't hear any of your
greetings oh well knowing the type of person she was she probably sensed my
presence and wanted to make me feel good so then in your opinion nobody else in
the neighborhood knew about her hearing loss either no I wouldn't think so it
certainly appears that your business is booming you made rapid progress at an
early age it's not easy for a young man to achieve such quick success mr. jeep
oh you're right the contracts I made with the car manufacturers just happened
to work out before we begin I'd like to extend my deepest condolences for the
recent loss of your aunt and uncle. Thank you. Their passing was a great loss. They were the
only relatives I had left in the world. It appears they never had any children of their own,
so they must have taken good care of you since you were their only nephew.
Yes. They treated me as if I were their son. Sir, tell me you'll be able to catch the murderer.
I will. I'm pretty sure I know who's behind it. Me too. I bet it was that Japanese doctor,
wasn't it? Sounds like you're very well informed. Well, of course I am. As a matter of fact,
I've heard he's been linked to other murders similar to this I'm curious just
how much do you stand to inherit you see I found out that mr. yo pay was quite a
wealthy man so what his wealth has nothing to do with this serial murder
case sir I presume you are the sole heir to their considerable estate seeing as
how you are their only nephew it's inappropriate to be discussing my
inheritance in these circumstances a company can appear to be booming on the
surface but underneath may have serious cash flow problems that have gotten out
of hand it's a common occurrence in the business world just a minute you're
implying I murdered them when there's a serial killer on the loose how dare you
what are you so worried about you have a perfect alibi for the time in question
and you have plenty of witnesses you bought your secretary and some others a
a nice dinner after a long meeting what what exactly are you getting at that it
appears that you could not be the murderer I'm sure you agree
inspector lungi well what do you want kipper what the hell is going on going
on with what don't play dumb inspector I've been out digging up stuff on that
nephew for the last couple days his company looks profitable at first glance
but turns out to be holding a lot of bad stocks and bonds.
Cash-wise, it's in a world of hurt.
And now, I found out you've been investigating the same company.
I want the truth. Who killed those folks, Lungay?
In light of what you've uncovered,
do you still think this case is related to the other middle-aged murders?
All of the newspapers have printed a variation of my story.
If the cases aren't related, then it's just sensational journalism.
My reputation could be damaged.
Your instincts are correct.
It's the work of a copycat.
It was set up to look like the serial killer.
That's just great.
I've got to publish a retraction right away.
No.
It's fine as it is.
Huh?
You'll continue writing your follow-up stories
as if this case were another one of the middle-aged couple murders.
What?
It's not ethical.
No way.
I won't do it, I tell you.
Oh, but you will.
I'm an honest journalist who believes in reporting the whole truth.
And you're not going to tell me what I can write.
Well, let me give you the truth.
You have good taste, really. She's quite lovely.
You have a pleasant home,
with a devoted wife and a doting daughter who both adore you.
But it was impossible for you to resist the charms
of that attractive other woman, wasn't it?
Continue as before.
No, beef it up a little.
Write a special report about the serial murders.
If you do as I've asked,
He'll most certainly come
I'm counting on you
Yes, who is it
Excuse me ma'am. May I ask you some questions?
Well sounds like the yo pace were really a wonderful couple
They were.
I see. And you're absolutely certain they didn't have any adopted children?
Oh, yes.
Did any children, children that you'd never seen before, live with them, even for a short time?
No, never. But they took very good care of their nephew. He was the apple of their eye.
Ah, would you like more tea? It won't take a minute.
Uh, I'm fine.
A little more tea won't hurt you.
There's no mistaking him.
He's the man from that photo, and he's in my dining room right now.
Nothing to worry about.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Inspector Lungay, someone's here to see you.
Well, who is it?
He says he's the nephew of the Yopes, that couple that was killed.
inspector you believe i'm the one who murdered them i'm your suspect right you think i killed
my aunt and uncle for their money that's what you hinted at the other day let's face it we both know
that i have many debts right now and the inheritance money they ended up leaving me will more than
likely get me out of this whole mess however that's not the kind of person i am is that really
all you came here to tell me all i came here to wait a minute how dare you speak to me in such
a condescending way well if you'll excuse me there's somewhere i have to be right at the moment
don't you walk away i demand an apology for your disrespectful behavior
perhaps you weren't aware that the police had been following you well now that order has been
cancelled your local law enforcement thinks that you're innocent isn't that good enough for you mr
jeebel well do you agree with them or am i still the prime target of your investigation
you want to know if i think you're guilty that really doesn't matter to me at the moment
my chief concern is to catch the man i've been after
the blood stain over there can only mean one thing
he must have missed then am I to assume that you're convinced the Japanese doctor is responsible for
killing my aunt and uncle never assume anything I've concluded it was a copycat murder made to
look like the middle-aged couples homicides but how can you be so certain about that because
there's one element this case has it makes it different from all the others the killer cornered
victim here but he doesn't finish him off he waits till his victim gets over there before
delivering the final blow but why why does the murderer hesitate
it's not him that element is emotion emotion yes you see the man i'm after always takes
small valuables he tries to make his crimes look like robberies he murders
quickly without hesitation or emotion at least that's his goal but this crime
scene is full of emotions the killer panicked when he saw his face and the
victim's face together in the mirror you needn't worry from what I've observed
the police in this town are totally incompetent
This crime was definitely not committed by Johan.
But somebody wants the police to pin it on him.
How much longer is this all going to continue?
When will it end?
Hello. It's been a while.
So we finally meet again, Dr. Tenma.
I've been looking all over for you, for a very long time.
I've been hoping to have a quiet chat with you.
There's no use in running away anymore.
Stop trying to escape and talk to me.
The fact is, there's no place you can hide, Dr. Tenma.
Yes, you're all mine.
Why couldn't you just leave it alone?
I'm guilty. I confess. I want to turn myself in, all right? I'm the one who came in and killed him!
Your confession means nothing to me. Just stay out of my way.
Tim, come on!
He's been seriously wounded.
I've got to do something now or he's going to bleed to death.
Who could have stabbed Inspector Lungay?
I'll drop him off in front of the hospital and get away.
Damn. Where are they?
I need the keys to the handcuffs. Tell me where you put them, Inspector.
Don't bother reaching for your gun. I took it off you while you were unconscious.
Don't be so stubborn! Just give me the keys! I'm a doctor, but I can't help you like this!
I examined your wound the best I could. It appears that only your muscles sustain the damage.
But you're losing an awful lot of blood. If we don't stop the bleeding, you're going to die!
Come on, confess. Do it, Dr. Tenma.
Confess to what?
That you murdered the director of Eisler Memorial Hospital along with three others.
And that you've been on a three-year killing spree targeting middle-aged couples.
It's time to come clean and admit what you've done.
If you keep this up, you'll be a dead man.
Come on, Doctor. Don't try to fool me.
You're only fooling yourself by running around chasing this elusive Johan.
Johan doesn't exist. Admit it. You made him up. You're a killer.
You're Johan, Dr. Tenma. Own up to it.
Inspector, right now you require emergency treatment.
I have everything I need to do the procedure.
Except for my hands! They're my tools and I can't save your life with them chained together!
Yes. When you're the well-liked Dr. Tenma, those are the hands of a highly skilled surgeon who has saved many lives.
But how many people have you killed with those hands?
You've got it wrong. I'm not a killer.
No, but you change into Johan.
When does the good doctor turn into the bad monster?
I already told you, you're mistaken.
Then let me tell you, I never make mistakes.
Your blood pressure's falling. You're going to lose consciousness soon.
Your crime scenes are always...
No more talking. It'll weaken you.
Your crime scenes are always lacking in something an emotional factor
Save your strength dealing with life and death every day forces doctors to check their emotions
Right. Dr. Tenma you develop a cold exterior and it's that coldness. I always find it your crime scenes
Cold calm emotionless taking of life. I am NOT that kind of man
Every time I operate a thousand emotions go through my head
They affect my every decision.
Is my diagnosis accurate?
Will there be any unforeseen complications?
Will my patient even survive?
How can I be calm when I hold a person's life in my hands?
In these hands.
How in the hell can I be calm?
Don't come closer. Stop.
I can save you.
I will. Shoot.
I need my hands to stop the bleeding.
Are the keys in your pants pocket?
Tell me.
I will.
You really had us worried for a while.
But you're looking quite well.
Lots better than when you're running around investigating crimes.
I guess this means you're not rid of me yet.
Yeah, you'll be back on your feet in no time.
That emergency procedure you received before you got here was done perfectly.
Your doctor said you wouldn't be alive without it.
I'm assuming that Temma got his hands free and used them to save my life.
Yeah, well, he got away, but we got Jeebel.
He confessed to murdering the Yope couple.
He stabbed you because you were on to him.
You did good, Lunge.
Thank you.
Well, what do you think?
About what?
It's quite clear that Tenma saved Lunge's life,
so I'm worried Lunge might have a problem pursuing him now.
I'm wondering if I should remove him from the Tenma case.
I'm sorry, did he call for you again?
Inspector Lunge can be very demanding.
Oh, he really isn't that difficult at all.
In fact, I find him to be very pleasant.
I keep telling him not to rush through the recovery process,
but he's quite determined.
He's already working on strengthening his grip and he's taking long walks down the hall.
He seems to be having a really fun time recovering.
He's having fun?
Yes, he's always telling me that nothing has been more enjoyable for him than...
What was the suspect's name again?
Oh yes, it was Tenma.
That chasing after a criminal like Tenma is the most fun he could ever have.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
© transcript Emily Beynon