you wake up leave me alone yeah like that's gonna happen now get up we can
still do this the easy way come on this isn't a hotel don't touch me how dare
you do you have any idea who I am
♪ He is risen ♪
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- All right, here's all the stuff you came in with.
If everything's in order, you can sign here.
Miss Heinemann, I don't ever want to see you tossed in the cooler again.
Passing out drunk, alone in a dark alley.
Be thankful something horrible didn't happen to you.
You got a cigarette?
Huh?
I'm just asking if you've got a cigarette.
There's no smoking in the station.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GROANING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Lighter. Where is my lighter?
My bag!
I want to know what you did with my bag.
And I already told you it's the only bag you had.
You liar! I know you're not telling me the truth. I had another shoulder bag. Where is it?
Probably with whoever stole it from you when you passed out drunk in the alley.
What are you going to do about it? I had valuables, important things in there.
I'll tell you what you can fill out a theft report if you like, but I really wouldn't get your hopes up
How the hell did you lose your keys my bag was stolen last night just hurry up and open the room for me
Huh
What what happened here
Damn, somebody really went to town.
Aw, man, this is awful.
I gotta change the lock now.
Which reminds me, Ms. Heineman, you still owe me back rent.
I don't wanna have to ask you again.
The deposit you put down has already run out.
I'm gonna need the rest of what you owe soon.
These people even broke into my damn suitcase.
Are you listening?
You have to pay for a new lock and all that back rent!
Well, I don't have any money.
- What?
- Fine, I'll get out.
Don't worry.
- Such a tragic story.
But still, I don't know what you expect me
to do about any of it.
You know, I seem to remember you being
the one who stormed out on me.
- Oh, come on.
That's all ancient history now.
So why not buy me a drink?
- Please, Ava.
It's just a stolen purse for God's sake.
You must've had some extra cash tucked away somewhere.
Honestly, I've yet to meet another woman
who could burn through money the way you do.
And here you are, finally coming to me for some cash.
This is it.
Welcome to rock bottom, baby.
- So how much?
- Huh?
- I'll sleep with you, you know.
I'm asking you how much you'd be willing to pay.
- [laughs]
My God.
Honey, as a general rule,
most men won't pay to have sex with women
they've already had a bunch of times.
You can at least buy me a drink.
Go find yourself a street corner to work.
Who knows, you might get lucky and meet some sad sack who's not too picky.
Desperate and middle-aged and drunk must be someone's type.
[laughing nervously]
Yeah, I'm positive you didn't leave any purse here last night.
Maybe you left it wherever you went next.
I don't remember anything after I left this bar you mentioned you had something important in your bag
If it's worth any money, you might as well kiss it. Goodbye
No, it's not it's not worth anything at all not any money that is
Hey, I've been looking for you I
Asked for you at the pub back there
And they told me you'd just headed in this direction.
Yeah, and who are you?
Are you serious?
We had such a good time drinking last night.
I was drinking with you?
Your bag.
That's why I was looking for you.
I guess this means I have to make awkward introductions again.
I'm Roberto.
So, shall we grab a little something to eat?
Your hotel room really that's terrible. I'm so sorry. Well, whatever. I mean, it's not like you did it
Well, no, obviously not. I didn't even dare look in your bag
Oh, look, my hotel keys are still in here a little late for those. I don't need them anymore. I'm sorry
It's all my fault if I'd returned your bag sooner
You wouldn't have been kicked out of your room in the first place. Hey, it wasn't your fault at all
Besides, I'm very grateful that you gave me back my bag.
Honestly, I'm kind of grateful that you lost it.
Huh?
Well, last night, as I watched you leave the pub,
I sat there thinking to myself,
"You shouldn't let this person slip away."
And now, thanks to your bag, here you are and here I am.
Hmm.
You have something very important in there, don't you?
I do.
This is all that I have left in the world.
Oh, a photo album. May I take a look?
You may.
That's my father.
He looks just like I imagined. He was a hospital director, right?
Yeah. Did I talk about him last night?
You did. You spoke very highly of him.
You mentioned that he died 10 years ago.
I could tell that you still miss him.
Let's see.
Ah, the ex-fiance.
- Please, don't tell me I told you about him.
- I believe his name was Tenma?
Quite a guy, this Tenma.
- I really wanna know what I said last night.
- Well, I wouldn't make a habit of it.
It might end up making other men jealous.
(laughing)
- Well, odd, this page is empty.
- Is that so?
- The photos that were on this page
looks like somebody tore them out.
- Well, I guess I didn't need those pictures anymore.
- So I see.
- Hey.
Let's get a drink.
- Sounds good.
So, you were running a security company.
I'm impressed.
Yeah.
In the south of France.
Then we had a bad day and one of our better clients was killed on my watch.
So that was the end of that.
We're both going through tough times.
Nah, forget it.
Let's drink to the here and now.
Mm-hmm
That's on it's good stuff, huh? So you like this song too, of course
Let's dance
(clears throat)
- Come on.
- Well, I don't really know how to dance.
- Just put your arms around me.
Good.
I knew a man who loved this song.
He wasn't a very good dancer either.
So, you'd end up dancing like this?
That's right.
(laughing)
How fun. How about another drink?
Just one more? Thanks, but I'm good.
Lightweight.
Time for bed. Sounds good to me, babe.
Mm-hmm
There's just one more thing I want to ask you
What's that?
the pictures
Where are they?
What pictures?
Those photographs you took out of the album, where'd you hide them?
- Tell me.
You see, I'm on to your little secret.
You're looking for Tenma, aren't you?
I know you kept those photos from burning
and I'm sure you have them with you somewhere.
- What?
You're saying you know where Tenma is?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
[laughing]
The photographs that you're talking about...
They're the ones with Father and that boy, am I right?
Johan, wasn't it?
[laughing]
I've seen him, you know.
Blond, charming, handsome.
He's grown up well.
I saw him a year ago in Dusseldorf.
Kenzo. Let's start over. You... you need me.
Kenzo.
You belong to me.
I will get you back.
Because you're mine.
So, what are you up to these days?
I've heard all sorts of rumors.
The rumors are probably true.
I've been married and divorced three times now.
Between my father's inheritance and my alimony,
I'm living pretty comfortably.
But enough about me.
How has life been treating you, Dr. Becker?
Huh? I don't know.
Nothing's changed with me.
I still have no chance of moving up in the world.
Tenma's now Chief of Surgery.
Word is, he's on his way to becoming Hospital Director.
Love to be in his shoes, let me tell you.
But please, who am I kidding? It ain't so bad.
I still manage to have a good time.
There's more to life than promotions.
I'd never want to be like Tenma and have no time for women or fun.
What's the point?
Is Kenzo...
Do you know by any chance if Dr. Tenma ever did settle down?
No, not yet.
And to be completely honest, I've introduced him to quite a few very nice women.
But you know him, no interest at all. His work comes first.
As a matter of fact, I'm about to set him up with a new girl.
God only knows if it's gonna work out.
She's the daughter of a state senator, and she is absolutely beautiful.
If she can't keep his attention, then I give up.
But, anyway, you called me about something.
How can I be of service, Ava?
You know, back when you were the daughter of the hospital director,
You gave me the time of day.
Who would have thought that you'd even think to call?
I understand you're well off, but really,
I think you're getting lonely, aren't you?
I mean it when I say it, Ava.
I'm more than happy to listen, anytime.
- Look, I don't want you to let them meet up.
- Huh?
- Dr. Tenma and the state senator's daughter.
Don't let him meet her.
- Man, I should have known.
You're still in love with him.
Don't let him.
[Rain falling]
Do me a favor, don't screw it up this time.
I went out of my way to set this one up for you, Tenma.
[laughs] Well, we'll see about that.
Hmm?
This is it.
This is the clock that Mr. Junkers was talking about at the hospital.
Excuse me, about the clock in the window--
Hey, what's going on?
You're already late for your date.
What are you doing?
That's a very beautiful watch.
Oh.
Why, thank you.
I mean, I wear a watch, but mine is nothing, a trinket.
I don't even check the time anymore.
I wonder why.
Time seems to be moving faster and faster.
Um, excuse me, but who are you?
I'm sorry, I don't mean to be rude,
but are you Senator Berker's daughter, Angelica?
Yes.
Goodness.
You're a pretty little thing.
Well, aren't you?
Uh, thank you, I think?
(laughing)
And you're convinced that the entire world
revolves around you, am I right?
Going through life thinking that there's nothing you can't have, it must be very pleasant.
I'm sorry, what are you trying to say? I'm confused. Who are you exactly?
I have this tiny little birthmark on my inner thigh. He used to kiss it.
How he used to love kissing me there. Dr. Tenma, that is. You know him?
Oh
No
See see she left because you were late and it's all because you had to stop in that store. Oh
Too bad. I'm sorry about that. Can you do me a favor and apologize for me?
Wait, hey Tenma
Maybe if you give her a call right now, she might come back.
Who knows?
I want to stop by the hospital for a quick minute.
What?
At this hour?
Ah!
I've had it with you!
Fine.
Leave.
(car engine rumbling)
- Kenzo.
You're mine.
You're all mine.
Mr. Junkers!
Please wait!
Kenzo...
What's going on?
Wait!
Kenzo!
I have to talk to you!
Mr. Junkers!
Kenzo! Please, just wait!
Kenzo?
[dramatic music]
Oh, great. I broke my heel.
♪ ♪
[sobbing]
Kenzo!
[gunshot]
♪ ♪
[gunshots]
[GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Kenzo.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I saw him, you know.
Oh, yes.
A year ago in Dusseldorf.
I saw him.
It was Johan, I'm sure of it.
You saw Johan, huh?
Guess I'll have to kill you.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)