(eerie music)
- You saw Johan, huh?
Guess I'll have to kill you.
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(laughing)
I guess I've seen something that I wasn't supposed to see.
I'm thinking it was that sweet-looking blond boy I saw in Dusseldorf a year ago.
Because I've seen Johan, this is how it ends up.
That's how it works with you.
It was dark and raining when I heard those three gunshots.
I was there alone and got scared, so I ran away.
At the time, I was pretty certain it was Tenma who'd been shot dead.
But the next day, there was this big article in the newspaper
saying that a man named Junkers had been found dead in the same location
and that he'd been shot three times.
So then that boy did it, didn't he?
Might want to rethink pulling that trigger.
If you kill me, you'll never get what you really want.
That photograph you've been looking for,
Let me tell you what will happen if you do decide to kill me.
If I die, I've arranged for that photo you want so much
to be delivered directly to the BKA.
If you want to see that photograph,
you need to tell me exactly where Tenma can be found.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
- Just what is so funny?
- Your whole body's quivering.
♪ ♪
You talk tough, but your legs are shaking so hard,
you can barely stand.
- [panting]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
You really do amuse me.
I'll tell you where he is.
So what is Tenma up to now?
Oh, he's still working as a doctor,
but our friend has gone underground.
Where is he?
There was this older guy in Hanover
who was the number two man in a certain organized crime family.
Well, this guy's boss kind of freaked out
and put out a hit on him, but the job got botched.
The guy got all shut up, but he didn't die.
Setemba's at this remote alpine estate, patching him up.
It's up on a mountain near Fusen.
(crickets chirping)
(footsteps)
(gasps)
- Excuse me, but why do you just stand there like that?
(birds chirping)
- Hey mister, it's almost time for lunch.
(thunder rumbling)
- Why in the world are we eating outside?
- I just thought,
the weather looks so nice this afternoon.
Why not mix up our routine and eat outside?
Well, have our lunch out here.
Dieter, go ahead and bring the plates out here.
Okay.
All your wounds are healing nicely,
and this fresh air will do you good.
I have to say, Doctor,
if you hadn't been there, I doubt I would have made it.
That country clinic was pathetic,
but the masterful skills you possess allowed you to save my life.
Maybe the one bullet just grazed your head and the other one went into your leg and passed through cleanly
Just be thankful. It didn't catch your femoral artery to be honest. You were quite lucky
hmm
Lucky, huh? Right. All righty guys lunch is sir. Wow. That smells good heckle
Surprising isn't it? It tastes delicious
Heckle may look more like a pickpocket,
but he's actually quite the chef, don't you agree?
Hey, and what in the hell did you mean by that?
This, my friends, is chicken meringue.
The key to the dish is the sauce.
You have to get it just right.
It's based on a recipe from a three-star French restaurant
called Le Petit Mess--
We don't care how it's made, just how it tastes.
A runt like you just can't appreciate
the subtleties of fine cuisine.
You know, this would taste even better
with a dash of soy sauce.
Soy sauce? Not that again.
You put soy sauce on everything.
Now, this is dining.
When you sit down to eat, this is how it should be.
What a waste.
All my life, everything I did was to make money.
But while I was earning all those millions,
I lost things much more valuable.
Both of my parents and my only brother disowned me.
Even my wife and son were murdered.
I always wanted to live peacefully
and dine like we're doing right now.
Money can really change the way people act.
Allow me to share a good example with you.
Five years ago, a covert banking organization was formed
to facilitate the underground funds flowing throughout Germany.
What these guys pulled off was absolutely amazing.
Within days of the dirty money flowing in through shady companies,
it would come out the other side perfectly clean.
Ah, a money laundering operation.
Exactly.
On top of that, this organization functioned in many ways like a real bank,
making loans and investing in speculative transactions.
And it grew unbelievably fast.
In five short years, they'd made a fortune.
Hot damn!
But that all changed this year,
suddenly vanished. He hasn't been seen in months and no one knows where he went. Guess
what happened then? All of it fell apart. The entire operation imploded. The associates
that remained started fighting over who would get what was left and who would be in charge.
Most of them ended up killing each other and the entire operation disappeared. If only
They'd been sensible and talk things out while sharing a fine dinner
So
You think that guy got murdered or did he just run off?
Huh? Keep up doc. I mean the head honcho guy who disappeared so kidnapped murdered. What do you think? Oh, no
I'm quite sure he's still alive
In fact, he might even be posing as a student somewhere a student
That's right. I forgot to tell you. I left out something important.
According to my sources, the guy who created that money laundering organization five years ago was just a kid.
Fifteen years old.
Fifteen years old? Your sources must be nuts.
No way a kid could pull off something like that.
But it's true. This kid did it.
It's as if he was conducting his own experiment to see how adults deal with money.
As though he were a child, playing around with a line of ants.
Where was all this?
Do you know where this covert banking operation was based?
The organization was headquartered in Dusseldorf, but the kid at the top was constantly on the
move.
He controlled the entire operation from wherever he was, you know?
And did anybody figure out the last place that he was seen before he disappeared?
That's all the details I know, but I heard right after their young boss went missing,
all of his money-hungry underlings went rushing to Munich.
To Munich, eh?
Hey, Doc, why the long face, huh? What's going on?
I know. Let's invite that man down the hill up here for lunch.
Sure. Why not? That's a good idea.
Sorry, Doctor, but that man's my bodyguard.
He needs to stay down there.
But haven't you been officially declared dead already?
You still think there are people out there who want to do you harm?
Are you planning to live the rest of your life in fear?
Hiding behind a bodyguard?
Helmut has been with me for a very long time, indeed.
Go ahead, son. Go and get Helmut.
So that's his name. He wouldn't talk to me at all.
I bet. Go and tell him that his duties as my bodyguard are over.
He's the only one left who's like family to me.
Ask him to join us.
Have him come here so we can discuss our future at this table.
Okay!
Mr. Helmut! Lunchtime! They want you to come up and join us!
Temma's right up there in the mountain villa.
You do want to kill him, don't you?
(phone ringing)
- Is something the matter?
- That was a security breach signal from Helmut.
Unfortunately, I think he's already dead.
- Wait, someone's coming after ya?
- There's no tellin', but I'd say someone's
heading up here even as we speak.
- Mr. Helmut, sir!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Go tell him.
You have to tell him to run away.
Hurry, go and tell Tenma now.
Tell him, damn it!
[ grunting ]
[ gunshot ]
Lady!
I said go tell him!
But your leg! You've been shot!
Don't worry about me! Go!
Hang on! Who's shooting at us?
[ gunshot ]
Did... did you get him?
I'm not sure.
But now's your chance to run for it. Get going!
You're out here in the open! I can help you!
Listen, I can handle this! Just go!
No, you can't! We need to go and hide! Quick!
Well, well. Looks like I was wrong.
She didn't want to kill Temma after all.
You gonna be alright, ma'am?
I'll be fine. But I think he's already heading up the hill on his way to the villa.
Not a chance. I would have seen him from here.
There's really only one path to get all the way up to that house.
What are you talking about?
I've explored this whole mountain,
and this path is the only way up there.
All the other paths lead to cliffs no one can climb.
So then if we guard this trail,
there's no other way Roberto will be able to get far enough
up the mountain to get to the villa.
You mean you know this guy?
I know him too well.
Roberto's after Tenma, and he wants to kill him.
You know Tenma? So who are you, ma'am?
Don't make me sound so old. Stop calling me "ma'am."
Now get out of here, kid. You get up there and tell Tenma.
Tell him to run away quick.
But... but, ma'am... I mean, lady, you're bleeding.
I'll be all right. You just get up there and warn him.
But your leg looks like it's bleeding a lot.
Tenma must've heard those gunshots.
I bet he's headed down here to take care of that guy.
But that's not good.
Roberto wants Tenma to come down here and try to save us so he can kill him.
Don't you see? It's a trap, and we're the bait to bring him here.
But what can we do, ma'am?
If we try to make a run for it with your leg, you might bleed to death!
Stop calling me "ma'am"! What did I tell you?
So just what are you to Tenma, anyway?
I'm his friend. What about you, ma-- I mean, lady?
Aren't you a friend of Tenma's, too?
You must be, 'cause even though you're hurt really bad, you're still trying to save him!
I'm not trying to be nosy, but you like Tenma, don't you?
Are you his girlfriend?
You just keep watching that side.
Do you like Tenma?
Yeah, I like him a whole lot.
What exactly do you like about him?
Lots of things. What do you like about him?
"I know you're there!
Crawl around all you want, but you'd be pretty stupid to shoot me again!
I already told you, if I die, that picture of Johan as a child that you want so badly
will automatically be sent straight to the BKA!
I mean it!
This is your last warning!
If you ever want to see that photo, then you'd better get the hell out of here right now!"
So that photo you've got is something he really wants.
It's a lie.
Huh?
And it might not work.
He's too smart to fall for such a trick.
Lady, are you feeling all right?
I'm starting to fade.
I've lost a lot of blood.
Now go.
Well, get out of here.
Save yourself.
I can't just leave you.
Tenma's on his way.
He would have been here by now.
He's got to be headed here.
I mean it.
There's no way he would ever come to save me.
Nothing but a waste of time.
- Deidara!
Deidara, where are you?
- Tenma, I'm over here!
- Just stay there!
I'm coming to get you, Deidara!
- Don't move!
If you try to come get us,
there's a man here that's going to shoot you.
That's why he's come here, Tenma,
- Wait, I know that voice, but it can't be.
- Tenma, this lady's a friend of yours.
She's been shot and she's bleeding a lot.
- It's Eva.
- You can't die now, not when I'm so close.
I'm handing you over to the police, Kenzo,
so you can rot in jail for the rest of your life.
You hear me?
You've got decades of suffering ahead of you.
I want every waking moment to hurt for dumping me.
Stop shouting! You're straining yourself!
Hey, Dieter! Just tell me if you can hear me, okay?
Can you tell where the shooter is?
No, I don't know!
I've got no clue where he is, or even if he's still here!
Stop yelling, Tenma.
I need Tenma alive.
Hang in there! He's getting close!
He's not coming, Dieter. You're wrong.
He would never come to my rescue.
It's all over for me.
Don't die, please!
Why would he ever want to rescue me?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[panting]
- Kenzo.
[thunder rumbling]
What's all this? Why'd you bring me out here?
It's time for lunch. Your leg has been healing up nicely.
And I thought you'd enjoy eating lunch outside in this beautiful sunshine.
You're a lucky woman, you know?
What do you mean, lucky?
Just that. The guy who shot you was a real pro. He knew what he was doing.
He understood how difficult it would be for him to infiltrate this mountain villa.
There's only one path to get up here, and there are security cameras everywhere.
He also knew this villa would be guarded by experienced men, so it would be like he was
attacking an alpine fortress.
That was the reason he used you.
Hold on.
What do you mean, he used me?
It's simple.
He must have figured that a pretty woman making an unexpected visit would have a much better
chance of getting all the way up here than he would.
But when you betrayed him, his whole plan was sunk.
He had no plan B. There were no other options for him.
So he got out of here quick and cut his losses.
- So then he got away. - That's right.
We searched the whole mountain.
This here's a special dish. It's called chicken merengue.
I tried to recreate the recipe,
but I can't guarantee it'll be any good.
You know, there's another way you were very lucky.
like Dr. Tenma treating you.
So is Tenma still here?
No. He already left.
Where to?
Think he said something about going to Munich.
Munich, eh?
All right.
Let's see if you and I can enjoy this chicken.
I got a feeling you like me.
I bet it's been a long time since you sat down and enjoyed a meal in peace.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)