Oh, Corinna, why are your letters ever, ever so short, as with Eupolis, the scholar of
the stars, and his, uh, astrology?
You drive my heart mad, and such the gold of ideas, its colors faded while the work
of the artisan--
Oh, enough already!
Well, what are you waiting for put the book on the shelf and go if I did something to offend me
You're offending me right now
I'm not sure what I did to upset you sir
But I'm sorry nonetheless if you can't wrap your tongue or your brain around Latin
You're of no use to me as a reader understood. I'm sorry, sir. I'll be more careful. I
Told you to get out
[MUSIC]
He really tore into you back at the mansion, didn't he?
Don't mope, Carl.
Business majors should have thicker skin than that.
Huh?
Uh, I'm sorry, but do I know you?
A cultural anthropology major.
I'm guessing you work for him, too.
Are you another one of his part-time student readers?
No, I'm more of a housekeeper.
Whatever needs doing.
He only lets boys do the reading,
as I'm sure you already know.
Anyway, he's got a different reader each day of the week.
Your Tuesdays, of course.
Hey, so what do you think of our boss, anyway?
The ever-mysterious Hans Georg Shuval, reclusive tycoon?
It's me. I was looking for work and the money was good.
Honestly, that's all I needed to know.
Wait, are you saying you've never heard the rumors about him?
He works the stock market like a marionette.
One phone call from him leaves banks across Germany quaking in their boots.
They call him the Howard Hughes of Bavaria.
He has no family, no close friends. It's just him and his money.
His fortune keeps growing and growing every year.
What on earth does he spend it on anyway?
Who knows?
Shuvalt's other nickname is the Vampire of Bavaria.
How come?
Just as the clock strikes 2 a.m.,
Shuvalt's manservant loads him into a car,
like a hearse, and whisks him off into the night.
I've seen it myself.
It's like something out of a horror movie.
Maybe he's getting some air.
I'll find out soon enough what old Shuvalt's up to.
What do you mean you're going to find out?
It's for my research paper, silly.
"Mental Activities of Medieval and Present-Day Financial Figures of Bavaria."
I looked out. Shuvald's a goldmine.
So you looked me up 'cause he yelled at me, is that it?
Just your name and your major. I'm not a snoop.
Anyway, I wouldn't lose any sleep over him chewing you out.
He yells at all the guys who read to him.
Yeah. Well, I guess it's a good thing I'm used to getting yelled at.
What do you mean?
Uh, it's just... I spent a lot of time in foster homes.
Some of them weren't so nice.
Oh, so that's why there's no record of you at any of the local high schools.
You looked up more than my major and name.
That's gotta be rough, growing up without your real parents like that.
The truth is, I came to Munich for school because I thought maybe I could find my mother.
She's here in Munich? That's great! Have you seen her yet?
"No, it wasn't meant to be."
"Huh? What do you mean? You can't just throw in the towel!"
"Hey, you don't happen to know your mom's name?"
"Uh-huh."
"Well, go ahead."
"It wasn't meant to be, okay?"
"Come on, tell me! If you don't, we both know I'm gonna look her up anyway."
"Margo. Her name is Margo Langer."
Silly you have her full name and you were ready to give up like that find her. What are you waiting for?
No, it's too late for reunions
Here we go Margo Langer, what do we got?
Oh, no
Like a chestnut mare at full stride passion electric
Uh, "Sparking Great Waves."
I can't bear this.
Only beautiful things are deserving of my love.
Your reading pains me.
Why didn't you explain, Carl?
If only I had known.
Now I understand why you gave up looking.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I already said that it doesn't matter, didn't I?
Carl, if there's anything I can do, just ask me.
That's sweet of you, but I'm fine.
Carl, I...
Hey, Lotte.
You said you wanted to figure out where Schuwald goes at night.
You're going to follow him, right?
Would you mind if I came along for the ride?
No, not at all.
Sure does beat sneaking through the darkness by myself.
I'm telling you, it's true!
Our Supernatural Phenomena Research Group
has finally hit pay dirt!
There is no way!
In any case, listen up.
Bishop Gropius, one of the founders of our school,
wrote this poem in the year 1502.
That much we already know for sure.
Now, consider the following verse.
"On the second to the last big year,
"the boy of Thursday will arrive upon the land,
"and the book shall go up in flames,
The entire world will be shrouded in sorrow. Crazy, huh?
So it's spooky. What's your point again?
Don't you get it, guys?
Look, it says right here, the second to the last big year.
What year is it? 1996, right?
So that means this is the year.
How do you figure?
Listen, the big year means leap year.
And the only leap years left in this century are this year and the year 2000.
He will arrive upon the land and the book shall go up in flames.
about the books in this land means that this university will go up in flames.
Okay, then. Who's this boy of Thursday, huh?
Thursday. Well, let's see. Donor star comes from the word "donor."
Yeah, and "donor" means "thunder." The god of thunder!
You've lost your damn mind.
Hey, this is going to be the front page story of our next newsletter.
It's no laughing matter.
I'll run the article if it'll make you happy, but come on, nobody's gonna buy this.
A god of destruction coming to our university?
Some vampire of Bavaria he is.
We've gone through all this trouble to figure out what the great big mystery was.
And this is what we find out.
Quiet. There he goes.
Well, that was stupid. I'm out of here.
- Huh? Carl? - I want to see what he was up to.
What do you think he was up to?
Hey, maybe this isn't such a good idea.
You're probably right. This is no place for a girl. You should go home.
Only beautiful things are deserving of my love. And...
Yeah?
I need to know. I need to know how miserable of a man he really is.
Yeah, it's open.
If you're looking for some fun, you came knocking on the wrong door.
I got out of the business a long time ago, kid.
Who are you?
Nice manners, kid. You want my name?
Shouldn't we start with yours?
Margot Langer. Pleasure's all mine.
I bet you're students from the university, aren't you?
Uh, right.
And both of us have part-time jobs working for Hans Schuwalt.
Congratulations.
What do you want?
Tell me why.
Why does he come here to see you in the middle of the night like he does?
I make him feel better.
But not in the way you're thinking.
Just 'cause he's up at this hour,
doesn't mean he's up at this hour if you catch my drift.
He brings me money. Scabs of it.
Huh?
And why shouldn't he?
When I finally went to Shuvald and told him who I was,
he broke down crying and apologized on the spot.
I had his son and he threw me out on the street
like I was a piece of trash.
Wait, so you're...
Carl, is she saying that you're Han Shuvald's son?
How would you know?
You liar! How dare you!
How dare you pretend to be Margot Langer!
Yeah! The real one was all over the papers a year ago!
Former prostitute Margot...
Former prostitute Margot Langer murdered!
Police say killer still at large!
The woman you call yourself is already dead!
How could any human being stoop so low?
You're using my dead mother's name to kill Shuvald out of his money, and he's falling for it!
(laughing)
Shuvald knows the score.
Oh, he knows I'm not the real thing, but he still gives me money, hand over fist.
All the money in the world can't buy him forgiveness from the real Margo Langer.
That ship has sailed. Guess paying a stand-in's the next best thing.
Money, money, money.
That's all the bastard's been living for,
and the only way he knows how to say sorry.
Don't look so teary-eyed, kid. You know Saint yourself.
You and I both know Shuvald's on his way out.
Take a good look at him.
If you're gonna play the long-lost son card,
better do it while he can change his will.
What are you implying?
You're giving me grief for being an imposter.
but you didn't exactly waltz in here with a positive paternity test.
Just watch out for the competition, boy.
You're not the only one who says he's Shuvald's son.
Huh?
Yeah, he came to see me a little while back,
told me the same sob story you did.
No way...
It can't be...
Carl's telling you the truth!
The other guy's the liar!
"Excuse me if I don't take your word for it.
For the record, I think you're both full of it."
"So this other guy, who is he?"
"Another student.
A bunch of you take turns reading books to Shuvalt, a different boy every day of the
week.
Ain't that right?
You've got that in common, Carl.
Yes, sir.
I think he's...
Uh-huh, he's the Thursday boy."
You could have insisted a little harder that you're his real son.
What's the point? I was passed along from foster home to foster home for most of my life,
usually sending me from bad to worse.
But I finally ended up with a couple who loved me as though I were their very own.
They're everything I ever could have wanted.
But their being so wonderful made me want to meet my biological father even more.
I thought that if I could see what a sad little man he was with my own eyes,
I could finally return my foster parents' love.
That's all I was trying to do.
Hey, Lotte, tell me something.
Have you ever seen this Thursday boy?
That's one day of the week I always have off from work.
But this one Thursday, I went in to grab something I'd forgotten.
And he was there reading, right?
Let me think. I want to say he had blonde hair and a very beautiful face.
Schufald's Thursday boy. Who is he?
Someone in this university is pretending to be me.
Carl, are you listening to me?
This is important. Take this money and ride the train on track number five.
Get off at the eighth station. A lady named Marta will be waiting.
What about you, Mom?
Honey, I already told you, I can't go with you.
But how come? Are you in trouble?
I don't want to go alone, Mom.
You have no choice. If you stay with me, they'll cart you off to some orphanage.
Around here, people will mock you as the son of a whore.
now go on what about my dad can't my dad make it better somehow his name is Hans
Georg Schuwald isn't it who told you that old mrs. Bella from across the
street my dad's rich isn't he she said he
abandoned us how come you would do something like that
He didn't abandon us, Carl.
Then I'll just go where he is and you can find us there.
No, you can't.
So when can I see him?
Oh, Carl.
When you're all grown up, you can meet your father if you want.
Don't hate him if he turns you away.
Please.
Why shouldn't I?
Because Mommy doesn't hate him, even now.
Keep this with you always.
It was a gift from your father on the day you were born.
Carl! I know who he is!
Earth to Carl! I know who the Thursday boy is!
What?
His name is Edmund Farran. He's a philosophy major.
I'm sure he's the guy we're looking for.
He reads books to Schuwald at the mansion every Thursday.
Edmund Farran, huh?
Get ready. He should be coming out of that lecture hall any second.
Hey, you wouldn't happen to know Edmund Farran, would you?
Hmm?
Oh.
Hey, guys.
Is Edmund here?
Who?
Edmund Farran?
I think he was a no-show today.
There you go.
Oh.
Okay.
So he dodged the bullet today.
But seriously, it's only a matter of time before we give that fraud what's coming to
No imposter's gonna cheat you out of Shuvald's inheritance.
It's not about the money.
Huh?
I couldn't care less if I see any part of his fortune.
But Carl...
No. If they want to rob Shuvald blind, they can go right ahead.
Who cares?
Then why?
Because...
Because I can't stand the thought of this bastard Farin pretending to be my mother's son.
There's no forgiving something like that.
With the petals of your silk flowers swaying in the breeze,
the cry of the mockingbird rang through my heart.
You haven't told me to stop reading yet.
Why is that, sir?
I berate you all the time.
Why do you insist on coming back?
Is the money that good?
That isn't why!
With all due respect, sir, it's nothing like that.
Is money the only incentive to do something in your world?
In my world or any other.
What are they like, your parents?
Actually, I was raised by a series of foster families.
I see. Forgive me for prying.
Would you meet your real parents, if you could?
[ Gasping ]
Well, sir, I...
Actually, I'm...
Yes, this young man who reads to me
just may be the one I've waited for.
[ Gasps ]
He doesn't seem to be after my money.
Who is he?
Never mind. I'm talking to myself.
It's time we called it a day, Neumann.
Oh, one more thing.
Regarding your Latin, boy, it is much improved.
Well, thank you very much, sir.
Looks like Edmund Farrin's playing hooky today, too.
I bet he's laying in bed with a bad cold or something like that.
Tomorrow's Thursday. He'll be there.
He'll be at the mansion and so will I.
Oh, I get it.
You're going to bust him as the faker he is right in front of Shuwald, right?
That's awesome. Let's go get him already.
Still no sign of him. He was supposed to be here an hour ago.
If he were sick and stuck in bed, at least then we would know where to find him.
Hey! Wanna barge into his room and confront him there?
Hold on. Don't tell me you looked up Faren's address.
202 and 204. Jackpot!
Here we go.
Knock?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[GASPS]
It's been so grim around here.
The whole school's talking about what happened to Edmund Farrin.
Who'd have thought he'd kill himself?
The school paper actually printed his suicide note, didn't they?
I can no longer continue to deceive.
So that's what it was about.
I guess so.
Spending all that time with Shuvald acting like his son,
maybe the guilt just blindsided him.
If he'd known he was going to grow a conscience, he'd have been better off not trying in the first place.
Lota. Yesterday must have been tough.
Hey, don't you know it?
Since we're the ones who discovered the body, the police held us for questioning all day.
Well, I didn't end up reading today after all.
Mr. Schuwald is taking the news very hard.
Oh, hey, I'm being rude.
This is Carl. He's the Friday Reader.
- A pleasure to meet you.
- The same here.
I'm Carl Neumann from the Economics Department.
- I'm Johann Liebert.
I study in the School of Law.
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)