And you haven't touched a drink since, is that correct?
Absolutely. Not even a drop.
Well, that's very good. But you have to continue to stay away from booze to give yourself the chance to start over.
There's no way I'm going to drink as long as I report to you once a week. I don't want to incur your wrath.
Yeah, just the thought of it makes me afraid.
What are you talking about? I always conduct myself in a very calm, professional manner.
I was kidding. I don't have time to drink anyway.
case since becoming a private investigator.
Well, that's very good news.
Dr. Ryfine, how would you judge this fellow?
What do you mean?
Using your knowledge of physiognomy,
I thought maybe you could tell me what kind of young man
appears in this photograph.
I don't practice physiognomy.
Richard, I'm afraid you're mistaking me
for some kind of quack fortune teller or weirdo psychic.
But you have a well-acknowledged reputation.
You're able to predict someone's behavioral traits
from just a single glance, right?
of accumulating information from observing patients.
Then can you use all of those years of acquired wisdom
to tell me if this guy looks like a con man?
Con man?
That's not possible.
A man with a face like his couldn't fool anyone.
Even if he tried some kind of con, he'd be easily found out.
Uh-huh.
What are the odds that he'd commit suicide?
Absolutely none at all.
People with faces like his would never kill themselves.
Well, I must say, Doctor, your observations seem to be pretty convincing
and give me quite a lot to think about.
And they're based on experience.
So, who hired you, if you don't mind my asking?
Hans-Georg Schuwald.
You're working for Schuwald?
I take it you know who he is, am I right?
Yes, I'm quite familiar with him.
He's the wealthy vampire of Bavaria.
Well, that immensely rich gentleman is my client,
and the young man in the photograph is Edmund Fahren,
who actually passed himself off as Shuvalt's son for a while.
Hmm. He eventually gave himself away?
Not really. Mr. Shuvalt bought every detail of his deception.
It wasn't your typical run-of-the-mill scam artist, you know.
I myself had a lot of trouble figuring out it was a complete fraud.
Even now, some pieces of the mystery about him still remain.
How did Farrin know so much about Shuvalt's missing son?
Where'd he get the information, and who supplied it?
The only way is to go straight to the source
and demand that Farran tell you.
- Yep, normally I would,
but the boy committed suicide, they say.
(choral singing)
(dramatic music)
Oh, come on now, Martin. Think of it as a favor for an old friend. At least let me take a look at the suicide note, huh?
The handwriting's been analyzed. Without a doubt, the kid wrote it himself, okay?
Look, you're an outsider now, Richard. I can't justify bending the rules.
The two kids who found the body, Carl Neumann and Loda Frank, didn't they work at the same part-time job as Edmund Farran?
They were just friends, that's all.
Well, maybe they weren't such good friends.
So, how are you doing anyway? Is it the same old grind?
Yeah, you know how it is. We never have enough personnel.
In fact, I've had no time to rest since I took over your position.
So, thanks a bunch, Richard.
Slowpoke Martin has become one of the big shots now.
You don't get to call me that anymore.
Well, you're not my boss anymore, so I don't have to put up with your wisecracks.
Oh, come on, Martin.
You just don't get it, do you?
You have no idea how much trouble you put us through.
We spent countless hours hunting down that serial killer
and had him in our sights,
but you were drunk as hell and killed him.
Believe me, it was no picnic cleaning up your mess.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I haven't got time to waste on simple suicides.
I'm a very busy investigator with important criminal cases.
- I wanna check out the crime scene.
been preserved right? I already gave the go-ahead to have it cleared out since
it's been determined that there was no crime. They'll be removing all of the
deceased's effects sometime today. Damn it! When did slowpoke Martin become so efficient?
I made it. They're supposed to be arriving anytime now to take everything
Don't worry. I won't be more than a couple of minutes.
He must have hung his rope from this pipe in the ceiling.
And it appears that he wrote a suicide note at this desk.
Here's a paper he was in the middle of writing.
"The Birth of Tragedy," "Process and Reality," "World Views on Psychology."
for the course for a philosophy student.
These must be the materials he was using for his paper.
Hm?
Caesar's Gallic Wars?
Now, what was he doing with this book?
Seems out of place.
Spanish? Or it could be Latin.
I can't read a word of it.
Hm.
This is the only passage underlined in the book.
That seems odd.
Oh, here it is. Room 204.
You two, better go down and get a bunch of boxes.
Okay.
Start with the books. It's gonna take a while.
I'm on it.
Hey, don't work too hard, guys.
Uh, hey, what should we do with this desk?
Uh, let's just leave it there.
All right.
Yeah?
I'd like to ask you a few questions about your former neighbor.
I have nothing more to say. Just leave me alone.
I'm not with the local police. I'm a private investigator. I don't care who you are mister
You're bothering me, and I have a paper due tomorrow
But I haven't been able to get it finished because of all the questioning and commotion going on next door all right
I'll be quick just one question then would you happen to know if these two were close friends of Edmund foreign couldn't say?
I'm too busy to hang out watching everybody around here
But as far as I know that guy didn't seem to have any friends. I ever saw really I've said enough go away
There's one more little thing.
Aw, come on, now what?
Could you translate this passage for me?
The part that's underlined in red ink.
Huh?
This is just ridiculous.
It's going to be your fault if I flunk my class.
I can't believe I'm doing this for you.
I appreciate it.
It says, "I can no longer continue to deceive."
What was the last thing you said?
I don't know.
I'm busy, okay?
- So I can no longer continue to deceive, huh?
Where have I heard that before?
(footsteps thudding)
(door creaking)
- So, you like coming here too?
Hey, we met a few days ago.
Johan, right?
Why don't you come all the way up?
You can get a much better view if you're standing up here at the very top.
Right.
Hey, thanks for the hand.
Oh man, kind of scary up here, huh?
It's not scary at all.
Johan, come down from there!
Come on, stop it!
I'm serious! You're gonna fall!
Do you come up here a lot?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah. Around this time, the lights start coming on and the neighborhood looks beautiful.
Family members are returning home, and the delicious smells of dinner begin filling the air.
It's something I've wanted for a long time.
Really?
Yeah. I guess because I never really had anything like that when I was growing up.
So tell me, what's your family like?
Oh, got it. Not something you want to talk about.
Wish I could say the same. Being bounced from one foster home to another made it important.
If you don't mind, I'd like to hear your story.
Huh?
Tell me everything you remember.
This is just sloppy police work.
I can no longer continue to deceive and those words are supposed to be proof. He was writing a suicide note
Hmm that wasn't a suicide note foreign was just working on translating a latin phrase from this book
So anyway, that's my story I
Wish it weren't so depressing, but it's all true
It's very strange, but I feel like I can talk to you about almost anything in the world.
Tell me one more thing.
That rich father of yours...
Are you talking about Shuvald?
Those tears in your eyes, are you crying for me?
Listen, we've got to do something, Carl.
I'm there every day, tending to housekeeping chores,
and I see changes in him that really have me worried.
Ever since Edmund committed suicide,
Mr. Schuwald hasn't been eating very much.
If he continues to starve himself,
he's going to end up dying too.
Carl, why don't you try telling him that you're his real son?
What have you got to lose?
I want him to get to know me first,
and then maybe Shuvald will grow to like me.
If I tell him the truth now, he won't believe it,
because he just doesn't trust me yet.
He could completely reject me,
and think that the only reason I'm coming forward
is because I'm after his money.
Seems like money means everything to him.
That's all he knows.
So how can he understand how I feel?
Well, we can't just do nothing.
Your father is in a deep depression,
and we have to come up with a way to get him out of it.
I see you're worried about him, but don't know what to do.
Huh?
I have an idea that I think might work.
I can no longer continue to deceive.
Edmund wrote these words, but they weren't meant to be a suicide note.
In his dorm room, I found this Latin book.
"Caesar's Gallic Wars."
And he was working on translating this underlined portion from it, which means his death might not have been a suicide
I don't have conclusive proof. It's just my gut feeling based on many years of police detective work
Have you been listening to a word I said anything at all?
No
Not really
[SIGHS]
Why?
It doesn't matter now.
Don't say that.
It does matter.
You have to believe me.
If I'm right that Edmund didn't commit suicide,
there's a possibility that your life's in danger.
That dear lad, he was my son, and I can't bring him back.
Nothing matters.
Now, wait a minute.
You know that's not the truth.
I've already told you the facts.
Everything about him, including his birth,
He was a fake, a con.
I'll grant you, he wasn't a very good con,
and apparently, he didn't make it a habit to fool people.
But that's precisely what he did to you, Mr. Shuvalt.
He deceived you.
I must ask you to leave now.
Mr. Shuvalt is tired and needs to rest.
I'm not going to let this investigation end yet.
And my decision has nothing to do with this being
my first high-profile PI job.
There is a far greater evil lurking somewhere behind this case.
Sometimes in life, even if we want to,
there are things we can't do over and we can't ever make right.
They're gone. Can't you understand that?
Yes, I understand. Only too well.
Good day to you, sir.
A children's rights treaty?
Yes. I guess you could think of it as an international rights agreement
to secure and protect the civil liberties of children in countries all around the world.
That's what I'm currently working on in my law class, anyway.
But my volunteer job with the orphanage is completely unrelated to that project.
I do this because I know I can help make a difference in their lives.
Hey guys, can we get back to what we were discussing earlier?
You said Shuvald went bankrupt three times in the past?
Yes. After each one of them, he would just disappear.
And when he'd reappear, he'd start from scratch,
and work to regain his fortune.
Mr. Shuvald told me during one of our Friday reading sessions
how this experience re-energized him, gave him new strength.
Well, did you ask him where he went when he disappeared each time?
Yes.
I think I get it. Your plan is to take him there, am I right?
Everybody has a place to go where they can feel good.
For you, Carl, it's the rooftop of the university building, where you go to watch all the city lights.
Mr. Koons, I think there's something wrong with the bathroom sink. It could be clogged.
Please? There might be water dripping out of those pipes. See?
Hmm...
Lota, there's nothing wrong with the sink. It's working.
Open up! Come on, open this door now!
Stop playing around, child.
( grunting )
Stop playing around! This is unacceptable!
Let me out! Open up this door now!
Where are you going with Mr. Schuwald?
Open up, you kidnappers!
I demand you open this door!
Hey, guys, that's that. Mission accomplished.
All right, let's go.
Aren't you going to tell me where we're going?
It's a surprise.
Look, lady, I'm well aware that you're not the real Margot Langer.
I just won information on Edmund Farran, the boy who died recently.
He came to see you not long ago, didn't he?
Farran.
Remind me which one he was?
Which one?
Apparently, I'm very popular.
I had two pairs of visitors.
Each said he was Shuvalt's kid.
Was he the blonde one?
- The black-haired? - Yeah, the black-haired one came with a girl.
Isn't that funny? I still can't believe he'd actually show up with a girl in a place like--
Black hair, you say? Did the girl have glasses?
I got photographs of them somewhere. These two?
- Yeah, that's who I saw. - You're positive about this?
He said that he was Hans-Georg Schuwald's son?
Are you sure this is the right spot?
Yeah, I'm absolutely certain. It should be right around here.
Care to tell me the name of this surprise?
Well, as a matter of fact, we brought you out to visit Owenburg Wood, sir.
We were hoping this place would cheer you up. I'm sorry.
Just let me out of the car
Can you see the lake from here
The leaves here always get so beautiful in the fall. Yeah very much so
Wait. Something is missing. What happened to the Wrens? Why don't I hear the chirping
of the Wrens? Yeah, I know. I'm so sorry. This place has
changed. They've turned it into a construction site.
You can't hear them, Carl? If you listen very carefully, you can make them out. Little
The birds delightfully chirping in the trees.
Many apples have ripened and fallen to the ground.
Here.
And when you turn in this direction, you will see a spectacular sight.
Autumn leaves ablaze in color in the afternoon sun,
reflected on the calm surface of the water like in a huge mirror.
You must see it, don't you, sir?
It's hard to believe such wonders exist.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I see it.
I can see it.
(birds chirping)
- Back up a second, I just remembered something.
You told me that you had two pairs of visitors
and you mentioned that the black haired boy
brought a girl with him.
- The blonde brought someone.
- Oh yeah, that's right.
He did have somebody with him.
That kid kept mumbling his words.
I could barely understand what he was talking about.
The gorgeous boy who came along with him
ended up doing the talking.
He was the one giving me the lowdown.
And hey, truth be told,
if his good looking pal would have turned around
and claimed he was Shuvald's son,
I wouldn't have had any trouble believing him.
Who's the other guy?
Tell me.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)