"You're looking very well."
"Thanks."
"And how's your job? Everything going smoothly?"
"Uh-huh."
"I'm happy you're doing well. Is Rosemary all right? How's she adjusting?"
"She's doing fine. She's made a lot of new friends."
"That's terrific. Sounds like she's fitting in. Yeah, that's really good news."
She's becoming used to her new school.
I should get going. I'm sorry.
It's getting to be quite late.
But right now, before I forget, I brought you some pictures.
They're new ones of Rosemary.
I'd prefer to see her in person.
How about two days from now? We could meet here again.
The fact is, I'm completely sober.
My life's back to normal again.
Well, actually, this may be the first time my life's been truly normal.
It's finally clear to me how much I've screwed up.
I'm gonna let her decide whether she wants to see you or not.
Yeah.
I'm really hoping she will.
I've got to go now or I'll be late.
See ya.
(eerie music)
- Yes, sir?
- Just more coffee, please.
(choral music)
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
- Dr. Reifvein,
Impression of this man tell me something Richard, huh?
Precisely. Why do you think you're here?
Well, you're here for counseling
I asked the questions remember and as I've told you before I'm a doctor not a fortune-teller
Right your insight comes from your years of experience with patients
Hmm. So who's the boy in the photo this time a person of interest in my case?
He made the initial discovery of Edmund Farnes body at the alleged suicide scene
I'm a friend of the deceased, that's all I know.
Well, here's what I know, Richard.
Yeah?
You're a dedicated workaholic,
but you've got to learn to take time for yourself to relax.
I'm beginning to do just that.
Will wonders never cease?
And Doctor, I have news.
About what?
Rosemary.
I might be able to see her very soon.
Oh.
Well, you must be looking forward to that.
Yeah.
But just remember.
Huh?
If you do get to see her,
you've lost. You need to be emotionally prepared for changes in her. No matter what. And listen,
you must not touch a drop of alcohol. Am I clear?
Don't worry, I won't.
I suppose you're off to work on your case again.
Yep.
Don't leave yet. I think it's time to talk about the event that got you kicked off the
police force. Tell me, Richard, what do you remember from that day?
Well, I remember all of it.
He was 16 years old and a suspected murderer.
I'd been drinking on the job when I spotted him.
I shot him dead.
He died because I was drunk.
You faced up to it.
But that doesn't erase it.
It will always be there.
And nothing can remove that memory from your head.
So do you know what's important now?
Giving myself permission to move on.
Right?
That's correct.
head of the class.
- Do I get an A plus, professor?
- Not so fast.
I don't give out perfect scores easily.
I demand results.
And besides, I'm not all that crazy about perfect patients.
They're boring, frankly.
(laughing)
- No way!
[HORN HONKING]
[GUNSHOT]
(eerie music)
- No.
(grunting)
Carl Neumann, a business admin student in the economics department at Munich University.
Apparently he told that prostitute posing as Margot Langer that he, too, is Schuwalt's
real son.
At this point, I don't know whether he was telling the truth or not.
However, I need to investigate that possibility.
Yes?
Excuse me. I finished all the cleaning, so I'll be going now.
Yeah. Thanks for all your hard work.
Cleaning for you is never hard work.
It's pretty rare for a man living by himself to be so neat.
It makes my job here extremely pleasant.
Well, lately I've been trying to clean up my act on all fronts.
I couldn't help but notice.
Yes. I may be able to see her soon.
Really? That's just wonderful. Your daughter will be so delighted.
Do you really think so?
Of course. What young girl wouldn't be happy to see her father?
Yeah. It was a tough one.
So, were you able to turn your paper in on time?
Carl Neumann, I can't figure you out. If you know for sure, then why haven't you told
Shuval that you're his son? Are you just another con man, or are you the real deal?
If you're legit, then what is stopping you? Don't you realize that any parent would be
overjoyed just to see their own child.
(light music)
I'm so sorry. She said she doesn't want to see you.
Oh. Well, that's fine.
She's made up her mind. I didn't want to force her. It's her decision.
Hey, that's okay. Don't worry about it. It's fine.
I've got to go.
- Yeah, fine.
(eerie music)
- Yes?
What can I get for you, sir?
A whiskey will do.
Sure.
Here you go.
(eerie music)
(glass shattering)
(bells jingling)
- Sir?
(footsteps tapping)
Then I'll just go where he is, and you can find us there.
No, you can't.
Oh, Carl, when you're all grown up, you can meet your father if you want.
Don't hate him if he turns you away.
Promise me that, no matter what.
Because Mommy doesn't hate him.
Keep this with you always.
It was a gift from your father on the day you were born.
"With none to admire them, the daffodils of Laris proudly bloom.
With none to mind them, the trees of Pieria rustle.
Oh, the bloody tracks of the nameless man!"
That was wonderful.
I must say, Neumann, you've come a long way and become an excellent reader.
Thanks very much, sir.
I'm impressed by how much your Latin has improved in the short time you've been reading for me.
To be perfectly honest, I'm being tutored by someone.
Oh. Well, he certainly is an excellent teacher. Would he be anybody I know?
Johann. Johann Liebert is my tutor.
- Yoha, a proficient young man.
- Yes.
- And not only in Latin.
- Huh?
- He has an extensive knowledge of law and economics,
an amazing aptitude, in fact, for whatever he studies.
He's a boy who's beautifully gifted at everything.
He's true perfection.
- Uh, um, Mr. Schuwald,
what would you think if a boy like you
Kim, what if Johann Liebert was actually your real son?
Then he smiled. It was the first time I'd ever seen him smile.
He made it clear that you're worthy enough to be his son, Johann.
To be honest, I was jealous.
No matter which way I looked at it,
you came off better than me.
I'm ashamed to admit it, but I do envy you.
Why don't you just tell him?
Huh?
Come on, Carl, what have you got to lose?
Go ahead and tell Shuvald you're his real son.
Will you stop it?
How many times must I tell you
I have no intention of doing that?
What would be the point if I did?
He would never believe me.
And worse than that,
He'll think of me as just another greedy predator
only interested in getting hold of his fortune.
He'll despise me forever!
How my mother lived her life until her death,
and with everything I've gone through up till now,
he knows nothing about me,
and I won't stand for him thinking I'm after his fortune
when he doesn't know a thing!
That's exactly why you should go talk to him.
You have to gain his trust,
make him understand the truth about his son.
I never believed that I'm his son.
Well, don't you have something from your past that would prove it to him?
What?
Anything he might recognize or remember. You know, something you both could recall.
No. There's nothing, far as I know.
Think back. There must be something.
I'm drawing a big blank. It doesn't matter. I don't want to tell him, okay?
If that's the case, can you explain why you spent all that time having me tutor you in Latin?
Wasn't it because you wanted to please him?
Because you wanted to make him proud of you?
I'm thinking that maybe...
I should quit my job being his reader.
Yeah, it's for the best.
Thanks for all your concern. I appreciate it, but I guess I'm done.
Yohan, wait. I feel you're entitled to know the truth.
I do have something that can prove who I am.
Well, what is it?
It's dumb. I don't know why I'm still holding on to it.
I'm not going to convince him, and I don't need to.
My foster parents are coming to visit me next week.
I've been fooling myself.
I'm not the son he'd want to have.
So I see.
When your mind's made up, it's important not to waver.
So for the time being, Carl,
I think it would be a good idea to let me keep an eye on your proof.
We're so happy to hear your studies are going well.
Isn't that right, Mother?
Uh-huh.
But I've been worried about you, Carl.
Well, uh, I'm always eating out so I know I have to be careful not to gain any weight.
Better stay away from your mother's cooking, too.
But it's so delicious.
How's your social life, son? Are you making a lot of new friends here?
Yeah. I've got some people I hang out with and can talk to about anything.
Terrific. It's always good to have friends.
Yes, that's very true. And it looks to us like you're doing quite well.
I'm extremely grateful to both of you that I can even be here.
sudden there's no need for thanks. For years I was shuttled from one foster
home to another where no one cared about me, but you two have treated me with such
kindness. That's because you're a wonderful young man. We both think so.
That's right, girl. Thank you for everything you've given me, Mr. and
Mrs. Lindner. Isn't it about time you stopped calling us Mr. and Mrs.? We came
here hoping that you would finally accept our offer. We know this has been
for you.
But now, with college treating you so well,
Mother and I were wondering if you'd made up your mind.
Have you decided to become our adopted son, Carl?
We believe in you, and we want you to succeed.
We trust you.
You trust us, don't you?
Oh, absolutely.
We understand why you might still be a little hesitant.
There's a chance your real parents are still alive.
No matter how much effort we make,
we can never be your birth parents, but maybe--
There's no "maybe" about it.
Because the both of you are as real to me as my birth parents could ever be.
Let's have a toast.
Feel like some expensive champagne, son?
Yeah!
Waiter! Bring us the champagne list!
We're celebrating! Today's a special day!
Hello, Carl speaking.
Hello, Carl.
It's me.
Do you know who this is?
Mr. Shoevault?
That's correct.
Now, what's this I hear about you quitting your job?
Uh, right, sir.
That's very disappointing.
for any inconvenience this might cause.
- I just hate to see you abandon your Latin.
You put so much hard work into it.
- Thank you for your concern, sir.
- It really is a shame.
I'm going to miss you, you know.
As a favor to me, if you don't mind,
would you read to me one last time?
- Sure, it'd be my pleasure.
How about the third chapter of "From Aeolus to Lemnos"?
Ah, a splendid choice.
That mysterious sea beckons for the death of even the god Phoebus.
What other pleasure could there be
than to wish death upon the sons and daughters of Cerberus?
Now, move forward, softly whispers Zeus.
Move forward, move on.
and dance in the temple that belongs to the dark gods,
the gods of Juno, who dwell in the sea,
the earth, and the heavens.
From the summit of the Parthenon,
steal the forbidden apple of Campania,
and bring forth the apple and everything,
everything to save my soul.
Oh, bring forth everything to save my soul.
(dramatic music)
- Mr. Shoevault, but your phone call.
- Magnificent.
So heartfelt and meaningful.
The best I've heard in my whole life.
Why did you keep this from me?
- Is that mine?
so many memories I gave it to Margo a long time ago a good luck charm I wanted
to pass that luck to you this is yours car my son
I've put you through so much.
Oh, Father!
I've found my son.
This is all thanks to one person.
He told me about you.
about everything. His help was invaluable, so from now on, he'll be working for me as
my secretary. He is a young man who can be trusted.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]