That's good enough? When you say that, just what exactly do you mean, Mr. Schuvald?
I've decided that I've learned enough. I am calling off the investigation.
But sir, we had a breakthrough, and I'm close to another. I checked out Carl Neumann, and one thing's certain, that boy's your real son.
I'm quite grateful to you for all you've done.
Now, hold on. There's still more to be done.
There's still the Edmund Farran issue to figure out.
Edmund pretended to be your son, but some evidence I uncovered seems to indicate that he didn't really commit suicide.
If that's really the case, someone else is pulling the strings and may have killed Farran.
It has been solved to my satisfaction.
Father, I made some tea. Would you care for some?
Yes, I would.
Oh, good afternoon, detective.
Would you care to join us?
No, thank you. I'll be going.
Once again, good work. Just send me your bill. Good day.
It sure looks nice outside.
It does.
Oh, and Johan's come as well.
What a surprise. So Johan's decided to visit.
Shuvald had always been known as a distrustful man with a sour disposition.
Who would have thought that he'd turn into such a good-natured soul when he found his son?
With that smile of his, who'd have guessed that people still call him the Vampire of Bavaria?
What a surprise. So Johan's decided to visit.
[FOOTSTEPS]
♪ To live in His presence ♪
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- How cute.
So, you're trying to track down this puppy, eh?
What a job.
My client told me her ex-husband basically dog-napped the little fella.
I guess disputes over pets can be just as bad as ones over kids.
You're right about that.
I think I'll have some wine, if that's quite all right with you.
You go ahead. I'll be sticking with the sparkling water.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
I know work's scarce at the moment, but it's a good choice on your part
life with alcohol I'm doing okay at least on that account what do you mean
are you saying there's something else in your life that's bothering you well I
find that with all the free time I have now I end up rehashing things a lot such
as I spend hours and hours pouring over this personal notebook I have of
unsolved crimes cases I never solved as a detective how interesting so tell me
when you look at it how do you feel I feel frustrated there were so many
I wasn't able to solve it haunts me to think of those vicious killers still out there walking around in our world
They're free because of my incompetence
Even now I can't seem to catch them. You're being too hard on yourself
You could have caught them you had the skills to solve those cases
But your self-critical nature was impeding you Richard you got frustrated that you couldn't read these murderers minds and that caused you pain
So I turned to alcohol
Sure. Of course you did.
Gentlemen, dinner is served.
Oh, good. It's time to eat.
Actually, I think it would be in your best interest for you to keep trying.
Hmm?
I would encourage you to keep looking at your old police notebook.
But why? I'll just become angry again.
Stop thinking that way.
You have to analyze what you did in the past in a new light.
Your mind is clearer now that should help. Let's be frank with each other
We both know that you shot a young serial killer when you were drunk
And I must say you are facing the reality of what happened that night admirably
But now Richard you face a far greater challenge
Facing your thoughts when you pulled that trigger
You're still haunted by that boy you see him in your mind every day, don't you?
When you've brought everything to light, all those things festering under the surface,
that boy's ghost will finally move on.
I see. When I've brought everything to light, huh?
The Homer murder case is a good place to start. The victim, Joachim Homer, had a long and
steady career as an accountant. He was never involved in anything shady and had no enemies.
And when he was murdered, there were no signs of a robbery.
Then there were those two Voice of God cases. The victims were a former housekeeper and
a chauffeur. What connected those two killings was that the words "I have heard the voice
of God" were left scrawled on a wall at both crime scenes.
The Dornach Company President case.
Lothar Gauck was one of the wealthiest businessmen in Bavaria, and his body was discovered in the Hartoltz Forest.
And then there's the Spira couple case.
Both were forcibly drowned, and their bodies washed up along the Isar River later on.
This one's still being investigated as one of a string of murders involving middle-aged couples.
A material witness in that case disappeared, a Japanese doctor who's still on the run.
Oh, man.
The more unsolved cases I had, the more booze I drank.
Then it felt good, but it's different now.
This is tough. It feels just like the doctor said.
So I'm sober, my mind is clear and I'm feeling calm.
Hey.
Hold on a second. Come on. Think think hard Richard
(panting)
- So, you tried doing it again and what was the result?
- I did.
I looked at all my notes and I thought of something new,
but then I...
- You saw that boy's ghost again,
and once that happened,
you lost your train of thought, right?
- Uh-huh.
- There's no need to worry.
When you have an important thought like that,
sooner or later it will come back to you.
What was it that I realized?
An idea flashed through my mind.
It felt like it was a key to solving one of those cases.
Just my imagination.
Who's there?
Show yourself!
Whoever you are, I'll catch you!
This is like that time, way back.
I was running after that punk just like this.
I chased him down an alley.
Sorry for coming here so late at night, Doc.
Nonsense. If you think you've figured things out and you're ready to share them, go ahead then. Tell me everything.
Back then, I felt myself looking deep within that killer.
That's when I knew it existed in this world.
It was true evil.
And once I saw it standing right there in front of me, I shot and killed him.
That's good. Thank you for sharing, Richard.
By telling me this, you're well on the road to recovery.
There's still more, Doctor. It just came to me.
Hmm?
That idea that had flashed through my mind before.
All those unsolved cases I had been working to solve separately.
I realized they are actually one single case.
Huh?
Greetings, my dear Dr. Gillan. I'm writing to thank you for sending me a copy of your
recently published book, Transcendental Criminal Psychology. I found your book informative
and a very interesting read, and it pleases me to see that a student of mine from Dusseldorf
University has now become a leading authority in the field of criminal psychology. Now I
- I have a question for you regarding another matter.
You told me in a phone conversation
that you conducted a lengthy interview
with the serial murderer, Peter Juergens.
After you spoke with him, you told me that Juergens claimed
that a friend of his had encouraged him
to murder the victims.
Sadly, my memory isn't what it used to be,
so could you please tell me again,
what was the name of Juergens' friend
whom he said told him to kill?
I'd appreciate that information, as it may aid an associate of mine.
P.S.
As I mentioned earlier, you were quite a student in college and excelled in my class.
And you had a fellow colleague who was equally bright.
You often competed with him for the best marks.
He graduated and became a neurosurgeon.
At any rate it seems that he's become a suspect in a multiple homicide case with your expertise
I'm hoping you could help me get a better picture of who he is. Please. Tell me everything you might know about him
What kind of person is he and where do you think he might be right now this dr. Tenma? I
Remember you you're a detective
Well, I used to be and now I'm a private investigator
I'm sorry to show up unannounced here at your door, ma'am.
And I hate to bring up a subject I know must be painful for you,
but I would appreciate it if I could ask you some questions again.
Of course you can.
It's been four years since I last spoke to the police,
and it seems like they're done with their investigation.
Mr. Schuwald?
Yes, I believe your mother was actually employed by him.
Wasn't she once the head housekeeper at his mansion?
She was, but she worked for Mr. Schuwald 20 years ago.
She wasn't fired, so do you happen to know why she quit?
Well, at that time, she became very ill,
and after her sickness, she only worked close to home, in the neighborhood.
Was that it, or could it be she had some problem with Mr. Schuwald?
No, not at all. They were actually quite good friends.
She told me that she used to read poetry to Mr. Schuwald when he was still able to see.
My mother just loved reading poems to him.
Come along. I want to show you something.
Look how generous he was to her.
I've kept all of them because they remind me of my dear mother.
Every one of those books are collections of poetry that were given to my mother as a thank you from Mr. Schubold.
How things change.
The head detective in the doorknock company president case is now just a private eye.
You worked as Mr. Gawk's chief business liaison and personal secretary.
I ask you once again, did anyone hold a grudge against him?
You mean, did anyone hate him?
There aren't enough hours in the day to count all the people who despised him.
In business, Mr. Gawk was such a fierce adversary
that he personally forced some of our competition to go bankrupt.
But there was another powerful and well-known businessman in Bavaria wasn't there.
How did Mr. Gauk feel about him?
I take it you mean Mr. Schuwald?
Well, they were lifelong rivals in business, but of course you knew that, right?
They knew each other very well.
When Mr. Gauk was still alive, Schuwald's company went bankrupt two times.
That second bankruptcy happened when Mr. Gauk undercut Schuwald's prices for the purpose of ruining him.
is that Mr. Gawk was consciously trying to crush him.
Mr. Shuvald made certain we suffered serious losses, too.
So then they both hated each other?
Of course.
A few times, they happened to be at the same party,
and if looks could kill, they both would have been dead.
Oh, it was very tense.
They had explosive fights.
Like two vipers.
But those snakes understood each other's every move.
Only those two tycoons could talk to each other on the same level.
I never felt like they were enemies.
This may sound weird, but they were really more like friends.
[Gunshots]
Huh?
[Gunshot]
[Scream]
Hey! Careful up there!
Careful up there!
- Oh yeah, I knew Hans real well.
Poor Hans was one of those two people
that ended up being victims
in that awful Voice of God murder case.
That Hans was a good guy, he deserved better.
- Just what is it that makes you say
Hans was such a good guy?
- He was nice, always treated me to a drink or two.
- Generous, huh?
I heard that Hans used to work
for Mr. Schuwald as his driver.
He told me that, but he worked as Shuvald's driver almost 30 years ago.
Did Hans say why he stopped driving for Mr. Shuvald?
Well, that was around the time old Shuvald's company went bankrupt.
That's why he was fired, huh? So Hans never said that he and his boss didn't get along?
Listen to me. What I'm about to say is to honor the memory of Hans.
If ever there was a guy who could get along with anybody and everybody, it was Hans.
He was a prince. Even rich bastards like that vampire of Bavaria, Shuvald.
He treated us poor folks like kings and Hans always said he was the one who taught Shuvald about bird-watching.
He taught him about bird-watching?
Uh-huh. Hans said Shuvald was more like a happy kid than a vampire when he took him to the forest.
It's hard to believe that was two years ago.
But whenever I think of my dear husband,
I just can't understand why such a kind and wonderful man ended up being murdered.
It's unfair. He died so horribly.
You have my sympathies.
Pardon my asking, but I believe your husband grew up as an…
Orphan?
Yes, he lived in an orphanage till he was six,
then with different foster families until he was eighteen.
After that, he became an accountant.
Is it true Mr. Schuwald, the business tycoon,
asked your husband to be his corporate accountant?
He did, many times.
But my husband always turned him down.
My husband was quite busy with work at the time, but that wasn't why.
He said Mr. Schuwald had a different set of financial principles.
When it came to money, my husband was very honest.
Again, thank you so much. I appreciate the help.
My husband's killer. Will he ever be caught?
I'll try my best. If I can do it, I swear I'll catch him.
Well then.
Oh, one more thing.
Yes?
I forgot to ask you if you knew how your husband and Mr. Schuwald first met each other.
Oh, that. It seems they met in the forest.
The forest?
Yes, they met in the forest back when Mr. Schuwald could still see. It was a total coincidence.
What were they doing in a place like that?
They were both there bird-watching. After they met, they went to the forest together all the time.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Birdwatching.
More like a happy kid.
Read poetry to Mr. Schuwald?
More like friends?
[GASPS]
[CRASHING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
Hey, buddy.
You OK?
Uh, yeah.
I'm-- I'm fine, thanks.
That guy was driving like an idiot.
From what I saw, it looked more
like he was trying to run you over.
- Man, what a creep.
- Dr. Rackvine, I've re-examined all the evidence.
And what I found out supports what I told you before.
Some of the key murder cases that I wasn't able to solve
all point to one killer having just one motive.
There's the Voice of God murder case
and the Dornach Company President murder case.
murder case? Look at the three of them. They're all extremely different. The methods in which
they were committed, for example. And the victims weren't related to each other. None
of them even knew each other. However, I have discovered that all of them shared one common
bond. There was a man who connected all the victims. And because they knew him, they were
all murdered. Every one of them was killed to further isolate Mr. Schuwald.
Hmm. There's also another connection in these cases that's rather curious. In the
Dornach Company president case, his secretary said there was a certain young
man who was supposed to meet with Mr. Gauk right before he was murdered. And in
the Voice of God cases, under "I have heard the voice of God," this name was
scrawled there by the murderer. And then there's the Spira couple murder case.
Since both of them drowned, that case seemed to be unrelated to the others.
But the name of the killer given by the Japanese doctor, who was the only witness in that case, was the same.
It was the same name in every case.
Johan.
Huh?
I've been in touch with a former student of mine who's now a renowned criminal psychologist.
He interviewed a murderer who claimed he committed his crimes on his friend's orders.
In here, he wrote that friend's name.
and the name that's in this letter is Johan.
Johan is a common name, but based on what you found,
it's also possible that all these cases could be related.
If by chance your findings are true,
this Johan has been systematically murdering people
for the past four years.
I can't help but wonder why this man known as Johan
is trying to force Schuwald into complete isolation.
Oddly enough, Margot Langer, the woman who bore
Juvald's son, conveniently died as well.
And there was that young student who was pretending to be Juvald's son.
He conveniently killed himself as soon as he made his claim.
If Johan really does exist, I wonder where he is right now.
Perhaps he's close.
What a surprise! So Johan's decided to visit.
Ah, Johan. The weather's so beautiful.
Yes, isn't it, sir?
Johan's there. He's right next to Shuvald.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)