(children laughing)
- Rainbow ranger kick!
(laughing)
- Hey, that's no fair.
- You're supposed to fall when I kick you.
(laughing)
- My evil empire's gonna take over the world.
Your puny little kick isn't enough to stop me.
Ugh, the bad guys always lose in the TV shows.
Don't you know anything?
(laughing)
- Well, well, how's the global domination coming along?
- Come on, Johan.
Tell him to stop breaking the rules and play the right way.
(laughing)
- The big secret to breaking the rules
is to make it look as though you're following them.
So, what sort of plans do you have for the Earth?
- Who knows, why should I care?
I'm just gonna destroy everything anyway.
- Hey, messing stuff up sounds like a lot more fun
than being a stupid hero.
Yeah, forget being a Rainbow Ranger, I want to be a villain, too!
Well, guys, shall we start making our way back?
- Okay. - Okay.
Come on.
- So, did you have fun today? - Yeah.
Time to go home.
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
finally starting to warm up a bit that's good i guess has rosemary uh you know uh caught
any colds this winter not a one too busy romping around with her friends to get sick that's
good she used to get those fevers like clockwork hey remember that one time years ago rushing
her to the doctor in the dead of night.
Those old pictures, you always keep them on you?
Of course I do. I bet she's a lot bigger now.
They grow up so fast. These photos of mine must be ancient history.
But still, no matter how grown up she gets,
I'll always know it's her the moment our eyes meet.
She'll always be my little girl.
Oh, almost forgot.
Whenever she's ready, please give Rosemary what's in this envelope.
They're newspaper clippings, mostly, and the official internal affairs report
from when I shot that young man who killed all those people.
I'm not asking you to defend me. You've done that enough.
I shouldn't have shot him. I'll be the first to say it.
I just want our daughter to know, to know the truth about her old man, even if it's terrible.
I understand.
As she said, either way...
I'll ask her again if she wants to see you. If she's okay with it, then so am I.
Really? Oh, thank you.
Just give me a call.
At the latest, I'm usually home by 9 o'clock.
Oh, Richard, it's good to see the old you again.
Uh, pardon?
That look in your eyes,
they shone like that when you first made detective.
Remember?
That fire you had in your belly when you and I first met?
We both had it.
So, what do you think? If you enroll today, we can get you in at a lower premium.
The thing of it is, we already have insurance. We don't really need another policy.
Let me just show you our rates, Mr. Liebert. That's all I ask.
The coverage we have right now is more than enough. I couldn't afford a whole new policy at the moment anyway.
We've had our current one for four years, ever since we moved into this neighborhood.
Four years, huh? Where were you living before?
Over near Mannheim in Brüntal.
Brüntal. How about that? It's a nice area.
So, are you folks from there originally?
Yeah, we are. And "nice" is an understatement.
So, do you folks have any kids?
A son, yes. He's attending the University of Munich.
Now that's what I like to hear.
As it turns out, we're offering a new plan that's perfect for young adults.
Hear me out. This won't take a minute.
Oh, your son, I presume?
He sure was a handsome baby. What's his name?
His name's Johan. Would you like some tea?
Yeah, don't go to any trouble on my account.
They must keep him pretty busy at school.
Seems like he hasn't called us in a long time.
Boys get like that when they leave the nest.
Sounds like you speak from experience.
Hello, Dr. Reiffein. I'm back.
Yeah, I went to Johan's folks' house.
That's the thing. They were normal as could be. Totally average.
Hmm. So what do you make of it, Richard?
Well, back in my detective days, I probably would have said,
"There's nothing fishier than normalcy," or something to that effect.
Now, I just don't know.
Hard to tell.
At any rate, I'm going to keep checking out the people around Johan.
Where's the flaw? Nobody's that perfect.
Yu Hong enjoyed a great reputation during his prep school days.
His grades were top-notch, and his evaluations paint him as a model student.
Huh?
But still, no matter how grown up she gets, I'll always know it's her the moment our eyes
meet.
She'll always be my little girl.
That baby's face in the photo...
There's no way he grew up to look like Yohan!
Here you go, sir. The birth certificate you asked about.
Ah, thank you.
"Johann Wilhelm Liebert. Date of birth, 9th of February, 1976. So he was definitely born
in this town." Hmm. Everything here reads pretty legit.
Mr. Hertz!
Huh?
How many times do I have to tell you? You cannot light up in here!
Just get me an ashtray. I promise I'll smoke it real quick.
I am not replacing all those damn files again, mister!
You had to recreate your files from scratch?
Uh, well, yeah.
We did have to ask people to resubmit their information.
It took a while, but we're a small town,
so we got all our ducks in a row again eventually.
(Gasping)
Hey, thank you so much for coming, Dr. Gillen.
Good to see you again.
It's been too long, Dr. Reichwein.
So I'm to understand that when Dr. Tenma came to see you,
he was looking for a young man he called Johan.
That's right.
But there was no evidence with which to corroborate his story.
However, if the young man in this photo is the friend
who manipulated my current research subject,
one Peter Juergens, a serial killer,
into committing another murder,
then clues must exist that tie these three events together.
I'm counting on you, Dr. Gillen.
Right. I'll get clearance to interview Juergens as soon as possible.
I'll let him see this photograph and monitor any reactions.
If it might help prove Tenma's innocence, it's worth a try.
(dramatic orchestral music)
So he's dead?
That's right.
The real Johann Liebert, who was born in Brüntal, died when he was two years old.
Hold on.
You're saying the Lieberts replaced their dead son with someone else, and after that
fire destroyed the original records, they used that chance to plug the other boy into
that identity?
I'm afraid so.
If they did, then who's this young man masquerading as Johann Liebert, alive and well?
"Beneath the lies, who the hell is he?"
At any rate, I did pass along Johan's photograph to Dr. Gillen when he stopped in to see me.
Hopefully he'll get to interview that killer of his again sometime soon.
Now then, how about dinner?
Sorry, but it's getting late. Another time?
What's this? You run around all day and now you're working through the night as well?
Hardly. I'm expecting a very important phone call.
Well, cross your fingers. There's a chance I may get to see Rosemary.
Really?
Don't worry, I'm okay. You're always telling me to focus on the road ahead, aren't you?
Of course. This is an important step in your recovery.
Yes, hello?
Hi, Daddy. It's me.
Hi, Rosemary.
Uh-huh. Yeah, Daddy's fine.
Of course. I'd love to see you.
You say when, and I'll be there.
Mr. Brown? It's Johan.
Tell me, Juergens, this young man, do you recognize him?
Maybe you've met him somewhere before.
I don't know him.
Hmm. This friend of yours, Johan, right?
You only know him through his letters, you've never actually met him, isn't that correct?
But Johan certainly seemed to know a lot about you.
Should I borrow your pen for a moment?
What's that? I'm sorry, you know the rules here prohibit me from giving you anything.
Give me your pen.
The park.
That's where I was. Killed someone the day before.
I remember thinking, "I'm gonna stop killing people.
I've had enough of all this."
That's what I told myself.
He was there, with a bunch of kids.
Uh, wait, hold on a second.
I should be recording this. Just start over again, please.
Come with us.
Huh?
Come with us. Come with us. Come... with...
Wha... what are you doing here?
We met at Mr. Schuwald's estate, remember?
Johann Liebert, sir.
I've been trying to get in touch with you, but to no avail, so I figured I'd drop by.
Yes? Oh, Dr. Gillen, it's you. Good.
So did anything interesting happen when you showed Juergens that photograph of Johan?
Wait, he's dead?
Correct. I'm at the hospital right now.
We still aren't done questioning me, so I'm stuck here.
Listen, we lost a vital witness tonight
because I was careless
and handed a psychopath a ballpoint pen.
But I do know one thing for sure.
Juergens committed suicide
because he saw that photograph of Johan.
- Hmm?
- I'll be over there as soon as I've finished up
with the police, all right?
- All right.
I'll give Richard a call and let him know.
(phone ringing)
- He'd better be home.
- A report for class, huh?
- That's right.
On the recent UN Convention on the Rights of the Child.
And if the treatment of juvenile offenders holds up.
Oh, how rude of me.
Care for something to drink?
- No thanks, I'm fine.
That's right, you do abstain from alcohol.
Yeah, probably for the best.
You did have quite a drinking problem.
I mean, you were drunk when you shot that boy, isn't that right?
Or, so I've heard.
Yes, I was. Not that it matters.
What I did is unforgivable, drunk or not.
I have a few questions about what happened, if you don't mind.
Tell me about the victim, Stefan Joos, age 17.
Of what crimes had the child been accused?
Don't be so naive, son.
Joos was a monster.
He was old enough to rape and murder nine women
and almost killed two more.
So you executed him?
No, I didn't!
Right, pardon me.
Speaking of, Article 40 of the UN Convention
states every child is presumed to be innocent
were you familiar with that yes of course I was I used to work in juvenile
detention I see and article 37 the one that goes you cannot impose capital
punishment or life imprisonment without possibility of release on any person
below the age of 18 you knew that one the convention agreements are considered
basic human rights for adults and children alike what kind of a fool do
you take me for you really think I planned it all out in advance my
Look, I know that what I have done can never be undone, all right?
And I accept the consequences of my actions.
Please, Mr. Brown, allow me to explain.
I'm not trying to antagonize you.
I just want to cover my topic from every angle.
I'm very sorry, sir. I really should have used more tact.
Shall we walk? The night air might do us some good.
I'd like to purchase the bottle, please.
Just something to take the edge off of the night air.
Oh, Dr. Gillen. I keep calling him, but there's no answer.
You know, Richard did say he might be getting to see Rosemary soon,
but this hardly seems the hour for a father-daughter reunion.
Well, when you finally do get a hold of him, let him know how dangerous that young man can be.
And tell him that I'm en route to his apartment.
Did you ever look into Stephan Joss's background?
Of course. He grew up in an East German orphanage or something like that.
There's more to it than you know, huh?
His crimes were to be expected if you knew his past
to a child like Stefan
That orphanage was hell on earth
He was a good boy
But that didn't save him from the horror that might have even made it worse
That orphanage devoured his mind and then picked its teeth with his soul
The Convention on the Rights of Children, Article 6.
The Right to Life, Survival, and Development.
Article 8, Preservation of Identity.
Article 19, Protection from Abuse.
To Stephan, these were so many fairy tales.
Evil. There's no more fitting word for a place like that.
I can barely speak its name aloud.
5-1-1 Kinderheim still sends a chill down my spine.
So, when will you be seeing your daughter?
What did you say? How do you know about her?
Before you answered the door, you were on the phone with her. Isn't that so?
When do you see her? Tomorrow, maybe?
Enough talk. What are you up to?
I'm just doing research for my report. That's all.
No, damn it. I'm on to you kid. You're gonna tell me what you've got planned for Shuvald
So, who are you who are you tell me
You got drunk and shot that boy to death that's what you said
"Plenty of people did see you drinking in a bar that day, but that was after you'd already
killed Stefan."
"It's kind of odd, Mr. Brown.
I've researched this case exhaustively, and try as I might, I can't find a single person
who saw you drinking before you murdered that young man.
Not a one."
"Mr. Brown, this charade has gone on long enough.
Were you really drunk when you pulled the trigger?
What?
You were quite sober, and you were calm.
You executed Stephanios,
and you knew exactly what you were doing.
No.
Did I get it right?
No!
How weak the mind when it wants to forget.
Maybe you didn't forget, maybe you're lying.
Is it a lie you tell everyone around you,
Perhaps a lie you tell yourself.
Were you absolutely certain he committed those crimes?
Certain enough to put him down like a rabid dog?
You're guilty of murder.
Do you think your lies can free you?
That boy's blood is on your hands.
How are you going to look Rosemary in the eye tomorrow?
Isn't her daddy a coward and a murderer?
Well, Richard, how about a drink?
Huh?
Dr. Gillen, is that you?
We're the police.
We've come here regarding your patient, Richard.
Richard Brown. He's dead.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)