our brother has answered his call and gone home to the heavens what lies here in this casket is
nothing more than the physical shell of richard brown we know his soul has been set free it will
go on and live forever let us embrace his memory remembering that wherever his family will be
this loving father and hard-working husband will always be there in spirit
after he had risen from the dead the lord said it doesn't make any sense
he just left so much unfinished i'm shocked that no one from the police force is here
richard was an excellent detective but not one of them came to pay their respects
it's ironic about him drinking on duty cost him his career and in the end a drunken fall is what
cost him his life at least that's what the police report said his voice was so alive when he called
He was very excited about seeing his daughter, but he never quite made it.
But his spirit has planted in each of us a seed of immortality.
I asked myself, did I really do everything I could to help poor Richard?
Why, of course you did, Doctor.
I just sat there listening to him spill out his life to me,
and I told him he was well on his way to making a full recovery.
I was wrong. I feel like I never did enough to help him.
Tenma is the key
If we could question him, we might get the answers to help us solve all of this
I do believe you're right
I think there's something we both know, Doctor
This wasn't an accident, or a suicide
As you said, a few hours before his death, Richard was on the phone happily talking to his daughter
He wanted to see her
Doctor, you did all that you could and you had helped him
Richard had quit drinking and was on the road to recovery.
Whatever happened, it wasn't your fault.
We'll be right back.
♪♪♪
Listen to this.
You aren't going to believe it.
I'm serious.
I found out my husband's having an affair,
so I confronted him, and now he won't even speak to me.
He just washes the car, cleans the garage,
and gives me the silent treatment.
I know he's avoiding me.
It's so obvious.
I wait up for him to come to bed,
but he falls asleep in his chair.
Besides being blonde and beautiful,
what's she got that I don't?
Huh?
Doctor, are you listening to me?
Uh, of course.
Please, continue.
Now, here's the part you were just not going to believe.
I decided to confront this other woman,
so I go over to her place,
and what do you think she said to me?
A homicide?
No, not a chance, Doc.
It was an unlucky accident.
Richard Brown was alone that evening when he went up to the roof of building number 12 at Munich University.
He polished off a bottle of whiskey, and he got so drunk he fell off the roof.
End of story.
The bottle.
Did you have it thoroughly examined?
Yes.
Of course we did, and we found Richard's prints on it.
If you don't mind, could I see that bottle?
Why, yeah, sure, I suppose.
But it's all in pieces.
Oh, Richard.
I think there's something we both know, Doctor.
As you said, a few hours before his death,
Richard was on the phone happily talking to his daughter.
He wanted to see her.
him yeah the guy in this picture was definitely in here that night was he alone i'm not sure i
really don't remember so you remember that he was here but you don't recall if he was here
with someone or alone it was him he had a cup of coffee coffee yeah that's the
reason I remember him most folks ordered drinks with alcohol when they come here
so tell me is there a chance this young man was with him that night I really
couldn't tell you you're not even trying look I told you I don't know we got tons
of customers who come into this place mister but like I told the cops I think
the coffee guy did buy a bottle of whiskey I got a receipt are you sure it
was Richard who bought that bottle I told you I don't remember all I know for
sure is on that receipt there's a cheap bottle of whiskey wait what did you just
say
Like this one, a fifth of blended whiskey.
I can't believe it.
Why didn't it hit me when I saw that bottle at the police station?
Have you been drinking again?
Well, um, just a little.
So what do you drink?
Scotch. I only drink scotch.
Hmm. So you're stinking up my entire office with the smell of cheap booze.
Cheap booze? You kidding me?
I'd never drink cheap rotgut if I'm going to drink its real scotch.
Or nothing else.
Richard didn't buy that bottle of whiskey.
Johan, it must have been him.
Hey, hey you! Stop running!
Oh, well, you know what?
Hey, what do you want?
Why'd you just try to push me onto the tracks?
What the... I don't know what you're talking about.
Get out with it!
Hey there, old man.
You got a problem with my friend?
Bad idea.
Who told you to push me?
You need to shut up.
At your age, old man, you should be at home playing with your grandkids.
- Hey, I still want an answer.
- Huh?
- Hold it!
You know, I trained as a border patrol officer.
- It really hurts.
- Speak up. Why'd you try to push me earlier?
- I... I don't know.
- Don't you dare try to pull one over on me!
- S-somebody asked me to do it.
- Who was it?
- It was some big guy.
- What do you mean, a big guy?
- A guy I met in the subway paid me
to push you off the platform and onto the tracks.
He gave me money to do it.
- Really?
♪♪
I bought you scotch, single malt, the really good stuff you liked.
You deserve it, my friend.
It's okay.
You can have a drink now.
You can count on me, Richard.
As God is my witness, I'll identify the guy who did this.
I swear it.
I'll uncover Johan's true identity.
So listen to this, Doctor.
- I finally told my husband what I think.
I said that his cheating on me is a disease
that's festering inside him.
Then I told that ape that he's the one
who should be sitting here and counseling, not me.
Doctor, did you hear what I said?
- Hmm?
Why, yes, I did.
Go ahead.
- Well, then tell me.
If my husband keeps this up,
I feel like my depression's only going to get worse,
isn't it?
- Well, no.
I don't believe you're really clinically depressed at all.
Huh?
Honestly, I'm more concerned about your husband's actions
than I am with your mental state.
We must find out why he's giving you the silent treatment.
That's what I think.
The big lug doesn't know which end is up.
Please, doctor, I beg of you.
Please make some time to see my husband.
Of course I will.
I have a slot open the day after tomorrow
at 5 o'clock in the afternoon, all right?
Thank you. I'll tell him tonight.
Make sure you give that cheating jerk a good talking to, Doctor
Don't hold back, you got that?
Doctor, that was the last of your appointments for today
Good, thank you very much, Merith
See you tomorrow, then
All right, then. Good night.
Oh, and there's one more thing.
Yesterday, you forgot to lock the stairwell door
to our office again.
Wait, I did it again?
I'm sorry. I almost forgot today, too.
I can't believe it.
Have a nice evening.
Hello? Dr. Gillen?
It's Dr. Reichwein.
I saw today's paper.
Why, yes, I saw your newspaper ad in there.
Let's talk about our memories of cheating, Rudy.
So you really think if Dr. Tenma sees this message in the paper
that he will try to get in touch with us?
Absolutely.
If Dr. Tenma sees the ad, he'll definitely contact me.
I worded it so it would be something that only he and I would know about.
I see.
now doctor please don't make any moves until we hear from him understood but
there's still one related matter that I need to investigate what's that this
prostitute who pretended to be Margot Langer just might have answers I'm
following up on something Richard said that prostitute told me that went far
and the boy who killed himself went to see her he had a young man accompanying
him he was a young beautiful guy with blonde hair whatever you do please be
careful oh I will if I want to get to the bottom of this I'll have to be very
cautious but Richards memory deserves no less well I'll call you later doctor
Oh, no.
So, Merith, today you forget to shut the window.
Margot Langer, huh?
Never heard of her.
Well, I understand she goes by the name of Sophie or something like that.
Oh, yeah.
So you want that fat old hat?
Is that what floats your boat, Gramps?
No, wait.
It's not like that.
Oh, you're blushing.
Fine, make a ride two blocks down the brick building, second floor.
Thank you, young lady.
But I know she's not there right now.
Huh?
I haven't seen her around in about a week.
She probably went to someplace that's nicer.
And where might that be?
Who the hell knows?
What makes that fat old hag so popular with all you guys?
My guess is she's with this really rich guy who used to be a regular customer.
You think she went with him?
Hey, what do you say you give me a try, old man?
You must have money, and I'm sure I'm more fun than her.
Do you know where she went?
How would I know?
Maybe she went off somewhere with that new customer of hers.
So she has a new client, eh?
Uh-huh.
She should know better at her age than to fall for a guy like him.
He was a large one.
So he was a big man.
Oh, yeah, and I heard he was pretty big downstairs, too.
Doctor, excuse me.
Do you remember me asking you if it would be all right for me to leave early today?
Yes, I remember that.
You said you needed to leave at five.
That'll be fine.
The only appointment I have left today is Mrs. Hess's husband.
Are you going on a date, Meredith?
Oh, don't be silly, Doctor.
Please make sure you lock all the doors.
I need to find that prostitute called Sophie who was pretending to be Margot Langer
and show her this photo.
If I can get her to confirm that this Johan was actually with Farin,
I'll have someone who can testify to that fact,
which would bring me closer to getting to the bottom of this mess.
Yes?
Yeah, my wife booked a session for me. Last name's Hess.
I buzzed the door. Please come in.
I might have better luck tonight if I go down there and look for Sophie again.
It's worth a shot.
uh good evening dr reichlein mr hess ah welcome it's uh nice to meet you please sit down i uh
this is my first time in counseling so well there's nothing to be nervous about
all you need to do is relax we're here to talk about whatever you want you can rest assured that
our conversation will be completely confidential what we talk about stays right here you won't tell
my wife of course not how have you been feeling lately and what is it you worry
about my worries yes yours well my wife she found out about my affair and your
feeling I feel like I'm a stranger in my own home I just washed the car and clean
up the garage that's all I do every day does doing things around the house make
You feel better?
- Not really.
And it seems like I hardly ever talk to my wife anymore.
- Do you want to talk to her, but can't find a way to?
- Well, I don't know about that.
- Well, what about the mistress?
- What?
- You know, the woman you had an affair with.
Have you two--
- Yeah.
I guess so, I killed her.
- Hmm?
- Well, I mean I had a dream where I killed her.
- So how often would you say
you have those kinds of dreams?
- Oh, not often, just once.
I really don't have many dreams, Doc.
- Guess I did it 'cause I was lonely.
- Is that the reason you chose to have an affair?
- No, it happened after I met him.
- Met who?
- I met this really beautiful young man with blonde hair.
Before he showed up, I felt like I was living underwater.
No matter how many people I killed, even after the wall fell, it was as if I was in a dream.
After that, everything was a lot more real.
I didn't feel like I was all alone anymore.
uh would you like some hot tea perhaps no thank you I'm fine well I could use
some I'm feeling a bit thirsty you can just wait here
my secretary's already gone for the day she has a date
She really knows how to brew tea.
It's too bad she's not here to make it for us.
Hey, Doc.
Yes? What is it?
I figure your job's gotta be pretty tough.
I mean, there's a lot of pressure.
People telling you all about their dreams and secrets.
Including ones that you probably don't want to know about
You know, ones that could get you into trouble
Like mine
I mean, now you have to walk around knowing I'm a hitman
So
Anyhow
If you want to make amends towards your wife
You... you need to start talking with her.
I hope you forgot to lock that damn door, Merith.
Wait, why aren't you?
Get out of here, now!
Dr. Tenma?
I've been watching over you, Dr. Reitwein.
You're still in great danger.
You need to get out of here.
Now run!
© transcript Emily Beynon