Go on, young man, eat. This place is known for its tasty vice-versed.
Mmm, mmm, isn't it wonderful? Your name's Dieter, right?
Doctor, you better eat now or there might not be anything left when Dieter's done.
There's no need to worry, Dr. Tenma.
This place is safe. Only local folks come here.
And if a strange face tries to get in, our friend Otto here will show them the door.
Show them the door.
Hmm.
You know, business has really dropped off since I've been doing that.
Now, who just ordered the Spetzla?
Oh, that would be me.
I pulled together a bed in the attic.
If you can ignore the rats, you should sleep pretty good up there.
Thanks, I owe you one.
He's quite a kidder, but a decent guy.
E, you can't do much on an empty stomach.
Thank you for getting me a safe place to sleep.
I should be the one who's thanking you.
By now I'd be dead in the morgue
if you hadn't come along and rescued me like you did.
Feeding death makes this meal taste even better.
Go on, dig in.
I already spoke to Dr. Gillen.
He was very pleased and relieved to hear that we found you.
He left an ad in the local newspaper trying to contact you.
Did you see it by any chance?
Let's talk about our memories of cheating.
So you did see it?
I did.
Well, then why didn't you try to contact him?
Because I didn't want anyone else getting involved.
But that's what friends are for, especially during times like these.
So, earlier you said you were watching over me.
That's because of the Richard Brown incident.
Please explain.
You probably know best what happened to him.
Brown was drunk when he shot down that young serial killer.
That night cost him his career and his family.
As I read about the boy Richard had killed, Dieter recognized the photograph.
Dieter said that boy was in 511 Kinderheim.
And what's 511 Kinderheim?
It's an orphanage that was in East Germany.
A very special one.
Dieter's foster father was one of the instructors,
and he kept pictures of the children that lived there.
And this orphanage figures into things.
Johan used to call it home.
Huh. So you're saying there's a connection between Johan and the serial killer that Richard shot?
I'm not sure.
Brown died before I could get any details from him to tie this all together.
But he led me to you.
I saw you at his grave.
I thought you might be able to fill in some of the blanks.
So that's it.
Oh, Richard.
Even in death, you're still helping us get to the bottom of this.
I know that until now you've been all alone out there.
But now, we're gonna solve this together.
We must strive to prove that you're innocent.
I think I know where we can find Johan.
Wait till you get a load of this.
I thought I had it on me.
Damn, I had a photo of Johan before.
Of all the stupid...
I must have left it in the office when I was attacked.
If you left that picture there, that man trying to kill you probably found it.
If that's the case, it's good as gone.
That man said he'd been sent to me for counseling by his wife.
Her last name was Hess, but there was nobody I could find with that last name.
He was a hitman, and he certainly tried to live up to that title.
Hmm. Johan is here, and so am I.
There must be a way to actually meet him, right?
Mm-hmm. I will meet Johan, face to face.
We'll be right back.
We'll see you next time.
Welcome to Talbach and Schuwald AG.
This is their headquarters, the epicenter of the Schuwald Financial Group.
A year ago, Mr. Schuwald was rarely here, but lately he's been around a lot.
Every morning, Mr. Schuwald leaves here to tour his affiliated offices.
Richard discovered this pattern when he was still alive.
This firm has grown exponentially as of late.
His entire financial group has seen huge growth and profits, and the reason for all this is
quite clear.
The turnaround began when a certain youth became Schuwald's right-hand man.
And here they come now.
Schuwald's the older man in the wheelchair.
Karl's the young man pushing him.
Now look closely.
Tell me, is the blonde one Johann?
That was him, there's no doubt.
Good.
This was the first time.
Huh?
I've only seen him at night.
I've never seen Johann in the daytime before.
Well, I'd say it's right about time we shed a little light on the matter.
This is my only chance.
That's true. We might not have another chance to prove your innocence.
But we must be judicious here.
You'd better keep lying low in Otto's attic for now.
To prove you're innocent, we must be thorough and methodical.
I should have another look at Richard's file.
Ah, here it is.
Good thing I decided to bring this one home.
Yes, my friend.
It'll be just a little longer, Richard.
I promise you, we will avenge your death soon.
We have discovered Johan, and we've got Dr. Tenma, the key witness.
There's just one thing left to do. One thing.
All that's left is to find someone who saw Richard the night he died.
There's got to be someone.
Once we find that person, we'll be able to prove that Johan was with Richard the night that he was killed.
Even if that doesn't work out, there's that young man Farin who claimed he was Shuvald's son and then committed suicide.
If we can find that prostitute far and visited,
we'll be able to prove that Johan was there with him.
We've got to find someone who can put Johan at the scene of the crime.
There's even a third way to make our case.
We can question the couple who claim they're Johan's parents,
and then we'll be able to find out who this imposter really is.
Keep in mind that we've discovered the real Johan Liebert's burial plot.
We're slowly tightening the noose around this Johan character's neck.
Mm-hmm.
You know, Tenma, looking at your sad eyes,
I find myself feeling the way I did when I looked at Richard.
You look like, well, it's as if you're trying to take on the troubles of the whole planet.
But don't despair, Tenma. You're not alone.
There's Dieter, and now you've got Dr. Gillen, and I'm here as well.
Things are going to be all right from now on.
Now go get yourself some sleep.
Because... I didn't want anyone else getting involved.
This was the first time.
I've only seen him at night.
I've never seen Johan in the daytime before.
This is my only chance.
Wait! Why aren't you...
Get out of here, now!
Now run!
This is Reichwein speaking.
Doctor, it's me, Gillen.
Ah, what a coincidence. I was about to call you to discuss what our next move should be.
I'll stop by later today.
By the way, where's Tenma?
Tenma? Why, he's at the safe house or so I believe.
Wherever he is, I need you to make sure that he stays put.
there's an issue that's been bothering me I feel it too it's dr. ten was
mindset he doesn't appear to want to go after Johan in spite of the fact that
doing so could prove his innocence I don't want to believe it but that's
exactly what I'm worried about
Dieter what are you doing here he told me he sent me over here then where's
Tenma he's gone off to where to take care of it what ten was planning to fix
it himself. Stop him, Doctor. Please, you gotta stop him. Don't let him do it. Tenma's going to become a killer.
That's enough for today. We're done.
Don't say that now. I'm just getting warmed up.
Doc, this is where it gets real interesting.
Not today. We'll pick it up from here next time. How about that?
I tell you, the third one I killed? Now that's a great story to hear.
she was only 18 come on doc hear me out the way i lured her into my house was great she had no clue
you gotta hear how she screamed when i strangled her listen to me doc come on
where's timba runoff to think rudy
Greetings, Dr. Gillen
At last we meet
And who are you?
My name is Inspector Lungay
I'm with the BKA
Actually, I'm well acquainted with your work, Detective
You've been responsible for the apprehension of many of the serial killers that I've interviewed
Since I read your book, one could say that I know of you as well
Why, thank you
What a remarkable piece of work. Transcendental Criminal Psychology.
What makes it a great book is that you possess deep insight into what goes on in the mind of
a serial killer. I especially liked your explanation of what motivated Heinz Kahl's
behavior in Chapter 3 of your book, on pages 262 to 294. I tend to agree with your supposition
that the trauma he experienced during his childhood turned him into a sociopath and
then a criminal. Well, then we think the same way. I feel honored that you've read my book
so thoroughly. My investigative methods also require me to get into the minds of these
criminals. I try to predict what their actions will be by acting out what it is I think they'll
do next. It sounds like you have a lot of experience. We should discuss your techniques
when we have more time. I would have to agree that neither of us have much time. I need
to ask you something now. Lately, you've been driving a lot to Munich, isn't that correct?
That's right, what of it? Please, doctor, have a seat for a minute. This won't take very long.
You've seen a psychologist named Reichwein three times this week. Why so often? Simple. He was one
of my professors from university. Dusseldorf University. Correct. There was someone special
in your class this one fellow student of yours who went on to become a brilliant neurosurgeon
where are you going with all this have you met up with dr tenma no what are you talking about
allow me to refresh your memory let's talk about our memories of cheating
rudy you placed that classified ad in every leading newspaper in the country from may 1st
to the 22nd. Imagine my surprise. Shocking. I never thought brilliant people like you or Dr.
Tenma ever had to cheat. Even as students, it seems out of character for the two of you.
It's interesting what best friends will do. Inspector, I wouldn't say that Dr. Tenma and
I were even friends when we attended Dusseldorf. Last May in Oder Park, with your help, the Velber
police were able to surround Dr. Tenma. They were poised to take him into custody, but at the last
In a second, he miraculously escaped.
Well, then you must also know that the wire I was wearing malfunctioned.
It's still possible that you might have helped him to escape.
Come on, I know that Tenma is innocent.
Really?
Have an open mind and listen to me.
The director of Eisler Memorial Hospital
and three other people that were murdered in Dusseldorf,
the murder of a patient in a building under construction,
the murder in Heidelberg. The middle-aged couples that were murdered across the country.
Those were the works of a madman, not Tenma. I reached this conclusion from interviewing
Dr. Tenma in person, as a criminal psychologist.
Interesting. So, where is he now?
Who knows? He's run off somewhere again.
Why did he run away? Why would he run away if he were innocent?
He is innocent!
You think so? He needs friends like you to help him, so why would he leave you in the dark?
Well, I have proof that he isn't the murderer you think he is.
Have a look at this, Inspector.
I personally compiled this analysis of all the evidence in this case.
You're very thorough.
So tell me, do you understand my conclusion?
Yes.
A strange death of Farin, the boy who pretended to be Schuwalt's son.
The seemingly accidental death of ex-police detective Richard Brown, who was investigating this case.
The questions and rumors surrounding Schuwalt's illegitimate child.
There's a young man who's at the center of this entire case.
When Tenma was questioned by police, he named this young man as the real murderer.
Johann Liebert.
While he was still alive, Richard Brown discovered a gravestone of a person with that same first and last name in Bruntal.
Furthermore, someone who admitted to being a hitman tried to kill Dr. Reichwein after he picked up the investigation from where Brown had left off.
Oh, I understand quite well.
But you're wrong. It's impossible to actually prove that all these separate events are connected.
Tenma has gone into hiding because he understands this more than anyone does.
Am I wrong?
I keep noticing that you tap your fingers.
Oh. That's just a little habit I have. It helps me to remember important points in a case.
As a psychologist, it appears to me that your own anxiety is manifesting itself in the way you constantly do it.
I do the same thing. I use my recorder instead of my hand.
However, the sounds that are recorded on this device are absolutely objective.
But in your case, the information that you remember when you're drumming your fingers has already been tainted by your own preset opinions.
That's probably how you've always done your job, Inspector. For all these years. Right up until now.
You believe that your memory is correct, and that your judgement couldn't possibly be wrong.
Do you have a wife or a family? Any hobbies outside your work?
You live for your job, don't you? Ever made a mistake?
Inside, aren't you terribly afraid to make a mistake?
The way you think, everything's black or white, so Tenma has to be a bad person.
And if your judgement turned out to be wrong, your whole world would fall apart.
You need to look at the truth.
This is a recent photograph of Johann Lehmert.
Can you prove all the deaths surrounding Johann is just coincidence?
This young man, where would I find him this very moment?
He's a student at the University of Munich.
At the moment, he's Schuwalt's private secretary.
So this is him.
I'll need to hold on to this photograph, Doctor.
From this point on, let's consider this a police matter.
You know, perhaps I made a terrible mistake.
Where is Dr. Tenma right now?
He should still be in Munich.
Yes, this is Lungay. Put me through to the Munich police. I need an emergency deployment.
Dr. Tenma is somewhere in the city of Munich.
A sniper rifle?
Look, I don't got a clue what you're talking about.
Wait, so Mr. Heitmeier didn't call you from his mountain villa in Fusen?
10,000 Deutschmarks in advance.
Here.
Your order is a little complicated for me to fill
It'll take about a week to get it
In the meantime, go get some sun
You look pale
Listen, you're getting yourself a good piece
But it's a waste if you don't know how to use it
Just remember that
Next in the news
City officials attended a posh reception
for the Munich Electronics Industry Trade Show
that's being hosted this weekend
by the state's Chamber of Commerce
in association with local business leaders.
Political and business figures
from all over the world are attending.
With the formation of the EU,
Bavaria's industries are poised
to become the center of Europe's media network.
This is the largest trade show
Munich has ever hosted,
and the monetary impact on the local economy
from this event is in the millions.
In a related story,
noted industrialist Hans Georg Schuvold,
who hasn't appeared in public for nearly 20 years,
was seen at the reception
and received rousing applause from the attendees.
Mr. Schuvold was in a wheelchair, but he appeared healthy.
© transcript Emily Beynon