[BELL RINGING]
Hey, Carl.
Oh, hi, Lota.
Do you have a minute?
Not really, I'm running late.
But what's up?
Nothing.
Maybe we could go and have a cup of coffee.
I thought you might want to talk about how things are
going with you and your father.
I mean, you were so worried before.
Not now.
I'm fine.
Everything's good.
Yeah, but...
I'm off.
Sorry Lota, but I've got to get home.
My father has a business meeting and I have to take him to it.
See you later.
Wait!
I bought tickets to a dance!
I was thinking...
maybe...
we could...
go...
[music ends]
[birds chirping]
Please finish up. The library will be closing shortly.
Oh, yeah.
We're closing now.
She's come back here again.
I bet a beautiful girl like that doesn't have to worry about getting someone to take her to a dance.
Oh man, it's so unfair.
What is it about her?
Come on, I'm closing up now!
Yes, ma'am!
I've seen her. Can't remember where.
A dance?
Yeah. I guess that's what it's called. Normally I wouldn't be interested in that type of thing.
But a friend insisted that I buy some tickets.
I'm afraid I'm not going to be able to make it. Sorry.
I have to go with my father to an official state banquet.
It's kind of an important political event.
I'm sure you won't have a problem finding someone to take you to the dance.
See you later, though.
No big deal. I didn't really want to go anyway.
"Research on Margot Langer"
Hello to Frank. I'm a Cultural Anthropology major.
And what about you?
Whoa! You've collected a mountain of information, Nina.
This page is about the accountant murder.
I also have a newspaper article on the Voice of God case.
And pages and pages on the middle-aged couple's serial murders.
You've done amazing research.
I was thinking mine was impressive, but you have me beat for sure.
Well, I've been researching all the unsolved murders in Bavaria
But at the moment, I need more information on the former prostitute Margot Langer.
Do you think you could help fill in the blanks?
Gee, I've told you pretty much all I know.
The child born to Margot Langer and the very wealthy Hans Schuwald
spent years in foster care, but was just recently recognized by his father
and accepted as his rightful heir.
Maybe he's the one responsible for the awful events surrounding Mr. Schuwald.
That's not possible. I'm 100% sure of it.
You're really obsessed with this.
I mean, considering that the research is just for a paper that you have to write for your class.
Y-you really think so?
This isn't about some paper, is it?
To be perfectly honest with you, I'm looking for someone.
Hey, can I ask you something?
In your whole life, have you ever had to worry about anything?
I've been wondering, do beautiful girls like you always get everything they want without
lifting a finger?
Does it fall in your lap?
What are you trying to imply?
Just, well, you can probably get any guy you want and never have to spend a minute worrying
about it.
It's fine, okay?
I'm sure you don't have worries like me.
Just forget it, alright?
Oh, man. Life just seems to be so unfair.
Listen, come with me to the dance tonight. It'll be a lot of fun.
Normally I wouldn't come to these type of things, you know?
Come on, let's give it a chance.
to me as long as they see I'm with you.
Hey, turn around.
Everyone's looking at us.
Hey.
Well, go ahead.
Talk to him.
I'll just take the leftovers.
Lota, stop it already.
Hi.
See?
You're a magnet.
Hi.
I'm Constantine, the president of the Supernatural Phenomenon
Club.
How are you doing?
Oh, boy.
Someone let the weirdos out.
Give me a break.
Who do you think you are trying to hit on, Nina?
Wait, Lota.
Nina, hold on a second.
How about the two of us hang out together tonight, you know?
Who, me?
He's made a mistake.
No, be happy about it.
Well, I'd better be going now.
Nina, wait!
Hey, he's really not my type. I mean, not even a little bit.
Stay with me, Nina, please.
Dang it!
It's kind of depressing. I don't think we're fitting in.
Really?
Oh yeah, really.
All those guys were talking to you, but one by one you pushed them away.
Come on, you're way too picky, Nina.
I wasn't consciously trying to be rude.
I guess it's just that... I'm out of practice.
Huh?
These guys all hang out together.
They're used to joking around and having fun, but for me, it's been a long time.
Nina, it sounds like...
You're pretty old-fashioned, despite the way you look.
Despite the way I look? And what exactly is that supposed to mean, Lota?
Hey, guess who's back? Wanna dance with me?
C'mon babe, what do you say?
Ew, please just go away. Leave me alone.
C'mon, don't be like that. Just one little dance.
Don't come any closer! You're drunk!
Hey, stop it! Let me go!
C'mon, cut it out!
Hey! You know, it's not like I'm asking because I dig you or anything.
You're a fine one to talk, buddy. You're just plain rude!
Come on, one stupid little dance. Let's get it over with.
Stop it! Come on, let me go!
If you don't dance with me, then I won't get paid.
Paid? To dance with me?
Yeah, but I'm not supposed to say anything. It's just between Carl and me.
You must have thought you wouldn't be able to find anyone who'd want to dance with you.
Carl did this?
Whatever. I'll dance with you.
So what do you say? Let's hit the dance floor.
I promise not to step on your toes.
Let me go.
Come on, sweetie. I know you don't mean that.
Please, stop it!
Give me one little song and I'm on my way.
Don't! I'm real sorry!
I won't ask anymore, I promise!
Let me go! Come on, please!
We're done.
I must be crazy.
I really liked Carl.
I even helped him get reunited with his father.
so much and I thought he liked me but ever since Mr. Schuwald acknowledged him as his true son he
he has no time for me he's busy with his father it's always his father
I feel so lost it hurts so much I never thought that getting rejected would ever feel like this
It's painful. Right now the world is full of pain.
But everything will be alright. I know it.
The bad things can't keep happening forever.
We have to do our part to stop them. Right?
"Cafe Vinyl"
I know what it is. About Nina. Why I thought I'd seen her somewhere before.
She looks just like Johan.
If this were a regular gun, you'd get high marks for skill, but in this case it's the
precision of the rifle rather than your ability, Doctor.
This weapon might not have tested well enough to be designated the official sniper rifle
of the German Army, but it can hit the center of a 5-centimeter target from 300 meters away,
even if you're an amateur.
I don't know what you're planning to shoot, but I'm going to give you a couple of pointers.
First, the closer you get to your target,
obviously, the better accuracy you'll have.
And, of course, you'll need to find a place
where you can get off a clear shot.
It comes with four .338 Lapua Magnum bullets.
But you won't have time to re-aim
and fire off all four of 'em.
Really, one shot's the most you're gonna get.
(waves crashing)
(birds chirping)
(eerie music)
(explosion booms)
(bird squawks)
- You come here every week.
So, are you an avid bird-watcher?
Uh, oh, yeah.
I don't know why, but Thursday seems to be the most popular day of the week for visitors.
Like that old man with his two young companions over there. And you, too, of course.
I suspect you like the solitude of this forest.
Uh, I'm enjoying it. And yourself?
It's complicated.
Well, actually, I'm making amends with this place.
And I've been doing so for over 60 years.
I haven't seen him before.
From the looks of it, he didn't even take one bite of my special dish.
Gosh, that is such a shame.
Are you ready for a fabulous prize?
It's time to find out who knows the answers.
Our first contestant is Max Feindler from Frankfurt.
And he's going to have a chance to win
a brand-new, fully-equipped RV.
Whoa! My family's been dreaming
about going camping in one for years.
Well, you'll be able to take them camping
every weekend in style.
But you have to answer all ten questions correctly
to receive your dream prize.
Ready for your first question.
Are you planning to sit here and stare at your food again?
You came in and did that about a week ago.
I make it my business to remember my customers.
If you don't have any appetite,
at least try some soup before you leave.
It's on the house.
Come on, you'd better eat.
Thank you for your concern.
I'll have a clear shot here.
I've got to take him out in this forest.
(gagging)
- Ah, thank goodness.
I know every inch of this forest. I've walked here for so many years.
Well, I must be getting old.
You may not have an actual fracture. I've wrapped it up as a precaution.
But you should get an x-ray at the hospital, too.
I didn't peg you as a doctor.
When I first saw you, I thought you were a birdwatcher or maybe a hunter,
but that doesn't seem to be the case.
What are you talking about?
All the birds.
Huh?
They're gathering together overhead.
A long time ago,
all the wild birds would flock together
when a young boy appeared.
He would extend his arm like this
and the birds would come to him.
As a young boy growing up,
he'd spend his free time in the forest with the birds.
But then things changed, and Hitler's era came along.
The boy was now a young man and joined the police force.
He was convinced that the National Socialist German Workers' Party
would turn his bankrupt country into an ideal place.
Then out of the blue, this young man was given an order.
A vicious criminal had escaped into this very same forest.
And because he knew these woods so well, he was commanded to go out and find him.
"Shoot the violent criminal on sight," they told him.
The young policeman chased the criminal through the forest that he knew like the back of his hand.
He kept on and on until finally, there he was.
He had him cornered with his hands up.
Then he realized that the vicious criminal was actually just an ordinary man.
A foreigner.
The young man felt he had no choice but to obey without question.
So he carried out his order.
Since that day, the birds never came to rest on his arm again.
For sixty long years now, this man of the forest has been trying to make amends.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Apologize though he may, the birds refuse to ever come near him.
That's amazing.
It'll be okay now, little bird. It's your home. We respect it.
Never again will blood be shed in this forest.
Isn't that right?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)