That's amazing.
It'll be okay now, little bird.
It's your home. I respect it.
Never again will blood be shed in this forest.
Isn't that right?
We'll be right back.
♪♪♪
We'll see you next time.
I don't know.
So you don't remember anything?
I need you to take your time and try to think back to the roof.
Any detail you can remember about what you were doing up there would be helpful.
Martin, you have to tell the doctor what happened.
If you hadn't hit the eave on the first floor
and got caught in the tree, you would have died.
Do you understand?
Please, Martin, just talk to the doctor.
If you don't, we're never going to put
all this foolishness behind us.
Madam, do please try to stay calm.
Doctor, if he were to die, I don't know what I'd...
I just don't.
It's all right, madam.
I'm here to see that your son gets the counseling he needs.
I know. I know. It's just...
Look, why don't we take this conversation outside?
Now, Dieter, I want you to behave yourself while I'm gone.
And remember, you're not allowed inside that room.
That boy, is he your grandson?
No, I'm just taking care of him for a while.
I don't know.
Uh, hi there.
Hi yourself.
Uh, my name's Dieter.
I'm Martin
Does it hurt
Does what hurt that stuff all the cuts under your bandages?
When you fell off the roof, but that was really scary for you
Hey, what are you doing? You shouldn't be standing up my shoes are in that bag down there on the floor get them for me
I can't you've got to lie down
- Look, just get the shoes.
- Where do you think you're going?
You're gonna get yelled at.
- Why should I care if someone yells at me?
It's not like I'm afraid to get yelled at.
It's just like he told me.
If you come back alive, step outside.
The world will be different.
Nah, the world didn't change. I'm the one who changed.
You see, I'm one of the special few who've been chosen.
I'm so bored
I never realized how boring this world is
Hey, look out!
Come on, hurry up. There's really nothing to be afraid of.
What did you do that for?
Check it out. Look how scared this guy is.
Martin, stop!
No, just look at him, Dieter.
Someone please help.
I don't want to die!
Yeah!
Guess you're lucky.
'Cause I'm gonna let you live.
I have an answer to that question.
Huh?
You said you thought that falling off the roof was scary for me, right?
Yeah, I did.
Falling wasn't even a bit scary.
After all, it's just a game.
J-just a game?
But so many people have died 'cause of it!
Ah, but it's so much fun.
Who cares about those guys?
Two people stand facing each other on the edge of the roof of an empty building.
building then you close your eyes and walk towards each other one step at a time it's like a duel
and it doesn't matter whether you fall or not if you survive you win why play a game like that
you do it so that you can bet against fate those who manage to survive are the chosen ones
how can i put this in a way you'll understand the survivor gets to keep playing over and over again
Yeah, but Martin, why play the game at all?
Because everything else is boring, that's why.
But the game is real fun.
And the best part is playing it again once fate has made you a chosen one.
Don't you get it?
And I thought for sure that you must be one of us.
Fine, I'll show you.
If you don't get it after seeing it, then you really are stupid.
Hey. Hey, you're not really planning on going up to the roof, are you?
Yeah, because I'm chosen. The superior will always survive, just like him.
Just like who?
The person who taught us the game, you dummy.
And who is that?
He's a friend. A friend to all the children who've been chosen.
now hurry up get over here i don't think i want to stop whining and come on let go of me
but you need to understand
those scars who did that to you bet it was your parents huh are you really gonna stay with them
after they did something like that you still want to be a part of this worthless world even after
Everything they've done to you come on you have to see
What do you think how's the view how does it make you feel oh?
Come on, there's nothing to be afraid of stand up close your eyes and take a step
Stand Dieter
I understand now. I get what you've been saying. It all makes sense to me.
I thought the world was filled with darkness.
That the future would bring nothing but more misery.
I mean, like, what's your favorite food?
I ate this really good sausage the other day, but if I die, I'll never get to eat it again.
You're such a coward.
I really like playing soccer.
If I die, I'll never get to play again.
You're so weak.
And I really like Dr. Reikwein.
And his secretary, Ms. Merith, is nice to me.
If I die, I'll never see him again.
There are always things to be scared of.
Learning to deal with that is part of growing up.
Tenma told me tomorrow's gonna be a good day.
If I die, I will never get to see Tenma again.
I'm gonna fall!
Don't panic. Just don't stand up yet.
I can't be like him.
I can't be like Johan. I just can't.
What did you say?
Johan is playing an even scarier game than this one.
He said that he was going to be killed soon.
He said that he was going to be shot by a Japanese guy.
I closed my eyes, and I walked across the edge of the roof.
I'm not kidding. I really did walk it.
And I wasn't scared at all, you know.
Joachim was supposed to be walking across for me,
but when I opened my eyes, he wasn't there anymore.
I really saw it.
He fell off the building and died right in front of me.
People really die.
Anyone want tea?
Oh, thank you.
Honestly, I just don't know about my son.
He doesn't seem to understand what he's done.
I'm glad he's still alive.
But when I think of what poor Joachim's parents are going through,
I just hope you manage to talk some sense into him.
At least he seems to listen to you.
Ugh. She gets on my case like that every day. Seriously, she doesn't understand anything.
She won't let me out of the house or watch TV or even read my comics.
Nothing's worse than boredom. I'll bring you something to help pass the time.
Really?
You may not be allowed to read comics, but a picture book should be okay.
Serious? A picture book? That sounds pretty stupid to me.
Hey, tell me about that freaky new game you said you were playing.
You said you were going to be shot and killed like any minute now.
Now that is exciting.
So come on, when is that Japanese guy going to shoot you?
Spill it, Johan.
Hermann Hesse, a first edition of Steppenwolf.
And this, a first edition of Hoffman's Night Pieces,
and a complete anthology of Goethe's poetry.
This is very impressive.
Despite being the head librarian of the University of Munich Friedrich Emanuel Campus Library,
I'm simply dazzled by your collection.
I managed to make my way through life without a proper college education.
I made up for this by reading every book I could get a hold of.
Well, your decision to donate this collection is a priceless gift to the university.
I cannot begin to express my gratitude.
My eyes are failing, and I've lost the keen vision that reading requires.
I'd much rather these books be accessible to your students than sitting here in my private stacks collecting dust.
Of course. You have a number of priceless books here, but I would also prefer to make them available to the public.
Oh, that reminds me. We've just finished arranging storage for them.
And would it be possible to arrange a meeting at the library to discuss holding a ceremony of some sort?
Well, how's the security there?
There are a few dangerous organizations we've had to keep an eye on ever since Mr. Schuvel re-entered public life.
We just want to make sure you review your guest list thoroughly.
Wouldn't you agree, Johan?
Of course.
It was Johann and Karl who thought up the idea of donating the collection.
They'll make all the necessary arrangements.
I'm Germont, the head librarian.
Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure's all mine.
This is where we'll be storing Mr. Schuwald's collection
The general public is not allowed entry
You've never been here, have you?
Of course, we'll maintain the appropriate temperature and humidity
for preserving the books as well as protective measures against theft and fire
What an amazing collection of books
A real testament to mankind, isn't it?
Oh, it's a testament. You're absolutely right.
And this is the central hall where we plan to hold the donation ceremony, with your approval.
The library's security will be tightened, just as Mr. Schuwald's assistant requested.
We want our benefactor to feel as safe as possible here.
Thank you. I am sure that my father will be more than happy to attend.
Isn't that right, Johan?
Is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Would you excuse me, please?
are you looking for something yes I was on the hunt for a picture book for a
good friend of mine for a friend you say yes for a friend in need let's see well
think I would recommend this one see the illustrations are beautiful oh yes
lovely but it might be just a tad too grown up oh I'm sorry I assumed your
friend was a bit older if that's the case then how about this one
Thank you very much, sir.
Oh, how embarrassing. I'm so clumsy. This happens all the time.
Ah, how about this one? It's a beautiful book. I highly recommend it.
did that one catch your eye
oh my that is beautiful who's the author of this i'm sorry may i it's emil
sherba moravia publishing it's a czech publishing company in prague there are quite a few talented
writers publishing picture books in czechoslovakia but i don't think i've ever heard of sherba before
Perhaps he's just not very well known
Is everything alright?
I... Help!
Somebody please help!
Man, this summer heat is really starting to get to me.
Just awful.
Right here.
It'll all end here, on this spot.
© transcript Emily Beynon
© BF-WATCH TV 2021