He was released?
Yes. Johann Liebert was discharged this morning.
Wow, that was fast.
They said he just collapsed all of a sudden.
But I guess it couldn't have been anything too serious.
Oh, you. You come by the library a fair amount.
Hey, you're a librarian at the university, aren't you?
Oh, so they let him out already?
that's a relief he gave me such a scare yesterday so you were there when he
collapsed then uh-huh he was trying to track down a book and I was the one
helping him just the luck of the draw and then it happened I've never heard a
person scream like that before what set him off he had this picture book and he
flipped it to a certain page picture book
♪ He is risen ♪
♪♪♪
© transcript Emily Beynon
Nobody'd think less of you for taking a few days off, you know.
Your EEG readings were normal.
They didn't show anything.
In fact, you're the picture of health.
You know, the doctor says it's probably anemia or fatigue.
Another possibility is that you experienced some sort of shock, or so the doctor says.
By the way, he also mentioned something about a scar on your head from a major surgery.
I'm just giving you a hard time, but seriously, you should probably take it easy for a bit.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You got some mail.
This letter came for you while you were in the hospital.
Oh, really?
It's strange.
They didn't put their return address, but I didn't hear any ticking, so I think you're
What's so funny, Johan? Come on, share the joke.
Just what did they send you, anyway?
Oh, it's merely a letter from the Red Hindenburg.
Huh?
You look pretty wholesome. You sure you're tall enough for this ride?
What, are you lost, kid? Or maybe you're looking to lose it, yeah.
If you want to learn your ABCs, I'm the perfect girl for the job. Come on.
You don't happen to know the Red Hindenburg, do you?
Huh?
The Red Hindenburg. I'm looking for her. She's nearby, or so I've heard.
Huh? Why are you looking for her?
Seriously, you must be into some pretty kinky stuff there, kid.
Fine, they're in the back.
I need my fix.
I'm coming down too hard.
Will I find a red Hindenburg at the top of the stairs?
It's open.
Oh, good, you came.
Make yourself at home.
Ah, yes, that face of yours.
You've such a beautiful face.
I saw you on TV, kid, the evening news.
Right next to Schuwald.
Smooth one, aren't you?
So now you're calling yourself the Red Hindenburg,
after calling yourself Margot Langer all that time?
And before Langer, the name was Blue Sophie.
Call me whatever, as long as I get paid.
Names don't mean crap, right, Johan Liebert?
If you simply must know, it's a pet name for my latest boyfriend.
He's waiting back there behind door number one.
Ain't ya, honey?
don't go getting any funny ideas sweetie he's holding a big gun in his hand and he's just
itching to give it a go you should see the one he's got in his pants
i'm impressed
warming your way into old shoe vaults confidence like that you're running one hell of a scheme
I'm not just saying it to be polite I remember you bringing that foreign boy saying he was
Schuwald's son who could have ever guessed the real deal would come forward those were some
pretty long odds right guess you knew better poor little Edmund foreign what a fool you practically
tied the noose for him as soon as he'd served his purpose hell kid it took me two years that's how
Long ago, the real Margot Langer died, and let me tell you, the timing couldn't have been better for me.
After she died, her name allowed me to cash in on Shuvald's guilt.
No point letting that money go to waste.
Whatever. It's not like the girl was my closest friend or anything.
She wasn't even turning tricks anymore.
She said she went completely clean.
We just had a couple of drinks, nothing more.
She probably didn't have anyone else to talk to.
I'd get her drunk, shed a few crocodile tears,
and suddenly her life was an open book.
I heard all about her fling with Schuwald,
and about sending his bastard to an orphanage.
And then the poor thing went and got herself killed.
I used the name Margot Langer to get Schuwald's money,
and I lived happily ever after, end of story.
When Margot was killed, the police concluded
she was the victim of a random attack.
Case closed.
Little did they know this dead former hooker
was just one measly piece in a big, gory puzzle.
Like Richard Brown, the former police detective.
I can't help but feel sorry for the guy.
If he hadn't gotten so nosy,
maybe he wouldn't have felt like jumping that fateful night.
Goodness me, what's the body count again?
Enough reminiscing. Let's get down to why I asked you to come here tonight.
Business, my dear.
And don't even think about squirming your way out of this one.
Ain't that right, honey?
So name a number. I'm listening.
What are you, deaf?
Tell me, what do you think is the ultimate fear?
Huh?
I really thought I'd already reached the darkest of the dark.
What the hell are you mumbling about now?
But then, ahead of me...
I beheld a darkness even greater still.
Wait a minute!
You think you can just walk away?
I'm leaving this town.
You see, Shoe Vault no longer amuses me.
Don't try to blow me off, kid!
It's no use.
How do you shoot a person who doesn't even exist?
I'm through messing around!
Honey! Honey, get out here already!
Honey, what are you doing?
Roberto, please!
Hello again. May I please have a balloon?
Here, take it and go get your fix.
How much longer is it gonna be, Doctor? Come on, he's bleeding from his head!
What? My kid's going in first. You wait your turn.
Quit your yowling, Brad. It's just a broken bone.
It hurts so much.
Mommy!
You said it, fella. Wine all you want.
There's still only one doctor here.
Am I right?
Hey, young man, what do you got in that bundle of yours, huh?
Uh, this? It's nothing.
You don't happen to know if this particular doctor is good, do you, sir?
Best of the bunch.
If it weren't for this doctor, all us Asians around here, we'd all be dead.
Especially the Vietnamese.
Really? You don't say.
Hold on. You're not Vietnamese, right?
No, I'm not.
Wait a sec. Where are you going?
Some of these folks are in a bad way, son. Let them go first.
Don't worry. I didn't come here as a patient for what it's worth.
Hey, hold up. You need to wait your turn.
He needs to be looked at right now, doctor!
My kid is first, you got that?
If you'd excuse me.
Hey, what the hell? Where do you think you're going, pal?
I'm sorry, Doctor. I just wanted to ask you something really fast.
Wait out there. How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't have time for this.
A woman. And she's...
Didn't you hear me? Get out of here.
How old could she be?
I'm in the middle of suturing this wound.
If anything goes wrong, it's on your head for distracting me.
A stab wound in the thigh.
It's from a knife.
Her stitches are neat, but...
I think the patient's going to need a drainage tube.
I think you need to keep quiet.
Otherwise, you'd better take this person to a real hospital.
They'll take care of it.
I don't know who you think you are, but this is a real hospital.
No, it's really not.
It's no hospital any more than you're a real doctor
If a real hospital were an option for these people
Don't you think they would have gone?
Most of the patients who come here are undocumented immigrants
If they took their problems to one of those real hospitals
They'd be sent to jail and deported to their country of origin
How many people do you think I've had die right here in this room
Because a real hospital wasn't a choice?
Save your judgment for things you actually know something about
insert the drainage tube now the knife he was stabbed with probably wasn't very clean
unless you insert a drainage tube the wound will get infected and form an abscess look i know what
i'm talking about here okay now remove a few of the stitches got it insert that tube about
Five centimeters. Gently now.
That's it. You did a good job.
Thank you very much. Who's the next patient?
You're finally awake.
You push yourself too hard.
Your patients told me you'd been treating them for two days straight without any sort of break.
I checked on everyone's post-operative status while you were asleep.
You know, you're pretty good at this for being underground.
How old are you, anyway?
17.
I never would have guessed it based on your work.
You have the skills of a practicing physician.
It just happened.
And the doctor who used to practice out of this building disappeared and left all his equipment behind.
The equipment won't get you far without proper training.
So, where'd you learn your techniques, anyway?
My father, he was a doctor.
Is that so?
He had a practice in Vietnam, and when he came to East Germany to study, he took me along with him.
He ended up staying there for keeps, even opened up his own little clinic.
And then the Berlin Wall came down.
He never had enough time to treat everybody, but he tried to help out the immigrant community as best he could.
Until that day
The day a man murdered my father
Some neo-nazi thug
Just because our skin is a different color
My father is dead
I was just a kid
So eventually they sent me to an orphanage
A German family adopted me soon after
Turns out the only reason they took me in was to look like good Samaritans to the neighborhood
We saved this poor little yellow girl, aren't we great?
So I ran away
Anyway, I'd been helping my father at his clinic from the start
I read a lot of the medical books in his library after he was killed
Someone had to carry on his mission, and who better to do it than his own daughter?
Step aside, I can finish up the boy's arm
That wasn't so bad.
Go easy on it for a while if you want it to heal right.
Okay.
Fine, then. Who's up next?
Most of them are treated and gone.
You know, you could be a top-notch doctor if you went to school.
This country is full of opportunities for people who want to learn.
Words of wisdom from a real doctor, unless I'm wrong.
I'm not going to close this clinic because you say so.
Hold on. That's not what I'm saying here.
I just thought that maybe you could...
If I leave, who's going to take care of all those people who come here for help?
No one. Nobody else here gives a damn.
Listen, what I meant was...
Mommy, don't die!
What happened?
My pimp, I pissed him off.
He said I had a smart mouth, so he shot me.
Mommy, Mommy!
Your mom walked all the way here after being shot?
Mommy said if we came here, you'd be able to make her better again.
But she's shot.
Please save her. Make Mommy better. I don't want her to die.
I will. Now go wait out there like a good, brave boy, okay?
Save my Mommy, Doctor. Please help her.
Around here, it's the prostitutes who always get shot or knifed or worse.
I wish there was something I could do, but I'm out of my league here.
We need to get her on the table. Lift up her legs.
No way! What do you think you're doing?
This woman needs to go to a real hospital!
She'll be dead before we ever get her to the emergency room!
I can't! I can't save this patient!
This one's too much for me!
A doctor never gives up!
There's always a chance as long as the patient is still breathing.
Do you understand?
Don't ever give up hope!
If the artery in her abdominal cavity had been damaged,
her blood pressure would have plummeted leading to immediate shock but she was able to walk here
on her own which means her blood pressure dropped gradually she's in a state of pre-shock which
improves her odds judging from the location of the bullet wound there could be some damage to
the spleen we can perform emergency abdominal surgery on her while transfusing blood simultaneously
all right let's get started pick up the scalp
It's amazing he can sleep so soundly.
I still can't believe there was no damage to the stomach, intestines, or any part of the digestive tract.
All we had to do was remove the injured portion of the spleen and stitch her up.
You did a great job in there.
Only because you were there with me.
Mommy.
You know, Dr. Tenma,
this place could use you.
No.
I came here because I had a question to ask
I spotted this article
Blue Sophie, also known as the Red Hindenburg
The word on the street is you were the first person to arrive at the crime scene
Are the rumors true?
Uh-huh
Can you tell me anything about what you saw when you got there?
Anything at all?
I got a call that somebody heard a shot, so I rushed over as fast as I could.
I got her in the back of the head, point blank.
She died instantly.
I've seen many crime scenes, but this one was different.
The feeling that I got when I walked into that room...
It wasn't a robbery. There wasn't any malice, either.
It was simply a killing.
Johan.
When you're in the darkness, you only sink deeper into it.
Keep the light shining.
Enroll in a program somewhere and study hard, okay?
You've got a real gift for this.
You'll make a fine doctor.
Hold on! Where are you going, Dr. Tenma? Please wait!
The darkness?
But you also look like someone sinking deeper into the darkness, aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
Please tell me that you'll come back someday. Can you promise me that?
© transcript Emily Beynon