Domo, your cooperation is greatly appreciated.
Thank you. It's a pleasure doing business with you.
Perhaps the next time we meet, it should be over a round of golf.
What do you say to that, huh?
All right, but only if you promise to go easy on us.
Of course. I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, domo.
Domo.
Domo this, domo that.
It's a thoroughly incomprehensible culture.
Ah, domo, domo. Apologies for the wait.
My meeting ran a little longer than expected.
The name is Iwai of the Kadufuku Corporation, Munich branch.
Inspector Lunge of the BKA.
Pleased to meet you.
Domo.
Domo Anabao. That was unexpected.
Coffee. Oh, and a refill for him, too.
My apologies, I know you were expecting to meet with Yamamoto today.
There was an emergency in the Czech Republic, but he's expected back in town sometime tomorrow.
You seem rather busy.
Oh, yes, I mean, you've heard.
Mr. Schuwald's corporate dynasty?
Ever since he came out of seclusion and resumed his financial activities,
all of his affiliate companies and related businesses throughout Germany have been very active.
The whole Japanese business community is desperately vying for his attention.
Why is he laughing?
So, Mr. Yamamoto will not be able to meet with you today.
But I can say that I knew Kenzo Tenma just as well as he did.
So feel free to ask anything.
But of course.
I have to say, Inspector, I'm shocked.
He's still under investigation?
Well, I'll just say that we haven't come to any conclusions.
I was floored to hear Tenma named as a suspect in your investigation.
I couldn't have imagined such a thing.
You just said you felt shocked. Was it really that unexpected?
Absolutely. Kenzo Tenma, a killer?
Come on. It's just crazy.
Not in a million years would I have pegged Tenma.
as a killer. We had drinks a couple of times. I guess about three years ago. He really didn't
seem like a bad guy. So he really didn't seem like a bad guy. You're saying you thought he
was a good guy then? A good guy? Let's see. I think reserved would be the word I'd use to
describe Tenma. What you're saying then is that not being open is what makes him a good man.
Well, it didn't prevent him from being social. That's what I meant by not a bad guy.
We'll be right back.
♪♪♪
Japanese people don't normally wear these sorts of clothes.
Japanese people are skillful with chopsticks.
So now I will be Japanese.
Domo, I'm Japanese.
I am a Japanese man.
I am a Japanese man. I am Tenma.
Hello.
Um, Father?
Yes?
It's me. How are you?
I'm fine.
I called because I heard you were in Munich.
I live here now.
Actually, Father, I'm a mother now.
I had my baby
I thought you'd want to know
I see
That's good
I know a lot of things have been said between us
But
I want you to see your grandchild
Will you see us?
Of course I will
Well, would tomorrow be okay?
Yes
As long as it's after six
Where would you like to meet?
Near Marion Plotz?
Okay
All right. See you then. Domo.
What?
Hey, you're pretty good with those chopsticks, you know that?
Is that so?
Sure. These days I see a lot of foreigners using chopsticks better than native Japanese.
So, Dr. Takahashi, as a former colleague of Tenma's, what would you say was your impression of him?
Let's see.
Well, as I remember, he wasn't a hard guy to like.
Though he was occasionally more than a bit indecisive.
Still.
Go on.
With a scalpel in his hand, he was a whole other person.
People called him a genius brain surgeon.
And I can say that was no exaggeration.
What about his parents?
Hmm.
He never really talked about his parents much.
But he said his father and older brother were doctors also.
So I guess they put him on the physician's path whether he liked it or not.
In fact, I think I remember him saying he hadn't been back to Japan since coming to Germany for medical school.
Matter of fact, his parents didn't come to Germany at all to support him when the scandal broke.
I don't think they made any public appeal for their son's innocence either.
I guess he and his family weren't all that tight-knit, you know what I mean?
Thanks for waiting. Sorry it's taken so long, but we've just gotten word from Yamamoto.
He's left Prague and is back in Munich, but unfortunately he has a client whose needs must be tended to immediately.
He seems to be a busy man.
If it's any consolation, he did say he was going to join all of us at a bar after work.
A bar?
That's right. Care to join us for a drink, Inspector?
The fates have delivered you this opportunity.
After all, it's always good to make a few new contacts.
No. Tonight I have to.
i guess he and his family weren't all that tight-knit you know what i mean
i am tenma
sounds great i would be happy to join you tonight
Well done, Iwai! Well done!
Inspector Lungay, how about a song?
Yeah!
Oh, this next song is mine.
Let's sing.
All right.
Let's hear it.
Great.
Good.
I am Tenma.
I don't fit into Japanese society
I do not ask others for help
I don't fit in anywhere
I have no home to return to
I am alone
Ah, domo domo
I'm sorry I'm late, guys
Oh, there you are, Yamamoto.
Inspector Lunge, you know, the one I told you about on the phone?
Oh, domo. I'm Yamamoto of the Munich branch of the Karafuku.
Domo.
So, how did it go with Mr. Kocht in the Czech Republic?
Ah, he's a tough nut.
Oh, yeah, that thing I was supposed to get? Done.
What thing?
You know, that one thing that Schuwald's right-hand man was asking us to get, the blonde guy.
That thing? That's great news!
Right now, kissing up to him is the best way to close a deal with Schuwvold,
so we gotta get on that man's good side and stay there.
I went poking through all the second-hand bookstores in Prague,
and I was finally able to find a copy.
Wow, so that's the picture book you wanted.
Unfortunately, it's kind of worn out and the cover's coming off.
A little restoration and it'll be beautiful.
Excuse me, I think we can use a couple of beers over here.
Mind if I take a look?
No, hey, go right ahead.
It's written in Czech.
All right, it's my turn again.
All right!
That's great.
What a time, we've been waiting for you.
Hope you guys have been practicing.
so inspector what are you looking up in that dictionary translating check check huh so does
it have something to do with that investigation you've got going no it's a personal project i'm
kind of surprised to see you're doing anything that's not related to your case it's from a
Picture book. I like the illustration. I just wanted to know what the passage said.
The inspector's reading a picture book. That's something you don't see every day.
Look at me. Look at me.
The monster inside me has gotten this big.
I see. So Johan is pulling the strings on that billionaire.
Dr. Gillen, you've been telling me all about this Johan person for a while now.
You've painted him as quite the monster, haven't you?
Monster, eh?
Well, yeah. I mean, I've killed some people, sure.
But he's transformed himself into the sort of creature I could only dream of becoming.
This Johan has become my idol, my hero.
Really? Well, there is one more question that I would like to ask of you, if you don't mind.
Knock yourself out.
If you were Johann, what would be the next move that you made?
Next?
Well, that's obvious.
The parents, you know, the Lieberts.
I think it would be time for them to die.
Uh, Mr. Liebert?
Mr. Liebert!
What brought you to that conclusion?
Because I've gotten bored.
Mr. Liebert, open up this door!
Mr. Liebert!
Yes, hello.
You're a psychologist?
I'm sorry, we don't understand.
What can we do for you, Dr. Reichwein?
I won't waste your time with a long-winded explanation.
I just want to ask some questions about your adopted son, Johan.
Johan? Adopted?
You must be mistaken.
That boy is our child. I gave birth to him and I...
That's enough, Mrs. Liebert.
I know for a fact that your real child is buried in Bruntal.
There was a fire that burned down the town hall along with all the birth records.
The fire allowed you to apply for a new birth certificate as if your original child were still alive.
What's this all about?
Look, I didn't come here to make threats, I promise you.
All I want to do is help if you'll let me.
Please, read this.
It's a report about Johan.
About Johan?
Yes. A friend compiled that information.
Oh.
I've met him.
He came to the house selling insurance policies.
That man was former detective Richard Brown.
He's a detective?
He was. He's dead now.
Just read.
The story actually starts a few years ago,
when an East German government official escaped and sought refuge here in West Germany in 1986.
What's it about? Is he after money?
Money? Nah, Johann couldn't care less about money.
Then why go after a billionaire like Schuwald in the first place?
You know that thing you did as a kid?
What thing?
When I was a kid, I would find a line of ants.
Yeah, and then I'd play with them, mess with their formation.
my god i refuse to believe this it's all simply dreadful this story is ridiculous
look i understand that you don't want to believe it the two of you lost your only son at a very
early age i know your life moves on and you wait to be blessed with a new child until one day a boy
nearly the same age as yours appears and to sweeten the pot the boy arrives with money
He provides you with a wonderful house to live in,
in a nice neighborhood with a beautiful garden.
And he provides you with love.
I understand that both of you want to believe in him.
However, everything that's written in these documents is true.
So who is Johan, really?
I need you to tell me about Johan!
Johan is a good boy.
Yes, he's just a very nice boy.
And he's very smart.
A clever boy.
You see, Johan is our reason for being.
And is that all?
You've been acting as his parents for years,
and that's all you have to say about him?
It's obvious neither of you knows the first thing about him.
I've come here because I need your help.
My friend Richard has already died at his hands.
Right now, as we speak, a man named Tenma is...
He's moving toward something drastic that can't be undone.
Please, you have to help me.
No, more importantly, you'll end up...
Like all the other couples mentioned in this report,
They were all previous foster parents of Johan's, just like you.
Murdered every one of them.
You have to leave now! If you stay, you'll die!
Oh, the apple tree bore such small fruit.
Uh-huh. But I think next year's apples will be much healthier.
That will be delightful.
Yes. So very delightful.
He's going to be killed by a Japanese guy soon.
Is that what Johan is telling those kids?
Correct. What do you think? What's it mean?
Well, he's not thinking about suicide, that's for sure.
Okay, but what does it mean?
Man, who really knows what goes on in a brilliant mind like that.
Although, I can at least say this much.
If nuclear war broke out and the world burned to ash, he'd still be standing.
he's basically telling us that there's nothing we can do and he's right everything we've done
so far has led us absolutely nowhere my god we weren't even able to save poor richard
look we can't just throw in the towel but we still haven't been able to track down dr tenma
oh face it we couldn't stop him from trying to kill johan even if we wanted to it's been in fame
Dr. Reichwein, please. We need to try and remain calm here.
Yeah, you're right.
He talked about breaking up the line of ants.
Even ants possess souls.
Doctor, where are you going?
At this point, we've got nothing to lose, do we?
Huh?
It's time to tell the old man our story.
I'm going to have a little talk with Schuwald.
What? An additional 50 chairs?
So many people. This list just keeps growing and growing.
You mean all of this is just for Mr. Schuwald's book donation ceremony?
Yeah. A lot of VIPs have been added. It's turning into a pretty big thing.
I guess everything Schuwald does is bound to turn into an event.
the library will be closing shortly
again
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but could you get that book down for me?
It's that Czech dictionary up on the top. I can't reach it.
Oh, okay. Is this it?
Yes. I'm sorry. Thanks a lot.
Sure.
Actually, I'm borrowing a Czech picture book. I'm trying to translate it.
I see.
Would you believe it? My friend collapsed right here out of nowhere while looking at this book.
Oh.
I thought that maybe there was something in the book that could have triggered that response.
So your friend, he's all right now?
Yeah, he's fine. Thanks again.
Sure.
Let's see.
Once upon a time in a land far away,
there lived a nameless monster.
He was dying to have a name.
So the monster--
so the monster made up his mind to set out on a journey
to look for one.
Weird book.
We're closing up, hon.
OK.
And we'll be closed tomorrow for the ceremony.
© transcript Emily Beynon