Has there been any change in his condition?
Well, uh, no, but Doctor...
And his pulse and blood pressure.
Dr. Tenma, what about Mayor Roddicker's operation?
Let's begin the surgery.
Uh, right.
wait what's our patient's name huh I want to know the boy's name well so we
don't even know his name it's all right hang in there I'll save you
Dr. Tenma! We have a problem! Those kids! Twins! The boy and the girl!
Did you search the entire hospital?
- I already checked, but they're both gone.
- Maybe they're off playing hide and seek
or something like that.
- They're off playing hide and seek
Something like that.
I don't know.
scaredy cat ten ma scaredy cat ten ma
where are you hiding at this time get out here you big baby
keep it up and you're gonna pee your pants again just like last time
It's getting late, kids.
Time for everybody to head on home, okay?
Bye!
We'll see you guys later!
See you later!
Okay, bye!
Wait, I'm still here.
Hold on, guys.
I was right here all this time.
Won't someone find me already, please?
I'm right over here!
Come find me!
Scary cat, Tenma.
♪ Where art thou deep in this land? ♪
♪ ♪
We'll be right back.
We'll see you next time.
That man who stopped by earlier this evening, he's still standing in front of the main gate, sir.
How should I proceed?
Well, who is he?
He said he was Richard Brown's psychologist, Brown being that private detective you hired.
I'll just go eject him from the premises, sir.
My son, I need you to tell me what you see when you look at this man.
Right. He's short and older.
What about his character? Look deeper.
I think he's a good person. I couldn't tell you why.
And now I'm staring into his eyes, and a desperate man is staring back at me.
I understand.
Thank you for agreeing to see me, Mr. Schuvold. I know it's late.
Well, your thanks are wasted on me, Doctor. My patience runs short.
Speak your piece and be on your way.
I agree. Let's cut right to the chase.
You'll be happy to know the length of this conversation depends entirely on you.
I'm assuming you came here to talk about the boy.
Huh?
About Johann.
Your silence speaks volumes, Doctor.
I knew this day would come eventually.
That sooner or later, someone like you would knock on my door.
And maybe shed some light on the grand mystery.
Mystery?
How any person could ever be that perfect.
I imagine having one's sight just confuses the matter, but I can always sense it.
Yes, the presence of something so unerringly precise, like Johann.
I feel as though he's not of this world at all.
I do.
Oh, he's very much of this world, I assure you.
And he's left a paper trail just like the rest of us, and here it is.
I'll read these now, with your permission.
Trust me, his imperfections run deep.
It all started back in 1986 when a nearly dead young boy was rushed to the emergency
room in Dusseldorf with a gunshot wound to the head.
And that's when he started up as one of your student readers.
My murdered friend Richard had a theory.
He theorized that Johann was the one who put the Farren boy up to pretending to be your
son in the first place.
It worked damn well, but then your real son entered the picture and Johann changed plans.
He quickly latched on to Karl, and Farren was a loose end.
He put Farren up to one last thing: suicide.
Sir, how did you come to be reunited with your long-lost son?
It's quite a feat after all this time.
I want you to think very carefully about how many people close to you have died over the
last few years.
The driver who had worked for you so unfailingly, the maid who'd read books to you, the accountant
with whom you'd go birdwatching, dead, every last one of them.
Your Johann murdered them all, don't you see that?
To create an empty space in your heart and then fill it himself.
We have to drag that boy's evil into the light of day.
But I can't do it without your help, Mr. Shuvold.
If we don't do something to stop Johan right now,
Dr. Tenma will!
- Didn't you say Johan toys with people
as though he's playing with a line of ants
taking delight in their pain?
To him, we're nothing but insects.
You must know what people call me,
that infamous nickname of mine.
Oh, yes, the much-feared vampire of Bavaria.
I'll be straight with you, that nickname pleased me very much.
I'd push myself harder and harder, never relenting, and oh, how it did grow.
How it swelled the monster inside me.
But to what avail?
They speak my name with such reverence, but now I'm a withered husk.
I, too, longed to toy with people,
as though they were nothing more than a line of ants,
just like this.
I see that boy fast becoming the person I've tried so hard to be.
They worship the dragon,
for he had given his authority to the beast,
and they worship the beast, saying,
Who is like the beast, and who can fight against it?
The revelation of St. John the Divine, is it not?
The only thing that can defeat the beast
would be a monster more fearsome than the first.
Father?
Hmm?
What was that about? You talked all night.
Tell me, Carl. Where's Johan?
Oh, he said he's heading straight to the ceremony after he wraps things up at Esterhoven's office.
But, Father, you're looking pretty worn out. If you want me to cancel your appearance, I will.
No. Let's get ready to go to the ceremony.
Dr. Tenma, you're not to blame.
You did your job as a doctor, and you did your best.
You are not to blame.
Please live on, and continue to save as many people as you are able to.
Nina...
Well, that's a real shame.
So, you're going to call it quits, huh?
And just when you were really starting to get the hang of it.
Thanks again for the job, sir.
Well, be sure to visit if you're ever down this way.
Sure. Well, goodbye.
She was such a pleasant little thing, too.
Uh, hello. May I speak to Loda Frank, please?
Oh, I'm sorry. Loda's out at the moment.
Oh, I see.
In that case, could you let her know I'm leaving Munich on the three o'clock train?
Yes, of course.
Oh, and what was your name again, dear?
It's Nina.
Nina Fortner.
He's here. His car just pulled up at the rear entrance.
The vampire of Bavaria. Out in the sun, no less.
Shh. He'll hear you.
You have seen the guest list, right?
Of course. It's a real who's who. And not just a Bavaria. Business figures from all over Europe and Japan. Even ambassadors and government officials.
This is hardly a simple book donation ceremony, wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. They say every move Shuvald makes sends ripples throughout Europe. He plays the continent's economy like a marionette.
This is his first public appearance in I don't know how long. They all turned out to see the legend in person.
The charity's fine, but donating his personal library like this, doesn't it seem a bit, well, final?
Hey, don't say that.
He's the keystone of the EU. We can't have him calling it a day just yet.
Carl?
Yes?
I forgot some papers. I need you to go retrieve them for me.
Well, sure. What kind of papers are they?
Just go to the mansion and get them. They're on the desk in the study.
But, Father, you…
Johan will be here soon enough.
Leave everything to him.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
What's going on with the investigation, Inspector?
Why, it's proceeding smoothly.
Proceeding smoothly?
What?
I told you Temma was in Munich because I thought I'd convince you with my information.
I thought you were ready to exonerate him.
But you haven't done a damn thing with it!
Did you even bother to check on Schuwald's secretary, Johann Liebert?
Don't you see there's absolutely no doubting he's the mastermind behind all of these murders?
Are you even listening to me?
If you don't hurry, Tenma will...
If you don't hurry and take action, Tenma will stop Johann the only way he can!
Calm yourself, Doctor.
My investigation is going exactly as planned, I assure you.
If that's all…
Johan is real. He's right in front of us.
Open your eyes, Lungay.
Indeed, spoken like a true criminal psychologist.
He's right in front of us.
I harbor no doubt regarding Johan's existence.
Johan does exist.
Within Tenma's head, that is.
So what's the latest? Have you gathered any new information?
Nope. This guy keeps singing the same old song.
The gun in question turned out to be a Mauser SR-93.
Says he sold it to a Japanese man.
You want us to tighten the screws?
No. That's probably the extent of what he knows.
Yeah.
A Mauser SR-93 is a sniper rifle, unless I'm mistaken.
Yeah, high-precision model.
Who on earth could he be targeting?
I am Tenma.
I am Kenzo Tenma,
and I've recently come into possession of a powerful sniper rifle.
My name is Tenma,
but sometimes my name...
...is Johann Liebert.
I killed the hospital directors, and now I have this high-precision gun.
I killed several middle-aged couples across Germany.
And now, who am I going to kill next?
I am chaos incarnate.
I embrace chaos.
you should probably eat something you know oh thank you Dieter I'm okay I'm
just a little tired that's all I'm not throwing in the towel
No, sir.
I know I'm not much to look at these days, Dieter,
but I served as a medic with the border patrol.
I'm still plenty tough.
I'm going to save your doctor friend no matter what.
I promise.
Don't underestimate a former police doctor.
Now, since you went to the trouble of making me all this,
I think I'll dig in.
I mean, no one should fight on an empty stomach,
right, Dieter?
of course
hey where are you going
Schuwalt's book donation ceremony
you wait here
and Tenma's there right
don't follow me Dieter
stay here
It's Schuwald.
Huh?
I need to speak with Hans-Georg Schuwald now.
Call his estate.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Unless I've got the date wrong,
today is his book donation ceremony
at the University of Munich library.
We've got an emergency.
Huh?
I know Tenma's next target.
And it's Schuwald.
And so, in light of his generous donation, it's only fitting that we honor our benefactor.
Please help me welcome Mr. Hans-Georg Schuval.
Where's Johann? Is my secretary in the library?
Huh? Um...
Ah, he's right over there.
You've come.
I brought him back to life.
That monster, I brought him back.
Nina! Wait!
Lona! I'm so glad you came.
I tried, but the person I'm looking for, I'm not going to find them here after all.
And we were just getting to be friends, too. I'm sorry.
You're twins, right? You gotta be, you look just like him!
You are, aren't you? Well, aren't you?
What's this picture book? Cause this is what he was looking at when he started screaming!
A book?
I'll be right back.
♪
© transcript Emily Beynon
© BF-WATCH TV 2021