I brought him back to life. That monster. I brought him back.
Of course!
Hey, where are you going?
Schuwalt's book donation ceremony. You wait here!
And Tenma's there, right?
Don't follow me, Dieter! Stay here!
It's Schuwald.
Huh?
I need to speak with Hans-Georg Schuwald now.
Call his estate.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Unless I've got the date wrong,
today is his book donation ceremony
at the University of Munich library.
We've got an emergency.
Huh?
I know Tenma's next target.
And it's Schuwald.
Nina! Wait!
Loda! I'm so glad you came.
I tried, but the person I'm looking for...
I'm not going to find them here after all.
And we were just getting to be friends, too.
I'm sorry.
You're twins, right?
You gotta be! You look just like him!
You are, aren't you?
Well, aren't you?
What's this picture book?
Because this is what he was looking at when he started screaming.
A book?
♪
Ken...
♪♪♪
We'll be right back.
once upon a time in a land far away there lived a nameless monster the
monster was dying to have a name so the monster made up his mind and set out on
a journey to look for one but the world was such a very large place the monster
They split in two and went on separate journeys.
One went east, the other headed west.
The one who went east came upon a village.
There was a blacksmith who lived at the village's entrance.
"Mr. Blacksmith, please give me your name," said the monster.
"I can't give you my name," replied the blacksmith.
"If you give me your name, I'll go inside you and make you strong," said the monster.
"Really?" said the blacksmith. "If you make me stronger, I'll give you my name."
The monster went into the blacksmith.
And so, the monster became Otto the blacksmith.
Otto was the strongest man in town.
Then one day, he said, "Look at me! Look at me! The monster inside of me is getting bigger!"
Munch, munch. Chomp, chomp. Gobble, gobble. Gulp.
The hungry monster ate up Otto from the inside out.
Once again, he was a monster without a name.
next he went into Hans the shoemaker however munch munch chomp chomp gobble
gobble gulp once again he went back to being a monster without a name then he
became Thomas the hunter but soon munch munch chomp chomp gobble gobble gulp
Back he went, to being a monster without a name.
The monster next went to a castle to look for a nice name.
He came upon a very sick boy who lived in that castle.
If you give me your name, I'll make you strong, said the monster.
The boy replied,
If you can make me healthy and strong, I will give you my name.
So the monster jumped right into the boy.
And the boy became full of vigor.
The king was overjoyed.
He announced,
The prince is healthy. The prince is strong.
The monster became quite fond of the boy's name.
He was also quite pleased with his royal life in the castle, so he controlled himself no matter how ravenous his appetite became.
Day after day, despite his growing hunger, the monster stayed put inside the boy, but finally, the hunger just became too great.
Look at me. Look at me, said the boy. The monster inside of me has gotten this big.
The boy devoured the king and all his servants.
Munch, munch. Chomp, chomp. Gobble, gobble. Go.
The castle was lonely now with everyone gone
So the boy left on a journey
He walked and walked for days
And then one day
The boy came upon the monster who had gone west
I have a name
said the boy and it's such a wonderful one at that but the monster who went west replied
who needs a name i'm perfectly happy without one after all that's what we are nameless monsters
the boy ate up the monster who went west
At last he had found a name, but there was no longer anyone to call him by it.
Such a shame, because Johan was such a wonderful name.
You've read this before, haven't you?
So you can recheck
Are you Czechoslovakian?
I'm not sure
Wait, how come you don't know for sure?
I was very young
Three or four. I think somebody read this story to me back then.
Who are you, really? I mean, could it be possible that you aren't actually Nina Fortner at all?
And if that's not who you are, then who in the hell are you?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know? We're talking about you!
So you're the one who should know, right?
Tell me what's going on here!
I need some answers!
Why did I get such a bad feeling when I read this picture book?
What does that mean, Nina?
A student named Foren, who claimed to be Shuvald's son, committed suicide.
The detective that Shuvald hired fell off a building and died.
And the prostitute who called herself Margot Langer was shot to death.
After reading this book, why is it now suddenly occurring to me
That these three horrible events are somehow linked
And I'm getting a weird feeling that everything is somehow connected with Johan
Oh man
Sorry, I overreacted
You know that person?
The one who collapsed after he saw the book
Does he really look identical to me?
Is he my mere image?
I'm talking about your friend, you know, Johan.
You think he looks like my twin, is that right?
Where is Johan right now?
Uh, he's at the university library attending the book donation ceremony.
Wait! Hold on, Nina! Wait a second! Hold on! Where are you going?
The grand collection that the Schuwold Financial Group representative,
Hans-Georg Schuwold, has generously donated today
to our university's Friedrich Emanuel Campus Library
is very important, comprehensive, and valuable.
We are very honored and extremely proud now to have in our possession
what you could call one of Germany's most magnificent treasures.
and we have a duty to preserve and protect this outstanding collection of
humanity's wisdom of ages. We have been entrusted to keep this for future
generations.
Next on our program is a message from the Dean of the Friedrich Emanuel campus,
Professor Steinbeck.
what
pull the trigger
if I pull the trigger
everything will end
just move
Doctor
I don't want to die
Liv, please
Mr. Maurer!
I have to do it.
Shoot him now.
♪♪
take notes doctor this is how to shoot a gun
and by donating such an enormous and valuable book collection to our university he is performing a
great cultural service for everyone in our beloved state of bavaria on behalf of the
university of munich i am proud to introduce you to our benefactor at this time ladies and
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you, Hans-Georg Schuvel!
Now watch how it's done.
Just pull the trigger.
It seems like it's a huge success.
A great number of people have gathered here.
I guess that Mr. Schuvald is well-liked.
Must be nice to be him.
and valuable book collection to our university, he is performing a great cultural service
for everyone in our beloved state of Bavaria.
On behalf of the University of Munich, I am proud to introduce you to our benefactor.
At this time, ladies and gentlemen, I present to you Hans Georg Schuvelt!
♪♪♪
So I am the one you're after, is that right?
Would you look at all those faces out there?
So many people.
A big crowd just to see you.
Now I understand.
How could you even consider this?
Now, now, don't spoil the fun
You can watch me, if you're quiet
Everyone, please, listen carefully to what I am about to say
I want you all to stay calm
It is extremely important that you do not panic
As you all may know, I am blind
so I am unable to tell how many people have gathered together in this room tonight.
You need to leave the library this instant.
That's right. Just stay down there and be a good boy.
It's a real shame you won't be able to watch me do this.
get away from here go right now single file and don't push
♪♪♪
What's happened?
There must be an electrical showing!
Call the fire department! Hurry!
This wasn't in the plan.
I was supposed to shoot Shuval.
So how come there's a fire?
I get it.
You changed your mind, didn't you, Johan?
This is better. Much better.
They're running around like ants, bumping into each other, trying to get out, just like ants!
Amazing. You're amazing, Johan. Amazing.
Ah! Come and watch!
Doc, it's burning!
No! No! The books are burning!
Everyone is running and falling over each other,
without a thought for anyone but themselves and you sense it in the room
the fear
I have to shoot you won't be able to do it I have to shoot you I'm sure you can't I have
to kill you you're a doctor of medicine and you've dedicated your career to saving life
Taking life is my job, and I do it well.
Give it up. You can't do it.
© transcript Emily Beynon
Thank you for watching!