[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[CRUNCHING]
[BUZZING]
[GASPS]
[ZAPPING]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
Huh?
[ZAPPING]
Ah!
Must be an electrical short!
[ZAPPING]
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[SHOUTING]
Call the fire department!
Hurry!
[SHOUTING]
This wasn't in the plan.
I was supposed to shoot Shuval.
So how come there's a fire?
I get it. You changed your mind, didn't you, Yo-Hai?
This is better. Much better.
They're running around like ants, bumping into each other, trying to get out, just like ants!
Amazing. You're amazing, Yo-Hai. Amazing.
(laughing)
Come and watch.
It's pretty.
No, no, the books are burning.
Everyone is running and falling over each other,
without a thought for anyone but themselves.
Can you sense it in the room?
The fear.
(dramatic music)
Whether or not he is successful on his first kill, that's what it all comes down to.
Remember, either he's got what it takes, or he doesn't.
So, have you ever trained with a gun before?
Uh, no.
I guess that means that you're self-taught, then.
Actually, I've never shot a gun before.
What? You mean not even once?
Right.
Remember, two shots.
Whenever you fire your gun, you always pull the trigger twice.
It betters your chances of taking out your objective.
If you can't do that, then you're as good as dead. It's all over.
I have to shoot.
You won't be able to do it.
I have to shoot you.
I'm sure you can't.
I have to kill you.
You're a doctor of medicine.
And you've dedicated your career to saving life.
Taking life is my job, and I do it well.
Give it up. You can't do it.
(grunting)
- Remember, two shots.
(gunshot)
(screaming)
[GUNSHOT]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
It can't be.
I wasn't hit at all.
I can do this...no more shaking...Johann...
Damn! The smoke's in the way!
Now! I have got to get him now!
[PANTING]
[COUGHING]
You're not getting away.
I won't let--
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[COUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
(crowd murmuring)
- Stop pushing!
- This side is no good!
Please, help us!
- Someone help us!
Let us out of here!
- Listen, do not panic.
Everyone, please remain calm, I beg of you.
Follow the directions of the security guard so that we can--
Sir! All the doors have been locked from the outside!
That can't be!
Whatever happens, you will take Mr. Schuwald with you, understood?
Yes, sir!
So, have they found an escape route?
Huh?
Can you tell me just where you plan on taking Mr. Schuwald in this sea of fire?
Come on! We must break down the door!
Right!
The books are burning. So many of them alight. The flames quickly consuming everything they touch.
You describe all of this with such damp calmness. The flames. The chaos.
You're getting quite a thrill out of sharing this hellish scene with me, aren't you?
It's how you always sounded when you read to me, and now you're going to take my place.
No, I've since given up on that.
Something that's even more compelling has popped into my head.
You're not afraid, even now, Mr. Shuvalt.
Answer me this.
Where did you come from?
Who are you?
Or what?
Can you see me now?
I know you can barely see anything, but when I'm this close to you...
What can you see?
What do you see when you look into my eyes?
I was born in a town that was straight out of a fairy tale.
Many people died there, and when I walked away, I held hands with my other self.
To me, it seemed like we were the only two people in the world.
Neither one of us possessed a real name.
(eerie music)
(heavy breathing)
(gunshots)
- Hey, lady!
Wait, it's you.
Dieter, do you know this young lady? Have you seen her somewhere before?
It's burning!
I forgot some papers. I need you to go retrieve them for me. Go to the mansion and get them.
They're on the desk in the study.
These, huh?
Oh.
It's my mom.
"Herflig Detective Services, investigative report about Margot Langer and her death."
Margot Langer, whose real name was Helenka Novakova, was born in Prague, Czechoslovakia
on August 12, 1955.
In the spring of 1970, when she was 15 years old,
she somehow illegally gained entrance
into former West Germany.
Four years after entering Germany,
Margot became a high-class call girl in Munich
with a clientele consisting mainly of politicians
and influential businessmen.
Even though her name was secret in high society,
she became famous.
Our client in this investigation, Hans-Georg Schuwald,
was one of her more generous and steady patrons.
Oh, Father, even after it all,
you were still trying to find out more about Mother.
At age 22, she bore Mr. Schuwald a son.
That male child was given the name of Carl.
Carl, are you listening to me?
This is important.
Take this money and ride the train on track number 5.
What about you, Mom?
Honey, I already told you, I can't go with you.
I don't want to go alone, Mom!
You have no choice!
If you stay with me, they'll cart you off to some orphanage!
Around here, people will mock you as the son of a whore!
Now go on!
What about my dad?
Why doesn't he help us? Doesn't he love me?
Why'd he abandon us?
Don't hate him if he turns you away, because Mommy doesn't hate him even now.
I'll miss you.
Mom!
Her son Carl was moved around to many different sets of foster parents
The young man went through a lot, but eventually ended up in a loving family.
But he felt as if he was always... always alone in the world.
Of course it wouldn't say that in the report.
Margot Langer remained a top high-class prostitute, but retired in 1992.
Furthermore, there are rumors that Langer was involved in an affair with the president of an underground bank just before her retirement.
Investigating Margot's alleged affair, a lot of information was learned about this underground bank's operation.
This bank laundered money for Germany's black market companies for five years starting in 1991.
"Money laundering" is the term used for an organization in the business of taking illegal funds and turning them into legal currency.
After her retirement from prostitution, Margot Langer left Munich and lived in Offenbach-Hesse.
This is a picture of the apartment building that she lived in at that time.
She shared her third floor apartment with a young man about age 18.
The nature of their relationship is unknown.
Margot Langer lived in Offenbach for nearly four years,
until on November 2nd, 1996, she was found dead on Haida Street.
According to police files, her death was the work of a phantom killer.
The culprit was never found.
Oh, Mother.
Damn.
Margot Langer sent a letter to a close friend three months before her untimely death.
We were able to obtain the letter and have attached a copy to this report.
Oh my god, this is her handwriting.
I have finally retired from working and living a very peaceful life.
In this piece, I'm filled with thoughts of my lost son.
I also think about my best friend from Prague.
We tried to escape from Czechoslovakia together.
but she was captured at the border and taken back to Prague.
Later, I heard she gave birth to twins and was very happy.
Recently, I met a young man who is about the same age as my son.
He looks exactly like my friend in Prague.
When I'm with him, I feel like I'm talking to my own son.
I'm sure my boy has become a fine young man, just like him.
He must have grown up to live a happy life.
That's what I hope for.
I'm all right now, Mom.
And I know that I'll never feel alone again.
I know Dad sent me here because he wanted me to read this.
Now I get it.
I understand what she meant.
I understand completely.
It's all right.
I understand.
Damn it.
Every one of these doors has been locked tight.
Dieter, did you find a phone to call the fire department yet?
Yes, sir.
I called them.
How could this have happened?
What the hell's going on in there?
(thunder rumbling)
- Break the door, break the door!
(coughing)
(panting)
- Out of the way.
Everyone move!
(gunshots)
Help him! Help him!
Try to...
Come on, you guys!
Harder! Harder!
Now stay calm! Don't push! Go one at a time!
Nobody panic!
Help evacuate the women and elderly first!
Thank you so much!
Without your help, none of us here would have had a chance!
Two shots left.
Huh? Hey, where are you going?
Are you crazy?!
(dramatic music)
Johan...
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
- No, don't!
- Tenma, please, you can't shoot Johan!
- Nina.
Hold on, what are you doing?
Nina, don't!
Don't do it!
(yells)
(dramatic music)
(gun firing)
- Nina, don't shoot!
Don't do it, Nina!
(gun firing)
Lina!
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]