We've just confirmed. At least five are dead and 34 injured due to a fire that broke out here, at the University of Munich's Friedrich Emanuel Campus Library.
A grueling search for the missing is still underway.
Earlier, we had a chance to talk to some of the survivors. Let's take a look.
I just suddenly found myself surrounded by fire everywhere.
The smoke was so thick in the air I could hardly breathe. I thought I would die.
Then somebody rushed in and saved us.
Yeah, he was this young Asian man.
Is he all right?
I saw him shoot the hinges off the door to get it open, but after that,
if it weren't for him, so many of us would have died.
The police have confirmed that the fire was started with a mixed kerosene gasoline accelerant.
The police have also promised to bring the arsonist to justice as swiftly as possible.
¶¶
♪♪♪
We'll see you next time.
It's completely destroyed
So much for this so-called legacy of human wisdom
Ashes to ashes, I guess
Were there any fingerprints on the sniper rifle we found?
I don't think we're going to be able to pull any reasonable prints
On the other hand, the weapon is a Mauser SR-93,
just like the one purchased by that Japanese man who we believe to be Dr. Tenma.
I'm telling you, it's going to be difficult to find any trace of the perpetrator.
A fire this hot really cleans a crime scene.
There's no such thing as a clean crime scene.
Huh?
Here's a cufflink.
Here, send it to the lab.
Someone was here.
And nobody can do anything without leaving some sort of trace of themselves.
If there were such a person, he could hardly be considered human.
But let's suppose someone was here and that we still couldn't find any trace of him.
Who does that?
Only a demon.
However, since no such thing exists, there must be someone real to arrest.
Arrange a meeting with Shuval for me.
But he's still held up in the intensive care unit.
Admittedly, his burns aren't really that severe, but because of his advanced age, the doctors are refusing to allow him any visitors.
Let's go.
You're being unreasonable, sir. He's not ready for visitors yet.
He's conscious, isn't he? I only need a few minutes of his time.
My patient, Mr. Schuwold, is suffering from severe shock. He needs absolute quiet.
Who's the young man?
Oh, him. That's Mr. Schuwold's son.
I'm sorry such a terrible thing happened to your father.
My name is Lungay. I'm with the BKA.
Sir, I know I've already talked to the police about this,
but there's someone I really need to find.
Wait, who is he?
The person in that photograph is the man who tried to assassinate your father.
Huh?
Are you sure you don't recognize him?
I've never seen him before, but maybe Johan would have.
Johan?
That's what I've been trying to tell everybody!
His name is Johan Liebert, and I need you to find him!
Johan Liebert, eh?
The last time I saw Johan, he was going to attend the ceremony at the library with my father.
But I've searched everywhere, and I can't find him!
Johan.
Johan Liebert.
Yes, I understand. I'll call for a search immediately.
This is the room Johann Liebert was renting. Like I said before, he moved out of here two
Two weeks ago.
We checked at the law school at Friedrich Emanuel, but his name didn't show up at the
registrar's.
He really wasn't a student.
Didn't he say his parents lived in Offenbach?
about them? Yeah, that parent angle turned out to be another dead end. It seems they never really
talked to any of their neighbors. I guess there's nothing left to do except dust for prints, huh?
We're probably not going to find anything. I have no data to input. Never before.
I've never seen a room so devoid of any human presence
Yeah
I am Johan
I am Johan Liebert
Who am I?
I was here
But I don't exist
Am I a demon?
I'm just glad your injuries weren't that bad, Nina.
I'm sorry to make you worry, Loda. Thank you.
Well, of course I was going to worry about you.
I mean, they kept pulling survivors out of the library, and you were still nowhere to be found.
I didn't know what had happened to you.
Still, it's a miracle you made it out of the library all on your own with those injuries
Even the firefighters were shocked
That's because someone saved me
Somebody saved you?
Nina, you were the last person that made it out of the building
A Japanese man
Huh?
Do you know if there was a Japanese doctor among any of the survivors?
There were some Japanese people, but all of them were just businessmen.
That is impossible.
Huh?
Inside the library, I was trapped under a curtain when he found me.
Nina!
I'm sure that he was real.
I know he was.
According to witnesses,
just before the fire started,
you told everyone attending the ceremony to evacuate.
Why? What would cause you to do something like that?
You knew something was about to happen.
Was that it, Mr. Schuwald?
Why don't we call it a day?
Mr. Shuval, do you know the man in this photograph?
Can you see the man in the photograph clearly, sir?
This is the man who we believe tried to assassinate you.
We have witnesses placing him at the library.
But here's what doesn't make sense to me.
All of our witnesses claim to have seen this man rescuing people from the fire.
Look, that's enough. Please, just let him rest.
Don't forget to contact me if you should remember anything else.
Just one more thing.
Do you know where your secretary Johann Liebert has disappeared to?
Please, just leave already!
Looks like he's gone completely senile.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
I mean, when you see something that terrifying at his age, you know.
So ends the reign of the Vampire of Bavaria, once great emperor of the business world.
No.
Huh?
He understood every word I said.
Oh.
Let's question the other witnesses, shall we? Do you have the list of victims?
Oh, yeah. But what's this all about?
We have testimonials that point to our man Tenma trying to save people from the fire.
Maybe it's just like that multiple personality theory?
Nina. Nina Fortner.
What about Nina Fortner?
If you're looking for Nina Fortner, she checked out of the hospital this morning
And unfortunately, the address we have for her in the police register is fictitious
How about the hospitals?
Yes, sir
I'll look it up right now
Nina Fortner
There was a Nina Fortner whose parents were killed in Heidelberg
Her current whereabouts are unknown.
Thank you for sharing such a painful story with me.
You know, Nina, it matches up perfectly with another story from ten years ago told to me by Dr. Tenma.
Tenma?
Yes, and that story started him down a path that led him here.
And from here he set off on his journey to kill Johan.
Nina, that day, I went to the library because I thought that Tenma was going to carry out his assassination attempt
But then, with that fire, I don't even know for sure if Tenma was there, let alone Johan
Please, Nina, let go of any thoughts of chasing down Johan
He's not someone you can handle yourself
Look, I know the police don't seem very helpful.
But we have to try and lay low and take our time to fight this.
I promise the truth will be revealed in time.
It's okay. We're all here for you.
You must be tired.
Please feel free to stay here as long as you like.
He was there.
Huh?
Tenma, I mean.
I saw him that day.
Tenma was there in the library.
♪ ♪
You've got to eat something.
I know, Dieter. Thank you.
It's called a kaiser roll.
It has roasted ham and gouda cheese on it.
Tenma really likes them.
That's very kind of you.
It's yummy.
Really?
Nothing picks me up like something delicious.
Tenma always used to say that too.
I want to see him.
I want to see Tenma again.
Yeah
The weather's finally starting to look nice again
Father, when you're feeling better
Why don't we take a vacation together?
Maybe the two of us could tour Asia
I think a change of atmosphere would be nice
Why don't you just rest a bit longer?
I know you've been through more than enough recently
bridge there were three father what is it are you trying to tell me something the three frogs
three frogs in his eyes what i saw hell right there in his eyes
hell in the eyes of a living human being.
Carl.
Yes?
I need you to deliver a message to a certain man.
I... yes.
There's a man.
A man waiting in Dresden.
In Dresden?
What do you want me to say when I find him?
I want you to tell him that I...
Yes.
And the man in Dresden, he'll know what you're talking about, right?
So, should I leave now, Father?
I understand. I'll leave immediately.
Carl, I know that your mother hated me in the end.
You're wrong. I promise, she never hated you.
Carl, when you return from Dresden, can you promise that you will come back and stay with me?
Yes.
I'm afraid.
I see. Afraid of what?
I don't know, but I'm afraid.
Try and stay calm. We need you to remember, just go slow.
Like a town from a fairy tale.
A fairy tale village. Where was it?
The feelings that you had when you were looking at this picture book.
Just tell me whatever pops into your head.
Dr. Gillen, careful.
Just a little bit more.
Stop! That's enough!
There were three.
There were three frogs.
There were three frogs?
Three frogs.
What are you talking about?
Picture.
What? Is there a picture of three frogs in the children's book that made Johan faint?
I've been through that book cover to cover a dozen times and I've never seen a single frog anywhere.
Then where did you see them?
It's all right. Why don't we stop here for now?
Okay.
I'm going on record saying it was a mistake
to trust that Inspector Lungay from the BKA.
Yes, I think it's time for us to rethink our strategies.
The next time we take anything to the authorities,
we'll talk to his superiors.
And that's only after we've taken our time
to gather irrefutable evidence to support our claim.
Agreed?
You think we should take our time?
How much time?
As of now, the profile we built for Johan
is vague and unimpressive at best.
Johan was Schuwalt's secretary.
It's reasonable to think Schuwalt might have some information.
But he's not taking visitors at the moment.
How about his son, Carl?
Don't know. He's been gone for the past couple of days now, and I can't get a hold of him.
It's nothing concrete, but I've heard some of the witnesses say
that an anonymous Asian man was seen rescuing people from the library fire.
But if they find Tenma's fingerprints on the sniper rifle,
then all those witness reports won't mean anything.
They'll just assume he's guilty.
Why wouldn't they?
It all will have been for naught.
How long do we have to wait?
We don't have any time.
By the time the truth is revealed
and the police finally make a move,
by that time,
Tenno, he'll already be...
Nina.
I'm so sorry.
Nina, I understand how you feel about this.
I told you before I lost one of my closest and dearest friends
Richard to this case. He had such a bright future ahead of him, but Johan cut his future short.
I am not giving up on this. I never will.
Now, let's eat.
Three frogs
Like a town from a fairy tale
With three
I remember
Peter, I...
I'm going to.
What are you saying? Dieter, you can't come with me.
You need to stay right here, all right?
And please tell Dr. Reichwein that I said thank you for everything he's done for me.
Take care.
Dieter!
I wanna...
I wanna see Tenma!
the third day was a bus too
wait in the town square he says
he's gotta be kidding
this place is just too big
Sorry, Father. It doesn't seem like I'll be meeting up with the man you talked about after all.
Carl.
Huh?
You're Carl, right?
Wait, it's you!
The man who was attempting to assassinate your father.
Is that what the police told you?
Uh, yeah.
Well, at least it doesn't look like they have anybody tailing you.
For three days, I've been watching you from that building.
All right, you can give me the message now.
Try and hold on. We're almost out of here.
Just run. You have to go. The police are on their way.
But I can't just...
In Dresden, the public square by the station,
my son Carl will bring you a message I...
Give me the message.
Here it is.
Chidok Bridge and the Three Frogs.
My father said something else also.
If the monster that you're chasing happens to have a twin...
The mother of those same twins is still alive in Brokk.
© transcript Emily Beynon
© BF-WATCH TV 2021