Just run. You have to go. The police are on their way.
But I can't just...
Interested. The public square by the station. Wait there.
Give me the message.
Here it is.
Shidok Bridge and the Three Frogs.
My father said something else also.
What if the monster that you're chasing happens to have a twin?
The mother of those same twins is still alive in Prague.
(dramatic music)
- There!
Hey, guys!
(laughing)
Over here!
Over here, you guys!
- Cut it out, guys!
Give me back my shoe!
- Cut it!
Here you go!
- It's not yours anymore!
- No way, cut it!
- Come on!
Stop messing around already!
- Give it back!
- Yeah, kick it to me!
(children laughing)
- So, Mr. Grimmer, have any luck?
Did you find some of the information you were looking for?
What you're after won't be easy to locate.
Record keeping changed when the East and West united.
Data from before then is hard to find.
- I thank you for this opportunity, Principal Garbrecht.
Frankly, I'm surprised you have even this much left.
Most have far less.
And of course, you're quite correct.
When the Berlin Wall fell,
Well, almost all of the data involving East Germany's unsavory practices disappeared forever.
You know, I feel quite sure that the children in the orphanages of the old East Germany were victims of physical and mental abuse.
But of course, the real challenge here is actually finding any written records to prove my thoughts are true.
Your thinking sounds right.
You know, most of East Germany's orphanages were being managed under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
But a much bigger problem was created when the authorities classified a child's parents
as criminal offenders, political prisoners, spies, or even illegal immigrants.
In the midst of all of the orphanages that took care of these children, there was one
special orphanage run by the notorious Internal Affairs Ministry.
Apparently there were many instances of abuse, and these inhumane personality corrections
took place in that one particular orphanage.
Anyhow, that's what I want to find out, in as much detail as possible.
every last little thing that happened there.
I'm leaving no stone unturned.
- My, that's a tedious task, huh?
I'd like to help, but there's not much information to share.
Most of those involved have passed away,
kept silent, or they're leading new lives.
- I'm sure you're right.
Even Mr. Schnurr, who's now an instructor here,
won't speak with me.
- Wait, did you say Mr. Schnurr?
- Yes, he was a teacher at East Germany's
6-2 Kinderheim under the old regime.
I requested to interview him about his past,
You refused my request.
Listen, there's a real possibility
Mr. Schnurr terrorized children
while he worked in East Germany,
so I'd be a little more cautious around him if I were you.
Oh, would it be all right if I photocopied
some of the information in these books?
- Sure, that would be just fine.
Mr. Grimmer, if I may, you are a newspaper journalist
from West Germany, isn't that correct?
- No, I'm from this side.
I worked as a reporter for a newspaper in Leipzig.
Well, I never expected a human rights advocate like you to be from the Eastern Bloc.
It's true.
During that time, I used to travel all over the world as a special overseas news correspondent.
Yeah, I went everywhere on missions for the government.
Do you understand?
I used to be a spy.
Here we go.
Goodness, your bag looks awfully heavy.
Well, it's packed with all the data I've collected traveling around East Germany.
I can't wait to read up on your findings.
So, where are you heading to next?
Oh, to the Czech Republic.
On to Prague. Thank you for all your help, Principal.
(crying)
I heard you're getting treated pretty badly by those boys.
And they ended up taking your shoes away, didn't they?
You know, crying won't help.
(crying)
Hmph.
(sobbing)
- Hey, you know what?
It's been proven that people can live without shoes.
After all, every last one of us was born barefoot.
But I must say,
anyone who bullies other people by stealing their shoes,
they're the worst.
Anyhow, now you have shoes again,
so there's no need to cry anymore.
I'm guessing they're a little big for you, am I right?
Excuse me, sir?
Do you have a second, sir?
Of course. What is it?
I'm kind of in a fix.
You see, I have a big problem.
My briefcase that had my passport in it was stolen just a while ago.
Your passport was stolen? That really is a big problem.
I turned around and it was gone.
I'm on my way to see my younger sister who lives in Vienna only yesterday
I got a phone call saying that she suddenly collapsed. She collapsed. You need to find a way to get there as soon as possible
Where are the police? Maybe they can help you. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I already talked to them
The bigger problem is my poor sister doesn't have any money for a doctor
Oh, no, that's got to be the worst news yet and to top things off my stolen briefcase had my wallet in it, too
No, I know I can't go but if I could at least find a way to wire some money to my sister
She could get some medical attention, but now it's looking like I can't even do that
So just how much do you need? Oh, no, no, no, no, you don't need to help out
Honestly, I don't need that much money
Really?
All I need is to pull together a small amount of cash just enough so she can see a doctor here
I'm just sorry. I don't have more to give you. Oh
Thank you, sir. Don't cushion. I swear that I'll pay you back very soon
Just write down the address where you want me to send the check.
That's all right. No need to repay me.
Just see that your sister gets the help she needs, okay?
God bless you, sir! Thank you so much!
I wish you and your sister all the best!
Come on, buddy. How could you hand over your money to that hustler?
Huh?
He was lying. His story was just a scam.
A scam?
That guy works this train station all the time looking for suckers like you.
I can't believe you got fooled by that hustler.
I really got fooled?
Attention. The express train to Prague will be departing from track 7 at 3.15pm.
Dammit!
I didn't think it was going to make it for a sec. Thanks for your help.
Hey, thanks again for earlier.
You mind if I sit here?
No, go ahead.
So, where are you headed?
Oh, me?
I'm headed for Prague.
I'm guessing you're Japanese, am I right?
Huh?
Konnichiwa.
Oh, domo.
You know, I've visited Japan a couple of times.
Oh.
How long's it been since I was there last?
Well, it's been a couple of years, I can tell you that much.
The last time I was over there was a business trip.
I went to Akihabara to purchase some wiretap equipment and other high-tech gadgets.
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
This song, it was really popular.
I'm sure you know it.
"Kita no hakaba dori ni wa"
No, no, that's not right.
"Kita no..."
It's "sakaba dori ni wa."
Oh, that's right. That's how it goes.
"Kita no sakaba dori ni wa"
Oh, and there were these robots.
My son would have loved it if I'd brought back a plastic model toy for him.
So where's your son now?
Oh, he's gone. My son died.
Departure passport check. If you would present your passport.
Oh, sure. Of course.
Thank you.
Look, there's the Elba River.
How's the trout fishing been on the Elba River this year anyway?
It hasn't been very good, sir.
Oh, is that so?
'Cause last year I caught a trout this big on that river.
That wouldn't happen this year.
Dankeschön, sir.
He's on to the fact that was a fake passport you just showed him.
You need to get moving.
Right now, Dr. Tenma.
How is it that you know who I am?
That's not important.
What does matter here is that the border police have realized your passport's a fake, and I'm sure they're on their way.
So you need to get out of here right now, Dr. Tenma.
Move it, you.
Come on, we need to get past you.
Sorry about this, guys. My duffel bag's so big and overstuffed, I guess I'm kind of stuck here. I can't seem to move.
Get out of the way right now!
Believe me, sir, I am trying to get out of the way.
What's in that bag anyway?
Some very valuable items.
Oh good, I finally got loose.
(dramatic music)
- Do you know where that other man went?
Answer me!
- Huh?
- There was an Asian man who was sitting with you
in this compartment.
- Yeah, you're right.
Well, maybe he got hungry and went to the dining car.
- Move, men.
Check the next car.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
- This is passenger car two.
Emergency.
We have an Asian man using a fake passport
who's running loose on this train.
- What's wrong?
Stop this train immediately!
You did very well back there
They're not chasing us they're searching the other way
Since the train was stopped. I figured I should get off. Oh, I guess I forgot to introduce myself doctor. My name is Grimmer. I
Thought you might need some guidance dr. Tenma, so if you'd like I could show you the way to the border
I'm very well acquainted with this area.
Actually, I fished around here quite a few times.
It's mountainous terrain, so the hike ain't easy, but the view is great.
Grimmer.
Why did you help me, anyway?
Huh?
Oh.
Well, you see, I worked for a newspaper company in East Germany,
but now I'm doing my own thing as a freelance journalist.
I've read every article about you I could find, and I have to admit I find you very interesting.
Being falsely accused of crimes was a part of everyday life in East Germany.
Political prisoners charged without merit, accused murderers who weren't really guilty.
Seeing that happen all the time, you got to have a pretty good eye for spotting who was guilty and who was innocent.
And I'd say you're innocent. Does that sound about right, Dr. Tenma?
Listen, do me a favor and stop calling me doctor.
Huh?
But Dr. Tenma, you're one of the world's most brilliant neurosurgeons. Aren't you proud of that?
I am no longer a doctor!
So, what do you think?
It's a magnificent view, isn't it?
And from here we can see anyone coming up the mountain after us.
That said, I think we've earned a well-deserved break for lunch.
Would you care to join me for a sandwich?
I also brought a rather nice red wine.
Oh, and some delicious cheese.
Thank you for your offer, but I really need to keep on moving.
It's hours until sunset.
It'll be easier and safer trying to cross the border after dark.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Meeting outside like this is just the best.
It's such a treat to do this once in a while,
isn't it, Dr. Tenma?
Enjoying delicious food while taking in a wonderful view.
It's moments like this that help me truly
feel the pleasures of living.
I must admit, I have a profound respect for you doctors.
Journalists like myself serve to entertain people,
Others feel happier to be alive after reading my articles, but what you do, that's powerful.
You literally give people life.
But I...
I shot a man, and I did it on purpose.
It happened last month in Munich.
It's the first time I shot someone.
I think he probably died.
My hands were trembling so much I couldn't aim.
I didn't think I'd really be able to do it.
But after I shot him, my hands stopped trembling.
And now, I know that I have to shoot another man.
I have to stop a man that's pure evil.
One thing is for certain...
I'm no doctor.
When I see the Elba River, I think of how I'd give anything to change the past.
I made a difference so I could have shared the joy of fishing here with my son.
What was he like, your little boy?
You can catch a trout this big in that river.
My poor son died without me ever sharing the pleasures of the outdoors with him.
What makes me the saddest is feeling that his life could have been saved
if a doctor like you had been there for him.
I swear, you can catch trout this big.
I'm not kidding around here.
The other side of that mountain is the Czech border.
Follow the forest path past there and you'll hit a road where you might be able to get
a ride.
As for me, I'm heading back to the train station now.
I never would have made it this far without you helping me.
I truly wish you the best of luck, Dr. Tenma.
Say, if we meet again, let's plan for another great picnic, alright?
Hey, Dr. Tenma!
Everyone in this world carries around their own sins.
And they never go away.
But that doesn't change the fact that we do what we must.
Ah, how wonderful.
I'd always heard this was a beautiful city.
This may be my first night in Prague, but I'm already enchanted.
It's like a village from a fairy tale.
Excuse me, do you mind if I sit here?
Sit yourself.
I must say, I'm completely captivated by this city.
You're Mr. Pedrov, right?
You bought your Russian citizenship, and now here you are, living in Prague.
I'd like to ask you some things about your past, sir.
Would you be willing to help me with some answers, Mr. Pedroff?
Oh, my mistake. Your real name is Reinhard Biermann, isn't it?
There was this very special orphanage located in East Berlin, right?
It was more of a laboratory, really, where experiments were conducted on children's personalities.
It was called 511 Kinderheim, and you were the director there, Mr. Biermann.
You should know all about the abuse that went on there.
After all, sir, you were the one running the place.
Just what were you trying to achieve in those experiments back in East Berlin?
At 511 Kinderheim. Care to explain it to me?
(clicking)
(explosion)
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]