So, Mr. Pedrov, oh, my mistake, your real name is Reinhard Biermann, isn't it?
There was this very special orphanage located in East Berlin, right?
It was an experimental lab where the staff did personality corrections on the children
that were housed there.
It was called 511 Kinderheim, and you were the director there, Mr. Biermann.
You should know all about the abuse that went on there.
Just what were you trying to achieve in those experiments back in East Berlin?
at 511 Kinderheim. Care to explain it to me?
(inspirational music)
Hey, please, wait a minute.
Don't rush off, Mr. Pedrov.
You're unique.
You're both a psychologist and a psychiatrist.
You used to work for the Internal Affairs Ministry, focusing on personality programming,
a form of brainwashing.
You see, that's what got me thinking.
Why would someone with your skills in behavioral modification have been appointed director of a mere orphanage?
I mean, certainly there were people more qualified in the field of child welfare, right?
Leave me alone.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Just go away.
So, where did you hide the records?
You know, the results of your experiments at 511 Kinderheim.
Now, I've heard all the usual rumors that when the Berlin Wall was destroyed, a countless
number of secret documents disappeared, and there's a theory that they were sent to the
Soviet Union by train via Romania. While en route, there was a revolution in Romania,
the Ceausescu government fell, and supposedly the German documents were lost. But I have
a feeling that the data concerning 511 Kinderheim was not among those lost papers. Do you know
Because you, sir, are a true academic.
You're devoted to research.
Data and statistics are far more important to you scholarly types than life itself.
You wouldn't let go of something that important, would you?
I'd sure like to see that data. Must be interesting.
There's nothing.
What were you hoping to accomplish there?
at your lab at 511 Kinderheim.
Go away!
Your experiments, were they really successful?
It must have given you so much pleasure to use children as human guinea pigs.
Your experiment... it failed, didn't it?
In 1985, 511 Kinderheim burned to the ground, and according to the rumors surrounding that
tragedy, the children of the orphanage killed each other.
At the time, I was no longer director of that facility.
The incident does not involve me at all.
Lucky you. You were able to escape death.
Now, the director right after you wasn't so lucky.
He was the first one killed in the rampage.
That catastrophe never would have occurred if I had still been there.
I assure you, my experiment was a success.
Oh-ho. So now it seems you're admitting to it.
You're telling me the experiment went well, so I shouldn't need proof.
Right?
Huh. You know what I think?
Even if many of the records went up in smoke during that fire in 1985, not everything did.
So, the experimental data from your time as director of 511 Kinderheim is still intact somewhere.
Careful, you're treading on dangerous territory right now.
Who knows what could happen.
That almost sounds like a threat. You should know I'm not afraid of taking risks.
Get lost.
Sorry, but I'm going to follow you everywhere until I get the information I'm after.
Back off! I'm warning you not to ever come near me again!
Just disappear!
Grandpa, we found you!
We've been looking for you! You were gone a long time!
Hey, who's that guy with you?
Him? Forget about him. He's nobody.
Come along, let's go home.
Walk away, leave this alone.
Living out the remainder of his life peacefully surrounded by his grandkids,
to think back then, he did such horrible things to children.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah?
Who is it?
You have a delivery from Mr. Pedrov, sir.
Mr. Pedrov?
Sure, give me a minute.
[YAWNING]
[GROANING]
[GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Corner rooms with a bad view are convenient,
especially in moments like these.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GRUNTING]
[THUD]
[GIGGLING]
[CHILDREN CHATTERING]
Wow.
It's been a hell of a morning.
I almost didn't make it out here.
Yeah, a couple of strange men showed up at my hotel room.
[CHILDREN CHATTERING]
Here we sit, watching your grandchildren play.
This is wonderful.
You know, when I was working for a newspaper in old East Germany,
I couldn't even dream of a moment like this.
Thankfully, times have changed.
Now, I'm a freelance journalist writing whatever I want.
Gosh, that was unimaginable just a few years ago,
back in our socialist society.
Being free is nice.
I've been watching you ever since I left the hotel.
Did you know that?
Great home.
I saw you when you came out the front door and thought to myself,
What a space. I'll bet you have nice big rooms.
Upkeep must be difficult. And rent's expensive, isn't it?
Spending the whole day at a cafe,
taking walks and playing with your grandchildren,
all the while maintaining this leisurely lifestyle without working.
So I wondered, where do you get the money to afford this?
You must have sold something.
Maybe the data to your failed experiment?
Did you get a good price?
I told you it was a success.
That's all the more reason for it to get a good price.
Just leave me alone.
I have nothing to say to you. Now go.
There they are again.
Earlier he was at the movies with those two, and now they're all eating parfait.
(suspenseful music)
Each time they look different.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
(suspenseful music)
It can't be.
(panting)
Hi. This is Mr. Pedrov's home, right? May I come inside?
Hey there.
(suspenseful music)
(explosion booms)
- This is horrible.
I know what he's up to, he's doing it again, right here, he's trying to replicate the very
same experiment.
This is unconscionable.
How could that man do this?
He's trying to replicate the very same experiment from 511 Kinderheim.
There's a red light district at the German border.
These boys were born there, but were never nurtured.
And some were just abandoned by their impoverished mothers.
Their business fell off when the Berlin Wall came down.
So you just went there and gathered up all these children for the purpose of continuing your 5-1-1 Kinderheim experiment here?
Oh, Mr. Pedrov, I didn't realize you had a guest.
Yes. Don't worry about him. He's going home now.
I was planning to prepare dinner. Will Kanedliki be all right for tonight?
Yes. Everyone loves your Kanedliki so much, that would be just perfect.
You're convinced I'm continuing with 5-1-1 Kinderheim?
I will tell you again, I have no need to continue that experiment.
That project was a huge success.
Oh yeah? Based on what?
The educational program I created for the experiment.
It shaped personalities so they were eager to absorb all kinds of knowledge.
Educational? There was nothing educational about it!
That was human experimentation, damn it!
Calm down and think about it for a moment.
What is the purpose of education?
Isn't it supposed to help people acquire knowledge and skills to become useful members of society?
The instructor's main task is to create conditions to stimulate learning.
All education is an experiment.
At 511 Kinderheim, everyone was challenged to learn.
A highly advanced educational system was established.
You did such horrible things, and now you want to justify them?
Horrible things?
Yes! Think about what your advanced protocols did to their minds!
You're a freelance writer.
You don't possess the scientific background to critique my procedures.
What's with that look?
What about the incident where the children killed each other?
Do you deny your experiment was the cause of that?
I told you, that happened after I was removed from my position as Director.
The emergence of an unexpected anomaly threw the entire program out of control.
Unexpected anomaly?
Like what?
Like darkness.
Hatred, apathy, destructive urges.
Unfortunately, people easily succumb to these negative forces.
Once they get in, they're hard to stop.
And soon, they possessed all of 511 Kinderheim.
Yes, one boy arrived and all that began.
I suppose next you're going to tell me that didn't have anything to do with you as I keep telling you
The experiment was very successful. That's a lie
And you know it all those children at 5-1-1 kinderheim shared a common character flaw
There was one thing they could not do they were incapable of loving
an interesting comment
Now then our little chat is over, and I would like you to leave
Don't even think of telling anyone about this place.
Sorry. You're breaking one of this country's laws.
I have to report this to the police.
I think you're forgetting you're not in Germany anymore.
The Czech Republic is a democracy.
They frown upon things like an unauthorized orphanage with an unlicensed director.
You want to make a deal?
That's what this is all about.
You're offering to not report me if I cooperate.
from my experiment.
All right. Let's go.
What are you planning to do?
You guys want to play some soccer?
Yeah!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Where do you think you're going with the boys?
Oh, didn't you hear?
We're going out to play some soccer.
(children cheering)
- Listen up, everyone.
Mr. Pedrov and I are sort of working out a deal,
and I want you guys to help me make the right decision
in this matter because it concerns all of you.
If I reported him to the proper authorities,
then you'd all be free to go.
I mean, you'd like to leave, wouldn't you?
- Hmm?
But you'd have more freedom out of there! Don't you...care?
Heads up! Ball's coming to ya!
Huh? Oh!
(children laughing)
- Happy faces.
How can they be so genuinely happy?
(children laughing)
Impossible.
- Where are you going?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Come on, Thor!
- [panting]
- Hey, are you okay?
♪ ♪
- Wow, what a beautiful lady.
Yeah.
[knocking]
-Pedroff, I need to know if you altered the pro--
[ Gasps ]
[ Explosion ]
♪♪♪♪
What happened?
Mr. Pedroff!
-Get off the floor!
Mrs. Adams, please!
♪♪♪♪
-Mr. Pedroff!
[ Gasps ]
Can you hear me?
Grandpa!
Grandpa's hurt!
Mr. Pedrov, tell me who shot you!
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Woman!
Woman?
Grandpa, please are you alright?
What happened? What happened to you?
Oh no! Grandpa, you're bleeding!
Mr. Pedrov, please tell me, did you alter the program this time?
The key, the key, the card, and the secret code number,
you'll find them hidden behind the third drawer of my desk.
They're for my safe deposit box,
where the experiment data and tape can be found.
What tape?
Of an interview with a certain boy,
recalling his past under the use of chemically induced hypnotism.
That boy is the malevolent monster.
His darkness and evil influence led 5-1-1 Kinderheim to destruction.
So now, what do you think?
Are these children lacking anything in their development?
Mr. Pedrov, I don't know.
But it appears you educated them differently than those in 511 Kinderheim.
Apathy. Hatred. Destructive urges.
Dark forces I wanted them to repel.
But how could I do that?
What would make them resistant?
It was love.
Yes, it was.
That's the new discovery I'd factored in.
Mr. Petrov, love isn't any new discovery.
Parents give it to their children all the time.
It was an experiment.
Grandpa, please don't go!
Thank you so much!
[MUSIC]
[Music]