The key, the key, the card, and the secret code number.
They're for my safe deposit box, where the experiment data and tape can be found.
What tape?
Of an interview with a certain boy.
That boy is the malevolent monster that led 5-1-1 Kinderhype to destruction.
(thunder rumbling)
(choral music)
(upbeat music)
♪
(dramatic music)
(car horn honking)
- Well, here's his office.
(knocking)
Inspector Zaymon, I brought the witness.
- Huh?
Inspector?
Hm?
Oh.
Ow!
Ow.
Sir, this man was the first to arrive at the Pedrov murder scene yesterday.
Ah, Mr. Grimmer.
Sorry about having to keep you here at the station overnight.
I, uh, slipped and dropped my nail clipper under my desk.
Yeah, when you're a guy my size, seems like you bump into everything.
Oh.
Hey, you're a pretty tall guy yourself.
Yeah, I find I bump into a lot of things as well.
Anyway, I'm in charge of this murder case.
My name is Zemon.
Hi, I'm Grimmer.
All right, please have a seat.
I was just in the middle of clipping my nails,
so I hope you don't mind me finishing them.
Go right ahead.
My wife's always nagging me about it.
If my nails start to grow out, she
really doesn't like that at all.
She can't stand seeing the white part.
So, thanks to her, sometimes I wind up cutting them too short.
Oh, yikes.
Well, that must have been a terrible scene yesterday.
Yeah.
I mean, who would have thought something like that would happen?
I understand you're a freelance newspaper journalist, is that right?
I imagine you might have known about the murder victim's past.
Mikhail Leonidovich Petrov.
That's him.
His real name was Reinhard Biermann.
He was an East German.
After Germany's reunification, he
was accused of various illegal activities,
including suppression of human rights,
illegal detention of minors, and several charges
of extreme child abuse.
He escaped here to the Czech Republic
right after the wall fell.
The German government maintained the charges against him,
but we chose not to extradite him,
allowed him to be free, and kept him under surveillance.
Is that so?
Indeed.
We kept an eye on him and found he
secret police types.
- Why the Czech secret police?
- You know how brutal their tactics were
when it came to restricting free speech and thought
during the Cold War, don't you?
Well, they also gave their support
to the terrorist activities
of some extreme leftist organizations.
Be that as it may, though,
with the peaceful separation
and subsequent democratization
of the Czech Republic and Slovakia,
they went underground without being noticed
and without causing any trouble.
That's who Pedroff was in contact with before he died.
We think he was probably selling them information, he had.
What we have yet to ascertain is--
Oh!
Ah, look at that.
Cut it too short again.
Ah.
Oh, yeah.
Did you happen to see a woman leaving the crime scene?
Excuse me?
Mm-hmm.
It appears there's a fairly good chance
and allegedly she's quite beautiful.
- Right as we got to Pedrov's,
the boys said they saw a woman leaving,
but at the time, I guess I didn't notice her.
- That's too bad.
- What about the children?
What's going to happen now to all those orphan boys
that Mr. Pedrov adopted?
I'm curious.
- Child services told us to keep all of them overnight
right here at the station, but as of today,
most of them are gonna be sent out
to different local orphanages.
- Huh, I see.
for you getting dragged right into the middle of this huge mess it's fine come
to think of it what exactly was your purpose in trying to contact Petrov oh I
wanted to ask him questions about his past you know the kind of stuff you were
mentioning earlier well how did things go did he tell you anything no before we
could talk all right that's perfect they look great my wife can't get mad at me
now. You can go now, Mr. Grimmer. And again, I apologize for keeping you here so long.
No problem. Oh, uh, I almost forgot. Fury died. Did Mr. Pedroff happen to say anything
to you by any chance, anything at all?
- No.
(gentle music)
- All right, you're Milosrov, you're Joseph.
So where's Tomas?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Good, all of you are here.
Now let's get in the van, everyone.
Come on, enough of that. Let's get going.
You three, you're going to Winovledi Orphanage.
Honza, Antonin, Izzy.
yes sir this must be sad for you I mean you boys got along so well and now
you're being pulled apart but even when you're apart you're all still under the
same sky and someday you'll all play soccer together again just stay positive
you three Antonin you're the group's leader aren't you keep everyone in touch
by writing letters to them.
If you do that, it'll keep all of you feeling good.
Attaboy, Antonin.
(sighs)
(speaking in foreign language)
- What?
Oh, the Hotel Kafka.
Before that, let's stop at Prochazka Bank.
Um, I don't understand Czech very well.
Could you speak to me in English or German, if you please?
Why are you stopping here? We're not even...
Hey mister, you could have at least warned me you were going to pick up other fares.
Wait, what's going on?
You're driving us way outside of town.
I just want to go back to my hotel in the city.
The key...
The key!
What are you talking about?
(grunting)
(speaking in foreign language)
[GASPING]
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING]
Well, are you all right?
You know, I had a hunch you might be in danger,
I better follow you you heard much you look pretty rough
Inspector those two were probably hooligans from the former Czech secret police
Do you have any idea what they might have wanted from you? No, not really
I can't imagine them doing something like this without having a good reason. They had no reason to do this
Are you sure you're not trying to hide something here? What?
No, I find that rather hard to believe you gotta know why they did this to you. No, I'm telling you I don't
So you've already taken it from the safety deposit box at the bank, huh the tape
The audio tape
My friends here are looking for his roots
For whose roots? What do you mean?
We're searching for the monster's roots. They're going to sell for quite a lot.
Monster?
We'll know a lot more when we get to hear the tape.
We'll know precisely where in the Czech Republic the monster's mother is living now.
Right.
Oh, hello.
This is Inspector Zaymon.
It's that man who got caught robbing the supermarket.
Did he say who his partner was?
Well, that's great.
Good work, Detective Suk.
Me?
Oh, I still have something I have to attend to.
Yeah.
I'll be back at the station in about an hour.
I'll see you then.
Guys, I think that's probably enough, or he won't be able to talk.
So, Grimmer, now do you feel like talking?
Where's the key, huh?
Look, I don't know what this key is that you keep talking about.
Wait, let me reason with him.
Mr. Krimmer, it's really pointless of you to try to hide it from us.
That safety deposit box key Pedrov gave you, where is it?
Well, like I said before, I can't tell you what I don't know.
I gotcha. You want money, don't you?
Well then, let's make a deal here.
How much are we talking about?
Nothing. I may be a hack journalist, but at least I make enough at it to keep myself fed.
Mr. Grimmer.
What a mess. This is just not right.
You know, my wife would say your nails are in desperate need of a trim.
I told you how she likes them, didn't I?
Why'd you do that? You shouldn't move.
Now, let's try again.
So, where is it? Where's the key?
I asked where.
Even if you did visit that bank,
and you're able to open the safety deposit box with the key,
and you got the tape and the data,
it wouldn't be of use to you.
Who possesses that tape is of extreme importance to the organization.
They're trying to do something big.
They're going to restore the Eastern Bloc to its former glory.
The exact identity of the monster is recorded on that tape of Pedroff's, and they need to
know everything about that monster.
That monster is like a king.
That monster can unite them all.
All of those orphans from 511 Kinderheim.
Yes, those children were selected to be communists of the highest order.
The 5-1-1 Kinderheim Group was the most elite group that East Germany had.
And the monster can summon all of them to do his bidding.
It's been said that he was able to control all of the workings of 5-1-1 Kinderheim,
and that he was the one who had it destroyed in the end.
He's a real monster, and the only person who could unite that elite group.
All right, now where's the key?
Hmm
You think they're an elite group
What's all funny
Why the hell are you laughing
What do you want? Is it money you're after I get it. I'm a capitalist. Hey, I love having lots of money
I'm not taking sides
I just want to sell them Pedroff's tapes so they give me a load of cash.
What's your angle on this?
Is this all for social justice?
There's no reason for you to go this far for that.
Just who are you, really?
You say you're a journalist from the Old Eastern Bloc,
but most of those folks were agents for government intelligence.
In fact, the very best of those agents were spies.
Who was it that sent you here?
What? You think you're a super-spy?
Huh. Sure.
I'll just bring you around!
You're going to die if you don't talk.
Okay, this is your last chance. Where's the key?
You ever hear of the Magnificent Steiner?
[coughing]
It was a cartoon that was on TV in West Germany in the 1960s.
The signal was so strong, you could even watch it in East Berlin.
The main character was a pencil necked weakling,
but when he'd get into a really dangerous fix,
This secret friend of his would come and save him, and beat his enemies to a pulp.
However, the main character never saw this secret friend of his.
He always blacked out before he arrived.
One day, he realized his special friend was himself.
And whenever he got into a situation that was truly desperate,
He would somehow transform into the terrifying Magnificent Steiner.
When he came to, he'd find all the evildoers bleeding at his feet.
This transformation made him unstoppable.
Well, you better transform.
Come on, transform right now.
Pour some water on him.
He'll tell us about it soon.
(crickets chirping)
- And who are you?
(eerie music)
(dramatic music)
(gunshot)
(groaning)
- What happened?
A woman came in and...
[GROANING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
A woman came in, and I heard a single gunshot, and one of those men was shot in the head.
[GUNSHOTS]
But on the other two bodies, there weren't any bullet holes.
[GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(gentle music)
The Magnificent Steiner.
I did it again.
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)