Where's the crime scene?
Down those stairs.
How many victims?
Three men, detective.
You can start looking for any evidence up here.
Before we start taking any action, shouldn't we wait for Detective Kratki to arrive? I mean...
I'm taking charge here. Start looking for witnesses, or anyone suspicious.
But there aren't any people around here.
I said look for anyone suspicious!
But no one's here.
Are you telling me you can't follow my orders because I'm a rookie?
Get moving!
I'm Detective Suk, Prague Police.
As crime scenes go, this one is pretty brutal.
Yeah.
Inspector Zemot.
He was savagely beaten to death.
I can't even make out his facial features.
His face is completely unrecognizable.
I guess it's good he had his police ID with him.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have been able to figure out who he was.
The bodies of two other men are over there.
We haven't been able to figure out who they are.
One took a gunshot to the head.
The other was beaten to death like the inspector.
Preserve the crime scene!
Yeah, so I haven't found anyone suspicious yet, sir.
(dramatic music)
I'm telling you, it stinks.
They make fun of me just because I'm a rookie.
The other police guys all look at me like I'm crazy when I give them an order.
You have to work to earn their respect before they'll listen to you.
He's right.
I'm a detective!
Yeah, you're a rookie detective.
And when you got to the crime scene, you took one look and lost your lunch.
Just because you grew up liking cop TV shows doesn't mean you can do the job.
Jan, you always got carried away, even when we were back in college.
Yeah, what do you know about how I feel?
Inspector Zemon was murdered.
He always treated me like I was his own son.
When I started, I didn't know anything.
But Inspector Zemon was there for me.
That man taught me what it takes to be a real detective.
I respected him, you know,
for caring enough to help out a guy like me who needed a hand.
I will avenge his senseless death if it's the last thing I do!
I swear I'll track down his killer and I will make him pay!
Okay, well, uh...
We have a staff meeting early tomorrow morning, Yan.
Hey, what kind of friends are you? It's still early.
I'm fighting for justice to protect both of you.
So come on, support your local police and let's have another round.
Just one more, what do you say, huh?
Hey, cut it out, crime fighter.
You know, we're out there working for justice, and to get murdered, that's so sad.
That's a hell of a role-board.
Huh?
Hey Yan, what are you looking at?
It's her. It's that girl from the grocery store.
Huh?
I've seen that girl twice when I went to the supermarket.
It was after working night duty.
That's her.
I really wanted to introduce myself to her then, but I didn't.
Looks like I've got another chance.
Hey, Yan, don't even try it.
She's way too pretty to go for a guy like you. Seriously.
Uh, hello.
Hi there.
You don't happen to remember me from the supermarket.
No, I guess you don't. I've wanted to talk to you for a while.
Oh, my name's Yansuke, and I'm not some random barfly.
I may not look it, but I'm a policeman.
Actually, I'm a detective, but don't be scared of me.
I'm off duty now. I just wanted to meet you.
Man, I don't think she's even said a word to him.
Yeah, he's striking out. You better go give him a hand.
Sorry for butting in.
Our friend here is feeling pretty depressed. Any chance you could talk to him for a bit?
Something terrible happened to the superior of his. He's all broken up.
Oh yeah, he's been pretty depressed.
Come on! I haven't acted depressed at all!
I never met a person as kind as he was.
Inspector Zemon was an inspiration to me.
His murderer took that great man away from us.
I know I'll find a way to bring him to justice.
Oh, wow. Here I am doing all the talking. Sorry.
You're passionate about what you believe.
You've got to try your best to catch his killer.
Oh, I can't believe this.
I finally get the chance to talk to you,
and I haven't even asked you about yourself yet.
So, uh, what's your name?
- I wish I knew my real name, but I don't.
- What?
Well, maybe I can help you.
Yeah, I'll figure out who you are.
IDing people is part of my job.
Maybe I can guess your name.
After all, I am a detective now.
I'm betting your name is...
- I told you I don't even know my name,
so there's no way you can guess it.
I'll tell you two things I know about myself.
Chidok Bridge, and Three Frogs.
And that's all I know.
Hold on!
Hey, wait!
Wait a second!
When can I see--
What did we tell you?
You blew it.
Next time, try picking one that's not so pretty.
All right, we've identified the two men
murdered at the same time as Inspector Zemon.
Victim number one is Chestmere Murat.
is Yakov Suhacek.
Turns out they were both sergeants
in the Czech secret police.
After the fall of socialism, they went underground
and started getting up to all sorts of no good.
After analyzing blood at the crime scene, we found something.
Besides Zeman, Marat, and Suhacek,
we IDed someone else's blood at the murder scene,
someone with blood type ABRH positive.
Judging from the amount of blood we found,
we know they were seriously injured.
At present, we're trying to actively determine
Detective Souk? Souk, wake up!
Yes, sir!
What on earth were you just daydreaming about?
We have lost a brilliant officer, Inspector Zemon!
We're facing a dire situation, and you're daydreaming here?
I... I'm very sorry, sir.
Anyhow, according to a witness,
there was a man seen walking away from the murder scene
at a time we feel was immediately after the crime.
He is described as a tall, thin man in his forties
Now, I want all of you to get out there and track that guy down!
Oh, well...
That girl... Guess she won't be back.
Mr. Detective...
Did you find your friend's killer? Have any luck?
Not yet.
It takes time, but I did get more information that might help.
The inspector, he was investigating a murder case just before he died.
Tell me more.
This old man, he was running his own illegal orphanage.
Somebody shot both him and his maid.
All morning, Zemon was busy questioning the man who discovered that crime scene.
Who was he?
Huh?
You know, who was the man who found the bodies?
He seemed nice. He was a tall, skinny-looking guy.
He was visiting from out of town.
He had this big, heavy duffel bag.
A tall, thin man.
And he was carrying a big duffel bag.
Could it be?
That man being questioned, do you know where he is?
Yeah, I think I do know.
I'll call the station and check.
C'mon, pick up.
Huh?
You go get him, Mr. Detective.
Hi, it's Sook here.
C'mon, not again!
Yeah, I'm here.
Chedak Bridge... and Three Frogs...
Wait, Chedak Bridge... That's over in Mikalska.
I need to find those Three Frogs.
(panting)
There they are.
If I come here, I bet I'll see her again.
(clears throat)
(whooshing)
- He checked out?
Well, when?
- Let's see, Mr. Grimmer, Mr. Grimmer.
Ah, it says here Mr. Grimmer checked out
the day before yesterday in the morning.
- There's no doubt.
I know exactly who murdered the inspector.
It was Grimmer, he slept here in this room.
Damn, why couldn't I have figured
this whole thing out two days ago?
Don't worry, Inspector. I'll still catch that bastard.
I swear.
Hey!
My word! Detective Suk, what are you doing here?
Chief Detective Patella, I could ask you the same, sir.
I see.
Well, using your wits, you progressed this far all by yourself. That's impressive.
Thank you.
And sir, I knew I'd be the first.
To make a breakthrough in this case, I just knew I would.
And I won't stop doing all I can to make sure that cop killer is apprehended.
Yeah, you've really pulled things together here. Great job.
Thanks, Chief.
Now, I'm ordering you to do me a favor here and keep this whole thing top secret.
Huh?
But Grimmer killed them! All the clues lead to that conclusion!
We can't just let him go-
Just hold on, Detective.
This case is a little more complicated than you think it is.
What?
Inspector Zemon had been assigned to a special investigation.
It was top secret.
Wait, the inspector was working undercover?
Right. He was investigating former Czechoslovakian secret police agents.
Some of them had faked their records and were working as officers on the Prague police force.
Inspector Zemon was working with members of the Czech secret police?
You know those two corpses we found with Zemon?
Both of them were formerly Czech secret police.
And aside from myself and the chief, almost no one knows about this.
Don't stick your nose in too deep. You could get yourself killed.
Not a word to anyone about this. Got it?
Sir, what should I be doing regarding this case?
Whoa, just slow down.
Grimmer might come back to this hotel at any moment, so you need to be here.
Keep your eyes peeled.
By the way, Suke, you happen to find yourself a girlfriend yet?
At the briefing, as you sat there, you had this smitten look.
C'mon, who's the lucky girl?
Uh, she's not really my girlfriend, sir.
She just hangs out at this bar where I usually go.
She a pretty girl?
Oh, yeah. She's very pretty.
Well, in that case, introduce me to her.
What's the name of that bar now?
I wouldn't call it a bar.
I don't feel right about doing that, sir.
But didn't you just tell me she's not your girlfriend?
Well, I suppose that's true, but...
Suk sends his regards, honey.
Well, hey, he wasn't kidding. You really are a beauty.
Who are you?
Glad you asked. I'm one of Suk's bosses.
But tell us my name we were talking and he said that there's a real beauty that he meets here
He couldn't come tonight. He's stuck doing a stakeout. How about I buy you a drink?
Hey, come on, honey, don't leave why not just one little drink
Hey there, Suk.
Oh, Detective Janacek, it's you.
Good morning, sir.
Vitella and I had a little chat.
He met that girl you're going after.
Said she's a real knockout.
Uh, sir, you went to that bar I talked to you about?
Oh, yeah.
But, you didn't do anything to her, did you, sir?
Please, say you didn't.
Ah, now, come on, Suk.
Don't get so excited, my boy.
Yeah, but everyone at the station knows that Chief Patella here really has a way with women.
Relax. She gave me that cold shoulder pretty quick.
That gal of yours must be a pretty tough cookie.
Most girls fall for him in a heartbeat. It's true.
She's a nice girl.
I... I mean, she's a good listener and interesting to talk to.
It's fun just to be around her. She's cool.
You're not talking to me, are you?
Anyways, Chief Farabek wants you to meet him right now in Inspector Zemon's office.
Oh, uh, yes sir.
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
Someone gave me these. Want a whiskey bon-bon?
Nope, I'm off candy.
Fine. Hey Sook, you want a bon-bon?
Uh, no thank you sir, I'm okay.
Hey, hold on a second.
Yes sir?
Don't say a word to the chief about our tall, thin suspect.
Right.
Poor Zemon. What a way to go.
Looks like his desk has pretty much been cleaned out.
All that's left are these two boxes of his personal stuff.
See to it that his widow gets it.
It looks like a key for a gym locker.
God, that smells!
Nothing in here but sweaty shirts, stinky socks and moldy towels.
A notebook?
Look. What the heck is this?
It's got detailed personnel files of everyone that's on the force.
Oh, wow. It's even got my whole record in here.
Inspector Zayman had been assigned to a special investigation.
It was top secret.
Right, he was investigating former Czechoslovakian secret police agents.
Some of them had faked their records and were working as officers on the Prague Police Force.
Wait, there's something missing.
Two files aren't in here.
Chief Detective Patella's and Detective Janicek's.
(suspenseful music)
- You're right, Detective.
This is a suspiciously large amount of cash.
- That's why I brought it here, Chief.
- Hmm.
So, tell me, Sook.
What do you surmise about Inspector Zaymon
from these things that you found?
It appears that Inspector Zemon was conducting an internal investigation.
Mm-hmm.
And, as a result,
he discovered that Detectives Patella and Janicek
worked previously in the old regime as agents for the Czechoslovakian secret police.
Mm-hmm.
I think,
and it makes me sad to say this, sir,
the inspector must have taken all that cash as hush money
in return for keeping quiet about the truth.
The implications of this evidence are serious.
I know. I feel sick just saying it.
Detective Suk.
Yes, sir.
You need to keep this matter completely to yourself.
We'll talk again later.
Now return to your regular duties.
Yes, sir!
I never thought this would happen.
Yeah, things have become complicated.
We were plain stupid to do what we did.
Why'd we take a guy like Sook so lightly?
And we haven't even settled the matter with this guy Grimmer that killed Zaymon.
And now there's an even bigger issue that we have to face.
So then do we offer the rookie money, like we did with Zaymon?
If that doesn't work, the only option is, you know...
Whatever it takes.
for allowing former secret police into the force.
From here on, we've got to keep a tighter lid on all of this.
Once Sook's gone, things will be as smooth as silk.
My head.
I sure could go for a nice drink right about now.
How about a whiskey bonbon instead?
Hey, they're better than nothing.
Besides, these were a gift from a real beauty.
Here, Chief.
(chewing)
- What's wrong?
You look depressed.
- I feel like I can't believe in anything anymore.
- Why do you say that?
What's wrong?
I'll help you if you want me to.
- I believed in him.
I never would have thought that Inspector Zemon
could do such a thing.
What happened?
I believed in him.
Right now, the only person who I really believe in...
[GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It's you.
[MUSIC]