From here on, we've got to keep a tighter lid on all of this.
Once Sook's gone, things will be as smooth as silk.
My head. I sure could go for a nice drink right about now.
How about a whiskey bonbon instead?
Hey, they're better than nothing. Besides, these were a gift from a real beauty.
What's wrong? You look depressed.
I feel like I can't believe in anything anymore.
Why do you say that? What's wrong?
I'll help you if you want me to.
I believed in him.
I never would have thought that Inspector Zemon could do such a thing.
What happened?
I believed in him.
Right now, the only person who I really believe in is you.
A TERRIBLY SHOCKING DISCOVERY WAS MADE EARLY THIS MORNING AT THE PRAGUE POLICE STATION.
THREE MEN, HEAD CHIEF HAMRICK, CHIEF DETECTIVE PETELA, AND DETECTIVE JANICZEK WERE FOUND POISONED
TO DEATH IN A CONFERENCE ROOM.
TWO BIG QUESTIONS REMAIN, JUST HOW THESE POLICEMEN WERE POISONED AND WHO WOULD DARE TO COMMIT
SUCH A BRAZEN ACT?
There have been rampant rumors of the Prague police force having ties to the former Czechoslovakian secret police,
but these allegations have never been substantiated.
However, with the murder of these three prominent policemen...
Hey, here comes a cop.
Detective, do you know who the murderer is?
Sir, can you confirm that the drug used to commit these murders was a muscle relaxant?
We've heard rumors that head chief Henrik was somehow linked with the Czech secret police.
Any truth to that?
Uh, well, I--
Is there any connection between these murders
and last week's killing of Inspector Zayman?
Well, we aren't investigating that.
I mean, we're not ruling out that possibility.
In saying that, do you mean the department strongly believes
that these two incidents are linked?
No, I-- Right now, the department is pursuing
all possible leads in this investigation.
Sorry, but this detective's not assigned to this case,
and we have no comment right now.
Suke, you need to button that lip of yours
and get out of here.
- Yes, sir.
- So exactly when are you going
to make an official statement?
- We will have a news conference
when we feel we've gathered enough information,
not a moment before.
(people chattering)
(gentle music)
Why are you here? Have you come back to interrogate them again?
I'm very sorry, ma'am.
Look, I've been given orders to investigate this case starting again at Square One.
This is my last stop.
I've already spoken with all the boys who got placed in other orphanages.
Think of what bringing this up again does to them.
Mr. Pedrov raised all those boys like they were his own children.
Now they have to live the rest of their lives with the image of him and his maid lying there, dead.
Even now, some of them still cry themselves to sleep.
I want to help them forget this as soon as possible.
And yet, that's not something they can just forget about.
Knowing that someone they truly loved has been taken away forever.
Fifteen minutes.
And don't go asking them questions that are too graphic, am I clear?
- Sure, it was lots of fun living with Mr. Pedrov.
Yeah, he and Mrs. Anna were really nice to us all the time.
- I see.
Now, I'd like to talk to you about the day you found them,
if that's okay.
That day you had Mr. Grimmer come to visit.
Had you met him before?
- No, not before then.
- Do you know why he came to visit?
- Uh-uh.
- As they talked, did Mr. Grimmer act friendly
towards Mr. Pedrov?
- Um, come to think of it,
but I didn't understand, they were talking in German.
But you know a few words in German, don't you?
Were there some words you did know?
He was saying that this place was unauthorized
and the police should be told.
So Mr. Grimmer said that?
Yeah. He also said "experiment" and the word "education."
Experiment. Anything else?
What else?
- Tell us if you don't want to, Honza.
- Oh, he said 511 Kinderheim.
- 511 Kinderheim, huh?
Okay.
So Honza, is that a place that you've heard of?
- No, never.
- Do you know it?
- There's no such place in the Czech Republic.
- I see.
So tell me about Mr. Grimmer.
What kind of person is he?
Oh, he's a really nice guy.
So you like him too, Izzy.
He played soccer with us.
He wasn't really any good at it.
But Mr. Grimmer looked like he was having a lot of fun.
The way he hits his soccer ball is just awful.
He went up for one and fell flat on his butt.
He's probably even worse than Honza.
Really!
The other boys told me you were the leader
at Mr. Petrov's orphanage.
Is that right, Antonin?
I wouldn't say I was really the leader.
- Well, you see, I'm just older than the other guys.
- Now, I'd like to talk to you about that day.
- Is it about Mr. Grimmer?
- Huh?
- One of the guys already told me
that you were asking Honza and Izzy about him.
- Oh, I see.
What do you think?
- I think he's a nice person.
I got a question for you.
Do you think Mr. Grimmer's a suspect?
- No, but we're still investigating.
- Well, Mr. Grimmer isn't the killer.
Mr. Pedroff and Mrs. Anna had already been murdered
by the time we got back home from playing soccer with Mr. Grimmer.
I told the police already, but I think I saw who did it.
As we got back home, I saw this beautiful woman with long blonde hair,
and she was coming out of our house.
Are you trying to catch him?
Catch who?
Mr. Grimmer!
No, but he sure is someone I'd like to have a chat with.
I'm actually going to meet him later on.
I promised him and we already set where we're going to meet.
And would you tell me where that is?
Sure.
You're sure that's alright? Because I might be forced to arrest him.
Well, you don't have to, 'cause there's no way he murdered anyone.
Hey!
Hi!
It's been a little while.
So, are you guys all holding up okay?
Things are a lot better.
You haven't been crying yourselves to sleep, right?
Izzy wet his bed twice!
Well, if the truth be known, I wet my bed until I was a lot older than he is now.
Really?
Hey, Antonin, did you bring that one thing I gave you earlier?
Thank you.
I'm glad you held onto it for me.
See, this is something very important Mr. Pedrov left behind.
- I'm glad you're all okay.
I wish I had more time to share, but I've gotta go.
- Can't you stay and play soccer with us?
- I'm sorry, boys.
I really should be moving on.
- But we're ready to play.
- Those are our new friends.
- Yeah, I can play for a while.
- All right!
- Come on, kick it!
Come on! I'm open on the right, guys! Pass it to me!
Oh! I got it!
Grimmer going in for the steal!
Max time! Stay on your feet!
That's easier said than done.
Throw in!
You're Mr. Grimmer, aren't you?
Did you come to arrest me?
Don't start waving your gun around.
Come on, there are kids here.
Then I order you to hand over your pistol this instant!
Sorry, I don't have one to hand over.
So you tossed it?
I never had one in the first place.
Tell me, did you kill Inspector Zemon?
I don't know. I can't remember.
I was half-dead from being tortured at the time.
Your nails, they're...
Now, I know it wasn't me who fired the gun,
but I might be responsible for killing the other two.
I passed out before it happened.
Mr. Grimmer!
Why are you up there resting?
Your team stuck playing a man down 'cause you went and took a break!
Sorry about that, guys.
Hey, I'm old! Cut me some slack!
Okay, you heard him, guys.
Antonin told me that you were planning to meet them to play soccer.
That's how I found you.
You're a person of interest, Mr. Grimmer.
Ah, so what's the verdict?
Am I the murderer you seek?
I don't know.
Over the past few days,
some of the people I deeply trusted betrayed me.
My faith in them was so totally shattered,
I don't know what to believe in anymore.
The only person you can truly believe in is yourself.
You can try to trust other folks,
but sometimes they let you down.
So, we going to the station?
No, just promise you won't leave town, okay?
So, where are you staying for the time being?
At the Pabla Hotel, room 302.
Whenever you decide I am the murderer, feel free to come and get me.
You be sure to hold on to that key.
I think it's the real cause of all these murders you're investigating.
It's to a safety deposit box.
Oh, that sign up there?
Well, it's actually an old relic.
It's a sign for a pub that was established here 200 years ago,
but the Three Frogs Pub has been closed down for ages.
Even though it's old and faded, it's considered a landmark,
It's been through world wars, the fall of communism, and disasters, too.
It's amazing that old thing has survived.
About a decade ago, it even made it through a fire.
Really?
Yeah.
This woman with a young kid lived up there on the second floor, right above it.
She sure was a beautiful woman,
but kind of antisocial, hardly ever went out,
and for a good reason.
Seems while she was living there, she was using an alias.
One day, this big official-looking black car came and it took her and the kid away for good.
It was a big deal. We all heard rumors that the woman was arrested for having participated in anti-government activities.
That sort of thing happened all too often in those days. We lived in fear because the government terrorized everyone.
It was really quite awful during those final years before the fall of communism. People disappeared all the time.
That woman who got taken away, did she have one child with her, or did she have twins?
No. She only had one child with her, and what a pretty face that kid had.
Was that woman's child a boy or a girl?
Huh. Let me think for a second. Now, which one was it?
Sometimes it's really hard to tell whether they're a boy or a girl when children are that little.
I can't remember.
All I can think about is how they took away that poor, innocent kid with them when they took the mother away.
Right after they left, the fire started.
I ran up there even though I didn't think anyone was around.
Then I got a huge surprise. Her child was in there!
The child must have been released, that's all I can figure.
But I imagine the fire got started when he got hungry
and decided to use the stove to try to cook something.
So where'd he go?
I hate to admit it, but after that fire happened,
I don't know where that young kid went.
I've always wondered what happened to that kid.
What if that child was one of the lady's twins?
Huh?
What if the police took away one child and left the other one up in that room?
Well, if what you just said is right, that might make sense.
But I don't get why you're so sure about the fact that she had twins.
So after questioning the boys, I was able to meet with Grimmer and check him out for myself.
But I really don't think he's the murderer.
I see. Well, I'm just an amateur at crime-solving.
Maybe I'm wrong about him, Mr. Suk.
He's not evil, that much I do know.
Just from us talking, he was able to help me figure out what's really going on.
At first, when Inspector Zemon was found murdered,
I thought it was my duty to avenge his death at any cost.
But then I opened my eyes.
I discovered that Inspector Zemon, a man I looked up to, was a corrupt cop.
for him. But that's all changed. And then after that, the chief and two senior
officers I always reported to wound up poisoned. When I heard that those men
might have been corrupt as well, it shook me to the core. I mean, it's beyond
belief. How far has this terrible darkness spread in the world? Darkness?
Yes, the dark specter of the Czech secret police hangs over all of this. The Czech
secret police worked directly under the former Internal Affairs Office.
They were a brutal force that served as an essential tool of the Soviet Union.
But when democracy came ten years ago, they were disbanded.
Their leaders were put on trial, but some escaped and went underground.
Even now, they're still planning to regain their former power.
That's as much as I know about them.
In their quest for power, many innocent victims have wound up dead.
Are the secret police the only ones behind these murders?
That's the question I'm faced with.
Is there any way we can really know just how closely the darkness has encroached upon the world we live in?
I don't think I believe in anyone anymore.
Mr. Grimmer even warned me, "Only believe in yourself."
He said, "When you trust other people, it doesn't always work out."
And as he said that, he entrusted me with something very important.
Sorry, I can't stop talking about this.
It's kinda tough on me not even knowing your name.
Oh, hey, listen, it's alright, you don't have to tell me.
I always thought when people spent time getting to know one another,
they told each other their names and about their pasts.
But just talking to you makes me happy.
(soft music)
- Both of my parents are still alive.
They're schoolteachers,
but my father used to participate in democratic activities
and the police always watched him.
So my mom ended up divorcing him
to protect me from any potential trouble.
When I finally told my mom I wanted to be a detective,
she got angry and told me not to do it.
Why did you want to become a detective?
I believe my friends at the bar told you the reason why, remember?
Wasn't it because you grew up liking cops on TV?
Yeah, I liked playing cops and robbers ever since I was a kid.
Of course, I always got to be the cop.
Bang!
You don't have to laugh that much.
Oh, come on, Suk.
So, what were you entrusted with?
Huh?
Earlier, you were saying the Grimmer entrusted you with something important?
Oh, it's a key to a safety deposit box.
A safety deposit box?
Yeah.
Apparently, whatever's stored in there is super important.
This old German man named Pedrov, who was running an illegal orphanage, was murdered last week.
And?
Inside that deposit box of Pedrov's is the data from some kind of human experiments he supposedly conducted.
According to Grimmer, the material that's in that box is the real cause of all these murders.
Huh?
Don't say that again! Don't tell anyone what you just told me! Not even the police! Nobody!
But... this thing isn't something I can handle all by myself.
She's right. She loves you a lot.
When you told her you wanted to be a cop, you know why she got mad?
It's because she was worried that something awful might happen to you.
I got a bad feeling about what you just told me.
The best thing to do is not to tell anyone.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I... I care about you, too.
My name... I want you to know my name now, Yan.
It's Anna. My name is Anna Liebert.
Anna... What a beautiful name.
So your last name must mean that you're German.
See you later.
Huh?
Anna...
[GIGGLING]
Good evening, Mr. Tulunka.
Oh, Anna. It's a nice night, isn't it?
Oh, good evening, Anna.
Good night, Mrs. Yalka.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER SPLASHING]
A safety deposit box key.
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)