This is the most scandalous case that has ever occurred in the history of the Czech police force.
Much to our dismay, we discovered that the three officers who were murdered were connected to the former Czechoslovakian secret police.
In light of these incidents, I would like to believe that all the dark connections which have stained our reputation have been purged from the Prague station.
Remember, you are proud officers of this force. I expect conscientious behavior from all of you.
And let me say this. As your new chief, I intend to carry out a very thorough reform here.
And my first order of business is to regain our citizens' trust.
I will now introduce you to the five-member Special Investigative Task Force,
which was sent over here from the government.
It goes without saying that I expect you to cooperate with them
so we may close the book on this atrocious case as soon as possible.
You're Detective Suk, correct?
Yes.
As your new chief, I would like to say thanks
for the fine investigative work that you've done on this case to help bring it to light.
You're very welcome, sir.
Oh, and by the way, Detective, what case are you currently working on?
The one Inspector Zemon was on, which involves the murder of Pedrov,
a man who was operating an illegal orphanage.
Very well then. Please continue to devote all your efforts to solving it, Detective.
Yes, sir. I'll be on my way then.
Oh, uh, one more thing.
That tall man who emerged as a suspect in Inspector Xie Man's murder,
do you have any pertinent details on him that you can give me before you get back to work?
No, sir. I don't have any solid information on him as of yet.
I see. You may go now.
Thank you. Good day, sir.
Yan Suk. He's been assigned to this division for a year now. Zayman took him under his
wing early on, and they became close. Suk uncovered Detective Patella and Yanichek's
hidden past. He also met with Chief Hamrick right before he died. I want you to keep an
eye on that kid.
Yes, sir.
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
(bells ringing)
(bell ringing)
- Hey.
- You know, when I called up that hotel
where you told me you'd be staying,
I was kind of surprised to hear you answer the phone.
Not that I'm complaining.
- Well, it sounds as though you thought
you were going to be deceived again.
- Maybe.
- Orange juice, please.
Mr. Grimmer, I know you wanted to meet me someplace where there were large crowds, but
is this spot really okay?
What do you mean by okay?
I spoke to the new chief.
He hasn't taken you off the suspect list for Zemon's murder yet.
Besides, you're being pursued by former members of the Czechoslovakian secret police.
Come to think of it, you might be right about the crowd.
Maybe it makes you safer.
There's no such thing as a safe place.
Fixin' to do it, they can get me any place, any time.
For example, they could take me out from that window
with the red drapes.
- Look, Mr. Grimmer, I want you to level with me, okay?
Who are you really?
- Just a struggling freelance journalist.
- But if that's true,
Guess I'm just nosy. Seems to come with the territory.
How can you make light of it?
At every moment, your life is in danger.
Don't worry about me.
It was my decision to get involved. I knew it was risky.
Sook is currently at a cafe in Republic Square, and he's not alone.
He's meeting with the suspect now. A tall, rather lanky fellow.
There's no doubt in my mind that it's Grimmer.
Yes. Should we continue to observe them for a bit longer, sir?
All of this started when you went to see Petrov.
This was a man who conducted brainwashing experiments on orphaned children in East Germany back before the Unification, right?
Right.
And then, before he died, Petrov gave you the key to his bank's safety deposit box where he kept a record of those same experiments. Is that right?
Yeah. And he also mentioned something about the monster's past.
I wonder what he could have meant by that.
It seems that there are many people who,
for whatever reason, want to get their hands on that data.
You mean the former secret police?
And also that lovely blonde lady.
The children at Pedrov's orphanage also mentioned her.
Called her the pretty blonde lady.
They said they saw her leaving the house right after Pedrov was mortally wounded.
Do you have any idea who that woman might be?
I don't have a clue. She's a mystery to me.
Is it alright you're being here like this?
Huh?
I mean, you haven't told your superiors about this meeting.
You're here acting on your own, aren't you?
That's not exactly what I'd call being an honest team player.
Look, I'm not planning to hide any of this from them.
I'm exercising my own discretion.
I'll report to my superiors
after I've gathered all evidence in this case.
And if I do a thorough investigation,
I can prove to them without a doubt that you're innocent.
Is something the matter?
Look slowly to your nine o'clock.
That suspicious-looking fellow
sitting under the umbrella reading a newspaper.
What do you think?
Secret police, you think?
Couldn't say.
Now then, shall we go?
Alright, but where do we go?
You brought it with you, didn't you?
You know, the key to the safety deposit box that I gave you.
Yeah?
Don't you want to find out the identity of this so-called monster?
Yes.
In that case, we'd better get going.
Though knowing who it is might be hazardous to our health.
You're looking a little pale, Sook.
Did I just see that pretty blonde lady?
Hey, what's wrong?
(scoffs)
- Uh, nothing.
I must have imagined it.
- Sook is on the move.
I'm on him.
(dramatic music)
I spoke with you before on the telephone.
I'm Detective Suk, Prague Police.
Just wait here a moment, please.
Thank you both for your patience.
If you follow me, I will take you to the vault.
This is where we have our safety deposit boxes.
You may use that room to view the contents.
Research papers, and a single cassette tape.
Well, I do have a tape recorder with me.
If you're ready to hear it, then I'm going to press play now.
Do you know what this place is?
5-1-1 Kinderheim.
That voice.
It's a boy.
What is your name?
My name is Johan.
[EXPLOSION]
What is your last name?
Let's try that again.
My name is Otto.
Oh, my name is Hans.
My name is Thomas.
My name is--
Which one is your real name?
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there lived a nameless monster.
The monster was dying to have a name.
before? I was waiting for Anna. Who is Anna? I was reading a picture book while I was waiting
for Anna. This boy was drugged, Suk. They gave him something before this session was
put on tape. Who is your father? I don't know. Your mother? I think she's alive. You know,
You're a very bright child is there anything you're afraid of
What is it that you are most afraid of
Let me ask a different question then have you ever killed anyone
Many people were dead
It was like
Ana and I were the only two people in the world
Where was that place?
Let's go back to that other question again.
What is it that you are the most afraid of?
The monster inside of me is getting bigger.
Munch, munch, chomp, chomp, gobble, gobble, gulp.
What I'm most afraid of, it's...
I feel sick. Like I'm gonna throw up.
What happened, Mr. Grimmer? Hey, are you alright?
Yeah.
What did we just hear on this tape?
I mean, was that little boy the voice of the monster?
I really don't understand what's going on.
Even though we don't know what this tape is about,
there are people out there who would do anything to have it in their possession.
For one, the former Czechoslovakian secret police…
And to them, it won't make any difference if we just listen to part of the tape,
or all the way to the end.
I'm sorry to tell you, but there's no turning back.
What are you going to do now?
Do you plan to return the tape and the research papers to the safety deposit box?
No.
Under normal circumstances, they should be stored here as evidence, but all things considered...
You're planning to hang on to them?
Then I think we should leave separately.
Let me serve as your decoy.
After all, it's me they're watching.
Oh, yeah.
Better give me your telephone number and street address.
If we're both able to make it home safely,
we'll have a way of getting in touch with each other in the future.
(dramatic music)
- I made it, and I don't think I was followed.
I'm starting to get a bad feeling about this.
I mean, I don't have a whole lot of confidence in him.
Says here he lives on Lanover Street.
What are you doing in my apartment?
What's going on?
That's the same question we wanted answered.
Do you know who we are, or do I need to enlighten you?
You're both part of that special task force.
The government assigned you to the Prague office.
My partner here is Detective 3rd Grade Novak, and I'm Detective Zanda, also 3rd Grade.
Care to tell me why the two of you broke into my place?
How long have you been meeting with Grimmer?
And don't tell me you don't know what I'm talking about.
You two just met at the cafe in Republic Square
and went to the Prochaska Bank together.
You also know the man in this photograph, don't you?
Huh?
Captain Karl Lanka.
He was an important name in the Czech secret police,
who are now underground.
What? No, I've never seen that man before.
Our task force ran a check on your bank account.
made a hefty deposit. Where'd all that money come from?
Huh?
Wh-what are you talking about?
I don't know anything about a deposit!
We've heard your mother is currently being hospitalized
for a serious illness at the Krumov Hospital.
I understand that hospital care and private nurses
can get quite expensive.
Yeah, so what are you trying to imply?
Well, after your mother separated from your father,
without any support from him.
Which says to me, you must care a lot about her.
- Just what are you suggesting, detective?
- We would like to search each room of your flat.
- Yeah, do whatever you want, what do I care?
You're gonna see I'm not hiding money or anything else!
Because I've got nothing to hide.
Hey, Zonda, come here for a second.
Where'd you find these things?
They aren't mine!
They were on a shelf in a cabinet above your bathroom sink, Detective Suk.
No!
I don't know what they are!
They don't belong to me!
We can't say for sure what this drug is until we check it out in the lab at the station
But in the bodies of the three dirty cops who were murdered in your station
We found a muscle relaxant mixed in with this type of candy
Whiskey bonbon candy
You can tell us your side of the story back at headquarters
As you wish
Investigate me as thoroughly as you see fit.
Oh, we will.
Can I ask for a favor?
Before we head out, can I change into a clean shirt?
I've been wearing this one all day.
Fine. But hurry up.
Just calm down. Calm down.
I haven't done anything. My record's perfect.
I just need to go in and explain to them that I'm innocent.
(dramatic music)
Wait, I smell gunpowder.
(door creaking)
(dramatic music)
(panting)
(heavy breathing)
(eerie music)
(dramatic music)
- Sook!
(glass shattering)
(explosion booms)
(ethereal music)
(dramatic music)
[ Music ]