This news story about the police just keeps getting worse and worse.
Any new info coming in?
Yeah, that was the police calling to say they're holding a press conference about the case at 3 p.m.
Then let's get rolling to the Prague Police Station.
In all my years, I've never seen a case as crazy as this.
Now don't tell me you've been here looking through those documents since I left you last night.
Yes, but it looks like I've found that article I was looking for.
Thanks for all your help.
Hey, you're welcome.
Glad it worked out.
Oh, one second.
I've got a question.
Can it wait?
I'm kind of in a rush right now.
I know.
In this article I found, there's this Mr. X.
Mr. X, huh?
That's right.
Three years ago, your paper ran an exposé entitled
"The Truth About the Former Czechoslovakian Secret Police."
Oh, yeah.
That article explained how after the wall fell, that instead of pulling back,
the German right-wingers and the former Czechoslovakian secret police
extended their influence even more by organizing crime syndicates.
As a matter of fact, I'm the guy who wrote it.
You wrote this article?
Well, what would it take for you to introduce me to that Czech secret police agent you interviewed,
the man you referred to as Mr. X?
You said before that you're a special correspondent here from Japan.
So enlighten me, why would you want to have an interview with our Mr. X anyway?
Well, he's newsworthy.
I'm sure the folks back home would be interested in finding out about how abductions, imprisonment, and other things were done here during the Cold War.
I gotta tell you, those guys are crazy.
I feel like I really risked my life to do that interview back then.
They're still very dangerous.
And they're still very active, based on what just went down.
I know you've been in here a while, but did you hear the latest update?
I mean, have you seen the headlines from this morning yet?
Well, I...
If you're trying to do a story on the secret police,
you should be following this big story
we ran about Detective Suk.
Here's a copy of today's final edition.
You can read German, can't you?
This young guy, Jan Suk, was working as a rookie detective
in the Prague Police Department.
After shooting two detectives
from a special investigative team
who were assigned to keep an eye on him,
Suk's run off somewhere.
He's flown the coop.
This inspector named Zemon was murdered,
and it turned out he was a corrupt cop
who worked for both the former Czech secret police
Sook discovers that fact and goes to the chief to report it,
not knowing that he has ties to the secret police as well.
But someone poisons the chief and his two cronies,
and all three of them die.
Sook's hailed as a hero for helping to clean up the department,
but then he goes and kills two cops who were assigned to watch over him.
Sook was a promising and skilled detective.
He was a young man on his way up.
Just what is it that you're mumbling about exactly?
Three superiors poisoned to death by whiskey bonbons with a muscle relaxin' in them.
It's Johan.
Excuse me. Could you please tell me if Yansuke's mother is here?
Well, are you with the police?
No.
She's staying in room 409.
Thank you.
Sir, keep your visit short. She may not want to talk.
(footsteps approaching)
- Pardon me, ma'am, but are you Yansuk's mother?
- Oh, Yan.
My Yan, at last you finally come.
- Ma'am, I'm not Yan.
- I'm so glad you made it here, my son.
Won't you come closer and let me see your face, darling?
You should relax now. Go ahead and lie down.
Oh, Yan.
Ma'am, have you received any phone calls or letters from your son Yan lately?
That Katerina, the girl next to me, is so cruel.
She took my toy and won't give it back to me.
You know, it's that precious little stuffed animal that Aunt Mary gave me.
I want to be sure you know something.
Your son is an honest cop, and he's innocent.
Well, I'll be going now.
Hold on. Tell the truth.
I have a hunch you've been playing there again, weren't you, Yan?
You always liked playing cops and robbers at that same place.
What place are you talking about?
as your own little hideout, son.
But I know all about it.
The abandoned building on Bruno Street.
- You found out about it?
- That's right.
I certainly did, Jan.
- Take care.
- Now don't go getting hurt, son.
Be sure to come home in time for dinner.
"Once upon a time, in a land far away, there lived a nameless monster. The monster was
dying to have a name."
There lived a nameless monster.
I figured I'd bring you some food.
And the latest newspaper.
You're getting to be quite a celebrity, you know that?
Tell me.
Are you concerned someone will find that tape and research papers
from the safety deposit box that I sent to my mother?
Well, one thing's for certain.
with your mom than if we had them here with us.
After reading all about what happened,
I have to say it's amazing to me
how much your situation reminds me of that other incident.
It's uncanny.
- What incident?
- I'm referring to something that happened in Dusseldorf
about 10 years ago.
This one hospital's director and two other doctors
died after ingesting poisoned candy.
The main suspect at the time
was a promising young neurosurgeon.
- What ended up happening to him?
- Poor guy's been on the run ever since.
You're still in good shape, Yan. After all, you have me as a witness.
You mean you actually saw her as she was coming down the stairs of my apartment?
That I did. Our infamous blonde beauty.
But even if that woman really is the murderer, if we can't find her, we have nothing!
Calm down, Suke.
No! Are you saying that from now on we're stuck being on the run?
Why did all this happen to me?
What the hell did I ever do to deserve this crap?!
Take it easy.
Are you saying that from this moment on,
you expect me to just disappear off the face of the Earth?!
Cool it!
Come on, pull it together!
I've told you how to handle this, haven't I?
Remember when I told you the only one you can believe in is yourself?
Good. That's much better.
Now, let's eat.
You know,
to come here and play cops and robbers in this very room.
That desk?
It was the police inspector's desk.
It's hard to believe that it's still here, just as it was.
I would sit behind this desk and give out orders to everyone,
just like on TV.
Gentlemen, this case is a real tough one,
but all of us must do our very best.
In the name of justice, we must prevail today.
Evil run rampant.
Feels like old times.
No!
Sook!
Stay still.
We're surrounded.
Don't worry, Suke. I got you.
Let's get you away from the window and behind this desk.
I can't even stand!
That's fine. You're probably in shock.
The question is, who shot at us?
Where are they shooting at us from?
That shot didn't hit any vital organs. You're gonna be fine.
I need to borrow your gun.
(coughing)
- The tape.
(guns firing)
(knocking)
- Raw soup!
- Oh my god.
Hold on, I'm coming to get you!
(screaming)
The sniper's missing his heart and head on purpose.
- Give us the tape!
- Damn it, we don't have it with us!
(gunshot)
God, they've got a shot at both of us through that window.
- Help me, Grimmer!
- Okay, I'm gonna work my way over to you, Suk.
- Look, I'm coming for you right now.
(gunshots)
- It hurts, it hurts all over!
- Just breathe, try to stay calm.
- It's all over, Grimmer, I'm gonna die!
- Just be quiet and breathe!
- Please, listen!
- Save your strength!
Wade, if you can get out of here. I want you to go. Don't worry about me.
I won't leave you here to die!
They're right there above us.
They're speaking in Czech, but what in the hell are they saying?
[GASPING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
Oh, God, it hurts!
[GASPING]
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Drimmer, please. I don't want to die here.
(panting)
(screaming)
(snoring)
(gun cocks)
(speaking in foreign language)
- Can you speak German?
- Yes, a little.
- Who are you aiming at over there?
- Wait, who in the hell are you?
Answer my question. What are you doing?
Okay, okay. We took care of them.
We're done. Two of our guys charged that building.
The detective and tall guy have already been wiped out.
I'm too damn late.
(footsteps approaching)
- It's quiet up there.
(gasping)
(creature growling)
[GASPS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[GASPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I know you.
Look what he did. The Magnificent Steiner.
Your name's Grimmer, right?
It's the Magnificent Steiner, folks.
He's done it once again.
What happened?
Hello, Dr. Tenma. I'm glad that you showed up when you did.
Could you save his life, please?
"Suke is a fine young policeman, so please, do whatever you can to help him pull through.
He's not the only one who needs a doctor."
"Who did this, do you know?"
"Guess it was probably me.
Or my other half, rather.
The one that's deep down inside of me.
See, Doctor, I was one of those special children at 511 Kinderheim.
The Magnificent Steiner!
All right, everyone, are you ready for action?
What sort of adventures are awaiting us today?
If you're ever in trouble,
Anytime! Anywhere! I'll come and save you!
The Invincible Magnificent Steiner!
Evil will never go unpunished, for I am...
THE MAGNIFICENT STEINER!
I was glued to that TV whenever I had the chance to watch
The Magnificent Steiner in action.
The main character on the show was a frail young man, and the bad guys would always corner
him at the worst possible moment.
But before you knew it, the Magnificent Steiner would appear and flatten all the villains.
I didn't realize it at first, but the Magnificent Steiner started showing up in my life for
real.
Whenever I was in real danger, he'd appear and rescue me.
He would defeat all the bad guys.
The only vivid memory that I still have from being a child
was watching the Magnificent Steiner on TV.
That's it.
All of my other memories were taken away.
Every last one of them wiped clean out of my mind
at 511 Kinderheim.
Listen to me babbling away like this. I mean, you don't want to hear about my past. It has nothing to do with you.
Alright. I've treated him as best I can.
Thank you, Doctor. So, do you think he'll pull through?
All of the bullets that hit him passed through cleanly, but the wound that runs from the auxiliary artery to the brachial artery is pretty serious.
That sling I tied on him should keep enough pressure on it to stop the bleeding.
That's all I can do for now, but he's in shock.
to a hospital as soon as possible.
Mr. Grimmer, you just said that your past
doesn't involve me, but it does more than you can know.
Especially 511 Kinderheim.
Now, let's get an ambulance for Sook.
- Where's the guy that's hurt?
- There are three men in there.
We're gonna need another ambulance.
Call dispatch.
- How bad off are they?
- Not bad, we need to move 'em, but... - But what? Well, what's wrong?
These guys have already received first aid. And proper first aid, at that.
Wait, you're saying somebody already took care of 'em?
Grimmer, look. It made the news.
Oh, yeah? What are they saying?
They're speaking Czech, so I can't follow it.
But I found out the name of the hospital where they're being kept.
It's "Yakuba Zimi Memorial."
Once they ID Suke, the police are probably going to arrest him.
It's a sad state of affairs.
Suke's innocent, huh?
He is.
I wonder if I should go and testify.
So then, Dr. Tenma, how on earth did you know we--
Can we talk about what you were saying earlier?
Please.
There's something I need to know more about, Grimmer.
Actually, I don't really remember being there.
I don't remember that period.
I can only remember the fragments.
Dark hallways.
A stain on the ceiling.
The sound of doors squeaking.
The smell of my moldy bed.
The memories came back to me at least a little bit, after I was finally freed from that orphanage.
I can almost hear someone saying I was fourteen years old.
Now that I think back to then, when I was first enrolled in that strange school, they
went and gave me a brand new name.
It's only then that I became Wolfgang Grimmer.
The place where they chose to raise me was this totally artificial neighborhood.
That little bubble was our whole world, and we weren't allowed out.
There was some man playing the father figure, and a woman to play the mother, too.
They taught me languages there. Russian, English, Spanish, French.
I could speak, read, or write 'em all.
You were trained to be a spy?
I must admit, the schooling they gave me did serve me pretty well.
The toughest thing to master...
...was just learning how to smile.
Now then, we have to go to the hospital where they're keeping Suk.
Mr. Grimmer, they had your picture in the paper.
They want you as a witness in this case, you know that.
I know, but I'm the only one who can prove Suk's innocence.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)