Hello, Anna.
The wind's getting cold, isn't it?
Hmm?
That's strange.
She always smiles at me and says hello.
Oh, Anna!
Are you headed home for the evening?
[panting]
Hey, Nina!
Looks like all the restaurants in this neighborhood are already closed.
Let's go back to the hotel, Nina.
What's wrong, huh?
For some reason, people on this street talk to me like they know me.
But they called me "Ana" instead of "Nina".
[silence]
[music]
Interesting.
So, what's wrong with this picture?
I'd say a lot.
Suk is the main suspect in a multiple homicide case.
I don't see any police or security anywhere.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go in there and take a look around.
Sure, but I think I'd better tag along. I could use some answers myself.
It's quiet as a tomb. And there's not a single policeman in sight.
Excuse me. There's an injured man being hospitalized here. Suk is his last name?
Huh?
Yon Suk. He's a police detective.
A cop?
All these men were injured at this vacant building on Bruno Street.
Oh, he was one of those unemployed men who were injured in the fight?
Unemployed men? Fight?
That's them.
Who knows what story they're reporting on the news, but what you're saying is probably the real deal.
So, could you please tell us what rooms they're staying in?
After their serious injuries were treated, they were all moved to another hospital.
To another hospital?
Where?
I don't know. It says a large ambulance came and loaded up all six of the patients.
That's exactly how many of those goons attacked us. There were six of them.
What about Souk? Detective Yan Souk, where's he? He's the one that was shot.
According to our records, there weren't any patients brought in with any gunshot wounds.
Wait, is there any record of a patient with the name Yan Souk even being brought in here?
No, not at all.
You have research data and an audio tape from 511 Kinderheim.
The former director of 511 Kinderheim, a man named Pedrov, gave them to me before he died.
He was running this illegal orphanage in Prague.
Those things you have, who exactly would be interested in them?
I don't know for sure, but I've got a hunch.
I'd say the Czech secret police have a keen interest in obtaining any material from 511
Kinderheim.
That said, where are you keeping this data and the tape?
Well, they're not on me.
I've stored them in a secure location.
Sook was shot because you possessed something they want, and it probably led to him being kidnapped from here.
What's just as bad is we can only imagine what they'll do to Sook to force that data and tape from my hands.
God, what a mess.
The contents of the tape and the data. What are we talking about here?
The research data was a list of technical terms. It also contained a list of names.
I didn't have the time to examine it closely.
I only listened to part of the tape.
So what was this tape a recording of?
A child talking.
A child?
This young boy was probably drugged, then the interviewer asked him questions.
And when this boy was asked his name, his answer was "Johan."
Hm?
Dr. Tenma, is something the matter?
511 Kinderheim.
And research data.
Y-Yohan...
Where is that tape right now?!
It might be best if you come with me.
Tell us where Suk is.
We can discuss that after our business.
Where's Suk?
Would the both of you come with me, please?
Dr. Tenma, you really should have stayed behind.
No. I also have a couple questions that the Czech secret police might be able to answer for me.
So you're saying you have your own agenda, huh?
Well, the first question that needs answering here is whether we can negotiate with these people at all.
Hold on. You didn't drive us all this way to treat us to dinner, did you?
Welcome, gentlemen. Come, have a seat.
I know that face.
He looks familiar. He must be a high-ranking member of the Czech secret police.
You're right. He's Captain Karol Lanka. I did research on him at the newspaper.
Now we're getting somewhere.
"First, I want to express to you my sincerest apology for what happened.
The men I assigned to this have taken actions that were far too heavy-handed.
This was an error within our chain of command.
We've been awfully misunderstood, by you and the world.
We are viewed as a rogue gang of ruthless killers."
"So where's Sook?"
"Sook is not in any danger.
He is resting comfortably at one of our hospitals."
I don't want you thinking of us as thugs. After all, it's not like we've killed anyone.
What about the woman?
What woman?
Wasn't that blonde woman who killed Pedrov acting on direct orders from you?
I've heard about this woman's murderous activities, but she isn't working for us.
In fact, she's been quite disruptive to our plans.
We are not in the business of killing people.
A German associate of ours informed us that he wanted the tape and the data,
And we were delicately negotiating securing them from Pedrov in the middle of all this he was murdered
Well, there must have been a lot of money involved. Yes, but that negotiation failed
We are here to discuss business of a more pressing nature
I want that tape and data in trade for the safe return of sook sounds fair
But I don't have those things our sources say you do have what we want. I
I won't.
Who knows what could happen if that information got out into the world for a second time.
We must never allow something like that to happen again.
There's no point in talking about things like that now.
After all, it doesn't really relate to our present discussion.
That's where you're wrong. You see, I'm from there.
I was there.
As a child, I was sent to live at 511 Kinderheim.
I see. How old are you?
Well, when did you leave that place?
I was fourteen years old, as near as I can tell.
And that was thirty years ago.
When were you there?
Who knows? Guess I got there when I was about eight.
So that must have been around 1963.
I guess.
Did you know this boy?
He's my nephew. In the early 1960s, I was officially stationed as an intelligence officer
in East Berlin, where I worked as a spy for the Czechoslovakian embassy. I had a beautiful
younger sister. She married this East German. After being married a few years, my younger
sister and her husband plotted to defect and cross the Berlin Wall. During their attempt
to cross over, they were shot dead.
My nephew was all that was left of their family.
I heard it was a wonderful place,
so I signed him up to live there.
It was touted as an ideal environment
to prepare and educate children with dubious pasts
so they would qualify to become
the communist elite of the future.
I gave it my all.
I used all the influence I had to be sure
that he would get into 511 Kinderheim.
"I don't know him. I have no memories. None from that time. Or even before then. I don't
remember what happened there. I was brainwashed. I can't even tell you my real name."
"I see. You're trying to make a profit off of something that was reprehensible. You want
to sell information that includes experimental data that was collected from your own nephew!
We've strayed off topic.
You're attacking instead of discussing things in a calm, business-like manner.
Very well then, you may go.
We're done discussing things for today.
"I await your acceptance of my offer.
Take these gentlemen where they wish."
"I can't believe he sent us away.
What do we do?
Saving Suk is what's important.
If we give him what he wants, I think he'd release Suk to us right away."
(door opens)
- You okay?
- Hot cocoa.
- Huh?
- I remember.
I remember.
Grimmer, come back!
(glass shattering)
Once a week we got cocoa.
He always looked forward to drinking it!
Your nephew was so kind to me!
When I got a fever and slept in the infirmary, he brought me his cocoa.
He gave me his, even though he liked it so much.
It was delicious.
I'd never had cocoa that delicious in my entire life.
And I wanted to thank him in some way for what he'd done for me.
And that's when he said to me,
That's when he looked into my eyes and said, "Remember me."
Back then, while we were there, we all did stuff like that.
We talked about ourselves to the friends we made.
I don't really know why, but our memories about ourselves would fade day by day
after those strange lessons they would put us through.
We could hardly remember our names after a while.
That's why...
We had our friends remember who we really were!
He loved hot cocoa drawing pictures and bugs fascinated him
But he didn't like bug collections because he didn't like having to kill the bugs
The most funny ever had was spending a day in the forest with his parents
He caught a lot of butterflies there
But then when he went back home, he set the butterflies free his lifelong dream was to become an entomologist his name was
His name was his name was Adolf Reinhardt
That boy was my nephew.
Welcome home.
Keeping secrets from him is dangerous.
You're definitely a no-no.
People can become...
...whatever they want to be.
A toast!
Hey, welcome home.
Hey, Nina, what's wrong?
I... Somehow, I... I know this place.
The brick road leading up to here...
The scenery's familiar...
And even... this old sign...
I know all these things.
You lived here?
I don't know.
But I...
But what?
I'm afraid.
So do you know this door?
I'm not sure.
But I...
Hold on.
I'm so afraid.
(door creaking)
- I also recognize these stairs.
- I couldn't sleep, not after what you said.
I thought about it all night.
(birds chirping)
- But Dr. Tenma, that research data and tape
really shouldn't concern you.
- Actually, they do.
- Looks like we're not gonna have time to talk.
- Huh?
- I guess they're ready to do some more negotiating.
Our Czech secret police have dropped by for a morning chat.
I guess they want an answer.
- So, have you had a chance to think everything through?
- I have, and I don't plan on giving you
the research data or the tape.
- So you're saying that you don't care
what happens to Detective Suk?
- If something happens to Suk,
that precious data and tape
disappear from this world forever, I guarantee.
- Your attitude keeps us from making progress.
- Hold on.
I am willing to offer you a chance to listen to the tape.
The only condition I have
is that you forget this whole business
about getting your hands on it
that German friend of yours.
I'm fine with meeting you somewhere
and letting you hear the tape in private
if you want to listen to it by yourself.
I think that you should want to listen to it.
I think you should hear it for your nephew
who lived in 511 Kinderheim.
You should listen closely to what exactly
that boy Johan said on your precious tape.
- So that's the deal you're willing to make?
- I didn't say anything about making a deal.
- That's enough!
We don't have time to be going on and on like this.
As we sit here discussing the finer points of some deal,
an innocent person could be killed because of that tape!
Tell me, how many people that were somehow involved with the Czechoslovakian secret police
have been killed because of that connection?
And just who do you think killed them? Any idea?
I know exactly who this relentless killer is.
It's a person who wants the tape more than anyone.
It's Johan!
What are you trying to say?
I haven't the faintest idea what you're talking about.
Don't you play dumb with me.
Your German friend who wants you to track it down
should have told you what kind of tape it is.
So what is he hoping you're going to find?
The monster's identity. That was all.
I didn't want to get you involved.
But now I'll tell you everything
before anyone else is murdered over this.
I see. So this killer, Johan, has come to Prague searching for his origins to uncover
his past.
That could be. Johan could be here trying to erase his past completely. You created
this mess. What the hell did you do 15 years ago? Back then a mother and her daughter lived
in Mokulski near Chedock Bridge.
Then one day, both of them were taken away
by your secret police.
When your thugs took Johan from the building
with a sign that has three frogs,
what did you do to him?
- These stairs.
Big brother!
- Are you okay, Mina?
- He was taken and dragged down these very steps.
They took him away.
- Who was?
My big brother...
During that time, I was indeed in a position where I could get any of the information I wanted.
But the Three Frogs building, grabbing a mother and a child...
I don't recall any of that.
Don't give me that!
As high-ranking as I was, there were some things even I didn't know about.
Like the things that man did.
We didn't even know which branch of the secret police he belonged to.
Why we couldn't even figure out whose chain of command he was supposedly following.
He was given free reign and detained as many people as he cared to, for no real reason, and never had to report it.
We all wondered to ourselves, "How can he do that?"
He was only the rank of captain, but unbelievably, his office was somehow headquartered in a luxurious mansion.
Ah, yes. He was called "The Man of Red Rose Mansion," I believe.
Are you saying that this captain was involved?
He was a very elegant, quiet man who kept to himself.
He never wore a uniform, and he loved having tea and cake.
What was his real name?
It was Franz Bonaparta.
I see. Bonaparta.
However, I'm not certain if that was his actual name.
Bonaparta was also known to have a pseudonym.
Why would he need one?
Well, you see, he was also the author of a children's book.
Are you afraid of this door?
I... I... I was reading a picture book in here.
Then the door opened. Someone came back home.
Children's book.
That's right. It was a strange picture book.
It was called "The Nameless Monster."
There's nothing in here. Nina...
This memory is real. I've been here before.
I was reading a picture book, sitting here by myself.
But the one who opened the door and came back...
was me.
How could that be?
I was greeting myself.
Welcome home.
[MUSIC]
(dramatic orchestral music)