Are you okay, Mina?
He was taken and dragged down these very steps.
They took him away.
Who was?
My big brother.
Ah, yes.
He was called the Man of Red Rose Mansion, I believe.
What was his real name?
It was Franz Bonaparta.
I see.
Bonaparta.
- I'm not certain if that was his actual name.
Bonaparta was also known to have a pseudonym.
- Why would he need one?
- Well, you see, he was also the author
of a children's book.
- I, I, I was reading a picture book in here.
Then the door opened, someone came back home.
- Children's book?
It was a strange picture book.
It was called "The Nameless Monster".
There's nothing in here.
Nina...
This memory is real.
I've been here before.
I was reading a picture book,
sitting here by myself.
The one who opened the door and came back...
was me.
How could that be?
I was greeting myself.
Welcome home.
[Music]
[MUSIC]
You're looking for Yon-Suk's mother?
Well then, Mrs. Suk is right down the hall in room 409.
I'm sorry to say the poor dear's memory comes and goes in spurts.
You'll have to be patient with her.
(door creaking)
- Yan?
Is that you, dear?
- No.
- Oh my, what a beautiful girl.
Are you one of Yan's little friends?
- That's right.
- You've brought such pretty flowers.
- I'll put them right here.
How about that?
- I have to be very careful
so my Aunt Olga doesn't take them.
She's always coming around poking into my things
and taking what she wants.
She was in here yesterday,
and when I turned my back, she took my favorite doll.
- Well, she sounds perfectly horrid,
but I think she passed away over 10 years ago now.
Don't you remember that?
- Oh, that's right.
I'm surprised at how much you know.
- I've heard a lot from Yan, ma'am.
- I see.
Where is he?
Is it a school day?
Mm-mm.
Oh, of course.
He's already finished with that.
He's a detective.
Everything's fine. Your yawn is alright. There's nothing to worry about.
I like talking to you. You have a sweet face and very kind eyes.
You can tell me about anything you want. Whatever you can remember.
Well, let me think. Katerina next door is very stylish and knows what the latest fashion trend will be even before it's...
Oh, this is so much fun.
It's been a while since I've had such a good time.
I'm glad to hear.
I must think of a way to thank you for your visit.
You don't need to do that.
Actually, though, I was really hoping that you would show me that thing
that Yan recently entrusted you with.
He entrusted me with something?
Yes, a cassette tape.
Of course I remember. There it is.
It never would have occurred to me that you would have sent them to Sook's mother.
It shouldn't take very long.
I'll wait here while you go in and collect the tape and the documents.
Make sure you don't forget about our arrangement.
Remember we did make a deal.
Come on, let's get going, Dr. Tenma.
I'm sorry that I said before this had nothing to do with you, Doctor.
No words can describe how I felt when you told me everything that you've been through.
The last ten years must have been horrible for you.
But this cassette tape may be the key to unlocking the whole story, and you'll be able to prove
When that happens, your entire life will change for the better.
But, Mr. Grimmer, what about your life?
Well, while it is true that I've been on a mission to investigate 511 Kinderheim and what it did to the children,
the truth is...
even if it all becomes clear, it won't lead to any big changes in my life.
(footsteps)
- So you're friends of Mr. Suke
and came to check up on his mother?
At the moment, she seems to be doing quite well.
- Good.
- You know, I think the conversation she had
with her other visitor today
really helped to lift her spirits.
- Other visitor?
What was their name?
- I don't know.
All I remember is she was a beautiful, long-haired blonde.
(grunting)
(panting)
- The tape!
- You actually did come.
I was told to expect you shortly, and here you are.
- The tape, where is it?
- Let me see.
Right here.
"I want to know how Yan's doing."
"At the moment, he's..."
"Take me to the hospital where I can see Yan."
"My Yan is in big trouble, isn't he?"
"My mind is alert and has been very clear since that pretty girl's visit."
"Talking to her reawakened my memories, but it might only last through the day."
"Please let me see Yan."
I will take you to the hospital where you can see your son.
Mr. Grimmer.
Turns out the secret police are willing to make a deal with us.
Mother, you're here.
Oh, Yan, why didn't you call me
so I could have come sooner?
I'm really all right.
It's nothing, nothing at all.
You're making light of it
to try to keep me from worrying, aren't you, dear?
Just like you did the last time.
The last time?
When you were nine years old,
you fell from that tree, don't you remember?
I was so worried,
Nothing was wrong and walked around claiming you felt just fine, but you had badly sprained your ankle
Dear God, please don't ever take him from my mind
Every day my mind slips a bit more so many things are fading away
Lord, let me remember. My son is the best child a mother ever had
Let's go back to that other question again.
What is it that you are the most afraid of?
The monster inside of me is getting bigger.
Munch, munch, chomp, chomp, gobble, gobble, go.
That's enough. I don't want to hear any more.
Regardless, you should listen to this. The nephew that you ended up sending to 511 Kinderheim
went through the same experience as this boy who was drugged and then interrogated on tape.
You should know what that experience entailed. You need to hear this.
I only listened this far into it the other day.
We need to hear more to get the full picture of what happened.
Let's continue on.
What I'm most afraid of, it's forgetting Anna.
The strange lessons we have every day are making my memories fade.
Please.
"Don't make me forget Anna. It's only Anna and me. In this whole world. Just give me that, please. Please. Please."
"That's all I can allow you to hear."
"I don't understand. Who's this young man talking on the tape?"
"What did he do? Did he erase the rest of the old recording?"
He didn't erase it, he taped over what was already there!
After listening to this tape, I finally figured it out.
Did the person who visited Sook's mother before record this?
Whose voice is it?
Dr. Tenma, what do you think?
I know this voice. It's what Johan sounds like today.
Where I must go...
I finally figured it out, Dr. Tenma.
He's on vacation?
That workaholic?
I can't believe it.
It's his first vacation since he started working here.
Well, it's not like we're especially busy right now.
Even for an elite officer of the BKA, he pushed himself too hard.
He just doesn't know his limits.
His wife and daughter left him because of that.
So, where's the inspector spending his vacation, anyway?
He said something about Prague and the Czech Republic.
But I wonder if he even knows how to relax.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE]
What would you like to drink, sir?
Just coffee.
Very well.
Wait a minute, I'm forgetting that I'm on vacation.
Make it a beer.
What kind of beer is this, waiter?
It's a local brew, and it's quite popular.
♪ ♪
[slurping]
You actually believe this investigative report will satisfy the public?
We don't know where Detective Suk is, and we can't prove that the Czechoslovakian secret police are involved.
If we release these half-baked results, the media will eat us alive!
There's a problem. All the people who would have been able to help us with this are dead now.
Blaming the dead doesn't let us off the hook. It's not that simple.
The public demands that we do a complete investigation.
- Yes, sir.
- If you understand, then go uncover something!
And while you're at it, find Detective Suk.
Immediately!
- Yes, sir.
- Whoops, excuse me.
There's someone here who would like to meet with you, Chief.
- You know I don't see anybody without an appointment.
Besides, now is just not the right time.
- But, I, well...
- Huh?
Oh, Inspector.
Well, this certainly is a surprise, Inspector Lungay.
We met each other at the Interpol conference.
I remember we had a very interesting conversation, and I was extremely impressed with the lecture
that you gave.
I'm sorry to be interrupting you at such a busy time.
Don't worry about it.
It was nice you dropped by on your vacation.
I am a bit envious, though.
Due to the present situation here, I doubt I'll even get away on a break.
Congratulations, new Chief Nepela.
You must be very busy.
You said it.
If you don't mind, I'd like to ask your advice.
The case we're currently working on
has grown into one big, tangled mess.
It involves a connection between the Prague Station
and the former Czechoslovakian secret police.
It all began when an inspector named Zeman
was found murdered, along with renegade members
of the secret police, which we thought
had been disbanded years ago.
At the time, Inspector Zeman had been conducting a murder
The victim had been running an unregistered orphanage.
We found out afterwards both Zemon and the orphanage director
had ties to the secret police.
This all happened before I took charge of this division.
Do you have any leads on the murderer?
A man named Grimmer, who discovered the orphanage director's body,
has surfaced as the leading suspect,
but the children saw someone else leaving the crime scene
immediately after the incident happened.
Who's the other person?
A pretty blonde woman.
That was just the beginning. This case has expanded.
Here's what we do know.
The former station chief and two of his veteran detectives were found murdered,
killed with poisoned candies.
As it turns out, those three dead officers
were involved with the Czechoslovakian secret police as well.
Do you know who gave them the poisoned candies?
We suspect a young detective named Jan Suk, who reported directly to Zayman.
Do you have any proof?
No, I'm afraid we have nothing conclusive.
But two detectives recently assigned to this division by a special investigative task force were found shot to death in detective Sook's apartment
very interesting
So where's detective Sook now right now his whereabouts are unknown
The circumstantial evidence all points directly to Sook, but you're wondering if he has a sufficient motive
Yes, that's true. And he's not the kind of man who would normally commit such a crime
Yes, but uh, how do you know what kind of man he is?
Let's just say that I know of a very similar case.
I'm impressed.
Even while on vacation, your hand tells me you're focused on work.
You know how to objectively amass data.
I remember when listening to your lecture.
I was impressed when you said you can perform a completely subjective investigation,
and at the same time that you somehow get into the head of the killer in question.
Can we try it?
What would you be thinking and where would you be right now, Inspector, knowing that
law enforcement is looking for you?
I'm sorry, but I just can't.
I'm on vacation.
I need time off for myself.
Oh, please forgive me.
I should be apologizing to you.
So, are you enjoying our beautiful city?
Mostly I've been visiting second-hand bookshops.
Bookshops you say?
Looking for something in particular?
Yes, and I searched thirteen stores for it.
But I finally came across one that had it.
Actually, I came here today to ask if you could translate this check into German when you had some free time, but it appears as though you're too busy.
Oh, I see. It's a picture book. I'm surprised. I never would have imagined you were into such things.
Leave it with me. I'll have one of my officers translate it by tomorrow.
Who is it for? Your child? Or maybe a grandchild?
Well, yes. I suppose it would be something like that.
Hey, Suke is an honest guy.
As his friend, I believe without a doubt that he is completely innocent.
Look, the police already asked me a whole bunch of questions,
but I know he's not guilty, no matter what they're trying to imply.
If you're in law enforcement, you've got to help him.
Make them listen to you.
If it will do you any good, we'll give you as much information as we can.
Unfortunately, I'm only here on a vacation,
so my influence is rather limited.
[SIGHS]
Were there any other people he was particularly close to?
He was working on getting this girl to go out with him.
Yeah, but so far, he'd only gotten
her to give him her name.
Hey, do you remember what it was?
Anna?
Yeah, that's right.
Her name was Anna Liebert.
She had blonde hair, and she was drop-dead gorgeous.
He was really happy.
He thought things between them were going pretty well.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Anna Liebert, one of the twins that
survived when the East German diplomat and his family
were murdered 10 years ago.
I don't think there's anything left now.
I remember that Emil Scherbe's "The Nameless Monster"
was one of the books we published years ago.
But if it was published during the old regime,
president of this publishing house.
Is it possible that Emil Scherbe was a pen name?
You're right.
Matter of fact, I believe it was.
Come to think of it, he had other pen names as well.
It was something Bonaparta, Jakob Farabek,
and, uh, I think Klaus Poppe.
Klaus Poppe's box is right here.
Oh, you found something?
That's a surprise.
May I open it?
Sure, go right ahead.
I'm sure it's all just a mountain of old sketches anyway.
A pregnant woman.
birth to a girl.
They were twins.
I see. You were able to get it translated for me.
Thank you, Chief Nebula. I do appreciate it.
Oh, there's something I've been wondering about.
If you don't mind, could you do me one more favor
and read the last paragraph of the book to me now?
Uh, let me see.
"At last he had found a name,
"but there was no longer anyone around to call him by it.
"Such a shame, because Johan was such a wonderful name."
My goodness, what a peculiar book.
Johan.
So, Inspector Lungay, how about having dinner with me sometime?
I, uh, never thought to ask, but how long is your vacation?
You there.
Uh, yes?
Cancel the beer and make that a coffee instead.
I think it's going to be a long vacation.
(dramatic music)
(gentle music)