Bad boy, you're such a troublemaker.
How many times are you going to pretend to run away from here?
You do that again, and you'll get no dinner, understand, Miloš?
All right.
You get your hands out of your pockets when you talk to me.
Okay.
You really mean it?
Yeah, it was that blonde lady.
So you said you saw her walking on Dominican Street, that right?
It could be that she lives on that street.
Yeah, so why didn't you follow her all the way home and find out?
Her stomach was growling like a tiger!
Here's the deal, guys.
It's up to us to go find out where that blonde lady lives and turn her in to the police.
Yeah. Mr. Grimmer didn't kill Mr. Pedrov.
We've got to prove his innocence.
Prove his innocence?
If we can do that, will it save Mr. Grimmer?
Sure. We're figuring out how to do that right now.
Come on, Meemosh. Hurry up and eat your food.
[Groan]
[Gasp]
(eerie music)
(choral music)
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- The first incident occurred right up there.
Petrov's illegal orphanage was in this building.
Someone went up there and shot down
the former 511 Kinderheim director in cold blood.
lived there said that a blonde woman walked past them right after it happened.
Pedrov was continuing his experiment here, but he did the complete opposite of what was
done at 511 Kinderheim. Instead of mental abuse, the children here were raised with
love. So tell me, you want to go in and take a look? The police have probably already carded
away everything in terms of evidence.
Wait, what are those on the door?
Mr. Officers, Mr. Grimmer is innocent.
Mr. Detectives, the blonde woman is the murderer.
It's those orphans.
The children who used to live here
must have come back and posted these notes on the door.
From Mr. Grimmer.
Milan Bocek.
It's a famous soccer player's trading card.
Those boys, that card is priceless.
- So, how should I react to this?
I mean, what kind of expression
should I make in this situation?
All of my emotions were taken from me at 511 Kinderheim.
After that, I had to attend another school
where I was taught what were
appropriate emotional responses.
Situations like this are very difficult for me.
What's the correct way to react to this gift?
Perhaps you should go and pay those children a visit.
So, you're Mr. Grimmer.
It seems like I'm always hearing the boys say such nice things about you.
The children are out playing in the neighborhood.
They haven't come back yet.
They really should be back by now.
Oh, here, look at this.
Find the children's journal entries, or rather a lot of letters that they've written to you.
"Mr. Grimmer, let's play soccer again."
"Mr. Grimmer, I'll teach you how to play soccer since you're not very good at it."
"Mr. Grimmer, I can't wait for us to play together again."
Right now, I'm still smiling, aren't I?
You know, I had to learn how to do this.
I actually had to learn how to put a convincing smile on my face.
I really only spent an afternoon with those boys, yet they have fond memories of that
time I shared with them.
Why do they seem to care about me?
That's because they admire you.
They probably like you.
They like me?
You know, Doctor, I've never understood these things, not really.
I didn't even know how to react when my own child was dying.
I was asking so many questions of myself.
Should I cry in this situation?
How much should I cry?
Should I wail out loud or gnash my teeth?
Even now, I still don't know how to react to it.
I wish I did.
Mr. Groomer, we need to talk to you!
Antonin, what's going on?
- We got bad news! - What is it? What's wrong?
We just heard something from the kids at Chesky Orphanage! It's terrible!
Just calm down, take a deep breath, and tell me what happened.
They found that blonde lady! We saw that one day!
Yesterday, we all decided to go out and try and find her.
And then, poor Milos...
Well, he's gone! Milos has disappeared!
I see. How interesting.
I'll give you all the people who have come to visit you here.
A certain middle-aged gentleman,
a long-haired Japanese man,
and a tall German man.
That's right.
There's one more thing.
I think you may have forgotten another person who came to see you.
According to the desk nurse,
a long-haired blonde woman came to visit you recently as well.
A woman?
No, there weren't any women who came to visit.
Well, the nurse said she was certain there was.
She said she was a beautiful blonde.
Yes, she was very beautiful.
But that was definitely a man.
I see.
So tell me, what's your name?
I'm Milosh.
I wonder, have we met somewhere before?
Huh?
Uh-uh.
What were you doing when I saw you?
Nothing.
I know your face. You walk around this neighborhood a lot, don't you?
What is it you're looking for?
I... look for... my mom.
Why don't you have a seat and make yourself comfortable? Here, have some juice.
So, are you about to move out?
Why do you ask?
Because you have that big bag, and there's no stuff in this room.
So your mother, she's somewhere around here?
Huh?
Your mother. You told me you were looking for her, isn't that right?
Yeah, but I don't really know if she lives here.
Then how will you find her? Do you have her picture?
Uh-uh. How come?
Too bad. You don't even know her face.
I'll know her. I'll know my mom when I see her face.
No one at the orphanage believes me either.
They all keep telling me it's not gonna happen.
But when I see her, I'm gonna know her face for sure.
Count on it!
Really?
Yeah. And my mom will know it's me when she sees me.
"Even if you did find your mother, what if she acts like she doesn't know you?"
"Huh?"
"Think you were born because you were wanted?"
"I mean, why were you abandoned?"
"Could it be that your mother left you because she hated you?"
"No way!"
There's nothing special about being born not a thing
Most of the universe is just death nothing more
In this universe of ours the birth of a new life on some corner of our planet is nothing but a tiny insignificant flash
Death is a normal thing
So why live?
You think you were wanted
(eerie music)
- Who wanted you?
So what is your reason for living?
Tell me.
- You're asking about a beautiful,
long-haired blonde woman?
Oh, that would be Anna.
- What?
Anna?
- So that young woman, Anna,
would you happen to know if she lives in this neighborhood?
- Yeah.
I think Anna lives in a three-story apartment building.
Go down this alley. It should be about two blocks down.
She's a very friendly, nice young lady.
She always says hi to me when she sees me.
Anna? Uh-huh.
She's such a nice girl.
She always has a warm hello and a smile for me.
What's her apartment number and which floor does she live on?
Oh, up there.
That's her apartment window on the top floor.
So if what the boys told us earlier is true, and it turns out the woman who lives here actually did kidnap Milos, and she happens to be a young blonde lady named Anna, then she just might be the one...
You're right. And if this young blonde woman is the person I think she is, I swear this will end here and now.
Looks like we're too late.
There's no sign of Milos anywhere.
She took him, didn't she, Doctor?
God, he was out actively looking for that blonde woman to try and prove my innocence.
"What should I do now? If you know, tell me. How is a person supposed to react to a situation this terrible?"
"Those boys got involved in all this because they were trying to prove my innocence."
"You can't blame yourself for everything. The boys told you that Milos usually walks around the streets of Prague. He's always out there searching for his mother."
"He must care for his mother an awful lot."
I don't have feelings like that.
When my son died, I didn't feel anything.
Many years ago, while I was working for a newspaper,
a female coworker suddenly came up to me one day
and told me that she loved me.
I ended up marrying her.
I'd been told that I'd be less likely
to be suspected of being a spy if I were married.
It'd be a good cover.
Soon she got pregnant.
She gave birth to a healthy baby boy.
went shopping and left me alone with the baby. My son was in his room taking a nap, and when
I went in to check on him, he was face down and had stopped breathing. I began giving
him CPR right away, and I called the doctor at the same time. I did everything I should
have done to help him. I did it perfectly, but my son died anyway.
At my son's funeral, my wife was so angry with me. She said, "How can you stay so calm
Why aren't you crying? Didn't you love him?
You've always been cold like that.
You've never shared your feelings with me, not once.
Look at you, you're a heartless machine, you can't love anyone.
You have nothing in your heart and you have no love for me.
And then my wife left me.
I have to find Miloš.
You told me that Miloš is the child of a prostitute
who worked in a big red light district near the Czech border, didn't you?
I did.
The blonde woman we're looking for is the person I suspect it is.
I don't think she's going to let Milos live.
What's worse, she won't just kill him quickly.
If this turns out to be who I think it is,
they'll confront Milos with the cruelest thing possible before finishing him off.
Follow this road. It will take you to Germany.
Will I see my mom?
The chances are good. There's a lively town up ahead.
You think that my mom's up there?
I'm going to wait right here for you. You go ahead on your own.
You'll know who your mother is when you see her,
and your mother will know just who you are when she sees you.
But listen, if it should happen that nobody calls out to you,
then that means you aren't wanted by anyone in the world.
What will you do with yourself then?
...
What will you do?
We'll go on, then.
I'm coming, Mom!
(crickets chirping)
- The cruelest thing, God.
(upbeat music)
- Thank you, ladies.
Thank you.
What is it, kid?
What do you want?
- I'm looking for someone.
- Well, spit it out.
Who are you looking for?
- My mom.
- Your mom?
That's a good one.
- What's so funny, mister?
- Nothing, no, actually, I know your mom personally.
- What?
You do?
Show me where she is.
- Well, that's hard to do.
There's so many places she could hide.
She could be anyone,
any one of 50 women.
(laughing)
- Oh my God, it's you.
My boy.
It's you.
- Huh?
Who are you, lady?
It's alright now.
Wait, I'm looking for my mom.
I feel so good. Just let me hold you like this.
What do you think you're doing without Brat?
You're acting like he's your kid, so is he?
Of course not.
You know I don't make mistakes that big.
Sure, I guess you got the clap on purpose.
Shut up! You got a problem? Come here, you!
What do you-- hey!
Let go of my hair!
Wait, hold on.
No, not here.
I paid you, didn't I?
I'm the customer.
You do as your customer says.
Let's go get a room, yeah?
Come on, stop!
There's a kid over there!
Oh.
Hang on.
Don't run away yet.
Stay here and watch.
I'm a schoolteacher in Germany.
At school, I have a spotless reputation.
I'm a gentleman, as well as a respected teacher.
Everyone thinks I'm a wonderful teacher.
I am a wonderful teacher!
Here, this is for you.
Think you were born because you were wanted?
Hey, kid. Got cash?
Are you sick, lady?
Yeah. I'm gonna die soon.
Well, why don't you go inside?
I can't. Because I'm dying and I have no money.
Give me some money, please.
Well, all I have is this.
Most of the universe is just death. Nothing more.
You think you were wanted?
Think you were born because you were wanted?
(thunder rumbling)
- I get it now.
I get it now.
(panting)
- This is it.
The district ends here.
I know, but they said they saw Milosh wandering around.
Should we go ahead and turn back?
I mean, he might still be in town, right?
Milosh?
Hey Milosh, it's all right. Everything is fine
Hey
Why don't you come back over here, huh?
Did your best you tried to clear my name didn't you?
I'm so lucky to have a friend like you
There's nothing to worry about here we go
It's all right, everything's all right.
Is this good, Dr. Tenma?
Am I doing it right?
Would it have been better if I'd been crying?
They never bothered to teach me such a difficult emotion.
Why did you do that?
Milos, what's wrong? What did you see? What happened, Milos? What did you witness? What
did you find out tonight? Milos, listen to me. I know that you have no mother, but son,
listen, we're definitely born for a reason. I want you to know that. Milos, you were brought
Someone wanted you to be here, definitely.
Someone definitely wanted you here.
I mean it.
Definitely.
(sobbing)
Dr. Tenma, I'm telling the truth.
I'm not wrong, am I?
- No, you're not.
- What expression do I have on my face right now?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're crying.
[MUSIC]
(dramatic orchestral music)