Oh, that mansion. Go right up the street, you should be able to find it.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
You're welcome.
(birds chirping)
Roses, huh?
Just like the castle in "Sleeping Beauty."
(choral music)
(upbeat music)
"It's Anna.
My name is Anna Liebert.
You go get him, Mr. Detective.
It's because she was worried that something awful might happen to you.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I...
I care about you.
(Hana groaning)
- Hana.
- Were you dreaming just now, Detective Suk?
- Hold on, who are you?
- Inspector Lunge.
I work out of the German BKA office.
- What do you want with me?
- Calm down.
You don't have to get up, relax.
Nobody sent me to arrest you.
I haven't even met with anyone in your division.
You've been assigned a very nice room.
I went to several hospitals that had connections to the former Czechoslovakian secret police before finding this one,
and judging by your excellent care, you must be a pretty important person
to the Czechoslovakian secret police, am I right?
I'm not. Please believe me.
I know everything you've been up to since you joined the Prague Division.
Inspector Zeman, who had close ties to the secret police, was beaten to death.
The Prague station chief and two detectives were killed with poison whiskey bonbons.
Two investigators from a special task force who were tailing you were found shot.
And at the moment, you're being pursued as the most likely suspect in all of these cases.
If you were to be judged on circumstantial evidence alone, then you'd be the murderer.
No, I'm not! I'm completely innocent!
Then what about that thin, lanky fellow named Grimmer
who Inspector Zemon brought in for questioning the day before his murder?
Mr. Grimmer didn't kill anybody either. He's not that kind of person!
So then, who is the killer?
Don't you know him?
Don't you know who the murderer is?
What is this? What are you talking about?
If I knew who it was, this wouldn't be happening to me.
My God, so many people have stabbed me in the back.
Now I find myself being framed for murder,
and all the police want to do is lock me up.
I've had enough of this!
Dammit, I'm so tired of being betrayed!
You're a detective, aren't you?
Act like it.
You have to calmly dissect and scrutinize everything.
Dig up the truth as rationally as you can,
even if you have to sacrifice your own happiness
There is really only one way to prevent yourself from being betrayed.
All you have to do is doubt the person you believe in the most.
Who the hell said you had permission to be here?
I want a meeting with your boss.
Tell him I want to talk to him about the Red Rose Mansion.
It's safe to say he'll want to meet with me right away.
Inspector Lungay of the BKA.
I ran a background check. Dug up some of your past.
I heard about your past too when the old regime was in power, Captain Lankay.
are for all intents and purposes leader of the Czechoslovakian secret police.
That's quite a position. Seems to be some trouble attached to you at the moment.
Why, thank you for your concern.
I'm envious of people in your position who can take such long vacations.
Two years ago, wasn't it? Your relentless ways drove the secretary of Mr. Boltzmann,
a candidate to lead the German Democratic Party, to suicide.
You have to be a lot smarter than that to move up in the world.
You and your people were quite foolish.
During the democratization,
if you had taken a softer approach and managed your secrecy,
you could have been the ones controlling the president's actions behind the scenes.
However, now the fear that people feel towards you and your men
is merely an illusion with no basis in fact.
So I see, you are quite clever.
You asked to see me. So what does a clever man like you want?
An answer. As you already know, I'm on a long vacation, but it's not entirely just a pleasure trip.
I'm here looking for something.
I'm looking for an embodiment of true fear.
I want to find out if a real demon was born in that illusion that you created during the reign of the old regime.
"Ah, you're referring to the Rose Mansion, aren't you?"
I found it, but before I got there, I wandered around quite a bit.
The man who wrote this picture book years ago used many pen names.
The name he used when he wrote "The Nameless Monster" was Emil Scherbe.
His address was a room in an old building in Prague.
At the moment, someone else is renting that room.
As Klaus Poppe, he lived on a farm, deep in the countryside.
But that place has already been torn down.
The Jakob Farabäck name only led me to a rented office.
But you didn't stop there, did you?
You finally arrived at Franz Bonaparta's.
Strange place to live, the Rose Mansion.
Franz Bonaparta.
he was. No matter how hard I searched, I wasn't able to turn up anything on him. That could
only mean one thing, that Bonaparta was one of you. That he's a former member of the Czechoslovakian
secret police. Tell me what it is you want to know. That's simple. I want to know everything
you know? I know nothing. However... However? There is something I've consciously been trying
to forget. And that is the fact that the Rose Mansion ever existed at all. I've avoided
thinking about it. That's why it still stands there, empty and untouched. All of the political
prisoners who were taken there, as well as the entire research staff, just disappeared
one night. I swear, that's all I know.
What's the reason for the plastered wall?
What wall?
I went in yesterday. There was no sign of anyone setting foot in there. The mansion
was completely unoccupied and looked to have been abandoned for some time.
But, the north wall on the second floor,
it looks like it was coated with plaster as though someone was trying to conceal something.
With your permission, I'd like to tear that wall down.
Captain Lenke, what are you afraid of?
I'm afraid you might die.
If you get any closer, you and I may end up facing an unimaginable experience of true fear.
(grunting)
(guns firing)
[FOOTSTEPS]
(eerie music)
(engine revving)
- Franz Bonaparta.
Goodness, haven't heard that name in a while.
- Oh, black is just fine, thank you.
What's the matter?
- Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm surprised that a Franz Bonaparte fan
has just suddenly shown up.
- I got your name from the Moravia Publishing Company.
It is my understanding that you were
Mr. Bonaparte's editor for several years.
Is that right, Mr. Zoback?
- It is.
I guided him and helped him as his editor,
but that was only when he was writing
under the pen name Klaus Popper.
I wonder if you can tell me more about him, like what kind of person he was.
He would come here to my home. We would discuss his work and sometimes rewrite sections of it.
Ah yes, he'd sit in that chair in the same position you're in now.
Often he would take a break and play in the garden with my daughter.
I didn't think anything of it at the time, but my daughter said something strange.
She said, "Papa, that man is scary."
Of course, she was very young, and now she's a full-grown adult.
I'm sure she's forgotten all about it.
At that time, could he have possibly been working for a government agency?
Well, probably.
I did assume that, but it was never discussed.
However, there was something about him.
I guess it was his manners, the way he spoke, the clothes he wore,
from the officials of the old regime.
Bonaparta was a practicing psychiatrist
and also a medical doctor.
He specialized in neurosurgery.
Oh, I see.
I'm trying to remember his last visit.
It was the summer of '81 or '82, I believe.
I recall that he just showed up here one day
without any warning.
He wanted to talk about a new book.
Oh my goodness. How happy he appeared to be at the time.
The new book. What was it about?
Well, it was about a monster falling in love.
It was strange. It was almost like a combination of Beauty and the Beast and Sleeping Beauty.
Of course, I vetoed it on the spot.
Then, at the door, as he was preparing to say goodbye,
He just stopped and said, "Maybe you'll like this better."
Then he turned to look me in the eye.
"It's a story about a door that must not be opened
under any circumstances."
I asked him if paradise was on the other side
or if a monster would come through the door.
And he said, "No, you can't open the door,
so I guess there's no story."
He laughed when he said that, and then he was gone.
And that was the last time I ever saw him.
So, Dr. Tenma, were you able to find out anything interesting or helpful about Bonaparta?
A little, but not as much as I hoped.
Mr. Grimmer, what are you doing here? Have you been following me around?
Perhaps. I'm just sitting here enjoying the sunny weather. It's nice.
You can say that again.
I knew it was him.
Is this the police department?
My name is Zoback.
I live on Schweig Court in a private residence.
A suspicious man just left my home.
Well, I'm pretty certain he's the primary suspect
in the serial murders that occurred in Germany.
Yes, he's Japanese.
And he looks like that neurosurgeon, Dr. Tenma.
(eerie music)
- Ethanol.
The smell of disinfectant.
(gun firing)
(grunting)
(eerie music)
(dramatic music)
- Death.
How many people died here?
10?
Or 20?
I guess a lot more.
(grunting)
(eerie music)
- I've seen that woman before.
She's the one from the sketchbook.
Could she be the mother of the twins?
Hurry up, or the older boys will take over the field first!
Come on, Milosh! Hurry up!
I am hurrying!
Go! Launch a counter-attack!
Uh-oh!
Fall back! No one's defending the goal!
Oh no, we're gonna score!
Hey! Huh?
Milosh!
Oh man, are you alright?
- Hey, really nice save, Miloš! - You defended a goal! Good job, Miloš!
Huh?
He seems to be happy. He's all right now, isn't he?
Well, Dr. Tenma, what do you think?
He's fine.
[footsteps]
Mr. Grimmer, wait up.
Don't you want to spend some time with Milos and the other children?
[footsteps]
I suddenly realized why I'm not really all that good at soccer.
I guess it has to do with playing as a team.
I'm just thinking about what lies ahead for Detective Suk.
He's the prime suspect in a murder,
His future is pretty much washed up as well. It's sad.
Even if he were to turn himself in, how's he going to be able to prove that he's innocent?
And how is he going to find any evidence to verify that the blonde lady I saw leaving his place even exists?
Suke's in a similar situation to the one you're in.
Except for him, there's one big difference.
What?
Time for us to say goodbye, Dr. Tenma.
Only one person knows it all.
everything concerning the events incriminating Detective Suk.
You're looking at him.
Here, give it a read.
I think the police will be very interested when they get it.
What is this?
Just a letter written by the perpetrator of the recent series of killings.
I even mentioned details the police haven't released.
I think it'll make a very compelling case for my being the real murderer.
What? If you send something like this to the police, you'll be arrested!
Ah, but before that can happen, Grimmer will suddenly disappear.
The police will be swift, but Grimmer will have already made his brilliant escape to Germany, say.
After all, he used to be a pretty good spy who could slip his way out of tight spots.
Think about it. You'll have no life. You'll be forced to live on the run!
I'll be fine.
"The truth of the matter is, Grimmer never really existed in the first place. It's not who I am. It's just a name I was arbitrarily assigned one day. So even if Grimmer is a suspect for the rest of his life, the real me is unaffected."
"Well, anyway, what do you think of my letter? Do you think the police will buy it?"
"Uh, never mind."
"I guess now you'll be heading off to that Rose Mansion, am I right?"
- That's right.
- You're almost at the finish line.
Your search might be coming to an end any minute.
- I don't know.
I can't be sure.
- Even if I tell you not to do anything rash,
I suppose you won't listen.
Just be careful.
- Mr. Grimmer, remember what you said
when we parted at the Czech border?
Let's have a picnic when we meet again.
We'll fish for rainbow trout on a beautiful day,
and have good wine and cheese.
I'm holding you to that.
Hmph. For the rest of my natural life, that sound is going to haunt me at every turn.
Come on, slowpoke! Hurry up! You want to be late!
I hurt my knee! It's bleeding a lot! It really hurts!
Don't be scared. Let me just see if you can move it.
It's only a scrape, but I'll put some antiseptic on it so it doesn't get infected.
Tough it out. You're a big boy. You can handle it.
That's better. You're very brave.
You're Kenzo Tenma, is that correct?
Prague Police, we have orders to take you to the station.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)