Why are you crying?
It's just my friend's letter.
My very best friend.
When I was 15, the two of us decided to cross the Czech border together, but my friend was
captured and she was taken back to Prague.
She says she's doing fine.
She's been such a good friend, she knows me better than my parents do, or even my siblings.
With the government's tough inspections and censorship, who knows what she went through to get this to me.
She says, "Please visit me if you have the chance. I miss you so much, my friend."
Near Jeddak Bridge, inside the Three Frogs.
"I want to go back... to Brock."
- Oh, Margo.
- Say...
Just for tonight,
I want you to call me by my real name.
I am Helenka Novikova.
For tonight, I'm no longer Margot Langer.
(upbeat music)
I sold my stock holdings in Reiserberger Pharmaceuticals at the right time.
And then, when I bought some stock in Neuter Laboratories, I really hit the jackpot.
Well, I wanted to celebrate, so I did.
So you had a drink.
Sure, just a little.
That wasn't too smart.
All I had was one drink.
For an alcoholic like yourself, that was a foolish choice you made.
it doesn't matter if you drink a little or a lot.
Another thing that concerns me is it seems you've stopped going to your group meetings as well.
So, um, by the way...
Doctor, you can keep a secret, right?
I've got this special woman I want you to meet.
Have you gone and found yourself another mistress?
Not really. Look, this one's got a serious issue with alcohol.
She's waiting just outside. Could you see her for a minute?
Have her make an appointment to see me.
- Come on, just see her for a few minutes.
- I'm making a house call next for a very important client.
I took a few days and went to Prague in the Czech Republic.
I found it a very nice city to visit.
I saw Prague Castle.
Oh, and the wonderful Gothic cathedrals.
It's such a beautiful place when the old town plaza is all lit up.
It's just like a land out of a fairy tale.
- What about Cheddark Bridge?
Did you go and visit the Cheddark Bridge?
- I did, exactly as you told me to do.
Here it is.
See, I took a picture of the sign with the three frogs.
- And the woman, was she there?
- No, sir, in fact, no one was living there.
Unfortunately, I didn't find any useful information
for you by going there.
It was so frustrating.
and find Tenma, or any good leads on Dieter and Nina.
- Here, take this.
It's a rabbit's foot.
It's for good luck.
Now listen, please give it to our child after it's born.
Margo, no.
Helenka, you must know.
I thank you.
Excuse me, ma'am. I've come from Germany, and I'm searching for a missing woman who
might have lived around here a while ago. Do you know a young woman by the name of Margo
Langer? Wait, sorry, her real name was Helenka Novikova.
- (gasps) Helenca.
- Anyway, Mr. Shuvald, your son Carl
recently gave me a call.
He expressed some concerns to me
about the fact that you haven't been eating properly.
I'd classify that experience you had
at the library fire as traumatic.
A near-death experience can change one's life, you know.
I sense that paralyzing fear still hasn't left you,
- I'm very blessed to have Carl here with you.
He's a wonderful, thoughtful, and loving son.
You really have nothing more to worry about.
Please do try to eat regularly, won't you?
- The monster.
- Hmm?
- As long as that monster exists, it's so difficult.
How did he know so much about Margot?
Where could he have obtained all that information?
He knew much more than Carl or I did.
Years ago, Margot told me of this girlfriend she had
who knew her even better than her own siblings or parents.
I remember that conversation.
This was the woman who Margot exchanged letters with.
Now, in the 1980s, you began to search for Margot,
who at that time had gone missing.
You went to Prague and actually met that woman, didn't you?
Considering she was supposed to be Margo's best friend,
I assumed that woman might have heard something from her.
I was wrong.
She said she didn't know where Margo was.
But for a while, we did talk quite a bit about Margo
as we stood in the doorway.
And that's when they were listening.
Listening in on every word.
Who do you mean?
They quietly listened to what we said.
They stood behind the woman, absorbing it all.
Those twins.
(knocking)
- Yes, come in.
Welcome, have a seat.
You're the young lady Mr. Thalbach
wanted me to see, aren't you?
And you're a compulsive drinker.
Please just relax.
Today all we're going to do here
is have ourselves a nice, friendly chat.
- Doctor! - What is it, Merith?
Can't you see I'm right in the middle of a session?
He's on TV! It's Dr. Tenma!
Excuse me for a second.
Repeating our breaking news story,
Czech police have announced that they have recently arrested
and taken into custody Japanese Dr. Kenzo Tenma.
It appears Tenma was discovered
while he was attempting to avoid authorities
by hiding in the city of Prague.
He is a witness and possible suspect
in the poisoning of three doctors
at Dusseldorf's Eisler Memorial Hospital.
He may also be connected with the murders
Fortner couple in Heidelberg, and the phantom killing at Heidelberg Castle.
For now, these are all the details we have.
Tenma.
Oh, I'm sorry, ma'am. You're not really allowed in here.
Could you wait outside?
Uh, Ms. Heinemann?
Kenzo.
I'm sorry for being late, everyone.
Why, Mr. Hess, you look ten years younger.
Playing with my grandchildren is keeping me young.
Huber, how you been?
I'm actually finishing up my final academic year.
I hear you're pretty busy too, Mr. Kiefer.
I was bragging about you, saying how I'm friends with a screenwriter.
Who's going to Hollywood?
I just happened to catch the eye of a producer who has a big imagination.
My first story idea's in development, and my mind's brimming with new plot lines.
You're on your way!
You know, that surgery saved my life.
If my surgery hadn't been a success, I wouldn't be here to hear your laughter, thanks to him.
And I never would have walked in the park with my grandchildren. Think of that. Right there.
He always sat over there by himself, drinking his tea.
Other doctors went to nicer cafes, but he came here because it was closest to Eisler Memorial Hospital.
And when we patients would come in here...
He would look at us as he sat there.
And smile at us and wave.
He was the kindest doctor.
Yes.
A great doctor like him.
He would never do this.
No!
And that's the reason why I've gathered all of us here today.
The others who aren't here said they feel the same as we do.
After all, they were Dr. Tenma's patients too.
Bad news, Dr. Schumann!
Mr. Merkel just collapsed, sir!
I'll be right over.
But I'm busy at the moment.
You better go and wait for me there.
All right.
Really? Dr. Temma wouldn't do those things.
Calm down and listen to me, Mom.
Please, dear, go to him quickly.
But, Petra, I can't just...
Don't you give me any buts!
Dr. Temma has been charged with a crime he didn't commit!
If he hadn't been around, you know I wouldn't be alive right now.
My dear Dr. Shuman,
are you so heartless that you don't want to help the man who saved your wife's life?
Then what will happen here?
You know darn well I'm the only doctor in this village.
What'll happen to everyone that lives around here if I go and leave town?
You want to go, don't you?
Quit your blabbering and get going right now!
Dr. Temma needs your help!
I took an oath, and if there's a patient who needs me, I can't just leave him.
That's the way Dr. Tenma would have behaved.
Please, doctor, would you see us now?
Be patient. I need a little more time.
Well, hurry up!
Stop your whining. The doctor's taking a big risk by practicing without a license while she's going to school.
"When you're in the darkness, you only sink deeper into it.
Keep the light shining.
You've got a real gift for this.
You'll make a fine doctor."
"Dr. Tenma..."
All right, I'm ready to start now.
Whoever's first, come in.
Get a lawyer.
Right, but Father, wait.
We still have no way of knowing exactly where in Germany Tenma will be sent.
Then we'll have to retain a lawyer that can defend him in any of the German states.
Get us the best criminal attorney you can.
Yes, sir.
We must help Tenma.
Yet he is the only one who can do it.
He's the only one who can get rid of the monster.
- We need strength in numbers.
- Well, let's try calling in more
of Dr. Tenma's former patients.
- As individuals, what we say may not matter much,
but as a group, we might just--
- That's right.
Let's ask Eisler Memorial Hospital
for help in getting organized,
and we could ask them for funding, too.
- Forget it.
That's impossible.
Eisler Memorial Hospital is not about to help you with something like that.
Hey, I've been listening to all of you, and it's quite a touching story.
Really?
But come on, folks. Be realistic about the situation.
How's the Dr. Tenma fan club going to prove his innocence?
Oh, Dr. Becker, it's you.
You know Tenma had no alibi, and unfortunately, he did have a motive.
The police even came out and said they found physical evidence at the scene of the crime.
Even if you hire a brilliant lawyer to defend him,
and you gather a ton of people to make a lot of noise,
it's not going to help.
No matter what you folks do on Dr. Tenma's behalf,
it's impossible to prove that he's innocent.
Anyway, it's a real shame about his career.
Yeah, it's a real shame.
I'm going to ask you again.
Eva, what's your relationship to Tenma?
Look, Miss Heinemann. I don't know who you are in all of this.
But I'm on this train because I mean to save Dr. Tenma.
So I don't want you coming along if you're here just to do some sightseeing.
Eva Heinemann?
Heinemann! Miss Heinemann!
Are you the daughter of Dr. Heinemann, the murder director of that hospital in Dusseldorf?
Dr. Tenma. He had quite an effect on me. You see, he destroyed my life.
And yet, I'm the only one who can really save him now.
I saw.
Saw what?
Dr. Kenzo Tenma, prime suspect in the serial murders in Dusseldorf and Heidelberg, is still in custody in Prague.
However, officials have said he will be extradited to Germany as soon as possible.
He will most likely be sent to Dusseldorf where the first murder occurred.
No way. That isn't possible. That's him.
But that doctor couldn't have...
This is Dr. Tenma. He's the one who saved your life, Suk.
You're alive right now because of his first aid treatment. It turns out. Dr. Tenma has also been framed for a crime
He never committed. I guess you two are in the same situation, huh?
Tenma saved my life. He's going through the same ordeal as me
You're a detective, aren't you? Act like it. You have to calmly dissect and scrutinize everything
There is really only one way to prevent yourself from being betrayed
All you have to do is doubt the person you believe in the most.
I've got to go.
I've got to get to the Prague police station and talk to Tenma no matter what it takes.
There you are, Suk.
Well then.
Detective Brozek.
Detective Stransky.
Please, listen to me!
You don't have to run away anymore.
My God, you must have gone through a lot.
You've been exonerated, Suk.
A letter was sent to the station.
This is a copy of it.
A letter?
It's a handwritten confession.
It has details of the events that only the killer would know.
So, you've been cleared of all suspicion.
So, who sent that letter?
A journalist who goes by the name of Grimmer.
Yeah, Grammer's been put on our most-wanted list.
He's now our chief suspect.
Wait, just hold on a second.
Relax, Zouk. You're in the clear.
Inspector Zaymont's murder, the head chief's poisoning,
and the shooting of the two special team members
that had tailed you back to your apartment.
All those crimes are now solved.
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
- Bungie, where have you been?
I've been trying to get a hold of you.
Well, Chief, I was doing some sightseeing.
Give me a break. Don't act like I'm stupid.
Stupid? What are you talking about?
Quit the act. Don't tell me you haven't heard the news.
Oh. Are you talking about Dr. Tenma's arrest?
Ha ha. Congratulations, Lungay.
Huh?
You knew it, didn't you? You knew Tenma was hiding out in Prague.
Good work, Lungay. Your persistence in this investigation really paid off.
I just finished talking with the Czech police and they gave me all the details about what they're gonna do with Tenma
Tenma will be arriving in Dusseldorf tomorrow at 2 p.m. Since you're in charge of this case
You'll need to meet the Czech police to take him into custody
Anyway good work Lunga
Congratulations
Dispatch someone else to take care of it. What did you say Prague is a very nice place what?
Please understand sir right now
I'm still on vacation.
Hey, Lungi! What are you talking about? Listen!
Now let me see Dr. Tenma.
As I've been telling you, sir, you cannot see him.
And why not? I thought this country is supposed to be a democracy.
Dr. Tenma is already in the process of being extradited to Germany.
I just need to see him for a minute.
We came all that way for nothing.
All that time and effort, what a stupid waste.
Let me see him! I'm begging you!
On your feet.
Come with us.
When we interrogate people,
what type of person do you think gives us the hardest time?
People who remain expressionless no matter what we say to them.
People who don't say anything at all.
That's the hardest kind.
A love letter from the monster to the beauty.
This appears to be a draft for a novel.
"I've been watching you. I wanted to devour you whole, but instead everything about you
consumed me. When I was falling apart, how did I look to you? When I was falling apart,
the object you gave me, you left me a beautiful jewel, those twins who look as if they are
blessed with eternal life.
The most sinful deed is to take away a person's name.
Let's get your name back.
I'll give you your name back.
Your name is Anna.
Right now, I'm sad, sad, sad, sad.
It exists.
There are many people that met their end in that room.
And then, a horrific monster was born.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)