"My consciousness awoke inside a coin locker. In complete darkness. Blue. The blue skies.
The blue sea. And the blue window frame.
I want to go to Tunisia.
Gunter Milch, arrested in 1988 for attacking a Bayerisch Landesbank cash transport vehicle.
Placed in Badenburg prison to serve time, and in 1991 devised a means of escape, spent
six months filing through the iron bars of his cell with a large nail sharpened into
He was caught three days later and sent to Kreiner Prison.
In 1993, escaped through a drainage pipe.
Prison-issued garments soaked in sewage
were found on a nearby riverbank.
Soon arrested again for the attempted robbery
of a Maximilian & Company payroll delivery truck.
In '97, broke out of Ingeborg Prison
through a hole in a shower stall.
Spent a year digging an escape route with a spoon.
The toilets in this place stink pretty bad.
I escaped through a sewer once, so you better believe I know what I'm talking about.
Shut up!
Talk about looking down and out.
Eyes forward.
Yeah, if I'm not mistaken, that's Dr. Tenma.
Keep walking, pal.
I never imagined that fella would be looking so hopeless and pathetic.
[MUSIC]
I'll ask you one more time.
The poisoning of Dr. Heinemann, Director of Eisler Memorial Hospital, Dr. Oppenheim, Chief
of Surgery, and Dr. Boyer in 1986.
Confirm or deny it, which is it going to be?
From the beginning of this interrogation, you haven't uttered a single word.
Cut the crap, Tenma!
What is this going to accomplish?
The prosecution will go forward whether you keep silent or not.
And you don't stand a chance in court.
Why not talk to us?
Come on, why don't you make things easier for yourself?
What's going on? What's happening down there?
Looks pretty bad. Nosha's got severe stomach pains.
Hey, doctor! Dr. Duller! Has anybody seen Dr. Duller?
He's in the examination room. Apparently Peter drank some kind of cleaning fluid.
I'm heading over there now.
This is bad.
It sounds to me like he might be choking on something.
What?
I can't... I can't breathe...
Oh, man. Guess we have no choice but to ask him.
Huh?
Tenma, the doctor.
Think you can take a look at him, Doc?
Does this hurt?
[GROANING]
And what about here?
I'm going to need plenty of hot water, towels,
and fresh sheets.
Get out of the room.
This could be contagious.
[GASPING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[PANTING]
Why'd you pretend to be sick?
[CHUCKLING]
Come on.
I must be losing my touch. You're the first doctor to see through my act so fast
I had it all figured out if I got sent to the hospital. I'd have a better chance to escape
Do you know what I do when I want to rob an armored truck?
I jump out in front of the vehicle and pretend to be very sick
When the guards run out of the truck in a panic that my friend pops up with an automatic weapon and threatens to shoot him
I've never really killed anybody myself.
That's where you and me kind of differ.
So how about it?
What do you say we escape together?
You've already got the look of a man who's never getting out of here.
But if you stay in this dump, it'll suck the life right out of you.
I despise cramped spaces like this crappy little rat hole.
My consciousness awoke inside a coin locker.
in that total darkness.
My mom and pop would put me there
while they went off to work.
I waited in that darkness
for them to come and take me home each night.
"Let's go to Tunisia someday."
That's what they'd always talk about.
And pop would say,
"If today goes well, we're going to Tunisia."
But three days went by, and they didn't return.
Mom and Pop just left me.
They probably went to Tunisia by themselves.
That's the place to live.
As soon as I blow this joint and I'm out of these,
I'm going to Tunisia.
You're a real mess, you know that?
You look like a guy who's got nothing left to live for.
Unlike me, I got plenty of goals.
What will you do if they catch you again?
I'll just escape again.
I'll keep on doing it, no matter how long it takes.
Now then, I suppose this is going to be just another day of silence?
The truth of the matter.
is even as we speak right now, terrible things are happening.
So I have to tell the truth.
You won't believe it.
You won't believe a word I say.
But that won't stop me. I have to keep fighting.
And I'll keep on doing it no matter how long it takes.
Over and over again.
I'll tell you nothing but the truth.
"This court hereby sentences the defendant to 20 years in prison."
My path in life was chosen on that fateful day, when my father was found guilty.
After the war, my father moved from Sudetenland, Czechoslovakia to Germany, starting a small
radio station there in 1949.
But in the '60s, during the Cold War between East and West Germany, he was arrested for
being a spy and for the murder of a federal politician's
secretary.
This news shocked the West.
My father proclaimed his innocence,
but was convicted to 20 years in prison.
My mother believed in my father's innocence
until her death in 1971.
My father, filled with sorrow and regret,
died in prison a year later in 1972.
In 1973, while I was in the gymnasium,
my father's innocence was proven.
After graduating from Dusseldorf University,
I joined the large firm of Hoffman Law.
In my first case, I defied expectations
and proved the innocence of a falsely accused defendant.
One after another,
my victories in the courtroom continued to grow.
I, Fritz Werdemann, once the son of a spy,
am now a hero in the legal world.
Every day, the broadcast at my father's radio station would begin and end with that song,
"Over the Rainbow."
I see.
Both you and my father lived in the East,
so this song must have symbolized the free world to you.
Yes.
My father died before he was able to prove his innocence.
To honor his memory, I want to be involved in as many cases as possible
where the person standing truthfully and honestly
may be falsely accused.
I want you to tell me everything you know
about Dr. Tenma's case.
Ilsa, how did your prenatal exam go?
What did they say?
Everything's fine.
The doctor said to expect the baby any day now.
Did you pass a man in the lobby on your way up?
Yes. Is he the one you mentioned earlier?
He is. A man by the name of Alfred Ball.
He asked me if I wanted to team up with him on the Dr. Tenma murder case.
Well, if I remember correctly, you already refused to take Dr. Tenma's case.
Mm. But at the time, I was being solicited by Hans Georg Schuwald.
And it wasn't made clear to me then why I was being asked by that business tycoon to be the doctor's legal counsel.
However, the reasons Mr. Ball had were all perfectly clear.
What were they?
Every one of Mr. Ball's clients was a former patient of Dr. Tenma,
and he'd saved the lives of all of them before he went on the run.
And now, I'm certain about one thing.
Dr. Tenma was a well-respected and highly skilled surgeon.
So, are you taking the case?
Yes, but if I had made that decision when the billionaire was footing the bill,
we could have made quite a nice profit.
I doubt these patients will be able to pay nearly as much.
your legal work only for the money,
then you'd have a much larger firm by now.
How about that?
It's playing your song, honey.
- Please turn it off.
- Huh?
- Just turn it off, please.
- Sure.
How about we go out and get ourselves some dinner?
Carrying around another life must make you pretty hungry.
We'd better make sure you order enough food for two.
The baby always kicks when it gets to be dinner time.
So dear, what restaurant would you like to go to tonight?
I don't know.
How about that place we saw last week?
And then he just disappeared into the blazing fire.
And that was the very last time I ever saw Johan.
Do you want me to start my story from the beginning one more time?
Because I'm gonna keep on telling the truth over and over as long as it takes.
You're the fourth one, you know.
The other three who wanted to represent me all had the same suggestion.
That I should confess to some of the charges, admit to part of the crimes, delight in my sentence.
That's all they wanted to talk about.
I'd assumed as much.
It seems to me you don't really care too deeply about proving your innocence.
You apparently would rather spend your time proving the existence of a certain young man named Johan.
Yes, that's right.
Legal expertise won't help with that.
Dr. Tenma, when did these events all start happening?
Like I've been saying, when a boy with a gunshot wound to the head was brought into the emergency--
I know, but something must have happened before that, so what was it?
A Turkish woman was yelling at me.
Give me back my husband!
After all, people's lives aren't created equal.
But human lives are created equal.
Was what I did back then really the right thing to have done?
I just don't know.
There's no way of telling if a patient is good or evil.
My only crime is that I went ahead and saved the life of a little boy.
I don't know.
But...do doctors even have the right to choose who they treat based on the quality of a patient's soul?
People's lives aren't created equal.
They are all equal. I can't explain it, but I know that it's the truth.
It's the same way with lawyers.
We can't tell what kind of a person the accused is.
Here's a list of names of the people who asked me to represent you in these legal proceedings,
Doctor.
Mr. Mikhail Hodder, Mr. Stefan Krump, also Mr. Franz Kiefer, and Mr. Rudolf Huber.
Mr. Kiefer and Mr. Huber, glad to know they're fine.
Mr. Horst Hentschel, Mr. Harmut Hess.
Mr. Hess as well, it's good to hear.
I hope he's enjoying his grandkids, they're his whole world.
Time's up.
Thank goodness for that. They're all okay.
Dr. Tenma, I will accept your case. I'll represent you.
You know, lawyers can't tell what's inside a client's heart either.
There's only one thing we can do when we represent someone.
Try to have faith in him.
One more. Didn't you hear me? I said one more!
Ma'am, you've had enough.
Since when did this bar start refusing to serve its best customer?
Hey! You just laughed at me, didn't you?
No, not at all.
Yes, you did! You looked over at me with a big laugh!
Hey, hey, I know you!
You were always there, coming to our house with your hat in your hand, groveling.
You're the vice branch manager at Nordrein West Bank.
Don't give me that look! I can drink here if I damn well wanna!
Whether you like it or not, Eva Heinemann has returned home to Dusseldorf!
You've certainly brought me a wealth of important information. Thank you, Dr. Reitwein.
Listen, I've been trying to reach you ever since I heard that Dr. Tenma had retained you to represent him.
I'm sorry you had so much trouble. I've been out investigating everywhere.
Investigating?
That's right. I've been meeting with the former patients of Dr. Tenma who hired me on in this case.
Did you learn anything?
Well, just that they think he's wonderful and that they owe their lives to him.
But did you get any evidence that would be useful?
- Not really.
I'm hoping to find a witness or someone
who can provide Dr. Tenma with an alibi.
- In my opinion, to establish Tenma's innocence,
we need to prove to the world that Johan actually exists.
- Listen, Dr. Reichwein.
- What?
- Regarding that part about Dr. Tenma
planning to shoot that young man named Johan,
when you're called to testify, please omit that.
- Huh?
But wait a minute, my testimony about his plan
There is a Johan whether or not Johan exists. Dr. Tenma is innocent
Please hear me out. Dr. Reich vine the country wants this case closed. So any scapegoat will do right now
My child will be born soon. I want him to live in a world where true justice exists
Judges and prosecutors want to bring matters to a close quickly in order to do so
they carelessly rushed to condemn innocent people as guilty.
It's high time this country repented
for its lack of true justice,
and that's what's most important.
Well, Dr. Reichwein?
- Yes, that's right.
- Anyhow, I'm looking for a particular witness at the moment.
- Oh?
- She might know something
which could prove vital to Dr. Tenma's defense.
At least I hope so.
- Who is she?
- None other than my client's former fiancee,
Miss Eva Heinemann.
Is something wrong, Dr. Reikvein? You look surprised.
She's here in town.
Huh?
She came here with me. I guess she's decided to move back.
But that woman...
They were laughing.
Every last one of them was laughing.
They just give me one look and start in.
Ava, are you listening to me?
Quit bugging me. You're so annoying.
Just meet with the lawyer.
Is that for Tenma? Please!
Huh? Your memory's kinda shot, Gramps.
I told you before, I tried to shoot him once, but I couldn't pull it off.
I remember that quite well, but I was surprised to hear it.
But you didn't go through with shooting him.
That's right, I didn't shoot him. Do you know why?
It's because I can't have him die on me yet!
That man ruined my life. A fast death would be too easy.
to rot in jail for eternity to make him regret it.
I'm going to lock him up for the rest of his life.
He'll be sorry he left me when I'm through with him.
Yeah, maybe then he'll regret that he dumped me.
Passed out again.
You were asleep, you must have had a bad dream.
Three shots from the gun, but I didn't see anything.
I...I didn't...didn't see it.
Blond-haired man...blond-haired man...
Ava! Who did you see?
Did you see Johan that night?
"Over the Rainbow."
A song that symbolizes a great free world for all.
Your wife's gone into labor.
- Hello, Mr. Werdemann.
- What?
I've gotta be there.
Mr. Klinger, contact Mr. Ball immediately.
- Right.
- Ask him if he'll be able to meet with Dr. Tenma
in my place, because I'm having a baby.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Alfred Ball.
Mr. Werdemann asked me if I could come meet with you today.
How are you doing?
Getting enough sleep in this place?
- I guess.
- Well, that's good.
Oh.
I used to be right-handed, actually.
I'm still having a little trouble adjusting to holding a pen in my left to write notes.
You see, my right hand doesn't work too well anymore.
Perhaps you remember me now.
I know I've lost quite a bit of weight.
Yep, I gotta admit, I even impressed myself to think that I was able to escape that sea
You caught me by surprise when you actually shot me.
You know, it's kind of funny. I can't seem to hold pens worth a damn, but...
yet I'm able to handle a gun just fine.
To tell you the truth, I'm thinking of killing someone.
I'm thinking of killing your former fiancée,
the lovely Ava Heinemann.
[dramatic music]
[ethereal music]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)