Tell Helene and Gustav that I'm counting on them to tape Detective Forster, the crime
drama on television right now.
Huh?
It's my favorite show.
I'm addicted.
The reruns are on at ten on Tuesday mornings.
Tune in.
You might learn something.
Come on, Mills.
Will you get serious?
You shouldn't be kidding around right now.
The boss isn't happy with your sloppy work.
Do you have any idea how much trouble you caused by screwing up and getting yourself
caught?
If you are a complete idiot, the boss still sent me here to be your legal counsel.
So how about showing him a bit of gratitude?
Come on, who do you think you're kidding? You're here to keep an eye on me so I don't spill the beans, right?
I won't deny it. Listen up, Milch.
I presume you are aware of what would happen if you were to say anything, well, aren't you?
What are you so worried about? I'd never rat on any of my buddies.
That's very smart. I need you to stick to the scenario that I laid out for you and confess, all right?
All right. So has my next job been decided? I'd kind of like to prepare for it.
What do you mean next job? Given your present situation, you won't be getting out of prison anytime soon.
Yeah? How can you be so sure?
What?
Think about it. Did you forget who I am? I'm Gunter Milch, King of Prison Escapes.
*Sigh*
I'm getting way behind schedule, so just stop the nonsense.
If you follow the blueprint I'm drawing up and confess, you'll get out in about five years.
And don't forget to talk to them about that favor.
Huh?
I told you to tell Helene and Gustav to tape Detective Forster while I'm in lockup.
Hmm...
Yeah, but they're not very reliable, are they?
I may have to try it one more time while I'm still at this station jailhouse.
(evil laughter)
(choral music)
(rock music)
[MUSIC]
I don't know he's hard to figure but I did see blood in his vomit and you can feel his body's really cold
Hey, don't throw up in the hallway doctor. Oh, you came just in time. I'm glad you're here
Uh-huh. Keep an eye on this place for a bit
They just brought in a few young punks who went berserk on the third floor
Some people were injured so I need to get up there right away doc
This guy looks like he's gonna die at any moment
You back again Milch just put him on a bed over there. I'll take a look at him later
You'd better get me to a hospital right away before I die!
You'll be fine. I won't be gone long.
Damn, all of a sudden it's getting busy in here today.
Give me a break! You can't put me next to a serial killer!
I know my rights! I demand another bed! Why is he even here?!
The man's refused his meals and collapsed from starvation.
He's hooked up to an IV.
- Oh, I feel a lot worse just being next to him, see?
- Just lie there and be quiet.
- Doctor, you said some people were injured.
Do you have any idea how many?
- That's what I'll find out as soon as I get there.
- Wait till I get my hands on them.
Those punks are gonna do a hard time
when they're here with me.
- I've been thinking about what you said the other day.
I need you to help me.
I have to get out of here.
I'm thinking of killing someone.
I'm thinking of killing your former fiancée,
the lovely Eva Heinemann.
So, what do you think?
Personally, I like the idea very much.
You know, she's dangerous.
She knows a little more than she should.
That rainy night at the building, the one under construction,
she heard three distinct gunshots.
And she saw someone as well.
It was him.
Now we don't need people like her complicating things.
We really don't, don't you agree?
No, you... you can't!
It's not an option Ava would never even think to testify about that
All she wants is to get back at me to make me regret and suffer. She's mad that I left her
She wants me to spend the rest of my life behind bars for that. She'll only testify to things that will hurt me
Do you understand so?
So so that's why you need to take a little more time to consider my idea
She'll be out of the way once and for all and you may not have to go to prison if she's not on the witness
(dramatic music)
This could be very good for both of us.
Elimination is the winning choice,
no matter how you look at it.
I mean, what other options do you have?
If you go to the police,
they won't believe you, an accused murderer.
What are you gonna do, tell Mr. Vertimon?
I wouldn't.
I mean, think about it.
He could be one of us.
Who really knows?
We'll make sure you're found innocent. After all, that's what we brilliant Defense Attorneys do.
And once you're free and moved out of this place, you should have yourself a drink to celebrate.
Because by that time, that miserable, stuck-up, loud-mouthed bitch will be long gone from this world.
Never, ever to be seen again.
I
Want to escape
Hey get me out of here, I'm allergic
I can't sleep with this serial murderer next to me button it milch quit all that squawking
I buttoned it you button it as everyone got all their buttons now. Hey knock it off
They'll be moving me out of this holding station in five days
Then it's goodbye forever to serial murderers like you!
What's all the rocket for, huh?
Pretty fast recovery.
Yeah, just another one of your fake-outs.
I'm gonna be rid of you.
In five days, I'm done looking at your miserable face!
You're a real piece of work, Milch.
Enough already!
Just five more days to go.
So, on that particular rainy night,
from inside a building under construction you heard three gunshots,
and soon afterwards saw a young blonde man come hurrying down the stairs.
Is that correct, Miss Heinemann?
That's right.
Now what's the plan? Are you still proceeding with the case and denying Johan's existence?
I… I don't know.
Listen, Ms. Heinemann,
if I called upon you,
would you be willing to testify to this in open court?
No, I would not.
What could Dr. Tenma possibly want this late at night?
Would you kindly tell us what this is all about?
Well, I don't exactly know. He just asked to see you right away.
So what did you want to talk to us about, Dr. Tenma?
At Dusseldorf's Eisler Memorial Hospital there was the Director, Dr. Heinemann, the Chief
of Surgery, Dr. Oppenheim, and then Dr. Boyer as well, along with one Adolf Junkers, who
It was a patient of mine at the time.
It was me, I confess.
I did it. I killed every one of them.
The wind blew hard, the bottle fell over, the sandwiches were covered in dirt.
That's when he smiled so sadly.
According to this announcement made by the police,
murder suspect Kenzo Tenma confessed shortly before dawn.
Up until now, he had relentlessly kept silent about all the charges against him.
Now, in regard to the killing of the director of Eisler Memorial Hospital in Dusseldorf
and two other doctors, as well as the murder of Adolf Junkers,
he has admitted that he committed these crimes.
But that can't be!
This is breaking news.
He confessed? Why would he?
Kenzo Tenma, who had previously maintained total silence about the charges,
surprised authorities with his unexpected confession to the string of serial killings.
I want the truth!
Hey, what the hell did you idiots do to Tenma?!
What method of torture did you subject him to in order to obtain that false confession?!
Please take your hand off me and calm down.
I am calm, dammit! Just take me to Dr. Tenma!
I'll talk to him myself and find out what kind of treatment he received during his questioning!
It's useless, Dr. Reitwein.
I've already tried. He won't even see me, his own lawyer.
It would appear that his confession was completely voluntary, without any coercion.
But that's impossible!
I did a little research. It turns out that his interrogators are men I know personally.
And these are men who would never condone the use of torture.
Tenma summoned them both when he made his declaration.
Then he proceeded to willingly admit his guilt.
Wait, Mr. Werdemann. You're actually suggesting his confession to the murders is genuine?
How can I even begin to tell what he intended when he won't meet with me?
Mr. Werdemann, you've got to believe.
Dr. Tenma didn't commit murder.
I still believe he's innocent.
Hello, this is Werdemann.
Oh, Mr. Ball.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to be there, but some urgent business came up that couldn't wait.
That's all right.
How did it go? Were you able to talk to Dr. Temma?
No. He refused to have anything to do with me.
What can I say? I'm stunned.
Here we are in the middle of an effort to prove his complete innocence,
working hard to get them to drop all the charges they have against him,
then he breaks down and fully confesses.
In that regard, your father was very admirable.
No matter how unbearable his interrogation got, he never once capitulated.
Your father held steadfast to his innocence.
And he was innocent.
So then, any idea of what we should do now to help out Temma?
Mr. Vertema?
Anyhow, that woman, the key person who could prove Dr. Temma's innocence, what did you say her name was?
Oh, Eva Heinemann.
Right, and where is she now?
She's staying at a local hotel.
I'd certainly like to meet her and hear what she has to say.
Well, she can be a pretty difficult lady.
I think for now I'll try meeting with her again myself.
Were you admirable, father?
(waves crashing)
(somber music)
- Miss Heinemann, it's Fritz Werdemann.
Could you open the door?
I'd like to speak to you for a moment.
Look, you might as well let me in.
I know perfectly well you're in there drinking
because the maid's been trying to get in
day to tidy up the place.
Miss Heinemann, I fully understand that you have reasons to despise Dr. Tenma.
Your father's death was a big loss for you to bear, but if your relationship with Tenma
had continued, it would have helped heal the pain of that event and made your life easier.
When he broke off your relationship, you felt very alone.
Your life was thrown into turmoil, and you blamed Tenma for that.
"I'll tell you about my father.
They sentenced him to 20 years for espionage and murder.
For a very long time I was called 'son of a spy.'
Fingers were pointed at me and I was shunned.
My father's actions threw my life into turmoil.
But all that stuff didn't really bother me.
Would you like to know why?
Would you like to know how I was able to endure and keep on fighting?
It was because I believed, I truly believed.
My father is innocent.
He was innocent.
For me to represent someone, I must first believe they are truly innocent!
I'm going to prove Dr. Tenma's innocence!
Tenma has to be innocent!
Just like my father!
You must believe it! You must believe!
I'm leaving you phone numbers for my partner and myself.
When you're ready to testify, please give us a call.
What are you saying?
He's being transported to the detention center tomorrow?
He's only been here a few days.
Why is he being rushed off?
That is standard police procedure after someone willingly confesses.
Well can't we do something to delay it, Mr. Werdemann?
The police have been trying to convince Dr. Tenma to meet with us, but so far they haven't
had any luck.
Is Miss Heinemann there by any chance?
No, she went out.
For all I know, she's probably gone off to get drunk at some bar again.
Dusseldorf...
I remember all these places. Nothing has changed.
I despise this town.
(dramatic music)
- Oh, did you just get here?
- I've been sitting here staring at you
for the last five minutes.
I'm sorry, but I've never seen anything more interesting than this book.
I just had to write some of it down.
Do you want to go somewhere else to get a bite to eat?
Maybe you'd like some kind of foreign cuisine?
Italian might be good.
How about French?
Where would you like to go? You name it.
Don't let me tear you away from your book.
Why don't you just keep on reading?
Wait! Eva!
I didn't mean to...
Eva!
(dramatic music)
- This sandwich is the bestest ever!
(laughing)
- You brought your appetite.
Pretty good, huh?
(laughing)
- What are you doing?
- Holding it down.
There's a rock on the edge of the blanket, so it won't blow away in the wind.
That wasn't what I meant. I'm wondering why you're putting down a blanket at all.
It's fun having lunch out here every once in a while.
And the weather's nice, too.
And who would be having this lunch?
The two of us, of course. I made my favorite sandwiches. I hope you'll like them.
There are bugs everywhere.
It'll be all right.
They've all got dirt on them now. I'm afraid they're ruined.
You look hungry. Do you want this?
Franz, don't bother the lady.
Uh, honey?
Here.
Thank you.
Tasty, huh?
Start walking.
(feet clomping)
- Into the truck.
- Oh, hello.
This is Eva Heinemann.
I'm having trouble reaching Mr. Werdemann.
No one's answering his phone.
That's why I'm calling you.
- Oh.
Well, his wife just gave birth the other day,
at the hospital checking in on her.
But he has told me about you, Ms. Heinemann.
Please, feel free to discuss anything you'd like with me.
- Well, there is a matter I'd like to discuss.
- And what is that, may I ask?
- Appearing in court to testify to Tenma's innocence.
- Oh, I see.
Well, we're very grateful to hear that.
So, where are you staying at the moment?
I should be over to your hotel in a couple of minutes.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]