The wind blew hard, the bottle fell over, the sandwiches were covered in dirt.
That's when he smiled so sadly.
You look hungry. Do you want this?
Franz, don't bother the lady.
Uh, honey?
Thank you.
Tasty, huh?
Start walking.
Into the truck.
Oh, hello. This is Eva Heinemann.
I'm having trouble reaching Mr. Werdemann. No one's answering his phone.
That's why I'm calling you.
Oh. Well, his wife just gave birth the other day,
so he's probably at the hospital checking in on her.
But he has told me about you, Ms. Heinemann.
Please, feel free to discuss anything you'd like with me.
Well, there is a matter I'd like to discuss.
And what is that, may I ask?
Appearing in court to testify to Tenma's innocence.
Oh, I see. Well, we're very grateful to hear that.
So, where are you staying at the moment?
Yeah, I've written down the address.
I should be over to your hotel in a couple of minutes.
[Music Fades Out]
[Birds chirping]
It's all the timing.
They'll see me in the road, and they'll swerve and miss me.
And when the truck comes down this road, I fall.
They come, I fall.
I gotta get the timing floppin' just right here.
Hey!
They come, I fall.
Hey, honey!
What is it, Helene?
Come on, I'm busy now.
So are you really going to marry me today?
Hey, how many times do I have to say it?
Of course I'm gonna do it!
So you really mean it?
You swear to God?
I do.
Today, I'd swear to anything, Helene, baby.
Then come and kiss me, Gustav.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
I know how we can seal this deal.
Come on, get in the car.
Whoa! Hold on!
Come on, let go, you idiot!
Aha!
Damn, Helene, you been helping yourself to my stash?
Didn't we talk about you not doing that?
Nope, wasn't me.
I should have known all that sniffling
wasn't just for allergies, you selfish bitch.
I'm here getting high off my supply while I'm practicing to make sure we pull this job off!
Don't make a big deal out of it, Gustav. It's an easy job. It's a piece of cake!
You think this is easy? I make even a little mistake and I'll be the biggest roadkill you've ever seen! I'll be dead!
Wait, you're gonna die?
Yeah! One wrong move, it's bye-bye Gustav!
- I don't want you to die!
- Hey, I'll be fine, I live, I was just kidding!
- Oh, you're gonna wind up dead!
(sobbing)
- Hey, hey, I won't die, babe.
I still got this real big mission to take care of.
- What's that?
- My mission is for us to have a ton of kids together.
I want us to have so many kids
we can feel our own soccer team.
- Gustav, that sounds wonderful.
- Once I'm done with this job,
Then we'll both be totally set.
What do you say, Helene?
Will you help me complete my mission?
Mm-hmm.
Yes, Gustav, I will!
I'll have them!
I'll have as many children as you want, my stud muffin!
It's like I said earlier.
Now's not the time.
Gustav, I want to make babies!
Hey, just hold that thought for now.
It's almost time for the Detective Forrester show to come on.
Okay, the truck comes.
and fall. The truck comes, I jump out, and I fall. The truck comes, I jump out, and I fall. So when this truck comes...
To tell you the truth, I'm thinking of killing someone. The lovely Eva Hindemann.
No, you... you can't! Forget it!
The weather outside sure looks nice.
A day as fine as this and I'm stuck riding in this lousy truck.
And I get to share the ride with a serial murderer like you.
This must be my unlucky day.
But believe it or not, you're in luck.
You're thinking that this ride will be a boring transfer of yourself to another gloomy prison cell.
Wrong. I'm about to change that for you.
You're about to hear the most thrilling story of your life.
The twelve tales of escape that have made me a legend.
I will begin with my escape from Kreiner Prison. It is phenomenal.
Keep it to yourself!
Damn, these are epic. You got a better way to pass the time?
What time is it right now?
Excuse me, officer, what's the time?
It's 9.32 in the morning.
If I were free, I'd be getting ready to watch reruns of Detective Forrester on TV right about now.
Did you ever watch that drama?
It's a really wild series.
Well, it's just about time for them to be here.
- This job should be a real easy one to pull off.
You can just sit in the car and watch.
- What's with the gun?
You're not gonna use it, right?
- No way, Pumpkin.
I just brought it with to scare 'em.
- I won't have babies with you
and have to tell our kids their father's a killer.
Don't use that gun.
I'll even give up all the drugs.
(crickets chirping)
- Man, I love you, Helene.
You and me should get married.
I mean it this time.
- (gasps) Real?
- From now on, Gustav's going straight.
No more jobs where I have to carry around guns.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
I'm done with jobs where I gotta pack heat.
- Oh, Gustav.
- (sighs) Damn, that feels great.
(laughs)
What a weight off my shoulders.
Hey, Helene!
Hey, I love you from the bottom of my--
[screams]
[tires screeching]
[explosion]
What was that?
What's wrong?
I think I hit somebody.
Wait, what in the hell?
Hold it. You hit him?
Sit down, Milch. That's an order.
You hit him? But how?
Milch, what part of "sit down, that's an order" don't you understand?
That person was probably my little brother.
Huh?
I planned to free us. It didn't work.
Sorry, Dr. Tenma.
I taught Gustav the movement and timing of how to do it perfectly.
We worked so many hours to make sure he knew just how to fall.
I guess no one can stop a speeding car by falling in a road as well as I can.
He must have done a bad fall, but they still should have dodged him anyway.
Gustav wasn't good at it yet.
You could have at least tried to miss him.
Look, whatever you're going on about, you need to cool it.
Now listen, you come with us. Let's see if you really know this guy.
(metal clanging)
- Oh, Gustav.
I'm so sorry, Gustav.
(screaming)
- Elaine, I'm so...
Oh, this is bad.
- So, do you think he's still alive?
- Oh, geez, what are we gonna do?
- Hey, wait, I know.
We've got a doctor right here with us.
- Hey, you, get out of the truck.
- Yeah, get out.
Move it!
So Doc, what's the verdict?
Is he still alive?
How could I have done this?
How could I have believed that he'd be able to pull this off?
(sobbing)
- This can't be.
- We are screwed.
- Can't we find a way to smooth it over in our report?
- You can't just smooth over something like this.
- Then what are we gonna do?
This is a real problem.
(dramatic music)
- The key.
The key to these handcuffs.
Hand it over.
(dramatic music)
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPING]
Hand it over.
I'm not going to ask again.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
(footsteps)
- Are you waiting for someone?
- I am.
- Then may I get you a drink?
- A scotch please.
Wait.
Bring me coffee.
- Now back to the news.
This morning a fire erupted
at a large shopping center in Dortmund.
employees of the shopping center, they put out the fire themselves, but only after two
stores suffered smoke damage. Thanks to the quick thinking of those workers...
Well, there is a matter I'd like to discuss.
And what is that, may I ask?
Appearing in court to testify to Tenma's innocence.
I should be over to your hotel in a couple of minutes. Wait for me in the lobby.
Will I really be able to live with myself if I set him free?
this just in I've just been handed a bulletin informing us that at about 10
o'clock this morning in aircraft just outside of Dusseldorf two suspects in
police custody being transported to Hilden detention center have escaped
further details have not yet been released but we do have the names of the
two suspects who escaped and are still at large they are Gunter Milch who is
suspected of attacking an armored truck and Kenzo Tenma suspected of multiple
homicides. Police have issued an all-points bulletin to locate and apprehend the two fugitives
and return them to police custody.
But why? Why is he escaping when I'm about to...
Uh-huh. Yes, hello. Ah, Mr. Vertimon, it's you. Yes, I did hear what just happened. Such
a shame.
Why'd you have to escape now, at a time like this?
I don't understand. I've changed my mind. I want to help you.
I was about to come forward and prove your innocence. Why now?
No, it's hard to figure out what's going on with him.
I don't understand why he did what he did either.
Yes, that sounds like a good idea. Let's go to the police.
But first...
Actually, right now there's this little problem I have to take care of before that.
I'll handle it. Why, sure. Uh-huh. No problem. All right.
Well, that's the situation we're stuck with now, but we should deal with this calmly and methodically.
Yes, I agree.
Wait, that voice...
We must find out all the details as soon as we can, sure.
That voice...
Exactly. No, I get it. You're preaching to the choir.
- I know that voice.
- Yes, I'll do my best.
- Roberto!
(Roberto gasping)
(heart beating)
- And here's your coffee.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Wait, the ashtray, that cigarette isn't mine.
Oh my god.
Spider! Spider! Spider!
His smell...
It's his smell.
He must have been in here.
He was in this room.
Roberto was just in here.
(tires screeching)
- Oh, Gustav's dead, the man I love is now dead.
- Look, stop saying that he's dead, Helene.
He's still alive, but it's bad.
He hit his head, but there's no blood.
It's called a cerebral hemorrhage.
Ain't that right, Dr. Tenma?
I understand you're upset,
but we're gonna switch cars in the woods up ahead
as we originally planned.
- At this point, Gustav's dead weight.
We're leaving him behind in the car.
- No way!
- Just keep driving.
There's not enough time for us to make the switch now.
- What are you, nuts?
The police are gonna be on the lookout for this car.
If we stay in it, we're sitting ducks.
- Listen to me, if we can get him to a hospital
as soon as we can, there's a chance he could live.
- Drive to a hospital?
Now listen, I will admit your quick thinking back there
did turn my botched escape plan into a success,
and I thank you for that, Doc.
But when it comes to successful escapes,
And I say we leave Gustav in this car in the forest up ahead.
Well, I say you're driving straight to Eisler Memorial Hospital.
They can treat Gustav.
They've the best medical staff and equipment in Dusseldorf.
It's the hospital I worked at. Now move it!
(sobbing)
(knocking)
- The hospital's entrance is straight up ahead, okay?
No crying.
Once you drive through the gate, go directly to emergency.
Get this letter to Dr. Wagner.
I wrote down all the details of Gustav's condition.
- And Gustav won't die?
- Right now, he's still alive.
Don't you give up while he's got a chance.
You've got to go.
- Good luck, kid.
If we hang around here much longer,
this place will be crawling with cops
and we'll be back in our cells in time for dinner.
- Thanks for everything.
- So what are you gonna do?
Where are you gonna go?
I'm thinking you should stick with me doctor. You're an amateur at this stuff. There's a woman
I know whose life is in real danger, and I've got to get to her quickly a
Woman is that why you escaped you went through all this for a woman
Well, I've got a great proposition for you if you go with me to Tunisia you can get as many hot chicks as you want
Thanks, but no
Take care
[FOOTSTEPS]
Hey, doctor, I gotta know.
You didn't really kill anyone, did you?
I shot one person, but that man's still very much alive.
I knew you weren't a killer.
Well, now you're innocent on that count, Dr. Tenma.
But I suppose you know that now you
have a real criminal record.
Starting today, you're officially a fugitive.
Hey, we should have a fugitives' reunion in Tunisia someday.
It's a really great place.
(suspenseful music)
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]