Ava Heinemann? Oh yeah, she was here. She's fallen on pretty hard times, but her snotty attitude is still the same.
Come to think of it, it's gotten even worse.
Did Ava happen to mention to you where she was staying?
Yeah, she said she'd forgotten her cash and to collect the tab I'd have to go to her hotel.
I guess she still thinks she's a princess, huh?
And which hotel was that?
The stag in hotel. I mean come on. She stand at a third-rate hotel claims
She forgot her cash. He really thinks she's gonna come back to pay her bar tab
wait
Aren't you? Yeah, now that I think of it you were engaged to her. Yeah
He's that doctor
Yeah, hello police just now that serial killer was right here in my bar hey
Any idea where my coat went?
What?
I hung my coat up on the rack right there by your front door.
Huh?
(dramatic music)
(train rumbling)
(train horn blaring)
- Hello?
Yes, excuse me.
I'm trying to reach a lady named Ava Heineman
who's staying at your hotel.
- All right, sir.
I'm putting you on hold while I call her room.
Please stand by.
(phone ringing)
- Make it quick.
Please hurry.
- To tell you the truth,
I'm thinking of killing someone.
Your former fiance, the lovely Eva Heinemann.
- Come on.
- Thank you for waiting.
- Yes.
- We rang her room, sir, but she's not picking up.
- What's her room number?
I'd like you to deliver an important business fax to her, so would you please tell me what her room number is?
Please tell me.
Oh sure, she's in 402.
Our fax number here is...
Room 402...
(phone ringing)
- It's no good.
Mr. Ball isn't in his office
and he's not answering his cell phone either.
- I'm beginning to think that your partner
won't meet with us no matter how long we wait.
And here's what my reasoning is in saying that.
Mr. Ball became Dr. Tenma's lawyer
to prove his client was innocent.
Then Tenma complicated things by escaping from the police
after confessing to the crime.
With his client displaying that kind of guilty behavior,
Well, he's left with no choice but to withdraw.
Hmm...
Mr. Werdemann, are you going to quit too?
I don't plan on quitting, but I didn't plan on Tenma escaping either.
Since I'm his lawyer, I want him to trust me, but his actions are confusing.
We're all confused by what he's done, but do you even believe him?
Do you believe what he said happened in Munich, Mr. Werdemann?
Do you actually believe all of the things that Tenma has told you are true?
No answer.
To me, that means you didn't believe anything that he said to you, did you?
I was shocked and disappointed when I heard the news that Tenma had escaped,
but most of all I couldn't believe that he'd lied about his guilt.
And I had that same unsettled feeling during the library fire
Something like that is happening again, and Tenma escaped for that reason.
You have to believe in him, just like your belief in your father's innocence led you to become a lawyer.
The phone has been ringing off the hook.
The media is begging to have you answer one question.
As a top lawyer, will you still continue to defend Tenma?
Tell them at this time I have no comment.
Are you kidding? They won't take that for an answer.
They'll eat you alive!
Tell them that I will be holding a press conference
after I thoroughly examine all of the facts of this very unusual situation.
And until that time, don't let anybody into my office.
But you have a visitor waiting in your office.
So you let someone in here without consulting me first?
Look, I don't want to see anyone.
Sorry. I told him that and tried to turn him away,
- Well, he insisted I'm waiting for you.
- Who is he, anyway?
- Well, he's with, he's with the German Federal Police.
- The BKA?
Over the Rainbow.
It's quite a nice song.
I believe it was the theme song of the radio station
that your father ran.
- So, who are you?
I'm Inspector Lungay.
406.
405.
404.
Room 402.
That's her room.
(gulping)
- Guten tag.
- Oh, guten tag.
(gasping)
Pardon me.
- Huh?
- Where's the guest staying
What?
Oh, the woman who was staying in this room.
I was dropping by to visit her.
You were?
I was told this room's guest was already checked out.
Hey!
You see? Told you that person was gone.
Eva...
Inspector Lungay, you have my thanks for your thoroughness in the report that you wrote on Tenma.
In doing my research to learn more about my client, I read many reports. Yours was elaborate and outstanding.
I must say as well, I'm quite aware of your reputation as a star in the legal world, Mr. Vertimon.
I imagine you're here because of the news of Dr. Tenma's recent escape.
Even though he's a client of mine, let me assure you, he hasn't contacted me and I don't know where he is at this time.
Oh, so he escaped.
Actually, I'm not here on that matter.
I'm on something of an extended vacation.
You know, in a way, I feel like I've made an escape as well.
Having this time off has been refreshing.
Well, I hope you'll excuse me, but right now I have no time for small talk, so...
Of course. I do have a specific question, actually.
Maybe it's a habit I got through my work, but I just can't take a real vacation.
I find myself coming up with a theme for each of my trips.
This is the theme for this trip.
This picture book I'm holding.
Look, Inspector. I'm out of time. You have to leave.
Please, let's talk a little longer.
So you really haven't come here to talk about Tenma?
To be quite honest, right now Tenma is the furthest thing from my mind.
Besides, I only just heard the news about Tenma's escape.
I heard it while I was on my way over here.
Well, then why did you bother coming to my office?
As I said, it's this book.
I've become intensely interested in finding out about this picture book's author.
But the man who authored this book had many pen names.
The only German pen name he used was Klaus Poppe.
Learning more about this mystery man became a challenge for me.
I investigated further and came across the name of someone Pope was acquainted with.
Who was it?
Your father knew Pope.
The radio station your father owned had a program called "The World's Fables."
According to records in August of 1966, Pope's work "Where Am I?" was aired on his station.
I've read transcripts of your father's trial for spying.
The espionage trial shook all of post-war West Germany, or so they say.
I know that. So what's your point?
Records indicate your father had traveled to Czechoslovakia on numerous occasions.
Since he was just meeting a picture book artist, his trips went unnoticed and weren't brought up at his trial.
Just what are you implying went on?
Well, I'm implying that based on my research, your father appears to have been old friends with this picture book artist.
My father knew many people due to the nature of his work.
He met and had meetings with countless people.
That was his job.
So you're saying that your father and Poppe weren't well acquainted then?
Nonetheless, according to the investigative work I did,
Klaus Poppe usually met with people at his editor's house,
or they would meet at his vacation home,
which was an old farm in the suburbs of Prague.
But when he would meet with your father,
he always did so at a certain mansion.
the place was known as the Red Rose Mansion but he never did meet people in
that location while using the name Klaus Pope. When he used the Red Rose
Mansion he called himself by another name, the name Franz Bonaparta and he
was someone who was a very important person in the Czechoslovakian secret
police.
(eerie music)
- What are you, what are you trying to say?
- Spy kid, spy kid, spy kid.
- Son of a traitor spy, that's you.
- You son of a coward spy.
- Hey, if you don't like that,
then find a way to prove your dad's innocent.
- If the dad's a traitor, the son's a spy too.
Spike it! Spike it! Spike it! Spike it! Spike it!
I just want to learn about Franz Bonaparta.
What can you tell me?
I know of no such person.
In 1966, your father met with Klaus Poppe at a certain mansion in Czechoslovakia.
That's what really happened back then, isn't it?
It was just an author and a radio station owner having a business meeting.
That picture book author never went by the name Klaus Pope when he used the Red Rose Mansion.
Hold on. What exactly are you trying to say?
When that author of children's books met with your father, they met at the Red Rose Mansion.
Which means he wasn't meeting your father as Klaus Pope, but as Franz Bonaparta.
So your father was actually meeting with someone who was an important part of the Czechoslovakian secret police.
That's not what happened, dammit!
Please allow me to make one thing clear.
whether or not your father was a spy.
But my father wasn't a spy!
I know you believe that,
but your father surely must have known
Franz Bonaparte's real identity.
How is that relevant?
You may not wish to accept it, but it certainly appears
your father knew what was going on
in the Red Rose Mansion, didn't he?
No! No!
My father was innocent! Innocent!
You're wrong!
I'm hoping that you'll get in touch with me
after you calm down.
When you want to talk more on this subject call me and know this I don't care if your father was a spy or not
I'm not concerned with that. My only interest here is to learn more about Franz Bonaparta
My father was never
Excuse me your wife's on the phone. She'd like to huh
Huh? Is there something wrong, sir?
No.
It's your wife. She said she's calling from the maternity ward at the hospital.
Oh, I see.
Hey, honey.
So you can come home? Well, that's great news.
Sure, I'll come over there right away to pick you up.
Dr. Tenma!
Start driving now!
Just calm down. Listen, everything is alright.
- I said start driving.
Move it!
(tires screeching)
- Stop pointing that gun.
Just calm down, Tenma.
I don't understand.
What the hell's going on?
- Where is Eva?
Where is Eva Heinemann?
- What are you talking about?
Why in the world are you asking about her?
- Don't play dumb.
You really think I don't know
what you're trying to pull here?
Don't stop the car.
Keep your eyes on the road and keep going.
I finally figured out what you're really about.
You just wanted Ava.
I don't understand you.
What would I want with Ava?
Spare me your lies.
I know who you're working with, and I know what he's done.
You're partners with that man Ball.
What of it?
He's the man that I shot during that library
fire at Munich University.
I won't let any more people be murdered.
Answer me.
I saved Johan's life, that's what put this all in motion.
So many people have died since that night.
So many precious lives.
I've seen enough bloodshed.
I won't let more innocent people die!
Why did you stop the car?
Is that true?
I told you to keep driving.
Is all of what you just said true?
I need to know if it's the truth!
[ Horn honks ]
My father was suspected of espionage and charged.
He was proven innocent after the fact,
but it turned out he really was a spy.
I believed in my father's innocence, and I studied hard to become a lawyer so I could
fight injustice.
But while I was still in law school, I found something that devastated me.
I found decisive evidence that proved my father was a spy.
Ever since, ever since, I could never believe what anyone told me.
Me, the great honest crusading lawyer, the hero of the legal world!
My whole life is a lie, so I don't believe in anyone!
In reality, I really was the son of a turncoat spy.
Ever since I found that notebook...
Ever since I found that notebook that my father had written in the '60s,
as I flipped through its pages, everything about my father I had believed,
all that trust just crumbled.
There was the truth.
My father was a spy.
The notebook I found was a detailed record of years of contact.
"Contact with the Czechoslovakian secret police written in an unbreakable code.
Filled with mysterious people my father knew, including Franz Bonaparta."
Did he refer to Red Rose Mansion in the notebook?
Hold on, how do you know about that?
It's all falling into place.
Huh?
That man, Ball, he needed the notebook.
It's probably why he approached you in the first place, so he could get a hold of it.
Where is that notebook right now?
It's at my house.
I'm sorry.
He's been here all right.
And from the way he's left things, we know he was after that notebook.
Here's a letter that's made out to you, Tenma.
I can't say how, but he must have known that you would wind up being here.
Help me, Kenzo. Please, I'm begging you.
Come quickly to the Red Rose Mansion, Ava.
Does this mean that Ava's safe, then?
No.
This isn't her handwriting.
He's playing games with me!
He's toying with me like a cat and a mouse!
It's still here.
He didn't think to look through my old records.
Oh, for the rainbow.
This is the notebook.
Here, take it.
But what if someone else saw it?
Your father's restored reputation would be ruined forever.
I can't be worried about that anymore.
Can I trust you?
I heard everything you told me, and now I know why you're trying to do what you're
doing.
And yet I don't feel I can be of any help to you, but I need to know if I can trust
I don't think you should trust any person who carries one of these around.
I want to trust you.
(dramatic orchestral music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)