June 19th, my first meeting with Franz Bonaparte, RF-17-9.
He was a very quiet man.
He was graceful, dressed in a suit.
In the afternoon, the children gathered for a book reading.
- Where are you headed? - To the border.
- Yeah, which border? - The Czech border, sir.
- Get in. - Thank you.
In the afternoon, the children gathered for a book reading, a mysterious mansion, a mansion
with red roses, P. Brevnov W., a steeple on the left, a weather vane on the right, human
dignity, experiments, amazing experiments, deprivation of dignity.
So, where are you from? I was just asking what country you're from.
Oh, I'm from Japan.
I'm not sure you'll like this, but you're welcome to it.
Here you go. It's left over from my lunch today.
You're very kind, but I'm fine.
Eat. You look like you're about to collapse from hunger any minute now.
Ha, go on. I sure don't need it. My wife's been nagging me to lose weight.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
To start a long journey, you've got to have something in your stomach or you won't last till the end.
I have to end it soon. This long journey.
(dramatic music)
What do you mean?
You let him leave?
You just watched as Tenma walked away?
Yeah.
Why didn't you stop him?
Well, you of all people should know that you can't stop Tenma.
On top of which, with Eva Heinemann missing, our case is in dire straits anyway.
Tenma escaped from jail because he feared for her safety.
That lawyer who called himself "Ball" is most likely the same man who tried to murder me in my clinic because I knew too much.
And obviously, his most recent agenda was to get close to me to steal my father's notebook.
Your father's notebook must be extremely important.
Let's go then.
Where?
To where you're thinking Tenma's headed.
The Red Rose Mansion? How can we find it?
It might be easier than we think.
My father's notes were full of odd symbols and cryptic codes, but I don't think that was a code.
The Red Rose Mansion, followed by P. Brevnov W.
I think P is for Prague, and W is for West.
So it's in a Prague suburb to the west of Brevnov.
A place where you can see a weathervane on the right and a steeple on the left.
That's a start.
I just hope there's an eyewitness or something at that mansion that will help us get closer to ending this.
Although, I know that's doubtful.
Children gathered there in the afternoon for a book reading, at least according to father's notes.
Then those children could be our witnesses.
Mr. Verdaman?
Look, I'm sorry I admonished you for letting Tenma just take off like that.
If I had been standing there face to face with him, I'm sure I would have done the exact same thing.
So, let's go.
I was here...
Once I used to live in this town.
And I...
Welcome home!
Are you alright, Nina?
Yes, I'm fine.
I think you should stop this Nina you get lost every single time you try it
I'm sure I'll start to remember my brother talked to me back then and told
me what happened how he was taken away from the three frogs what he noted when
he left town and where he went past the train station the town on the left
Beside the river, driving alongside a trolley.
Turn right here, please!
We can't have that.
Keeping secrets from him is definitely a no-no.
You said turn right.
What's the matter?
It's nothing, really.
Any luck? Recognize anything?
I don't know.
Admit it, it's hopeless.
It was a long time ago, you can't expect to remember everything.
Nina!
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GASPS]
[WATER SPLASHING]
A weather vane on the right.
And a steeple on the left.
Nina!
[GASPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(eerie music)
- The Red Rose Mansion.
- So this is it?
- I don't know.
But I know I've been here before.
(eerie music)
[SIGHS]
This place.
That's weird.
What is that?
[GIGGLES]
[GASPS]
It looks like someone tore down that wall and found that door.
[Gasp]
(dramatic music)
- It's nothing but an empty room.
Nina?
Nina!
- Take this, you demon!
And this!
[GROANING]
The demon has been slain.
[APPLAUSE]
How do you feel?
Welcome back, Mr. Lipsky.
Did you have a good-sized crowd?
No.
Business was bad, as usual.
I don't know why.
They're such wonderful puppets.
The one I'm making now is even better still.
I'd really like to see it.
Once I'm finished, you'll be the first person I show it to.
It's time for me to go to work.
The restaurant?
Yeah. I can't earn a living with just the puppets.
Listen, I'm sorry I've stayed here so long. I don't mean to impose on you.
Oh no, don't worry about it. It's all right.
Mr. Lipsky, there's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
Three months ago, you found me unconscious and took me to the hospital.
I did.
I was wondering, why were you at that mansion?
Nina! Nina! Nina!
Answer me, please! Nina! Nina!
What's wrong?
When I go to that mansion, images come to me that I use for my work.
How should I put this?
I, um...
Now I've found something more inspiring.
Anyway, don't worry about staying. It's not an imposition.
You can stay as long as you like.
(sizzling)
- Nina.
Is it all right if I come in?
Well, of course it's all right.
Are you sure you're well enough to be up and about?
Uh-huh. Wonderful.
So your puppets are all born in this room.
Yes, but I haven't found an audience that enjoys them.
What is your puppet show about?
It's about the tale of a demon.
What's wrong, Nina?
Nothing. Please continue.
A demon is on a journey to find a dragon that will destroy the world,
but on his way, he comes close to the brink of death.
A young man who is passing by sees him dying,
and acts quickly to save his life.
When the young man learns the true identity of the one he saved,
He chases after the demon.
At the end of his journey, the young man finds the evil one,
and with a knife in his hand, he slays the demon.
I think it's an interesting story, but audiences don't seem to like it.
Are you okay, Nina?
I think if I were him, I'd have done the same thing.
I would do precisely the same.
But I must not let him do that.
- Nina. - Any person...
would have saved the demon's life if he could.
You think so?
There is someone who would probably appreciate this story more than anyone else.
- Who? - He's on these shelves.
They're all his picture books.
Jakob Ferebeck, Klaus Pope, Emil Scherbe.
The nameless monster.
I'm surprised you know it.
He wrote many picture books.
Those three authors--
Jakob Ferebeck, Klaus Poppe, Emil Scherbeck--
those were all just pen names used by the same person.
The author's real name is Franz Bonaparta.
Bonaparta? Why do I know?
People can become whatever they want to be.
"Because I wasn't a superior pupil, I was thrown out of the book readings."
"The book readings?"
"Mr. Bonaparte used to be in charge of book readings which were held at the Red Rose Mansion.
I was a student at the mansion then.
It took a while, but I understood what he was trying to do."
"Let's make a deal. Let's make a deal," said the demon.
"No, not at all," said the man with the big eyes.
"Sure, let's make a deal," said the man with the big mouth.
The man with the big mouth grew a beautiful garden.
The man with the big eyes was very hungry because he was very poor.
The man with the big mouth had fun every day.
The man with the big mouth was very full from eating the fruit from his garden.
So he didn't realize what was happening.
He didn't realize that his garden was drying up.
By the time he noticed, it was too late.
The man with the big mouth cried and cried in the garden that never grew again.
"I shouldn't have made a deal with the demon."
Big Eyes was dying from hunger.
Tears were trickling down from his big eyes as he cried,
"I should have made a deal with the demon."
"Let's make a deal, let's make a deal," said the demon.
The Man with the Big Eyes,
The Man with the Big Mouth by Jakub Ferebak.
Every Friday afternoon at three o'clock,
The children would gather together for a book reading.
We would sit around him and listen as he read a book to us
in a kind voice, very calm and gentle.
And when he was finished reading the story,
he would turn and ask us
the meaning of the story.
Do you understand?
I... I understand.
I also understood, after many readings.
He'd say, "Why don't we try reading this next?"
It's as if I've come here for the first time.
Although the journey's taken quite a while,
all the memories have come together.
The God of Peace was very busy.
He was so busy playing the trumpet
he didn't have time to look in the mirror.
The trumpet that the God of Peace played
made everyone very happy.
The God of Peace was so busy,
he didn't have time to look in the mirror.
The mysterious water created green mountains,
ripened the fields, and created flower gardens.
The God of Peace was very busy.
He was so busy naming people,
he didn't have time to look in the mirror.
Your name is Otto.
Your name is Hans.
Your name is Thomas.
Your name is Johann.
Gohan gave the god his hat in appreciation.
The god was very happy.
He put the hat on and looked in the mirror for the first time.
But what he saw was a demon.
The demon inside the mirror said,
"You are me and I am you.
What should I do?
No, no one can live happily with a demon here.
What should I do? What should I do?
Then, the troubled God...
Do you know what the God does?
I know. I figured it out.
Do you know? Do you know what that God did after that?
I know for sure.
"We finally meet. I'm back. Welcome home. It's me, Mother. Even you can't tell us apart,
can you? She is me and I am her. You are me and I am you. I understand everything now.
where we came from, and where we're going.
The weather outside is wonderful, Mother.
Everything is about to go up in flames.
(fire crackling)
(footsteps thudding)
(gasps)
- I know what the God does.
He grabs a gun, and points it at his forehead.
(rain falling)
- Shoot me.
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)