Shoot me, Anna.
So are you ready, children?
Really, there's no need to be anxious.
Your hairpin is crooked.
I'll fix it.
There.
Come on, let's hold hands.
All right, let's go.
I'm here in Dusseldorf, where the East German Trade Commissioner
who fled to the West, appeared before the press yesterday
along with his family and friends.
Mr. and Mrs. Liebert appeared to be in fine spirits along with their fraternal twins.
Mr. Liebert, what do you think of the West?
Well, being here is really very tough.
Huh?
Now that I've realized I'm free to say whatever I want,
I'm finding it tough learning to say what's really on my mind.
Actually, the real answer to that question is easy.
Just look at the smiling faces of my wife and children.
Well, looks like your twins have started enjoying their newfound freedom.
You're right. I'm so glad.
Mr. Liebert, would you care to tell us about your opinion of the situation in the East?
Johan, what are you doing?
Hey, Johan!
Huh?
Which hand am I holding it in?
Hmm...
That one!
You're right. Take it. It's yours.
Oh, look! An acorn!
Try again. Which hand is it this time?
This one.
You did it again. Here, Anna. It's yours.
Great!
Hey, let me see. Open up both your hands.
I should have known. No matter which one I picked, I would have been right.
That's true.
You see, it's because all of the acorns here belong to you.
[giggles]
Hey, Johan, did you see that town we drove through on the way here?
It was so different from the towns on our side of the border.
There were lots of nice places to shop.
And did you see all those toys and clothes?
I mean, you saw them too, didn't you?
Yes, I saw them.
Everything you saw, it's yours, too.
You mean it?
I mean it.
But why are they mine?
Why? Because I said so.
(dramatic music)
(water running)
(knocking)
I saw you on TV, Mr. Levert.
Well, we can't leave you standing in the rain.
Hey, Johan, did you hear someone come by?
Johan?
Where'd you go?
[GUNSHOTS]
[GASPS]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
(eerie music)
(sobbing)
(horn blaring)
[HORN BLOWS]
[GASPS]
Johan, what...
Johan, what did you do?
Every one of them...
When Uncle Josef and Aunt Clara died way back...
When Bedger died, were you the one who killed them all?
Today was special.
You killed them all, didn't you?
I had to, because the monster came today.
Johan, what are you talking about?
The monster came to take the two of us away.
Give me your hand.
Shoot me, Anna.
After you shoot me, wipe the gun with a cloth and throw it out the window.
Be sure to shoot me in the head.
Then run away.
Run away as far as you can so the monster can't catch you.
Even if I die, you are me and I am you.
That night, that awful rainy night, somebody's here.
Nina.
Somebody is inside our house.
But who?
Who could it have been?
It was...
The monster came.
Nina.
Nina... Nina...
Why would their mansion catch on fire?
That's hard to say. I thought nobody lived in that place.
All I know is that it was abandoned.
I heard it was arson.
Wow, that's too bad.
Dr. Tenma.
Do you think you could come with us for a moment?
General Wolf would like to see you.
Did you say General Wolf?
I'm here, General Wolf.
- Dr. Tenma. - Yes, sir.
- So you were called upon as well.
Find me at the Red Rose Mansion.
It was a letter from Yohan,
but I'm in such poor health
that I was barely able to make it here.
- So then you received that letter, too.
- It's ironic.
The only person who sends letters
addressed to a man named Wolf anymore is Yohan.
(gasping)
You shouldn't be speaking so much, General.
You see, my father was a military man.
From birth, I was destined to live as one of the chosen ones in our society.
But now, the only person who knows me for what I am is that monster.
I heard the Red Rose Mansion was set on fire.
Now that it's gone, the people from all those years ago will be coming back.
- People deprived of their names, like me.
- Have you been able to determine where the fire started?
- Yeah, seems it started in a large hall upstairs.
From the way the flames were concentrated up there,
it was probably started with kerosene or gasoline.
- Kerosene?
- Yeah, could have been arson.
- We won't be sure until after we complete
our investigation, but it looks like a wall
leading to the room was torn down.
- What's that got to do with it?
- Dunno.
Officers! Quick, come look!
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
I saw something at the base of this rosebush,
and when I started digging,
they just kept appearing one after another.
After all these years,
they'll all be coming back.
But there isn't a soul alive
who knows what their names are anymore.
Lord, what a sight.
There's nothing but rubble left.
It appears the only way for us to get the real answers we need
is to find Tenma.
Out of the way! Let me through! Out of the way!
What's this?
Hey, get me headquarters!
This is serious! We found skeletons! Tons of human bodies!
Forty-six people.
Yes, that was the number I was told.
One day in 1981, 46 people who were at the Red Rose Mansion just disappeared.
Back then, that was all the information I could get in East Germany.
They were conducting an experiment at the mansion.
An experiment?
Stay back!
Just stay back!
Move!
This is my theory.
You need to get back!
I believe it was there that monstrous child was born.
Johan, I'm cold.
I can't walk anymore.
I'm hungry.
Are we going to die here today, Johan?
It's okay. You can tell me.
Please, Johan, would you say my name?
I want to hear it one last time. Would you say it?
I can't do that. You and I have no names.
So, please, Yohan, say my name.
Say my name.
Blankets.
Yes, sir.
And bring something warm for them to drink.
Right.
(dramatic music)
- Because Johan was such a wonderful name.
When I found those two, they had no names.
I decided to give the boy the name "Johan."
That name seemed to awaken something inside him.
Enough. No point in talking about the past.
Let's talk of what we're going to do.
Although I won't live to see tomorrow.
(Groaning)
General.
- General Wolfe, that's enough now.
You need to stop talking.
- Eva Heinemann, Eva Heinemann's with,
she's with people from my organization.
There were four of us who formed our organization.
They were Professor Gielitz, now dead.
Myself and Eva's with the other two members.
They're trying to use Ava as a pawn.
You can't let them.
Whether I'm dead or alive, there's no stopping it.
It's all beginning to spin out of control.
Stop it! Save me, Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
My first name is Helmut.
I am Helmut Wolf.
All who knew me as Helmut are no longer of this world.
I'd like to hear my name.
Please say it for me.
That is the only proof of my existence.
- Helmut. - My name.
- You're Helmut. You're Helmut Wolf.
That's who you are.
- So this is it.
This is what Johann saw.
I see it now, a world without names You're General Volf
(birds chirping)
- Not much left.
And the gate's locked up.
The police probably don't want anyone looking around.
(metal clanging)
It's no use.
Mr. Lipsky, I know how important this place was to you.
It was where you spent time at the book readings as a child, but...
Nina, this place just might have been important for you as well.
Going inside the mansion could have been the key to bringing back your memories.
I had a vision.
All of them lying there, people piled up in the mansion's main hall, all dead.
It looks like that vision you had was really true, Nina.
When I saw the news, I knew it.
the bones of 46 people at the Red Rose Mansion.
- Tell me, Nina.
Do you know if it happened like Johan said it did?
- I don't know.
What did my brother Johan say?
Did he see them all get murdered?
What a horrible sight.
If I had been there to see that,
who's to say I wouldn't be a monster myself?
Seeing that would turn anyone into a monster.
- Nina, maybe it's a good thing
burned down. I thought seeing this would be more painful. I felt I couldn't keep living
if this place didn't exist. But I just don't feel that way anymore. For me, this place
is just too full of sad memories. I wasn't a superior pupil, and that was sad. I couldn't
to meet that man's expectations, and that was sad.
If I had met that man's expectations,
then maybe things would have...
Now I see it was better that I didn't.
He didn't need me, he never did.
- Mr. Lipsky, are your parents still alive?
- They are, but I've never really lived
with either of them.
I hope one thing for you,
If your memories end up returning, Nina,
I hope whatever you recall, that they're good ones.
My good memories?
Yes, they do exist.
I do wonder what a good memory is like.
Dr. Tenma told me,
"If you don't have any good memories,
then you make your own."
He said that we should just make some.
You do it yourself.
(upbeat music)
Deeter, you've got ketchup all over your face.
Well, so do you!
Huh?
(laughing)
- Uh, Nina.
I'm in the process of creating
a new puppet show at the moment.
- Great, what is it about?
- For some reason, no one ever feels like
watching the puppet shows that I create.
I think people might end up finding
this one a bit more interesting.
- Oh please, can we see your play?
- Yeah, yeah, can we see it?
I am a girl who's lost her memory.
I had a dream that I was being chased by a monster.
I had a dream I was chasing a monster.
But I like to sing.
I like to dance, too.
Someday, I'll have a wonderful dream.
Someday, that dream will come true for me.
Someday.
"I can't think of what will come next.
You know, I'd really like to give this girl's story some kind of happy ending.
And yet, I haven't been able to think of one.
But she deserves a happy ending.
I want her to be happy."
"Thank you so much."
The girl made up her mind to leave.
She doesn't know what kind of a journey it will be.
She doesn't know what is waiting for her.
But the girl will courageously continue her journey.
The girl turns and waves her hand again and again,
again and again.
And then she is gone.
To search for her happy ending.
(dramatic music)
(knocking)
- Nina?
Nina!
Nina, you've come back!
- I've been looking for you.
You're Mr. Lipsky.
You're the son of the owner of the Red Rose Mansion and Franz Bonaparta is your father, isn't he?
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)