If I had known this was going to happen, I never would have taken that job.
I didn't like anything about it, right from the beginning.
It'll be okay.
Just hang in there.
You probably only need a few stitches.
I told you Robbie. No hospitals. Don't take me to the hospital. Get me the doctor. The
Hellbrow Hotel. Look Martin, I know what you're thinking. If you go to a hospital, the police
are going to drag you right back to prison. Look, I get it, but there's no time to drive
around looking for that so-called doctor. I said the hotel. The Hellbrow. Your life
Life is more important if you're alive.
Hurry up! The hell prowl!
I should have known.
Nothing good ever happens when there's a woman involved.
I'm begging you.
Hurry up.
Get me to Dr. Tenma right away.
♪ God's a weakling in his flesh ♪
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- Behave yourself and don't be rude.
as someone you wouldn't be able to see under normal circumstances.
Well then, I guess I should have brought an autograph book.
If you fool around, I'll kill you.
Come in.
Allow me to introduce you to my man, Martin.
You may leave now.
I'm saying that I want to speak to your man in private.
Yes, as you wish, sir.
If you even think about screwing this up,
I'm going to kill you.
- Do you mind if I sit down in this chair here, sir?
- Go ahead.
How long have you been working for the baby?
- Oh, it's been almost three years.
- And before that?
Prison, huh? How many years? I was in for 8. Murder? Something like that. Considering
the crime, you got out rather quickly. I must have been a model inmate. I hear you're a
model employee, too. I'll do whatever's required. Any kind of job at all. Except...
- Filled with work that involves women.
- Oh?
- Well, when it comes to jobs, I'm not really that picky.
But when it comes to women, I don't like to take
any kind of gig that might involve them.
- This involves a woman.
The job that I want you to do will require you
to keep watch over a certain woman for a while.
- What a terrible job.
- You'll go to Dusseldorf, pick up this lady,
and bring her back to me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're perfect for the job because you
don't want an assignment that would necessitate
your involvement with women.
So I don't need to worry about you.
You'll be able to keep things strictly professional.
Are you Ava Heinemann?
Who wants to know?
My name's Martin, but I'm sure my name doesn't mean anything to you because I was hired by somebody to pick you up and take you back to Frankfurt with me.
By whom?
A tall man wearing glasses and a rather expensive suit.
A tall man wearing glasses? He's not associated with Roberto, is he?
Look, I really don't know much about him, other than the fact that he seems to be very important.
If you don't want to make the trip, I won't force you. I'm not too thrilled with the idea myself.
Right now someone is after me you don't say so how would you like to be my bodyguard?
Well, that is kind of part of my assignment. Anyway, wait here
Carry it
Let's go this is better than letting him kill me
What a pain in the ass.
The way she swings her hips, the smell of her perfume.
This is infuriating.
I hate this job.
Why don't you talk to me, Martin?
Alright.
If that's what you want me to do, what exactly should we talk about?
I don't really feel like talking now.
Then let's continue to be quiet.
How about a drink?
Have any alcohol on you?
Sorry, but I never touch the stuff.
I'm going to check out the dining car.
O-oh...
I see, so you're traveling alone, huh?
As luck would have it, I'm also traveling by myself.
Hey, why don't you tell me where you're staying? I'll pay you a little visit later.
Ah, let me give you my card. You may need--
What are you doing, pal?
What am I doing?
This woman asked me for a drink, so I gave her one.
Don't you lay a finger on her.
You don't even talk while you're having dinner?
Like I said before, I'll talk if you want me to.
I'm just curious as to why you don't drink.
My mother was a terrible alcoholic, but I don't mind if you drink.
Doesn't bother me at all, really.
If your mother drank, I'm sure she probably had a very good reason.
Oh, you think so?
Yes, I do. And I should know I have a very good reason for my drinking.
You might as well go ahead and tell me about it.
If you don't want to eat your meal in silence.
It could take a long time.
Hey, I'm in no rush.
I used to have someone I was going to marry.
He was Japanese and a neurosurgeon, absolutely brilliant at his work.
So then, you know what I did?
I tried to shoot my former fiancé.
Well, aren't you surprised that I picked up the nearest loaded gun and tried to kill that
man?
But you didn't actually do it.
Let me assure you your story is a whole lot better than mine
I'm listening. Why is my story better? Tell me I want to know I
Shot her. I actually went and pulled the trigger
My girlfriend and some guy were going at it in the bedroom. I
Went and shot both of them until there were no more bullets in the gun
The room was filled with the smell of their blood and her perfume
and reality set in there I was standing in the middle of everything all alone
Wow you're an idiot you know that you're probably right
(sighs)
I hate this job.
My boss is waiting inside this hotel.
You said you killed people, so just keep your filthy hands off me.
Which room?
I'll take you up to 'em.
Your attire is inappropriate. There's a dress code for this hotel.
Just wait in the car.
Ask for room 1014.
I don't know what the man in glasses will say to her, but if she refuses his deal, this
crappy job will be over once and for all, and I won't have to see her anymore.
What's the matter?
You don't look like it went very well.
Actually, it wasn't such a bad offer.
He said I could use this card as much as I want to.
Well, come on already, let's get going.
Where exactly are we going?
On a little shopping spree.
I really hate this job.
- Next on our itinerary.
- This is a menswear store.
- That's very astute of you.
I'm buying you clothes to make you presentable.
- But I'm okay with the clothes I got.
- Well, I don't care for them.
I don't want the men accompanying me all day
to be dressed like a bung.
I like this one.
Now to find a necktie.
Kenzo hmm here go try this one on for me
Neckties I hate them
How is it well hmm you look a little better now
But fix your tie it looks sloppy like that
Stop walking that way. You look like a thug with your shoulders slouched down.
I think the way I'm walking is perfectly normal.
Your idea of normal is lowbrow.
I've decided that from now on I want you to be my escort.
That means wherever we might go, I want you to look and act normally.
Don't embarrass me.
That's your job. That's what you were hired for.
Yeah, that's my job.
Don't put your elbows on the table.
Huh?
Fork in your left hand, knife in the right.
Don't make sounds when you chew your food.
So it's all true then, right?
What do you mean?
You know, that you were the daughter of the director of a big hospital.
Did you think I was lying?
Before I brought you to this city, I thought you were just a sloppy alcoholic with a lot of rough edges.
What about now?
You're a classy looking lady.
The way I appear now is my true form.
Yes, Eva Heinemann has finally returned to her rightful place in the city.
What's that you're holding?
An invitation to a big party.
Party, huh? Yes, that's the job that was given to me. What are you talking about?
I was told I have to attend several social gatherings. That's all I really know
Aren't you happy could be a fun job for you. You're coming with me. Yeah
You must escort me and appear to be a gentleman worthy of accompanying me
Just when I thought this job couldn't get any worse
How does it feel, being back in the company of people from your old social circle?
What could possibly be so funny?
Jeez, I can't tell what any of these people are going on about.
The weather report. The stock market.
I don't even know what language they're speaking.
Sounds like gibberish to me.
I'm starting to feel sick.
Oh, there you are.
Yeah. Hey, you don't have to worry about me.
Enjoy yourself.
- Let's go.
- Huh?
- We're leaving.
- What?
Hey, hold on.
- My job here is done.
He's not at this party.
We can go now.
- Who's not?
What are you talking about?
- Take me away from here.
Anywhere at all is fine with me.
Just take me away now.
- I didn't know at the time.
why her hands were shaking well I've managed to survive the day what's wrong
thought you told me you returned to the place where you truly belong every day I
used to live like those people you saw at the party I thought once I entered
The real me would fit in and feel right at home.
So I guess...
now you've discovered that you only feel comfortable in places like this bar.
No! This isn't the place for me either!
This isn't it! That wasn't it!
No matter where I go, I don't seem to belong!
I already knew that about myself!
I don't fit in.
As soon as this job is completed,
I didn't want to be killed by Roberto in Dusseldorf,
where I was so worn and shabby.
I thought it would be better to be killed here,
where I could die as the beautiful Eva Heinemann.
But when you die, it's all the same anyway.
I wanted to protect her it's a bad habit of mine always has been right then I
thought I want to protect this woman
Nobody ever gets the drop on you.
How in the hell did this happen?
I'm going to tell everything to Dr. Tenma. Better hurry.
Just hang in there, Martin. We're very close. Almost there.
Damn Naitai. If I hadn't put this on, I never would have had to go anywhere near there.
I never would have had to see such terror.
[GASPING FOR AIR]
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]