Yeah, like I know what your usual is.
Come on, when are you going to remember, Robbie?
And here it comes, a double cheeseburger that's well done,
extra ketchup, and thick tomato slices.
And if I see any pickles, I'm going to kill you.
All right, I'll hold the pickles.
See that Chinese or Vietnamese guy down there, he's been asking me about you.
Lately, he shows up here pretty regular.
He was asking who you were.
Nah, from the look of him, that guy's not Chinese.
or vietnamese oh no i'm betting he's japanese i'd say he's a neurosurgeon and a brilliant one
yeah that sound about right dr kenzo tenma
answer me
your ex-fiance's father was director at the hospital where you worked
What are you planning to do with Ava?
Ava?
That's Miss Heinemann to you, punk.
What, do you think you're still engaged or something?
Besides, you're no longer a doctor.
You're a fugitive from the law.
Why don't you go and serve your time?
It's where you belong.
You might even get out someday if you behave yourself.
You have to let Ava go.
Let her go?
You're talking like you think I'm holding her hostage or something.
She does what she wants.
I mean, hell, she's been going to parties every night.
I want to see her. Now, where is she?
You want to see her?
Come on. I don't want my place getting trashed.
Knock it off.
If you know what's good for you, you won't come back.
A-Ava...
Forget her.
(upbeat music)
Hold on, you saw Kenzo?
Yeah.
Two days ago.
I just thought maybe you'd want to know.
Can you believe he was asking to see you?
When he asked about me, did you hit him?
Huh?
Course not.
- How can you do a thing like that?
- Come on, we're leaving.
- What?
You've decided you've had enough of this party?
Is that it?
- Not just for today.
The party's over, I think.
I think I'm done.
- Job well done, Eva.
Will you allow me to accompany you to dinner?
- Why not?
Let me get this straight.
You dropped her off with your client at a fancy restaurant, and you're eating dinner
here?
From the way I see it, Robbie, the burgers here are a lot better than any of the food
at those parties or expensive restaurants.
I don't know whether I should feel flattered or insulted by what you just said
You sure are persistent you want to get hurt again
Didn't you understand me last time when I
You behind the counter, don't move!
If you move, I'll shoot him.
Look at that, Robby. A doctor with a gun.
Who hired you?
I know that the baby is the regular boss that you usually answer to.
But the person who ordered you to escort Ava is someone much higher up in your organization.
Who gave you your orders?
I couldn't tell you what his name is.
But I do know his face.
The guy wears a pair of glasses.
and what exactly was Eva given as her assignment?
I thought I told you last time.
He's just got her going to all these high-class parties.
She eats and drinks and leaves.
That's about it.
That can't be all she does.
Whatever he's got planned for her,
it has to be more significant than that.
Eh, well, it's not.
Tonight, for instance.
I'm listening.
Ah, forget it. It's really no big deal.
All she did tonight was point at someone.
She pointed at someone yeah, she pointed at this young man a young man. What are you like this?
He was a young man with blonde hair and a pretty face
She pointed at him like I'm pointing at you right now. That was it
So, where's she now, where's Ava
Having dinner with my boss that guy with the glasses. I told you about where tell me quickly. Where are they?
Don't you see? That was all they needed her for!
As soon as this job is completed, I'll probably be killed anyway.
The party's over, I think.
Where is Eva?
Wait!
(tires screeching)
- Where is she?
- I had her taken back to her hotel.
Now tell me something, do you have a gun?
No, I don't, sir. I try not to carry one of those around. Too much trouble.
Well, in that case, use this.
Do it right. Finish her off.
That day, the party we went to took place the same as always.
The smell of drinks and perfume, the obscure conversations, the empty laughter.
same, except for that one moment, that moment when Ava pointed at somebody.
Once she did that, the man with glasses walked over with another well-dressed young man.
After sharing a few words, those two young men shook hands.
I didn't realize it at the time,
but it would appear that that's when Ava's job was over.
I guess I always knew that you would be the one they'd send to kill me, Martin.
- Go right ahead.
The drinks are doing their job nicely.
I have no real regrets about what I've done with my life.
(laughs)
Oh, sorry.
I forgot you can't shoot me here in my room.
You told me that when you shot your girlfriend,
you found yourself in a sea of blood,
so this setup won't work, right?
It'd be better if you take me outside and shoot me,
'cause if you don't, you'll have to pay
(laughing)
Wait, maybe I do have one regret.
I'm having second thoughts here,
but it doesn't really matter, does it?
I was wondering, exactly what did I do tonight?
You saw me point out that young man, didn't you?
You know, I think I might've done something terrible.
I just brought together a horrible man
and the devil himself.
It was like bringing together Mephistopheles and Faust.
But who the hell cares anyway?
Too bad that now that I've done my job,
all these party invitations are gonna get wasted.
But the good news is I still have my invitation
to the most important party, don't I?
Hey, after you shoot me, do me a favor.
Maybe you can go to these parties in my place
after I'm dead and see what I've done.
(gulping)
- So, now then, go on and finish me off.
- Let's run away.
I want you to run away with me.
(laughing)
- Where'd you come up with that idea?
Me, run away with you?
You're kidding, right?
Refresh my memory.
When did you and I become so close?
I can't do it. I can't kill people anymore.
You can't kill people?
Well, I bet that you can still kill a devil, because that's what I am!
You think I bought you that new suit and necktie because I like you?
Those are the same clothes that Kenzo used to wear!
Don't you get it? I was just turning you into Kenzo Tenma!
Just kill me already!
Come on! Do it! Quick! Kill me! Quickly! Kill me quickly, you big jerk. If you don't kill
Tell me quickly, they'll come to kill you too.
Kill the devil, huh?
Come on, Mom! Wake up!
It's all right. After a nap, I'll start sobering up.
Well, you can't nap now! You'll die if you go to sleep here!
I'll be fine. Just leave me here so I can rest.
(owl hooting)
You look depressed today.
What do you mean, Robbie?
I always look like this.
So tell me, has anybody come around here looking for me today?
Well, nobody knew, but that Japanese doctor guy from yesterday left you this.
The Hellbrow Hotel, room number 205.
He said to call him if anything happened.
So, what'll you have, Martin?
Do you want your usual?
Not today.
Fill my stomach with your lousy burgers,
and I won't feel like going anywhere.
Oh, yeah? Where are you going?
Another party.
[Chuckles]
It's amazing.
I can go anywhere if I have a necktie.
Just a single little necktie.
Jackpot. So, he's the devil? After shaking hands with what seemed like countless people,
Well, he left the party alone.
(suspenseful music)
- On the sixth floor, huh?
But which one is his?
- Good evening, why don't you please come inside?
Make yourself at home, have a seat.
(footsteps)
- So you want to meet him too, don't you?
- Meet who?
- I'm waiting for him as well.
He'll be here soon.
Since we've got some time to spare,
let's talk about something.
What would be good to talk about?
Oh, I've got it.
Why don't we talk about the end of the world?
- The young man continued talking cheerfully.
He was like a kid telling his parents about how much fun he had that day at school.
That was how he talked to me.
End of the world? Please.
Just a crazy maniac spouting nonsense.
That's what I thought at the time.
What do you think? It's interesting, isn't it?
Have I piqued your curiosity yet, Mr. Martin?
Hold on a second, kid. How do you know my name?
I just know. Now let's talk all about you, shall we?
You've worked for the baby for three years, haven't you?
What? Did you look into my background?
Before that, you served time in prison for eight years.
That must have been awful for you.
You were released early for good behavior.
For a guy that got convicted of murder, you certainly got out quickly.
Did you like living with your girlfriend?
I'm pretty sure you did.
I'm talking about the girlfriend you shot.
Her name was... Eda?
I think it's pretty rude of you to talk about her.
That Eda was quite the drug addict, wasn't she?
And you did your best to try and keep her off the stuff, didn't you?
Goodness, that's a pretty difficult thing to pull off.
Were you... in love then?
Were you asking me for a beating?
Then she quit the drug somehow.
All was bliss and she would wait for you to come home every night.
Together, the two of you were quite happy.
Are you asking for a beating? Answer me.
But then one night, when you returned to your room,
you saw something that really made your blood boil.
There she was, with her old boyfriend.
She'd been doing drugs again. It was written all over her face.
But once she saw you standing there,
all she could do was say the same thing over and over.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
But you shot her, along with her ex-boyfriend.
That was your story at the trial, after all. Why'd you lie?
That doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
The truth was, she killed herself.
Your lawyer figured out from the lab reports that she shot herself.
They found traces of gunpowder on her right hand.
You stuck to the story that you gunned her down.
Tell the truth. She literally begged you to kill her, didn't she?
Ha! Am I right? I'm dead on, aren't I?
I knew you weren't the one who shot her!
And she really was begging you to shoot her, wasn't she?
Oh, I could just see it.
Please, Martin, shoot me.
Please don't look at me like that.
Shoot me now!
I want you to kill me!
Martin!
It wasn't me!
She did it to herself!
I didn't shoot her, man!
(panting)
See?
It was me, right?
Right?
(gunshot)
- Isn't it amazing that I was able to figure it out?
I'm right, aren't I?
- You're wrong.
- You made the decision to leave her behind.
And by doing that, you gave her just what she wanted.
- Like hell.
- I'm right.
It was the same with your mother!
Your mother froze to death.
She died unexpectedly when you were ten years old.
You've got a long history of abandoning women, don't you?
Ha ha! I'm right again!
I knew it! Amazing!
I really have a gift for this! What a skill!
Every night, your mother would get stinking drunk and you'd carry her home.
Isn't that right?
And your mother would always tell you to just leave her where she was.
the street, but you wouldn't listen. Instead, you'd carry her home every time. But then
came that one night.
No, Mom. It's too cold. You can't sleep out here.
This weather's fine. Stop falling on me. Just lay me right here.
Mom, wake up!
You left her there. Isn't that true? You left your mother there.
The next day, the police came to your house and told you that your mother had frozen to death.
You thought that what happened wasn't your fault.
After all, you had left her there because she told you to.
And you're right. It wasn't your fault.
Your mother and your girlfriend both wanted to die.
You were helping people who wanted to die to find some relief.
Why torture yourself? You did the right thing.
Look, you freed the two of them from the agonies of their worthless lives.
Now there's Ava. She too wishes to die, Martin.
It was at that moment that the devil arrived.
I walked by the devil, careful not to look.
Like a child, I repeated to myself, "Don't look, don't look, don't you dare look."
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)