No, Mom! It's too cold! You can't sleep out here!
This weather's fine. Stop pulling on me. Just leave me right here.
"You left her there. Isn't that true? You left your mother there.
The next day, the police came to your house and told you that your mother had frozen to death.
What happened wasn't your fault. You had left her there because she told you to.
Your mother and your girlfriend both wanted to die.
You were helping people who wanted to die to find some relief.
Why torture yourself? You did the right thing.
Look, you freed the two of them from the agonies of their worthless lives.
Now there's Ava. She too wishes to die, Martin.
It was at that moment that the devil arrived.
I walked by the devil, careful not to look.
Like a child, I repeated to myself, "Don't look.
Don't you dare look."
Now there's Ava.
She too wishes to die, Martin.
I want you to kill me!
Just leave me right here.
Kenzo.
I'm not going to do the devil's bidding, because nobody really wants to die.
♪
(dramatic music)
(door creaking)
(rain pattering)
- So where is she?
- Who, Ava?
She's already gone.
- You mean you let her escape?
- I mean I finished her off.
- What do you think, I was born yesterday?
Tell me the truth.
- Hey, why would I lie to you?
- How pathetic, Martin.
- Pathetic how?
- You're about to lose your life over a woman.
[GUNSHOTS]
Are you awake?
Time to pay the piper.
They just pulled up downstairs.
They'll be up here in less than a minute.
I stole you a maid's uniform and put it on the chair.
down the back stairs but what about you if the two of us try to clear out of
here together they'll see us for sure and we'll be dead but if you don't make
a run for it now they'll get you I can handle them myself look there's an
address on the note on the nightstand over there I need you to get going it's
It's Tenma's hotel.
Now get dressed and get going.
I'll be waiting at the Frankfurt Central train station.
Let's run away together.
"This is no time for cracking jokes.
Just stick to my plan.
Dammit, Eva, listen.
You'll be a lot safer if you go to Tenma.
Besides, I know that's what you really want.
I'm not asking you to.
I'm telling you.
Now go."
"What makes you think I'll take orders from the likes of you?
I was just kidding see ya good don't get yourself killed doing something stupid I
don't plan on getting myself killed for anybody
That's right, I don't owe her anything.
I don't need to go that far for her.
[GRUNTS]
(glass shattering)
One,
two,
three,
and four.
(moaning)
(lighter clicking)
What do you know?
I survived.
So she'll be at the Frankfurt Central train station?
I'm out of bullets, I guess my luck just ran out, and so it goes.
(grunting)
- You bastard.
You friggin' idiot.
Aim for the head, damn it.
- This just in, a gun battle erupted just minutes ago
at the Reagan Motel in Sosenheim.
The police are calling a gang-related shootout.
Robbie, did you hear that?
Robbie, they're talking about my epic tale.
Robbie.
None of the employees were injured.
In other news--
We made it, Martin.
Where?
Frankfurt train station?
Hey, doctor.
I've done the best I can for him.
He's lost a lot of blood.
We need to get him to a hospital.
Don't bother.
It's too late for me.
I'm not an idiot, Doc.
But where's Ava?
I don't see her anywhere.
What do you mean, where's Ava?
I sent her here.
Didn't she come to see you?
Huh?
Why are you laughing, you moron?
Don't talk anymore.
Right now, I can't do that.
Listen close to what I'm about to say.
Time's short. Where should I start?
I know way too much about so many things that matter.
Listen, the Red Rose Mansion experiments are still going on.
So you know what that means, but there's more.
The devil now has an apprentice.
The two of them together, that man introduced them.
He's trying to create a dictator.
Which man?
The man with the glasses.
He survived the Red Rose mansion. I know what his name is.
His name is Peter Chappick.
Peter Chappick? Who is he?
He's trying to control the devil, but that devil's a lot more terrifying.
He's much too powerful to control.
He's too much.
Go to the Yahrzeit Hotel, room number 606.
The devil's apprentice, that's where he is.
But I'm warning you.
You should never look at the devil.
And you must never do the devil's bidding.
His apprentice, don't you believe his lies?
Nobody wants to die!
Martin, hold on!
I'm so happy. I'm happy knowing that I'll never have to look at the devil again.
Ava, Ava's waiting for me. She's at the Frankfurt Central Station.
I'm glad.
She probably bought two tickets for as far as we can go.
Ava, she's waiting for you.
Protect Ava. I beg of you.
Take care of her.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Martin, wait.
You've got to meet her at the station, right?
Wake up.
Just so you know, it's going to be a long time before the first
Here he comes.
Are you waiting for someone?
I'd say it's a man.
I know.
I've been working at this station for a long time.
Well, then tell me, do you think this man is going to show up?
I don't know the answer to that.
I'm not a fortune teller.
But the way I see it, having someone to wait for is happiness.
Happiness. Whether he shows up or not.
It's happiness?
Sure. When you get to be my age, those kind of feelings just don't happen to you much.
Guess it is happiness.
Hey now, is this the fella you're waiting for?
[FOOTSTEPS]
Kenzo.
Martin's not coming.
He's dead, Ava.
[GASPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I was wrong. I guess he's not the fella she was waiting for.
He was badly wounded when he came to me. He gave me some important information and told
me you were here. With the last bit of strength he had left.
You need to leave here, and quickly.
Ava.
We still have some time until my train arrives here.
Will you stay with me?
Of course.
You don't want something a little stronger?
Martin, he, well, he told me that he really didn't like alcohol.
Oh, I see.
Here's to Martin.
So, it's been a while.
Yeah.
Are you taking care of yourself?
You're looking pretty thin to me.
Yeah.
It's strange.
Here we are holding Martin's funeral like this over cups of weak diner coffee.
He was a good person.
I did heartless things to such a good man.
I treated him badly.
It's horrible.
I made him wear the same suit and necktie I gave you a long time ago.
It was a cruel joke.
How heartless and horrible I really am.
I'm so mean. Why am I still alive?
Please tell me.
Look what I've done to you.
I even lied about you to make you look guilty.
How have I survived to this point
considering all the bad things that I've done.
- You're alive because Martin protected you.
- Why the hell did he do that?
Why would someone like him protect someone like me?
- Because nobody wants to die.
That's what Martin said to me at the end.
Just knowing that you'd be here,
waiting at the station.
He told me it made him happy.
You aren't safe here.
Go to Munich.
I know a psychiatrist who lives there.
You mean Dr. Reikvein?
You know him already?
I do.
He's a good man. Dr. Reikvein will find a safe place for you. I promise he'll take good care of you.
Then go straight to the police. Tell them that the baby and his organization are after you, and they want you dead.
They'll also need to know that Roberto's after you. You're going to have to tell them everything.
I can tell them about you, too. That you haven't killed anyone.
I'll explain Johan did it all. I'll tell them everything.
So please come to Munich with me.
But he's right in front of me, Eva.
He's so close now. You saw him at the party, didn't you?
At last I have Johan right in front of me.
I've got to end this.
I can't let there be any more victims like Martin.
Do you understand?
Ava, I have to end this.
I'll send a letter to Dr. Reikvein.
I'll give him all the information I have,
In addition to whatever you can tell him, in person.
Oh, Kenzo...
Your train's about to leave.
But Kenzo, I think I could help more if...
The best way to help me is by doing one thing.
Go to Munich and tell the authorities everything you know about this.
[BELL RINGING]
[HORN HONKING]
I'm very pleased you were able to assist us in finding Johan.
I'm quite grateful to you.
I'd been told there was someone who matched his description here in Frankfurt.
That's precisely why I asked for your assistance in this matter.
Excuse me for interrupting your dinner, sir, but you have a phone call.
Fine.
Hello? What is it?
Johan?
I see. Where is he?
He's at an apartment on Haldekker Street.
So, he's at an apartment on Haldekker Street.
Well, Yohan. Even I can put an end to this.
Go to the Yahrzeit Hotel. Room number 606.
The Devil's Apprentice. That's where he is.
So you're the one that wants a gun, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I've got all sorts of 'em.
I'll take the biggest one you have.
Beginners can't handle really big guns.
Just what are you planning to shoot, lady?
A real devil.
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)