You got a job as a waitress and found a place to live.
And you got furniture, too.
But this bed is terrible.
I'm just sitting on it and it's tilting like it's gonna sink into the floor.
If you put all your weight on it, it'll fall apart.
So it looks like I'm gonna be the one sleeping on this bed.
You'll be more comfortable on that sofa.
There's no place for you to sleep, Dieter.
Huh?
It's time you packed up your things and returned to Dr. Reichwein's place in Munich.
Why should I?
You know very well, because you have to go back to school now.
I don't need school. I don't want to go.
And just how are you going to learn anything?
You can teach me what I need to know.
It's more than just your studies.
You won't be able to make any friends living like this.
Well, I already have friends, named Nina and Tenma.
Besides, you need my company.
You'd be very lonely if I wasn't around.
Nice try, but you're going back to Munich anyway.
No, I'm not!
Forget it. I'm not going to Munich.
Wait a minute, Nina. Are you going back there again today?
Stop it already!
You've got to give it up now.
You keep going to that same place every day.
No matter how many times you do it, it's always the same.
You never remember anything.
Nina!
The three frogs. We lived here. Mother and I. And Johan.
Here, that day, as he struggled, Johan was dragged down these stairs and taken away.
No! Let go of me! Stop! Mother! Nina!
That's wrong.
Because Nina's the name I have now.
So what was the name that mother called me way back then?
Nina? Anna? I can't remember which one was my name.
The car those men put Johan into traveled along this same road.
Keeping secrets from him is definitely a no-no.
They gathered all the children together every single Friday afternoon at three o'clock for
book readings here at the Red Rose Mansion.
Looks like the lock's broken.
This is where they worked trying to create a superior pupil.
What is a superior pupil?
Yohan...
And they...
But who did it? Who was responsible?
He escaped.
"Yohan ran away. He ran through the rose bushes."
"Are you alright? Was this the pain? The pain is...could it be? While I...was waiting
this room for mom to come home for Johan to come home I was reading this picture
book people can become whatever they want to be by Franz Bonaparta readings
of mr. Bonaparta's picture books were being held at the Red Rose Mansion at
the same time I was reading this one as I waited for Johan to come home
I stood in this room facing the front door.
I remember I was smiling and said…
"Welcome home."
Welcome home.
Welcome home. Welcome home.
Now, come with me.
The door won't open.
No matter how many times I said, "Welcome home,"
the door won't open.
The door won't open.
That's because I--
I remember.
Stop it, Nina.
You don't have to remember it.
You don't have to remember anything at all.
I'm the same.
I have lots of terrible memories floating around, too.
But I don't have to remember those things,
and neither should you.
All right.
I'll go back to Dr. Ragvines and go to school.
But you come with me.
Let's go back together, Nina.
Come on, why don't we do what Tenma said?
We'll make our own.
Good memories only.
From now on, Nina.
Hold on a second, Chief Detective.
You mean I'm to be an observer
We're complying with your request.
Under the circumstances, it's the best we can offer you.
The best, really? I'm being allowed 30 minutes per person to observe.
I don't think that's enough time.
It's sufficient. You're just going to be listening.
And I think it's extraordinary that we've done so much to cooperate with you in this matter.
We've finally been allowed to talk to these people,
but it'll be a miracle if we can get any usable information from them.
I need more time. I need to collect as many testimonies as possible.
Don't be naive.
Most likely these people won't remember or want to talk about anything from their pasts.
The book readings occurred when they were just kids.
My own personal theory is, the numerous bodies that our men were able to uncover at the Red
Rose Mansion must have some direct connection to the former Czechoslovakian secret police.
However, the truth in this case may never be known.
Things like this usually remain a mystery forever.
Ah, here's the detective who's in charge of the case.
This is the lawyer from Germany, Mr. Werdemann. I'll leave the rest to you.
I'm Detective Suk.
Nice to meet you.
I prepared a list of questions in advance. I'll be asking them.
Please, do as I say. I need your full cooperation.
You're only coming in here as an observer. I want to make that very clear.
Number 3, Cerveni Street, also known as "The Red Rose Mansion."
It burned down, and this photo shows what's left of it.
From what we've ascertained so far, you were there in 1968
and participated in weekly book readings, isn't that right, Mr. Erno?
Well, Mr. Erno?
Does the name Franz Bonaparta sound familiar to you?
Look, would you please be quiet?
We don't have much time.
I'm just trying to be careful!
If you're this careful, you'll end up with no information when you're done.
You have no idea how hard we've had to work to prepare them for this interview process!
I'm not feeling sad.
I had always thought that the mansion was my emotional foundation.
And as I was viewing this image of the burned remains,
I thought I'd feel very sad.
But there isn't a bit of sadness anywhere in me.
Do you feel at all nostalgic about the mansion?
Nostalgic?
Yes, because you spent a lot of time there.
The mansion was like a school to you, wasn't it?
Mr. Vertimon, would you please be quiet and let me ask the questions that I've prepared?
I'm not sure I know.
Feeling sadness.
Nostalgia.
I'm not sure.
Emotional scars?
What do you mean by that?
Let me ask it another way.
Do you believe your participation in those weekly book readings has in some way negatively affected you throughout your adult life?
Uh...
Not really.
in your family life?
You don't have to answer that.
Remember, you have the right to refuse.
Well, I'm divorced.
There really weren't any big problems between my wife and me.
We got along for the most part.
But my children,
my oldest son and my second son, both committed suicide.
They didn't seem to have any troubles or problems,
but for some reason,
They both killed themselves, and I've always had to wonder why.
Is there something you're trying to say?
I'll save you the trouble of figuring it out.
I feel your whole line of questioning is far too by-the-book.
So far, you haven't been able to get anything useful from anyone.
I think you typify the way today's youth operates.
If it's not in a manual, you're unable to make a move.
That probably applies to how you pick up women, too.
Who do you think you are, my father?
Father, for the record, I don't have a father.
And if I did, I wouldn't want one like you.
The next person may come in now.
Memories of the book readings, huh? I'm not sure.
Anything you can tell us, no matter how small.
The God of Peace was very busy.
Hey, come on! What are you trying to do?
He was so busy playing the trumpet,
he didn't have time to look in the mirror.
It's a passage from Klaus Pope's The God of Peace.
It sounds familiar, doesn't it?
It does. I kind of think I remember it.
And there was another one.
Yeah, it was about the monster from the west and the monster from the east.
I liked that one much better.
Could you describe what you liked most about these storybooks?
Hmm, how should I put it?
I guess I could say that they all took me away to a different world.
Different how?
Crying when you're sad.
Being happy as well as being afraid and fearful.
All those feelings just seemed to go away, I'd say.
Why did you feel that way about these books?
I really don't know.
Actually, I didn't feel anything about anything.
Even your name disappears. I didn't want it.
Think about it. That's true freedom.
That's what it felt like, anyway.
But why did you feel like that?
Did Franz Bonaparta teach you to feel that way?
Hmm. Was he the person who held all those readings?
Was that the name of the guy?
This is what you clearly remember learning
That's what I clearly remember? No.
One afternoon, while I was there, a man came by to visit the mansion.
He said he was from a radio station.
He mentioned a song that was a favorite of his called "Over the Rainbow,"
and he took the time to tell me about the Wizard of Oz.
What was his name, did he say?
Tell me! Tell me everything about him right now!
Calm down! What the hell are you doing?
Tell me!
Anything!
What's going on? What just happened in there?
Suddenly it's as if your questions have personal feelings attached to them!
It's personal for you too, right?
You're the young detective who was framed for the series of crimes that were actually committed by the secret police.
That was you, wasn't it, Detective Suk?
You're desperate to dispel all the allegations and suspicion around you.
Am I wrong?
You and I are the same.
My father was imprisoned for working as an East German spy during the Cold War.
I always believed that he was falsely accused.
Then I found out that he was a spy all along.
I could no longer believe in anybody.
I no longer believed in anything in the world.
I'm pursuing a case involving a man who's truly innocent.
So now I found somebody I can believe in again.
That man from the radio station the witness was talking about?
That man was my father.
My father might have taken part in the brainwashing experiments that occurred at the Red Rose Mansion.
I mustn't look away. I have to find out the truth.
Say, may I go home now?
It'll be just a bit longer.
That man from the radio station that I was talking about?
to me. He said, "You get out of here fast. There's a wonderful land somewhere over the
rainbow. That's where your family is," he said to me. "Dorothy, the brave little girl
from the Wizard of Oz, is able to go back home in the end. You have to get out of here
too," he said. "Go home." So then directly after that, I cut all my
ties to the mansion. Have you heard enough? My wife and kid are waiting on me at home.
Yeah.
You mustn't look away.
I know.
We need to finish. There are two more.
All right. Let's keep going.
Come on, Dieter, stay focused.
I need you to hold this while I work.
After all, it's going to be your study desk.
Nina doesn't want to talk about anything
that happened in Prague just yet.
According to what I heard from you,
she's recovered quite a bit of her memory.
She's probably thinking about those things in her past.
But it seems that right before her memories
fully come back to her, she just stops remembering.
And that's because of you.
I keep wondering if maybe I did something bad.
- No, you certainly didn't.
You did a very good job, Dieter.
Now, what do you say we finish
putting this desk together quickly
so we can go have ourselves some weisswurst?
- Did you forget?
We ate all the weisswurst last night.
- What do you mean we ate it all?
Oh, darn it, you're right.
- Doctor!
We brought you something.
It's your favorite, weisswurst.
- How considerate of you, my boy.
You've saved the day.
- Dr. Reichfein, how are you?
I'm sorry for not contacting you for so long.
I'm sure I've had you worried.
But I'm fine.
The truth is, Dr. Reichwein, I have a favor to ask.
I believe you know Eva Heinemann, don't you?
She's being targeted by a certain organization right now.
I've sent her in your direction.
Please take good care of her.
And please, look after Nina and Dieter as well.
It'll all be over soon. I believe that there is only one way I can put an end to this.
Sincerely, Kenzo Tenma.
Tenma's letter arrived here about three days ago, but so far Ava hasn't shown up. There's been no sign of her.
I'm wondering what city this letter was sent from.
The postmark doesn't show up clearly. Is there a way to figure it out?
Probably. I'll try.
Then we'll know where Tianmei is, right?
Yeah, but in the meantime,
I'm a bit worried about this last sentence that he wrote.
It'll all be over soon.
I believe that there is only one way I can put an end to this.
Enough of that.
Let's go finish that study desk.
I could use your help.
I hope that beer won't impair my coordination.
Dr. Reichwein, I want to remember all the memories from my past.
When you remember them, are you prepared for the consequences?
Yes. I'm ready for you to try any means necessary to bring back my full memory.
To be honest, I don't want to try anything myself.
However, let me see what I can do if that's what you really want.
You're sure you're alright with this?
Yes, Dr. Gillen. But...
Hmm?
After you've put me in a hypnotic state, there might be some things...
that are absolutely terrifying.
Will you face them with me, Dr. Gillen?
Don't worry, Nina. I'll be here.
Every step of the way.
First, I want you to close your eyes.
Next, take a deep breath and release it, relaxing your whole body.
Tell me, what was your mother like?
My mother?
My mother was gentle,
the songs, the singing,
a very beautiful voice,
the smell of pea soup that she always made for us.
What about your father?
My father was…
a government soldier.
A government soldier?
Did you ever meet your father?
I never had a chance.
My mother told me what happened to him.
My father, he was killed.
My mother was a political activist.
Your mother, who had taken part in anti-government activities,
fled the country with her children when your father was killed.
Who was she running away from?
She moved us into the Three Frogs.
We had to hide there.
But then one day my brother was caught
by a man with glasses.
When your brother was caught, where did they take him?
To the Red Rose Mansion!
A lot of people died that day.
Did your brother see what happened to the people?
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts! The thorns hurt!
Welcome home.
Can you hear me, Nina?
I got it. I found out where Tenma's letter was mailed from.
Well, where?
It was Frankfurt.
Nina, you've remembered everything now, haven't you, Nina?
Not Nina. It's not my name.
Well, who are you then?
I don't want to say.
There's nothing to be afraid of. You can tell me. It's all right.
Who am I talking to?
Don't be afraid. You're safe here.
Don't wanna say.
Back!
And back!
I'm going to clap my hands right now.
And when I do, you're going to wake up from your trance!
Nina!
We're all right now.
Did I… Did I say something really terrible?
No, but while you were hypnotized, you refused to tell me everything, Nina.
But I'm sure you remember all of it now, isn't that right?
Dear Dr. Reichwein, Dieter,
Please forgive me for leaving so suddenly.
I'm going to Frankfurt, where Tenma is.
I know everything.
Who I am, where Johan came from, and where he is headed.
If I go, I can put an end to everything.
If I go, I can save Tenma.
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)