Listen, the Red Rose Mansion experiments are still going on.
The devil now has an apprentice, the man with the glasses.
'cause he survived the Red Rose Mansion.
I know what his name is.
His name is Peter Czapek.
He's trying to control the devil,
but the devil's a lot more terrifying.
Follow that car.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
There he is!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(tires screeching)
(knocking)
(choral music)
(rock music)
*Beep*
[silence]
[door creaking]
[footsteps]
Hello there.
Where am I?
[footsteps]
[door creaking]
You've finally come too.
- How do you feel? - I'm good, I guess.
You were lucky. You only sprained your ankle.
And from the looks of things, it didn't hit your head too hard.
- But I'm not a real expert like you are. - So you know who I am, then?
Dr. Tenma, the brilliant neurosurgeon.
- Saw you in the paper. - Who are you?
Me? I'm a dentist here in the area. Milan Kolosh.
I happened to be out for a walk when I saw you get hit by a car.
I can tell you, it was in a big hurry to get away.
Where do you think you're going?
I-- I don't want to trouble you.
Well, you know what would trouble me even more?
If you were to limp onto the street
and get yourself caught by the police around here.
Around here?
That's right.
This is Frankfurt's Turkish district.
Turkish district?
Scratch that.
I should say this was the Turkish district.
Almost all of this area is being cleared for redevelopment.
You see, for many years,
it was mostly Turks who lived in this neighborhood,
but now they've all moved out.
A while back, these right-wing extremists
tried to burn down the whole neighborhood,
but everyone who lived here joined together,
and we fought them.
- So is the Cafe Bahir still around, or did it close?
- Yeah, that place is shut down.
Hey, wait a sec. You know this area?
- Yes, a little.
- Well, if you can get up
with the rest of us.
Food tastes much better when it's shared.
Guess we're having Vietnamese food today.
That soup's for Ga, and there's some chai at home.
Minh makes really exceptional Vietnamese food.
Now don't be shy, eat.
- Delicious.
- I love pork myself, but the Turks forbid it.
is actually against their religion.
We don't really do much Czech cooking, do we?
That's only because Milan is terrible at cooking.
Sorry about that.
Each of us takes turns cooking the cuisine
of our own homeland.
It's wonderful to be eating food from different countries
every day, don't you think?
You're Japanese, aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
Tell us what Japanese food is like.
Oh, Japanese food, well--
That sounds good.
Maybe you could make us some.
I'd like to try it.
- Don't make katsudon because it has pork.
Sushi is raw fish and some people have a problem with that.
Wait, I could make oyakodon for you.
- Oyakodon?
- It means parent and child bowl.
It's chicken covered with eggs and sauce on rice.
- Why is that dish called an oyakodon?
- Well, the chicken is the parent and the egg is the child.
- A parent and child bowl?
(laughing)
- Who knew Japanese cooking had such a sense of humor?
- How funny calling the chicken and eggs
parented childs.
(laughing)
- Is something wrong, Doctor?
- It's nothing.
- Oh, is the food not to your liking?
- No, it's quite delicious.
It's fantastic food.
What a wonderful dinner this is.
It's been such a long time.
"Cafe Vinyl"
Well, good night, Doctor.
See you tomorrow.
So how long will it take until I can walk on this ankle?
I don't have any time to waste.
(eerie music)
- It's Peter.
Chapik.
A gun.
A report documenting Peter Chapik's movements.
- You knew something was odd.
Well, the police didn't converge here
so they could catch you, Dr. Tenma.
The truth is, the police were on that street
because they're on the lookout for me.
Peter Chapek is going to die by my hand.
Aw, no good.
Well, that's strange.
I used to be able to make paper airplanes that flew pretty well.
Milan's really good at making paper airplanes.
Yeah, they fly all the way to that roof over there.
I see.
Melon talks to both of us a whole lot.
And he's always making promises.
Soon enough, children will fly much farther than those rooftops over there.
We'll fly to Turkey, to Vietnam, and even the Czech Republic,
and all of us will get to see each other's homelands.
Right?
Yep.
Here goes!
- Huh? - Huh?
- Too bad. That wasn't so good.
- Why won't it fly?
- Aw, who knows?
- Peter Chapek is going to die by my hand.
- But why? Tell me, Milan.
Why would you want to do something like that?
- I'll tell you why.
Because that man, Peter Chapek, is the devil.
- [chuckles]
- In 1989, under a cloak of darkness
on the night before communism collapsed completely
in Czechoslovakia, Čapek escaped into this country.
He settled right here in Frankfurt
and began giving lessons to children
as a German language teacher.
He was a quiet man who appeared to be thoughtful.
But after a while,
the children who had attended his classes changed.
One by one, the children who left his tutelage
began to commit suicide.
And others began to display extremely violent tendencies.
Finally, one day, there was a massive, violent eruption.
They were stopped, but the children were trying to kill each other.
While he was in custody, I questioned the boy who was the ringleader of the incident.
I asked him why he had done it.
He sat with his head down and mumbled,
"I want to go back to the book reading."
The book reading?
While he was there that night, that poor boy found a way to kill himself.
And that boy was my son.
Chapek disappeared from town suddenly, during the rioting caused by the extremists.
After a while, he finally resurfaced again.
We could see he was a different person.
He was leading an underground organization in Frankfurt,
and had aligned himself with right-wing extremists.
He then began to implement his agenda by expelling Turks and other foreigners from town.
Even though I've studied him, I don't really know exactly what Čapek is trying to do here.
But I know in 1996 he was the instigator of the riots.
It was hell-bent on burning down the entire Turkish district, and us with it.
I bet you remember hearing about that incident.
I do. From the news.
The townspeople formed a community defense squad
as a way to fight the extremists.
However, in just three months' time,
the five leaders appointed to the community defense squad
all met an untimely death.
One by one, they all died in strange ways.
- And who were these five leaders that died?
- Suleiman's son,
Tung's father,
Min's husband,
Mustafa's son,
and Shemal's father.
They didn't simply die, they were murdered, all five, by Peter Chappick.
I don't know exactly why you're interested in Peter Chappick, but I will tell you this,
the man who's going to kill Chappick will be me.
"From the way this one's coming together, I think it should fly pretty well."
"It's hopeless."
"Not if we try hard."
"Even if we try hard, it's still not gonna fly right.
I know impossible's impossible.
Just like there's no way that we're gonna get to go on a trip to Turkey and Vietnam.
It's not like we have to go on a trip.
We like living here with Milan and everybody else, isn't that right, Tom?
Mm-hmm.
Our plane is finished. I bet it'll fly this time.
Here goes. See what I mean?
Oh!
Wow! Look! It's flying!
That's amazing!
It might not make it past those rooftops like Milan's do, but still, at least it's flying.
You mustn't ever give up.
What have you done with my gun?
My gun isn't in the drawer anymore.
Where is it?
I've got a chance to kill Peter Chapek tonight.
I'm going right now.
Give me my gun.
I'm sorry, but I can't let you do that.
I can't let you use your gun to kill that man.
I found this pistol I'm holding inside of your coat.
I want to do the job with the gun that I've trained with,
the one I'm used to shooting.
Come on, just show me where you put my gun.
You've all created a wonderful family here.
You shouldn't do anything to endanger them.
I've been following Chapek and tracking his movements for a long time.
My best chance to take him out is right now.
Please listen, Milan. I'm asking you not to do this.
I've already told you. I've got to kill him.
Even if you take your revenge, your son can't come back to you.
Think of what you have now.
You think you have the right to say that to me?
Please, Milan.
Your path and mine are almost exactly the same, right, Dr. Tenma?
I looked you up and found out some things about you.
And if what you said is true,
then both of us are trying to complete the same exact mission.
Peter Chapek wasn't always like this.
I knew him way back, before he became a devil.
(Peter gasping)
Peter Chappick and I were childhood friends.
We both came from the same place.
I was the one who invited him to come to this country.
Milan, do you know what's on the other side of the border?
You're not allowed to go there.
I know we're not allowed, but do you know what's out there?
I've heard there's this wonderful place beyond the border.
There's a town over there that's lit up all night.
Is that really true, Peter?
And who'd you hear that from?
Oh, Mr. Greger told me.
Yeah, but he's an alcoholic.
Well, I've heard beyond the border,
there's something that ruins people and kills their spirit,
so they wind up just like him.
There's something that ruins people? Really?
I sure would like to see that.
Why would you want to see that?
Go!
Wow! It caught the wind!
You're really good, Milan!
It's flying so far!
That's amazing.
That plane might actually cross the border.
Go see what's on the other side for us, OK?
Peter and I were raised in a quiet town that was on the
Czechoslovakian-Austrian border.
I was the son of a laborer, and his father was a bureaucrat.
But strangely enough, we were good friends.
In 1989, the Czechoslovakian communist regime collapsed, and
our small world changed forever.
And the one who helped him escape to freedom was me, his
friend. The one who invited that devil into this country.
I have to admit, I was worried about you during the Soviet invasion last year, Peter.
Many people that I knew well were dragged off, but thankfully I myself am safe and sound.
How about you?
- Oh, me?
I guess you might say I found my calling.
I'm making a living with my hands now as a dentist.
- You always were good with your hands,
so now instead of making paper airplanes,
you're pulling teeth, huh?
- I'd rather be like you and have the kind of skills
that get you ahead in this world.
- Even after the Soviet invasion, I prospered.
Maybe it's because of those skills you envy
that I still enjoy my current status.
To be perfectly honest,
I was having a lot of fun during the Prague Spring.
- Remember how we talked about that when we were young?
Always wondering what the other side was like.
So did you get your answer?
- I got it.
- And?
- There was nothing special on this side or that side.
Sure, this country is broken,
but that doesn't mean that the other side is any better.
- I see.
- Earlier you said I'm good at getting ahead in the world.
Well, recently I found someone
who actually wants to use my skills.
- Oh yeah?
His way of thinking is so captivating that when you finally meet him,
I bet you'll stop being so concerned about falling behind in the rat race.
Hmm.
Once I finally came to the realization that there was nothing better about this country or that one,
he gave me a completely different vision of life.
He is the one who'll bring forth something entirely new.
Yeah? So what's this new thing he's gonna bring forth, Peter?
What does he create? Well, my friend...
The results could be something rather frightening.
Thinking back on it now, something inside him might have started to break down then.
Now give me back my gun.
Here, let me give you back your gun, Doctor.
Don't do it, Milan. Nothing good can possibly come of this.
It's no use talking. I'm going to kill him.
You're willing to lose everything you have right now, your family?
You're forgetting he killed several members from that family.
In a very real way, I am the one to be blamed here because I brought him to this country.
They were killed. Even my son.
When they tried to burn down this neighborhood,
there was one person who all the Turks around here talked about and they praised him.
a Japanese man who tended to the wounded with absolutely no regard for his personal safety.
You're that man, aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
I believe in you, Doctor, and I mean that.
And I know what you're trying to do.
You and I are exactly the same.
I'm going. It's time.
If I let this chance go by, I may never have another.
Please, Mi-Lan.
Thank you for trying to stop me.
Thank you.
You know, Tin-Ma,
if the tables were turned,
I doubt that I could stop you.
(dramatic music)
- Hey, gotta go! - Go!
(gunshots)
- This is so tasty!
- Yeah, it's different, but it's really good.
- Japanese Oyakodon is really delicious.
(laughing)
- Is your leg all right with all this standing?
Can I lend you a hand, Dr. Tenma?
- No thanks, I'm almost done preparing your bowl, Min.
- Milan's running late tonight,
but I'm sure that he'll be home very soon.
- Well, Oyakodon tastes much better
So I'll make meal on his bowl as soon as he gets back.
In other news, a tragedy struck at about 11 a.m. at the Rottelheim Convention Center in Frankfurt today.
A man with a handgun opened fire into a crowd of businessmen.
However, police stationed at the convention, providing security, shot and killed the gunman.
Thankfully, there were no other casualties as a result of this attack.
Due to the large number of important financial figures present, there was significant cause for concern among the attendees.
One man's identity and motives are still unknown.
We turn now to footage from the time of the incident.
Everyone says it's delicious.
They really love it.
Well, I certainly hope Milan gets home soon.
And now we turn to the footage of today's incident.
I know that man.
Back at the Red Rose Mansion. He was there.
Keeping secrets from him is definitely a no-no.
[MUSIC]