Did you get the reception guest list?
Yes, it's right here. We've been going over it.
We've got a pretty good handle on who was there and their vantage point at the time of the incident.
So isn't it most likely that this guy was targeting the governor?
The guests were all VIPs. I'll bet all of them have enemies.
Well, keep checking around for any connections he may have with any of the guests.
The people here at Frankfurt Station are certainly abuzz over the convention center shooting. Very busy.
Although we've identified the attacker, we still don't know who he was aiming for when he pulled the trigger.
Oh, you were able to nail down his identity.
Yes. He was a dentist living in the redevelopment area.
A dentist? Damn, I don't like to hear that.
Why is that, sir?
Well, I've been so busy every day that I never seem to find the time to see one.
So I was thinking of going to a dentist and having some work done as soon as I retire.
But a gun-toting dentist kind of gives me the creeps.
As you can see, I'm Inspector Visbon, North Rhine-Westphalen Police Department.
Reinhard Dinger, age 42, taxi driver by profession, arrested in Frankfurt, suspected of killing
a passenger in Gunther Forrest Park, as well as the murder of Bilker Investment Bank employee
in '97, the '96 Hoffgarten murder, the '95 Rhine-Riverside murder, the Hilden
Dinger is wanted for all these murders which occurred around the Dusseldorf area.
I now affirm that the suspect is being transferred to the state of Nordrhein-Westfalen.
Is everybody ready to move him?
Yes, sir.
Come on.
All right, let's go.
Want a drink?
No, I'm good.
Smoking's not allowed.
There's a sign in this car that says smoking is prohibited.
Oh, you're right.
If only you had stuck to your morals that well instead of going around killing people.
You have any idea how many you've killed with those hands?
Watching you count irreplaceable lives on your fingers, I know the dead won't rest in peace.
I'm happy to say this will be my last assignment.
I'm retiring tomorrow.
It wasn't an impressive career.
Not stellar, but not bad if I do say so.
Now I can tend to my garden and relax and just enjoy being with my wife.
That's what life is really all about.
I want you to realize what wonderful moments you took from all those lives that you crushed. I want you to regret it
Even when a man spits on me you want me to regret it what?
Some man I picked up on Adler Street spat right on me when he was getting out of my cab
You mean you killed him just for that?
Spitting on another human being should be a crime. I mean is there any worse insult
The couple I picked up at Gerasheim Station were a whole lot worse.
They started having sex right there in the backseat of my cab.
In the backseat of my own taxi cab.
They asked for it, so I killed them both.
And a drunk teenager who had a really foul mouth on him.
A prostitute who tried to pay her fare with her body until I stopped her.
An old lady with smeared makeup who kept insulting everybody she saw.
All kinds of people took a ride in my taxi cab.
They were all just a lousy bunch of scum.
That's why I killed them.
- Well then, let me ask you a question.
What was it about that Bilker Investment Bank employee
that you murdered?
Exactly how was he scum?
An upstanding citizen who worked hard
and never smoked or drank
and loved his family with all his heart.
However, because you killed him, a certain corporate finance scandal that he was going to blow the whistle on remains an unsolved mystery
Ah, that one. It did leave a bad aftertaste
Look at you. You talk as if you're delivering holy retribution when you're really just trying to justify your actions
Well, that time, I didn't have a choice
Why? Did somebody force you to do it?
I can't tell you that, Inspector.
I told you, you can't smoke in here.
If you put another of those filthy cigarettes in your mouth, I swear I'll kill you.
Tell me something if you can. What made you turn out this way?
I've always been a righteous thinker. Things have to be correct.
I just got a little push on the back and that's all it took.
That morning, a man was walking his dog in the park when I came along.
The guy started kicking the dog, just for taking a crap.
The dog was whining as he kicked it.
All it had done was heed the call of nature.
So I made him stop.
The next thing I knew, the police were pulling me off of him.
Right at that moment, a boy appeared.
He watched, and then he suddenly spoke to the officers.
He told them it wasn't my fault.
He said the man with the dog had started the whole thing by attacking me in the first place.
He saved me from getting arrested.
I thanked the boy and offered to drive him home, but he said he had no home to go to.
It was odd, but I thought, "Okay."
Then he brought out his sister from the bushes in the corner of the park.
His twin sister.
I'm figuring I have no choice.
So I took them both back home with me to my apartment.
Here's the strange thing.
When they arrived, they took off their jackets and were wearing pajamas.
It was as if they had escaped from a hospital or something.
I figured they'd come from a hospital though, because the boy had a bandage around his head.
After we ate dinner that night, we watched the news.
I muttered to myself, as I usually do about stuff going on in the world,
"What depraved people there are. What a depraved world.
The bastards should die!"
And what do you think the boy said to me right after I muttered that?
He told me I was absolutely right.
And you won't believe what he said to me after that.
We don't need people like that.
That's the moment when I was totally liberated.
That's completely insane!
You mean to say that's when you started killing all those people?
- Well, that's it, Inspector. - Yep.
Your last job has been completed without any incident.
Yeah, and all I gotta do now is clear out my desk.
Thank you for the years of work you've put into the force, sir.
I feel a little frustrated, though.
There were still a couple of unsolved cases left.
Uh, what is it, Inspector Vizba?
Then he brought out his sister, his twin sister.
Both were wearing pajamas, as if they'd just escaped from the hospital.
Don't you remember anything about that night?
Could be anything.
Anything at all that you can recall.
Anything?
Hmm?
You know your name, don't you?
Isn't that right?
I figured they'd come from a hospital, though,
because the boy had a bandage around his head.
The twins! The boy and the girl!
They're gone, sir! We can't find them anywhere!
Uh, Inspector?
Huh?
You want to know how long ago it was when I met the twins?
Let's see...
About eleven years ago.
Can you describe them?
Think now, what did that little boy and girl look like?
They were very good-looking kids.
Yeah, pretty blonde twins.
God, I can't believe it.
The twins who disappeared that day.
The twins who hold a very important key to Dr. Tenma's case.
I'll be damned.
Only thirty hours left until my retirement.
A vampire.
I see.
So that's why you had to drink the blood of those thirteen people, in order to live.
Not just anybody, virgins.
I understand. So, let me ask you a question. Three months back, you killed someone. A girl from a general store in Frankfurt.
Her name was Frieda Schilling. Did you drink her blood, too?
Now, as you yourself have said, all of the people you've attacked up until this time have been teenage girls.
And you waited until you had researched their behavioral patterns for quite a while before assaulting them.
I understand that they had to be young because you need virgin blood in order to stay alive.
But this victim, Frieda Schilling, wasn't a teenager.
She was twenty-one, although she appeared to be much younger, as though she were in
her teens.
However, that's not really the problem here.
Frieda Schilling had worked at a cafe on Zeiler Street in Frankfurt since she was sixteen.
It was very close to a famous school, and the boys who attended that school were very
goddess. No surprise then, she gave birth to a baby at the age of 17. According to
various rumors, the father was a student from that famous school. Shortly after
the baby was born, her parents opened a general store. The family of the boy who
got her pregnant was very rich. With the money they received from them, her
parents were able to start the new shop. You knew that, didn't you? Since you did
thorough research into the other cases, I'm sure you also did it for this one.
Do you also drink the blood of girls who aren't virgins?
That one left a real bad aftertaste.
So why is it that you went after her?
I met someone.
He's the real thing.
What are you talking about?
I knew as soon as I met him.
I knew right then that I was nothing more than a mere blood-sucking bat who was just trying to be what he already was.
But he was a real vampire, no doubt about it.
So you're saying that was the man who asked you to do it? Who was it?
Where did you and this guy meet?
At a park outside of Frankfurt, in the suburb of Griesheim. It was a park just like any other one, nothing special about it.
There was a sandbox in that park. He wrote her name in the sand with a tree branch.
So then, I just knew who I was supposed to kill.
Do you know who this guy was?
Like I said, he was a genuine vampire.
It's strange when you think about it, isn't it?
Your murder of Erich Klemperer four months ago was all the way over in Frankfurt, when
all of your other missions were in Niedersachsen.
So why did you go to Frankfurt for this one?
a signal from the aliens this time as well?
Did they tell you they changed their minds and that you had to go kill someone in Frankfurt
rather than your usual area?
Or was there perhaps another reason behind your decision?
Klemperer certainly had a sordid history, that's for sure.
He escaped from East Berlin during the Cold War and managed to do well in the food commerce
business over the past several years.
persistent rumors that he smuggled young children over the east-west border as well.
In other words, he took children from the east side and sold them to childless couples
on the west who had the wealth to buy them.
I didn't get a message from the aliens. I met one in person.
It was very moving. An alien was standing directly in front of me, face to face.
Where exactly did the UFO land?
at a public park in the middle of Griesheim.
He spoke the language of the cosmos,
so to make it easier for me to understand,
he wrote letters in the sand.
I wish you could feel it,
the excitement that I felt so strongly.
So, are you all packed up to go, Inspector Vizba?
Yep.
We're all counting down the seconds to your retirement.
Everybody wants to get rid of me so bad, they're doing a countdown, eh?
Exactly.
Tonight we'll celebrate the riddance of a great nuisance by drinking.
Oh, and telling stories about working with you.
Sounds like it might be a rather unpleasant evening.
[laughs]
Who's that fellow?
Oh, him. Dr. Gillen. He's a criminal psychologist.
Apparently he's come here today to interview Reinhard Dinger, your serial murderer taxi driver.
Here at somebody's request?
Don't think so. It seems to be for some paper he's writing.
He's got influence in his field, so he can convince the big shots to give him permission.
And so, when the man got out of your taxi and spat on you, you ran him over.
Yeah.
I've said this over and over again during interrogations, that the people I killed were
all unnecessary individuals.
You guys don't get it.
You just can't seem to understand my righteousness.
Righteousness, huh?
Fine, then let me ask you another question.
You've always been pretty forthcoming during interviews, but you seem to have quite a hard
time discussing your murder of Fritz Oberth, the Bilker bank employee.
You have consistently claimed you were in the right as the main justification for committing
every one of the other murders, but that's missing when you try to account for this killing.
You've never given an acceptable reason for why you murdered Oberth.
I don't want to talk to you anymore. I'm done.
Dr. Gillen, how'd it go in there?
My name's Inspector Visbaugh.
Was there anything academically or scientifically interesting that Dinger was able to tell you in his interview?
Nothing. Aside from what he's already said before many times.
Excuse me.
Actually, I want to talk to him again.
There's something I really need to ask him about, face to face.
Today I retire from the force,
but I won't feel right until I get this out of the way first.
What do you think about this academically, hmm?
Suppose there was a monster-like child
who grew up and visited a man who owed him something from the past
You're right. I know it's an absurd story. Sorry I mentioned it.
No, let me hear more about it. I'm very interested.
Now you both want to grill me?
No way. I already said I'm finished talking to Mr. Researcher here.
My final shift hasn't ended yet. I'm still a detective.
This is an interrogation.
And it's regarding those twins I asked you about.
about yesterday you said the boy had liberated you that's when you began your
killing spree I'm just wondering if that little boy grew up and then 11 years
later came back to you and asked you to do something for him no matter what it
was he wanted would you have done it for him
well now I just don't know let me be more specific did you commit the murder
the banker, at the request of someone who asked you to do it.
This was a diligent man, and honest as well.
That's the kind of person Mr. Oberth was.
Quite unlike the scum you so often claim to be eliminating.
And this was the man who was about to blow the lid off of a corporate corruption scandal.
If you call him scum, the moral justification for your crimes is shattered.
"It wasn't a request, Inspector.
He and I didn't even need to speak to each other."
"Who's that?"
"For whatever reason, that bank employee was probably scum to him.
At least, that's what I tell myself."
"Why?"
"Because I think he's right.
That's why."
"And who is he?
Is he one of those grown-up twins?"
"When did you meet him?
And where was it?
In Griesheim, at a little park in the middle of the town.
At a park outside of Frankfurt? In the suburb of Griesheim?
At a public park in the middle of Griesheim.
There was a sandbox for kids and he wrote a name in the sand.
He didn't say anything, but I knew anyway.
He wanted me to kill the man whose name he had written.
words. We understood each other. We don't need people like that in this world.
What does it mean? It appears that all three men you interviewed may have killed someone
at the request of the same man. By having three unrelated serial killers perform the
acts, the significance of these murders would be much harder for anyone to spot.
The significance would be harder for anyone to...
What does all of this mean? Fill me in, for God's sake!
Dr. Tenma and Nina are both headed to Frankfurt.
It's Johan!
Unless I miss my guess...
He's definitely trying to start something in Frankfurt.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)