First came bouquets. So many they wouldn't even fit in my dressing room.
Next came designer clothes and handbags.
And finally, jewelry with rocks bigger than anything I'd ever seen.
I never knew who these wonderful gifts were coming from.
"It was you, wasn't it?"
"I must admit, I felt something special when I saw your show for the first time."
"Something special? Was it my boobs or my ass?"
"It's something that can't be seen."
"I wish you had come by my dressing room to meet me in person."
"What, even someone like me?"
"Huh? What do you mean?"
It seems you actually care. I feel you'd really listen to me and I like that.
This is so delicious!
I've never had food this good before!
Have as much as you like.
- It's just incredible.
Does the baby eat like this every night?
- Yes, sometimes the food tastes good
and sometimes it doesn't.
It all depends on the company.
- Do you always have a whole lot of company
surrounding you when you eat?
I'm used to eating meals by myself.
- Yes, there's always a crowd as long as I get to check.
- Really?
So why do you do it?
- I wonder about that.
Come to think of it,
no matter how many dining companions I've had
No matter how much they enjoyed themselves, I've always felt like I was eating alone.
And right now?
I'm having a lot of fun.
Well, that's good.
Do you think we could make this a regular thing? You know, us dining together?
Sure we could. But eating at places like this all the time could be tiring.
It's been strange lately.
Strange?
The way I'm feeling. I've never felt like this before.
For many years, right here in the city of Frankfurt,
I've worked long hours to build my kingdom.
I struggled hard and fought many battles to create a new order.
It was my dream to become like the Fuhrer, Adolf Hitler.
I've always had a dream, too.
My dream was to become a famous dancer.
So what I'm doing right now isn't what I thought I'd be doing.
But everyone seems to be mesmerized when I do my dancing.
It just feels so good when I'm performing.
Huh?
This is the first time in my life I've felt like this.
I'm frightened.
So what are you trying to say?
Well, it's just that it's…
it's about those three murders which have occurred in the past few months.
It's all as Johan wills it.
Yes, so you've said.
I just want to understand.
Now, the reason for the murders of the Bilker investment baker, Fritz Oberth,
and the grocer's daughter, Frieda Schilling, is apparent.
It was to bury scandals.
I understand the necessity of those two particular murders.
However, the foreign trader, Erich Klemperer,
do you know anything about him?
No, I'm not familiar with him.
He doesn't have anything to do with Johann.
Are you absolutely certain about that?
Do we know what Johan is trying to achieve?
Really?
Or even where he is?
I can't help but wonder.
Could it be that you're hiding something from me?
- You have no need to worry.
Anyway, the more important question is,
were you able to find Nina?
- She left the psychologist's house in Munich
quite suddenly.
is headed to Frankfurt.
- Correct me if I'm wrong,
don't you think that our absolute top priority
should be capturing Nina right now?
- Well, perhaps I'd better jog your memory
about Nina's true nature.
It can't be ignored,
although you might not want to remember,
she is Johan's sister.
- I'll never forget that look in her eyes.
(explosion booms)
That night we tried to burn down the Turkish quarter.
She bore right through me with those eyes
It gives me chills just thinking about it.
Isn't it splendid?
Are you talking about the program you created and set in motion?
I can't take credit. I only hount.
My master actually put it all together.
And it's working.
Everything is proceeding exceptionally well,
according to his program.
Are things really proceeding according to the program, as he says they are?
There it is! Right there! My favorite ice cream truck! This time it's my treat!
Isn't it good? I think they have the best ice cream in Frankfurt.
For the first time in a while, I feel relaxed.
Lately, it's felt as though there's been a dark cloud over me.
Why's that?
Yes, I wonder why.
It's really not at all necessary to have someone guarding me.
Nevertheless, young man, those are Mr. Chapek's orders.
I'm telling you, there's no need to worry.
Believe me, even if I'm outside, walking up and down the street,
there really aren't many people who know who I am.
That's right.
But it will cause us a lot of grief if you do whatever you want again.
That's why we can't let you.
What makes you think I did whatever I wanted?
Three people had to be killed unnecessarily to cover up your scandals.
How many do you think I can kill before they find out?
Just who do you think is responsible for affording you that luxury?
"The four leaders of the organization, Professor Giedlitz, General Wolf, Mr. Chapek, not to
mention your main supporter, your deceased father, you seem to think that you have succeeded
to your father's post by right of birth, but actually it isn't that simple.
What matters is whether or not you can prove yourself worthy of the post."
"What, are you trying to say that you should have been the one appointed to that leadership
You've been surrounded by a lot of scandal.
And I know the details about every bit of it.
Well, you know what they say happens to people who know too much.
Secrets have to be kept.
Wait till you're out of your diapers before you try and threaten me.
I have no intention of becoming your enemy.
Not so long as you're Frankfurt's leading right winger.
(Footsteps)
Hmph.
(Chuckles)
I had fun.
Me too.
I'm glad I was able to talk to you today.
I rather enjoyed it.
You can talk to me whenever you want.
You know, it's been quite a long time
since I've actually walked around Frankfurt like this
without a bodyguard beside me.
Alright. Want me to walk you home?
You? Walk me home?
You want to be my bodyguard, is that what you're saying?
I'm fine, really. That's the hotel where I live, right over there.
My goodness! You actually live in a hotel?
Here you go. I hope this'll do.
I don't want it.
Goodbye.
Oh, I'm so sorry. It's just a habit of mine. I apologize!
I've always done that. Bought people with fistfuls of cash.
Listen, maybe we could...
go up to your room?
I know that people always call you "The Baby,"
but what is your real name?
Well, actually, my name is...
Yes, we just now found out where his twin sister is.
Let him know but he's not answering
I'm on my way to his room as we speak. Yeah. All right
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[Door opens]
(door creaks open)
(water splashes)
[water running]
[water dripping]
(dramatic music)
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- Mr. Jaffic?
- Yes, it's me.
- It's, it's the baby.
He's...
Come along, don't be afraid, there's nothing to be afraid of.
(dramatic music)
- Are you sure you're feeling all right, Mr. Chapek?
You're looking a little bit pale to me.
Well, please forgive the rude question
I'm about to ask you, but we need to know
if you were the one who ordered the baby to be killed, sir.
- What an absurd question.
- Please understand, we're just asking to make sure.
In this day and age, by the crack of dawn,
news reports of the baby's death
and with the death of this important man,
the balance within the organization
might just suddenly fall apart.
It's hard to predict,
but I'm guessing things will get messy.
We will carry out the job we were assigned to do.
We thought that job was to protect you.
However,
if you were the one who had the baby killed,
then guarding you will no longer
be in our best interests.
I summoned the two of you
when I heard the news.
Why on earth would I do such a thing
if I had ordered the baby killed.
Good point.
So now you're afraid you might be the next target.
Since you're telling us you had nothing to do with his murder,
do you have any idea of who did?
Do we know what Johan is trying to achieve?
Really? Or even where he is?
What am I afraid of?
everything is proceeding according to the plan everything is proceeding
according to the program fine but for now we need to move you to a safe
location do you have one that you can suggest well I do have a mountain villa
in Idstein. Luckily, I've never told anyone about it. I should be safe. I can stay there
for a while. Anyway, what about the twin sister? Right before all of this happened, you said
you knew where she was.
Yes. She recently arrived here in Frankfurt. She's staying at the Toulette, a cheap hotel.
Capturing and securing this woman in a locked room somewhere will ensure my safety, at least
for the time being.
Hm?
Right. First thing tomorrow morning-
- You'll do it right now!
- Very well, sir.
(screaming)
- I've contacted two other professional guards
that work with us and told them to meet us
at your villa in Ichstein.
- That's fine.
- Last night, for some inexplicable reason,
the baby sent away his bodyguard and went off on his own.
You have us.
We'll take care of you.
Don't worry.
Very well.
You didn't even get a scratch on you the other day at the convention center when that guy
was shooting at you.
You're a lucky man, sir.
Milan, Milan, listen, I've met a wonderful man.
(ominous music)
- Pleased to meet you.
I'm Peter Chappick.
You've shown me something utterly amazing and wonderful.
I'm talking about your book readings.
I'm really eager to learn.
Could you tell me more about them?
If I may, I have a few questions on the new, hmm?
This is a good read.
(ominous music)
All the answers are in these books.
How beautiful.
My word, what beautiful children.
So these are the special children
who have been selected to lead the future of humanity.
According to Franz Bonaparte's plan, they are the ones.
Stop! Stop the car right now!
Is something the matter? I believe we're almost there. Your villa should be right at the end
of this road.
What did you say earlier?
Sir?
Something about hiring two other guards.
Yes, I told them to meet us.
And for all I know, they might have already arrived there.
Can they be trusted?
Is there any chance they could have told someone where they were going?
Huh?
Think about it.
Can you assure me beyond a doubt that they haven't leaked information that I'm heading to my villa up in the mountains?
Don't worry.
I promise you they're two very trustworthy people.
I've decided not to go there after all.
What?
This doesn't make a bit of sense.
So where are you going to go then?
I don't know, but we're definitely not going up to the villa.
Look, I don't see the point of driving around all night not knowing where we're going.
That is an order!
I know that you're feeling scared and threatened, but...
I think we should just go to your villa.
[panicked moaning]
The lighter...
He... he wasn't reaching for his gun. I panicked.
(dramatic music)
- Hello, it's me.
Anyone here?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[WATER POURING]
[GULPS]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[ROARING]
Joh-- Johann.
At the Red Rose Mansion--
[GASPS]
--many people drank that red wine.
[GROANING]
[GAGGING]
Don't worry.
I'm drinking it too.
What happened to the bodyguards?
They're supposed to be here for me.
Why did you do it?
Why did you murder the baby?
I don't get it.
We're all on the same side.
You... you were helping us.
We...we said we would look for your sister and hand her over to you.
Everything is going as planned.
Oh, really?
Well, your precious sister is already in our custody.
If anything happens to me, I promise you, your sister will die!
I refuse to give in to you, got it?
Everything has been going along according to my plans!
So what...am I?
The monster inside of me... wasn't inside me. It was outside.
What are you saying? Make some sense!
Franz Bonaparte.
He's alive, isn't he?
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)