Hello? It's me.
Anyone here?
(door creaking)
(liquid gurgling)
(gulping)
- J-Johan.
- At the Red Rose Mansion,
many people drank that red wine.
(gagging)
Don't worry. See? I'm drinking it too.
What happened to the bodyguards? They're supposed to be here for me.
Why did you do it? Why did you murder the baby?
I don't get it. We're all on the same side.
You... you were helping us. That was always the plan.
We... we said we would look for your sister and hand her over to you.
Everything is going as planned.
Oh, really?
Well, your precious sister is already in our custody.
If anything happens to me, I promise you, your sister will die!
I refuse to give in to you, got it?
Everything has been going along according to my plans!
So what am I?
The monster inside of me...
...wasn't inside me.
It was outside.
What are you saying? Make some sense.
Franz Bonaparte.
He's alive, isn't he?
(upbeat music)
Miss Fortner, are you here?
Miss Fortner?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[GUN COCKS]
[GRUNTS]
You move and you're dead.
Now tell me who sent you here.
He wasn't kidding.
The baby told us about you.
He said you weren't an ordinary girl.
The baby, huh?
The one who ordered you two thugs over here to collect me.
No. You see, miss, the baby is dead.
Dead?
It was Peter Chappick who told us to find you.
He wants to stay alive,
and his best chance at doing that is with you as his hostage.
Peter Chappick.
Let's go then.
I want you to take me to Peter Chappick.
We're the police.
I'm in charge here, and we've been authorized
to search the residence of Milan Kolash,
perpetrator of the Rotterheim Convention Center shooting.
Let's go.
Move aside.
Hey, stay back.
Is this Kolash's room?
So it seems, sir.
The police are going to come and search the house soon.
I'm leaving while I still can.
Mr. Doctor, why did Milan have to die?
For us. He died for us. Milan tried to avenge us.
That chapik, he killed our relatives, exterminated them.
Milan tried to get revenge for what he'd done.
Revenge! Let's get revenge!
We want revenge!
Yeah, revenge!
Revenge!
No! Don't say things like that! It's wrong!
- Come on, he died trying to--
- Milan wouldn't want you to think like that.
(Milan crying)
Revenge just breeds more revenge.
It's a vicious cycle that needs to stop.
Listen to me.
Milan never wanted revenge to poison you like this.
Don't give in to hate.
You're better than that.
Milan did his best.
He tried to put an end to all this.
You know what his one true wish for you was, don't you?
We know. He wanted us to visit each other's homelands.
So you both need to study hard.
And that way, someday, that wish will come true.
You take care, Mr. Mustafa. Thanks for your help.
Mrs. Min, thank you, Mrs. Suleiman, for all the great food.
Dr. Tenma, where are you going to go?
Looks like he collected a lot of information about a certain man.
A guy named Peter Chappik.
Yeah, seems like it.
Elon Kolosh was after this Chappik.
That seems pretty obvious to me.
We need to check out this Chappik guy.
Questioning him could help us.
Inspector!
You know the right-wing extremist leader known as the Baby?
He was just found murdered at the Kaiser Hotel.
"Somebody has to end this.
And it has to be me."
"I've seen that young man.
He's met with Peter Chapek here many times."
Is he the devil's apprentice?
(dramatic music)
- Follow that car.
- Johan.
Are you here, Johan?
(papers rustling)
(footsteps thudding)
- So, Johan, where have you been?
I thought...
If I recall correctly, you're Ava.
- Where is he?
Tell me right now.
(birds chirping)
- Mr. Chappick, we've brought Nina.
Mr. Chappick.
- Peter.
Father...
Chabig...
Don't be afraid. There's nothing to be afraid of.
Drop it! Now!
Which one is it? Is it Johan or his sister?
The truth is, at this point, it doesn't really matter.
Johan let me live because the one that's going to kill me is his twin sister.
"Is it all going according to plan? But whose plan? Is it my plan? Johan's plan? Whose plan
What is it? I wonder. I'm not sure I know anymore.
Please kill me quickly. Go ahead.
So then... Yohan was here.
Where did he go?
Take me to him.
I need to know. Where's Johan now?
It's so dark.
I'm scared.
I want to get out of here right now.
You think it's safe yet?
I wonder if it's still going on out there.
The massacre.
If I hadn't have brought you two together...
at that party...
you and that devil...
If I'd never done that...
"Martin. He'd still be alive. He wouldn't have had to die."
"Hold on. Let's discuss this."
"Where is Johan?"
"I don't know. I wouldn't mind knowing that myself. Please, stay calm."
I am calm. I've watched this place for two weeks, and I never saw him show up.
So you must know where he is, right?
As I said, I don't know where Yohan is. Really, I mean it.
My ear! My ear!
I'm not kidding around.
Ah, damn it!
Next time, it won't just be your ears.
That's a promise, Christophe Zivernisch.
I researched you. It wasn't that difficult.
After all, your late father, Ernest, was well-known.
Once I found that connection, it was easy, and in Frankfurt,
well, in all of Germany,
the financial power of the Zivernisch Group is well-known.
What a shock that you were the heir to that empire.
And Peter Czapek, he has brought you and Johan together.
What's he planning to do?
My ear is sure bleeding a lot. I need to see a doctor.
What's going to happen?
What will happen because I made it possible for you to meet that devil?
You're wrong. You're mistaken.
Tell me how I'm wrong!
Czapek thinks that he introduced us to each other, but the joke's on him.
You see, Johan and I, we've known each other for quite a long time.
What are you talking about?
Czapek doesn't realize the truth.
We became friends when we were much younger.
It was in East Berlin over ten years ago.
You two met ten years ago, over in East Berlin?
I was actually adopted by Zivernisch.
It's a strange tale.
I was secretly sold to their family by a smuggler.
You see, Johann and I first met each other in East Berlin's 5-1-1 Kinderheim.
5-1-1 Kinderheim?
We trusted each other, became friends, and we survived.
He and I were the only ones that survived.
I'm scared.
I'm so hungry...
I really need to pee.
Do you think the killing has stopped?
I wonder if everyone is dead.
I bet they are. All of them.
Then let's go outside.
Huh?
Come on, why not?
It's been pretty quiet out there for a long time.
Go out and check! If we stay in here much longer, we'll all go crazy.
Right. I'll... I'll go take a look.
Don't leave us behind. Come back and tell us if things are okay.
I don't know why it happened, but all the people who were at 511 Kinderheim went mad that day.
Not just the children went mad. The teachers started killing each other, too.
He hasn't come back.
He must have run away.
Really?
Yeah. He left us here and ran off.
You think?
He tried to save himself.
You mean that?
If you think I'm lying, go and check.
He's out somewhere. Probably relaxing and eating a nice warm meal.
Yeah.
Do you really think so?
Then I'm going to take a quick look around.
You won't betray me and abandon me here, will you?
Of course I won't.
He never came back either. But I continued to wait it out.
I'm going to stay in here and stay safe.
Starved and parched with thirst, I fell in and out of a light sleep.
Am I just gonna die like this?
"And then, there he stood."
"It's just you and me. Come with me, I have a plan."
"And that was Johan?"
"It's outrageous that Chapa keeps saying that all of this is his plan. Johan and I talked about it constantly back then."
What is this plan of his?
So, you want to hear it?
Well, do you?
You can't do that!
You can't just shoot off my ear!
The way my face looks is very important for a politician!
I've made a mistake. I'm going to be a leader and rule the world, right?
You hear me? We're a team.
Johan's going to make the world mine!
'Cause that's the plan!
What are you going to do about my ear?
I'm not letting anyone ruin our plan!
I won't let you!
Drop your gun!
Kenzo...
[Gasp]
[Scream]
Johan told me what to say when you arrived.
He said, "If my sister comes, tell her where I am."
Then he said, "That you would probably kill me."
Those were his very words.
"Tell me, why haven't you killed me by now?"
Your memories, have all of them come back to you?
They have.
Why don't you kill me then?
Do you even know?
How it must fill you, the hatred, the anger, the grief, how do you keep that at bay?
What are we? You know, don't you? Explain it to me.
I've heard about it.
I've heard the stories about how you twins were brought into this world.
[MUSIC]
(upbeat music)