Mommy...
Don't let go of my hand...
[ Music ]
>> The man was Czechoslovakian, but of German descent.
the eldest son of a family that remained in Bohemia after the Second World War, a soldier
who graduated from a military academy, an elite on his way to a promising career for
the good of his nation's future. His name? His name is not important.
The woman?
The woman was the only daughter of a grade school teacher in Moravia.
She was very beautiful with blonde hair and blue eyes.
She attended the University of Brno and majored in genetic engineering.
Her teachers were fond of her and envisioned a bright future for her.
Her name? Her name is not important.
The two of them met at a café in Prague.
It was only a matter of time before they fell in love.
Soon afterward, the woman became pregnant.
Then, the man said, he had to make a confession.
This was his duty, he said.
Race, intellect, charisma, physical ability.
Many factors were taken into account in selecting proper couples to create children.
The experiment was conducted with hundreds of similar pairs,
and they were merely one of many.
The man had followed the orders of the scenario and had performed his duty,
but now he had no intention of complying with those orders.
And then he said to the woman,
The two of them attempted to escape.
The man said he wasn't going to follow their plan anymore.
more, but even their attempt at escape had been anticipated.
The woman was carried off and confined to an unknown room.
"Just let me see him. Oh, he's been assigned to an important new mission. Just let me see him."
"He's been assigned to a very important new mission."
"Just let me see him."
"Sorry, he has been assigned to an important new mission."
The woman said over and over,
"Just let me see him. Just let me see him. Just let me see him. Just let me see him."
The woman knew that he was no longer alive.
The life in her stomach was growing steadily.
carrying twins.
- Turn your head this way.
- She started to realize what was going on.
The man who drew her pregnant form in his sketchbook
was none other than the man who was responsible
for the whole operation.
- I won't forgive you, ever.
"Come what may, I will never forgive you.
Even if I die, the children growing inside of me
will get revenge.
I promise you this."
"You say the most amusing things."
Her due date came, and she was finally about to give birth.
When she was placed in an isolation ward to calm the pangs of labor, she made her move.
[GASPING FOR AIR]
Although the air duct opening was only 20 to 30 centimeters
wide and her heavy body was racked with labor pains,
she pulled herself along and escaped
through the ventilation system.
She collapsed on the street, only a few hundred feet from the main gate.
Her water had already broken.
"How beautiful!
My word, what beautiful children!
So these are the special children selected to lead the future of humanity!
Wonderful!
I've thought of names for the babies.
That is quite unnecessary.
I've thought of names for them.
The names I'd like them to have.
They don't need them.
They're children.
So you have to give each of them a name.
Please give them a name.
No, it's all right. You see, they have no need for names.
Franz Bonaparte.
Johan asked me where he was.
Is Bonaparte still alive?
I won't forgive you, ever. Come what may, I will never forgive you.
Even if I die, the children growing inside of me will get revenge. I promise you this.
Onaparte is still alive, isn't he?
You should ask Johan for the answers.
He is here.
Some doctor you are.
There's a hospital up ahead.
If you tell me where Johan is, I'll take you there.
If you don't talk right now, you'll die from blood loss.
Well, I can't tell you what I don't know.
You know all right. Tell us.
You're some doctor. First thing you do is shoot me.
Then you threaten to let me bleed to death instead of saving me.
Tell me where he is!
Some doctor...
Tell us right now!
Hurry!
Can't tell you.
No... Ava...
There's a payphone over there.
Call the hospital and tell them there's an injured person in this car who needs immediate attention.
What? Are you out of your mind? He's about to tell us where to find Johan!
We're out of time. His life's in danger.
Sure.
Call them. Quickly.
You saved a life once again.
You're incapable of killing anybody.
Just can't help yourself.
He's been waiting to see you.
I'll tell you where he is, but go alone.
Kenzo, the hospital is sending an ambulance right away.
Let's get out of here now.
Where's Kenzo?
He's gone.
He left a message for you.
I can't get you involved any further.
I've already ruined your life.
I'm very sorry, and I hope you find happiness.
Why are you crying now?
I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
(sobbing)
(suspenseful music)
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[PANTING]
[LOUD RUMBLING]
You won.
[PANTING]
Welcome home.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Fire!
There are flames coming out of the three frogs! It's on fire!
There you go! Eat up!
Now, if you eat too fast, you're going to choke.
You must have been terribly hungry.
So then, where did you two children come from?
What are your names?
Goodness, you don't talk at all when you're eating, do you?
That's fine. We can have a nice little talk as soon as your tummies are full.
Hold on!
This way!
Wait for me!
What should we do?
What do you mean, honey?
Those children.
What if they don't have parents to take care of them?
Even if they do, there must be some reason they ran away.
Don't you think?
We used to want kids.
We thought it would be nice to have a family.
That we did.
Maybe we could take them in.
Don't be so foolish.
Sorry, I didn't mean it the way it sounded.
Anyway, I think we should call the police.
What's wrong, little one?
(leaves rustling)
- Mm-hmm, look at what I picked.
Aren't these pretty?
I'm gonna give them to that nice man and lady.
- You don't have to.
- Huh?
- I told you, didn't I?
I have a plan, a good one.
Let's go.
Come on! Wait! Wait for me!
Oh my God! Wait!
So, we finally meet.
That time, when I escaped from Red Rose Mansion and arrived back at the Three Frogs, you greeted
me.
This time, it's my turn to say, "Welcome home."
A lot of time has passed since I came to get you, in Heidelberg, on our 20th birthday.
Get me?
You came to kill!
You killed the Fortners! You killed the Lieberts!
Anyone who came into our lives!
You killed every single person who had ever treated us kindly!
All of them!
You murdered all those people!
You must live!
Oh, yeah, I was just saying what a great day this is.
Perfect weather out there.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry, sir, but...
Yeah?
Could you go just a little faster?
Hang in there, kid.
Shoot me, Yana.
I'll save you, no matter what.
Are you going to shoot me, like you did back then?
That's right.
And that will be the end to all of this.
The end.
What exactly is the end?
The end. The end. The end. The end. The end. The end.
I've seen the end. Over and over.
What is the end?
This is. You're going to die. And so am I.
You've seen it.
What exactly did you see?
Tell me!
What did you see?
You don't know.
Do you?
I'll tell you about it.
It's something that's truly horrifying.
I'm back.
(dramatic music)