"Hang in there, kid."
"Shoot me, Yana."
"I'll save you, no matter what."
Are you going to shoot me, like you did back then?
That's right.
I've got to finally put an end to this.
The end.
What exactly is the end?
"The end. The end. I've seen the end. Over and over. What is the end?"
"This is. You're going to die, and so am I. You've seen it. What exactly did you see?
Tell me! What did you see?"
You don't know, do you?
I'll tell you about it.
It's something that's truly horrifying.
I'm back.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
"Something that's truly horrifying," you say, "but it's mine to tell, a story of all the
things I've seen."
All of those details, the ones I told you about.
When I was taken from our place at the Three Frogs, I was brought to a room that had no
light.
It was pitch black.
I'd reach out to touch them, but the room gave me no sense of up or down, left or right.
But I knew someone was watching me.
This room was completely devoid of sound.
No, I did hear something.
Sometimes I could hear screams coming from somewhere not too far away.
My food seemed to appear out of nowhere, and I counted the number of meals as I ate them.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-three.
when I couldn't keep track of them anymore.
There was this man, just standing there.
Listen to me closely.
People can become whatever they want to be.
What's this? Tell me, is it really all right for a young child like you to be wandering
around here?
You know, this child's the one.
Oh, so that's the child.
"Ma, you are a cute one."
"Ah, so this is the child."
"How wonderful!
What a beautiful child you are.
Take a good look.
This child is the one."
"Ah, so this is the one."
"Here's the result."
"The result indeed."
"This one's special."
"One in a million."
I remember a man standing there talking, but I can only remember parts of what he was saying.
For us the chosen ones a toast to our country's future
When the first person collapsed, all the people around him rushed to his side.
Then one by one, all of the other people in that room collapsed as well.
Their moans of pain, frenzied shrieks, the screams.
The whole room was engulfed with their fear.
On that fateful day, 42 people perished in that room.
The only one left alive was Franz Bonaparta.
I began to run.
I ran away, to escape that horrible place.
I didn't even realize my arm was bleeding from getting scratched by the roses in the
garden.
I just ran.
I ran all the way back to the three frogs.
You were still there.
You greeted me.
I started to tell you, for days and days.
Explaining all of my experiences, and what I had seen.
You're wrong.
You're so wrong.
You are wrong.
It's all wrong!
(suspenseful music)
Nina, can you hear me, Nina?
Just calm down, all right?
It's me, Tenma.
You know who I am, remember?
Hey, just relax. Calm down.
That's it. That's better now.
It's going to be alright. You're alright now.
It's not... It's not... No!
It wasn't me there!
It wasn't me who greeted him when he returned!
He wasn't the one who came back.
I remember it.
What I said was...
I'm back.
Welcome home.
"Yohan's mistaken. Yohan just listened to my story when I came back. Because the one
who was taken to the Red Rose Mansion... the one taken to the Red Rose Mansion, that child
The one who was dragged away down that wooden stairway at the Three Frogs, the one who counted
all those meals in that pitch black room that had no walls, the one who stood in that room
I'm surrounded by corpses.
That child was me!
It happened to me, all of it!
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
(breathing heavily)
(door creaking)
I'm back.
Welcome home.
(sniffling)
(whimpering)
(sobbing)
- Tell me everything.
- Everything?
All right, then.
I told him what happened. I talked to him for days and days.
That's enough, Nina.
I told Johan about all the terrible experiences I'd had, but Johan thinks my experiences...
Please just stop.
Somehow Johan really believes that my experiences actually happened to him.
Because I told him Johan had...
It's alright!
Just now, I told Johan everything.
It looked like he was laughing as he listened to me.
But it also looked like he was crying, too.
I've... I've never seen such an expression before.
His face... I've never seen anyone who looked like that.
I should have done it.
But I couldn't shoot him.
I'm sure of one thing.
He will destroy himself just like me.
I know that I will destroy myself.
No, you won't.
But don't you see that I have to do it?
Nina, no!
Don't do it.
Because if something happens to you,
if you die,
what will I do?
If you were to die,
How could I go without you, Nina?
You can't give up.
Please stay alive, no matter what else may happen.
I beg you, Nina.
Yeah, it's me.
So you're telling me you found his car near the villa, then.
Yes. It's at the bottom of the ravine.
I found Edward dead inside the car.
We all know who did this.
I can guess Johan's next move.
He'll kill Franz Bonaparte. That's who's next up on his list.
His son's in Prague. I told Johan where to find him.
I don't know what he's about to do with that information.
But, do you really think that's where all this will end?
Will his destruction actually come to an end there?
His sister Nina's memory.
Or something is missing from his sister's memory.
Johann has another one. It's part of him. Another memory.
What was our goal? What was it that we were trying to create?
What was our purpose?
Tell me, Franz Bonaparte.
It's alright, we'll find it, where you belong, where we belong, we'll find it somewhere.
I'm glad you came to visit.
I never expected to see you around here.
Well, make yourself at home.
I just made some hot tea.
I've always wanted to share my very best tea with you like this.
Do you like it?
What do you think of the flavor?
It's a special herbal blend of mine.
I must say I'm quite impressed you'd come here to pay me a personal visit.
I know this must be an important matter, so you need something done then. I'll handle whatever it is you need
Just tell me
Who do you want me to murder next?
Huh, hey, don't joke around like that Johan
Come on stop it. I woke up
I woke up from the dream.
Are you tired or something, Johan?
What are you going to do about the plan?
I said I woke up.
Hold on a minute.
If you've changed your mind, what did I collect all that money for anyway, huh?
I woke up from the dream.
So tell me then, what did I kill all those people for?
There were so many visions I had of the end.
But now, I'm picturing a different ending altogether.
A clearer vision of the true ending.
It's from a memory only I have.
The real place where I must be.
[GUN COCKS]
[GASPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[FOOTSTEPS]
The place to be.
[GUNSHOT]
[FOOTSTEPS]
(door slams)
So this is Ruenheim.
I found it.
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
[ Music ]