So this is Ruhenheim.
This is it.
(dramatic music)
(barking)
Ludwig! You stop that!
What's got you barking so much?
(barking)
Looks like that bike of yours broke down again.
Yeah. The chain always comes loose.
My bike was once junkyard trash.
Guess it'll always be junkyard trash.
Well, in my opinion, your bike doesn't look like trash.
When I'm riding it, the guys say,
"Hey, look, here comes the trash rolling by."
Bunch of trash riding around on trash, they say.
- Don't listen to them, Vim.
Your bike is a well-built five-speed super cycle.
It just needs a little adjustment again, that's all.
Let's see now.
- Hey, looks like you've got a customer.
- Mm-mm.
Oh, he must be that man that called.
Hello. Did you call for a room?
I did. My last name is Lungay.
Welcome, Mr. Lungay. I am the hotel proprietor.
I was glad to hear that you had a vacancy on such short notice.
To be honest, we always have rooms available.
That's because it's still the off-season, right?
In our quaint little town, it's off-season year-round.
The only other guests that are staying here right now are that elderly couple.
The husband's confined to that wheelchair.
Seems like they've had a rough time on this trip.
Shall I take your bag, sir?
Oh, thank you kindly, Vin.
He'll be up in room 302.
How's the view from that room?
Well, your room has the best view in the entire hotel, sir.
I'll leave your bag here on the bureau, sir.
I don't think it looks like trash.
Huh?
No, it looks like a perfectly good bicycle to me.
You're Inspector Lungay of the BKA? Why would you be visiting our little police station?
I wanted to ask you just how many more officers you have in your force if I were to need backup here.
Well, if you contacted the state police,
they could probably supply us with quite a few officers
in less than an hour.
But I can't imagine that a situation like that
would happen in a little rural town like ours.
Right now, you should be checking up on every person
who's recently come into town.
Huh?
Do it fast before something terrible happens here.
All right! That's more like it!
Now it's working great!
Now to shift into high gear!
(crashing)
- What's the matter, Trash?
- Mr. Trash Bike is still riding around.
Go back to your crap pile, Trash Boy!
- Stop!
Hey, stop!
(thudding)
(laughing)
- Nice one.
Are you alright?
Are you here alone? I mean, are you traveling by yourself?
That's right.
Is this for work?
No, I'm doing this for myself.
Oh, don't you get lonely traveling by yourself?
No, ma'am. I guess I'm used to it.
I see. Do you have any family?
Yes, I do. I have a daughter and a new grandchild.
Oh, that's great. So you have a grandchild, too.
Grandchildren are such a blessing.
The two of us have a grandson that we're always thinking about.
In fact, I'm writing a postcard to him right this instant.
Letters are so wonderful.
When you write one, you can say things you could never say in person.
Oh, Mr. Lunge, would you care to write one, too?
Send a postcard to my grandchild?
I wonder what I would write about.
I'm sure anything would be fine.
What a shame.
If only I could draw well.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Could I possibly get a room here for tonight?
Yes, sir. Of course.
Glad to hear it.
I was enjoying a relaxing picnic out in the countryside,
but I got lost along the way.
Now that I finally made it here, it's already late.
Sometimes when you're walking, it's hard to plan for these things.
Anyway, I'm really grateful you have a room.
How interesting that nobody on that train wanted to get off at this town.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GUNSHOT]
Hm?
A gunshot?
I didn't hear any gunshots.
Yeah, what we just heard definitely
sounded like a gunshot.
Be serious.
I don't think anyone here even owns a gun.
I'd say the only one who might is that drunk across the way.
It would have been a lot louder if it had
been that close to our place.
That drunk's so out of it, he couldn't hit anything if he tried.
Oh, why'd you say "couldn't hit"?
Stop that talk!
I just lost again because you and your negative attitude jinxed me again!
- Honestly! - Oh, shut up with that!
It's not my fault you lose! Stop playing the lottery!
Ludwig!
My poor Ludwig isn't anywhere to be found
You, you don't think that it's possible that my Ludwig was…
Please calm down, Mrs. Hillman.
I assure you, you're imagining things.
There was no gunshot.
Really.
Why is that poor woman so upset?
Oh, well, you see, Mrs. Hillman's dog Ludwig is gone missing.
Aww.
That would make anyone worry.
I know.
Perhaps we should tell the police.
I've already gone to the stupid police.
But that man's no good.
He makes no sense.
- He may be a policeman, but I can't count on him at all.
That oaf is a policeman who hates dogs.
- Excuse me, but would you like me to go look for your dog?
- Are you sure you don't mind, Mr. Neumeier?
- Of course, since I'm going to be hanging
around town anyway, why not?
- Why sure, of course.
I know what Mrs. Hillman's dog Ludwig looks like.
He's that stupid dog that barks a lot, right?
- It seems he's gone missing.
You haven't seen him, have you?
- Nope, haven't seen him lately.
- Well, thanks anyway.
Oh, by the way, sir,
you haven't noticed any suspicious-looking strangers
showing up around town lately?
- Sure have.
- Yeah?
- I'm looking at one right now.
- A dog?
And you had me thinking you were gonna book a room here.
- Sorry.
I'm already spoken for over at the Hotel Versteck.
- That place has been stealing
everyone else's customers left and right.
- Wait, so you're telling me
really don't have any customers right now?
- No, not a one.
Because of that, it's nice and quiet here.
So if that dog had been barking as much as he usually does,
I definitely would have heard him.
- In other words, you didn't hear any barking today.
- No, I didn't hear a peep out of that mutt.
But here's what I'm thinking.
I did hear something earlier that sounded like a gunshot.
Maybe some weirdo got fed up with that dog
always being so noisy and went and shot it.
(birds chirping)
(footsteps)
- Good afternoon, Mr., what was it?
- It's Lungay, Mr. Neumeier.
- Right, Mr. Lungay.
Where are you headed?
- Actually, I'm out looking for a lost dog.
- I know what that's like.
So tell me, have you found any leads yet?
- Not yet.
- Well, in that case, I guess there's nothing to do
but keep looking.
(footsteps)
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Get going!
Go get me a drink!
No, Dad!
You shouldn't drink anymore!
You go buy me a bottle now!
I need another drink!
I don't have any money!
You've got money from working over at that hotel!
[SLAP]
[GRUNTS]
Go!
[GROANS]
[grunting]
I wonder if I've got enough to buy him a little one.
It's all right, Bim.
You saved that.
You earned that money by working very hard.
Seems like you got beat up a lot today.
Come on, my boy.
Let's go to the hotel.
"Cafe Vinyl"
I keep hoping that someone wonderful will show up here
and take me away from this place for good.
- Well, any Prince Charmings drop in recently?
- Not at all. Every day, it's the same faces.
I'm sick of this town.
- By the way, about that missing dog I mentioned.
- Oh, yeah, I know that dog pretty well.
You see, I walked Ludwig before.
- How did that go?
- This one time, Mrs. Hilmon had this awful cold,
and she asked me, so I walked him for her.
When I let him have a ham hock for my deli,
he kind of went nuts.
unbelievable strength, and before I knew it, he had pulled the whole thing away from me!
When he did that, where did he run?
Inspector Lungay, you were right on the money.
Something terrible has happened here, sir.
It's a lost pet. A dog has gone missing.
The gunshot earlier, did you investigate that?
Hey, that wasn't a gunshot, that was a car.
I mean, that's the only thing that noise could have been.
That sound was the car backfiring
You won't hear gunfire in this town. See ya
You'll be getting a visit from Steiner if you pull that stunt again
[FOOTSTEPS]
Hm?
It's you.
Hello, Ludwig.
You've had everybody in town worried about you.
And you just came back to get your bone, didn't you?
Hm?
Oh, nice to see you again.
Well, Mr. Lunge, it would certainly
appear the different clues have led us to the same place.
I'd like to know what you're doing in this town as well.
You're a detective, aren't you?
That's my theory, at least.
You certainly have the air of one.
I'm just here on vacation.
By the way you've been acting,
you don't look as though you're on much of a vacation.
Not too long ago, I was in Prague.
While there, I heard information
about somebody involved in a certain case.
He was described as a man with a gun.
He's described as a tall man who carries a duffel bag with him.
He has a friendly smile and brown hair.
In fact, I'd say you completely match the description that was given of this suspect.
Don't you, Mr. Neumeier?
Or is it Mr. Grimmer?
You never did tell me why you've come to this town.
One thing I'm sure of, this isn't a coincidence.
We really have been led to this same place by different clues.
Haven't we, detective?
Do you think you can stop it in time?
The massacre on the horizon that's about to sweep through this town.
Hey, are you checking your lottery numbers again?
Well, your husband's heading out to work
to pay for your little habit.
Don't make such a big deal.
You barely make--
Careful now.
The only way our future will get brighter
is if we win the lottery.
Instead of complaining, go earn us some more money.
Fine.
Hold on.
Yeah, spare me your apologies.
Oh, my gosh.
Why?
- What are you sputtering about over there?
- My God, I won.
- You won what?
- The, the lottery.
- Give it back.
Where did you put my bike, you creeps?
I want my bike back!
- Shut up!
We don't know where your stupid bike is, right?
- Yeah, but we did throw away some trash.
- You threw it away?
- Uh-huh.
We tossed it in the vampire's house up on the West Hill.
(laughing)
- Vampire's house?
Go up there by yourself to get it back.
No telling what could happen to you if you do.
See ya, trash.
Oh, it's you.
So, has anyone come knocking on our door?
No.
- Better keep the chain on, Franca.
Now then.
- Where were you?
- You're sure that you hid all the numbers, aren't you?
- I've checked it over a dozen times.
I really want it.
- A whole 20 million marks, huh?
- Well, what shall we do now?
- I went to a nearby town and...
- Oh my, what have you?
- Just in case we need 'em.
With that much money at stake,
- Relax, we won't need to use these
as long as no one knows about what we've got.
- Right, if you say so.
- What's the matter?
How on earth could anyone know the numbers
on the lottery ticket that you won with?
- Well, when I bought that ticket,
it was pretty much the same as always.
Give me the form.
- Here you go.
You never win, do you, Mrs. Hayner?
Try changing things up.
- What do you suggest, Mr. Conrad?
and says you're obsessed with the lottery
and you always play the same numbers.
How about if I give you some numbers to try
that I know are winners?
My birthday's numbers are lucky.
March 2nd, 1945.
I've tracked them and they seem to win more often than not.
At the horse races, I've hit it big twice with my numbers.
- Well, thanks.
I'll try them sometime.
- You're joking, right?
You really use the numbers in Conrad's birthday?
Wait, but there's no way he'd know that you used his birthday
and you didn't tell him that you did.
I just don't know.
Rumors might be spreading through the whole town by now.
Hey, now that I think of it--
What? Tell me.
On the way back home,
I stopped at the store to get some cigarettes.
That's when I noticed her.
The girl from the sausage shop gave me this weird look.
That explains what happened to me!
Now I get it!
When I went out to get some cigarettes,
to the alley to throw out the trash.
The drunk in the back was there,
and he was definitely staring at me.
Can you imagine what that drunk would do
if he heard about us having all that money?
He's desperate.
- Hey, calm down.
The only thing we can do now
is protect ourselves, whatever it takes.
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
(chickens clucking)
Well, there's the vampire's house.
A dead cat?
(footsteps approaching)
- Huh?
Someone's in here.
- From the looks of things around this house,
no one has been here recently.
All of the artwork is unfinished.
Did he stop drawing?
But perhaps he couldn't draw anymore.
Hey, what a surprise! It's Vim!
Mr. Neumeier! Mr. Lunge!
What are you doing so far from town, anyway?
Well, you see, it's my bike.
Some boys told me they took my bike, brought it up here, and dumped it.
I see. Looks like those boys played a trick on you.
I saw your bike hidden in the bushes.
It's at the foot of the mountain path that leads up here.
Huh?
Anyway, it appears that cat was shot with a submachine gun.
Then they're already near town.
They are, and they're close by.
Look at this.
The twins, it's them.
And this one, too.
Here's another.
And another.
They're about ten years old.
Hmm?
When I was in charge of Dr. Tenma's case,
these twins were about ten years old at the time.
These pictures must have been drawn right about then.
How many more drawings of those two are there?
Hundreds. No matter how many times he drew them, he was never satisfied.
Look at how they've grown.
Looks like there's going to be a lot of vines to pull out of the bushes this year.
This could really affect this year's Lingonberry crop.
Hello, I've never seen you around here before.
(eerie music)
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)