It's delicious. The best I've ever had.
I'm very pleased you like it.
It's our homemade lingonberry jam.
My! Homemade?
I was told to show this to any visitors who enjoy the jam.
This is a photo of the jam maker.
Goodness! He made this?
Yes. His name is Conrad.
There's a hillside in the middle of the town.
not too far away to the south where many lingonberry bushes grow and over the
course of time eventually he bought up the whole place and no one found a
reason to complain about him laying claim to the land because his jam is so
delicious yes that's right but he's also an enjoyable man and one of the few
people I can call a friend it was his idea to show the photograph his way of
I'm adding a personal touch to say,
please enjoy our authentic homemade jam.
(laughing)
- Well, his strategy is working.
We'll have to come back for jam, dear.
- Oh yes, absolutely.
- I'll tell him the next time we play chess.
He'll be very happy to hear that.
(dramatic music)
[MUSIC]
I wonder if there will be an attack on this peaceful little town.
An attack? There are other methods besides that.
There are cases where a single gun has destroyed a whole town.
1958, in Zweifelsstadt.
There was a series of murders in the state of Niedersachsen.
The townspeople began to suspect their neighbors of being the killer.
It left them on edge in a constant state of group hysteria.
one of the residents became so paranoid
that he ended up shooting his next-door neighbor
with a gun he had purchased for protection.
Nobody could stop it after that.
A fire was lit in the town,
and everything on hand was used as a weapon.
The townspeople massacred each other,
and there was not one survivor left.
Don't tell me that's going to happen here as well.
Because of one man.
We have to stop it before it starts.
No. I'm afraid it's too late. It might have already begun.
Come on! Give us your money! We know you got some, so cough it up!
No, please! That's the money for my...
It's your drunk dad's liquor money, isn't that right?
Tell your dad drinking isn't good for his health!
We're doing him a favor!
(laughing)
- What a wuss.
- Yeah.
- Well, let's get something to eat.
- Sounds good.
- What are you gonna get?
- Wanna go for the usual?
Got plenty to spend.
- Yeah.
- Little boy.
Don't you hate them?
Don't you hate them enough to kill them?
- Where do you think you're going?
- I'm going to have a little talk with Conrad.
- Talk?
What are you gonna talk to him about?
- When we passed the cafe,
didn't you notice that Ralph
and all of his customers inside
were sitting there glaring at us?
- Well, maybe they were just surprised
to see us out together.
That hardly ever happens.
- No, that can't be it.
Who knows what they might do
if they found out we had just won the lottery
and made 20 million marks.
- You mean, you think?
- That's why I wanna have this topic
out in the open once and for all.
I'm about ready to jump out of my skin here.
- Okay, for argument's sake,
let's just say that Conrad does know we won the lottery.
What on earth are you gonna do about it?
- I'll pay him whatever amount of money he wants.
I think that should do the trick to shut him up.
- But then what if Conrad gets greedy
and keeps squeezing us for more hush money later on?
- If that happens--
- What are you gonna do about it then, huh?
- I don't know.
Speaking of Conrad, isn't this the place where he picks all his lingonberries?
Uh, honey?
What?
You don't really think Conrad is a bad person, do you?
Uh, no.
I mean, he's not the kind of person who would ruin our good fortune
now that our ship has finally come in.
Well, what do you think?
Hmm?
(crickets chirping)
- What are you looking at?
(gasps)
Oh, oh dear, you didn't, did you?
- Of course I didn't.
- Oh my God, I can't stand it, this is too much.
- Listen, I'm telling you, I didn't do it.
- Well then who else would have done it?
- How should I know?
I just bought my gun, never been fired.
(sobs)
(barking)
- Oh, shut up.
God damn, that dog pisses me off.
Shut up, you old fleabag.
(barking)
- Well, you sure seem happy today.
Did something good happen?
Come on, spill the beans.
- Yeah, he finally showed up.
- Wait, who are you talking about?
- The perfect man who's going to take me
far away from this boring town.
(laughing)
- A drink, need a drink, oh damn.
They all look at me and laugh.
I'm just a big joker on this place, isn't that right?
But it's not funny at all, huh?
God, I need a drink.
Would this be what you really want?
You want this, don't you?
Your boy already took one. This one's yours.
[DOG BARKING]
[GUNSHOT]
A gunshot, and the dog's barking suddenly stopped.
[APPLAUSE]
Mr. Lipsky.
You're Franz Bonaparte's son, isn't that so, Mr. Lipsky?
Please, tell me where to find your father.
If I don't hurry and find him,
very soon a lot of people are going to die.
You know, don't you, Mr. Lipsky?
You know where your father is.
I suppose that puppet is modeled after Nina, isn't it?
I knew that you would be here. Nina told me where to find you.
Nina told you?
Could you open those for me?
Sure.
How long have I been like this?
Don't worry about it. You could use some more rest. It's important that you get it.
I want to thank you all that time. I could tell you were there watching out for me somehow
Please don't worry. I'm all right now. I
Don't want to die anymore
Dr.. Reich fine and Dieter should both be arriving here pretty soon now and you I have things to do. Where are you going?
I'm working on that
You've been looking over lots of documents that you've found.
Did you learn anything?
I'll be fine. You can tell me what you know.
I had some members of Prague's former secret police organization,
as well as some of General Wolf's men,
track down as much information as they were able to find.
You mean about Franz Bonaparta?
That's right. He's a very mysterious man,
a bit of a profile on him.
A German-born Czech.
It appears that the name Franz Bonaparte
is also an alias.
After World War II,
when most German-born Czechs
were chased from their homeland of Bohemia,
his family remained within the country.
It's unclear what kind of a role he served
in the communist Czechoslovakian government.
I discovered that he was once married to a Czech woman
they had a son. When their son was just a boy, he participated in the very first
book readings, the experimental testing that was run throughout the mid-60s by
his father. Franz Bonaparte's son is still living in Prague. Those were Peter
Čapek's last words to me, and in spite of everything, I believe he was telling me
the truth. I'm gonna show you something that I managed to find. It's a copy of an
This is an old photograph of the first round of pupils who were there and took part in the '60s book readings.
Apparently, the little boy on the far left of the photo was...
Not a superior pupil.
He was kicked out of the readings because he wasn't a superior pupil.
You already knew?
That made him an unwanted child of no use to Bonaparta.
I'm pretty sure that his son is the man I stayed with in Prague.
Assuming that he is Bonaparta's son,
Do you think he'd have an idea of where his father is?
I don't know, but he's the only possible lead we have right now.
And we have to hurry before something terrible happens.
Something terrible?
Yes, quite soon, I can tell.
I know what Johan is about to attempt.
What is it? Tell me.
The perfect suicide.
True solitude.
The only expression of love.
If we don't hurry, many innocent people are going to die.
Your bookshelves.
They're full of storybooks that Franz Bonaparte drew under pen names.
I've actually read almost all the stories myself.
And after reading several of them, it suddenly began to dawn on me.
For some reason, all of the characters that appear in his books have German names.
Even in Klaus Poppe's "The God of Peace," he uses them.
But the problem in this instance is the Klaus Poppe pen name.
Franz Bonaparta and all of the other pseudonyms that he wrote under were Czechoslovakian.
This is the only German pen name he ever employed.
Just maybe Klaus Poppe was actually the true name of your German-born Czechoslovakian father.
There was a detective who used that same line of reasoning
and also concluded that was my father's real name.
Detective?
He said he was Inspector Lungay of the BKA.
Lungay? Is he still here?
He was here weeks ago. He already left.
Where did he go?
He made this deduction.
No, actually, with him it was more like he became my father,
rather than using logic.
I am now Klaus Poppe.
I have no place that I can return to.
I will go back to my heart's one true home," he said.
Many years ago, the German-born Czechs
were driven from their home in Bohemia
when Germany lost the war.
Where in Germany were his ancestors originally from?
I'm not too sure of the location.
All I remember is my father once said to me
when I was very young,
"Our home is a small town in southern Germany
surrounded by many mountains."
I didn't want it anymore,
So I gave it to Inspector Lunge, a postcard I got three or four years ago.
The address of the sender was not included.
All it had was a hand-painted picture of some mountains with the initials "K.P."
K.P. Klaus Poppe. Could be.
I'm sorry to say that's all I really know.
Southern Germany. A town surrounded by mountains.
Will... will my... father be killed?
I can't tell you.
But I do know that it won't end there.
And Nina? Is Nina safe and sound?
I hope so.
I want to create plays for this puppet that always have happy endings.
Please, just keep Nina safe.
I will.
Can you tell me what's going to happen?
He's trying...
Johan's trying to recreate them.
Red Rose Mansion. Endless slaughter back at 5-1-1 Kinderheim.
Please listen.
No matter what happens, Tenma, come back.
You saved me and I'll never forget it.
You have to live.
The rain...
It started.
Give me a drink, I need some booze, damn it.
Well what's going on?
Did the police find Conrad's body yet?
No, they've labeled him missing and they've gone out looking for him.
- I knew we shouldn't have hidden the body in the forest.
We should have just gone straight to the police.
- What's the use of saying that now?
I think you're forgetting,
you're the one who thought I'd shot him.
Damn it!
This is what we get for winning the lottery.
- I keep on telling you,
you shouldn't have bought these horrible things.
- No use waiting.
There won't be any trains.
The Elgar River has flooded out the railway bridge.
All roads are closed due to the flooding as well.
A solitary island.
The worst possible scenario.
Klaus Poppe, is it?
Do you know about him?
Jakob Feuerbach.
And Emil Scherbeck.
Do you know about them? Because I think they and Poppe are the same man.
matter in art are different in each. When you've seen as much as I have, you notice
certain things. However, I couldn't tell you why he would use so many pen names, though.
His art is good. But for some reason, I really can't appreciate his work. There are plenty
of picture books around the world that have gloomy stories. But somehow, his art... different.
- How so? What do you mean? - Hmm. I guess you could say they're brimming
with malice. Before I forget, there's another one. This storybook from Helmuth Foss, published
in Germany in 1989. It's hard to get because there were so few printed, but I believe he
is also the same man as Klaus Poppe. How can you be sure about that? As I said, I'm able
to tell these things. When you do it long enough, you know. No matter how he changes
his art, there are little things that always remain the same. This story's content is
an about-face from the others. A thief sneaks into a quiet village in the mountains. He
plans to make off with a good sum of money from the villagers. But as he interacts with
the people of the village, he forgets how to steal, and eventually he ends up leading
a quiet life, helping the village folks. The title is "The Peaceful House."
Pope's usual unpleasant aftertaste is gone. However, his artwork takes quite a
turn for the worse. A bit of a strange thing happened. It
seems his story got better, but he forgot how to draw.
It's as if... as if he lost his purpose.
A peaceful home. A village in the mountains.
"Our home is a small town in southern Germany, surrounded by many mountains."
"A map."
"Hm?"
"Do you happen to have a map of southern Germany?"
"So what are you looking for?"
"A small town surrounded by many mountains.
There it is."
"Hm."
"Ruhenheim."
(dramatic music)
- Holy cow, it's a monsoon out there.
- So how did it go?
Were you able to locate Conrad in all that rain?
- Nope, not a trace.
My partners are still looking around,
but given the way it's been raining all afternoon,
the overflowing river's taking the trains
and roads out of service.
I know you must be concerned about your friend.
I mean, normally, this place is just so peaceful.
But then Conrad goes missing, and the next thing you know,
Mrs. Hillman's dog is shot dead.
Poor Mrs. Hillman is so distraught,
she's confined to her bed with grief.
And that's not all.
Mr. Kemnar was attacked leaving the pub last night.
I hear his condition is serious.
And the perp got away.
We got nothing.
If he should actually die as a result of those injuries,
it will be this town's first ever murder.
Things are falling apart and because of this rain we can't get back up.
What are we supposed to do with only a few people?
It must be the work of outsiders.
Crime in this town is basically non-existent.
It's gotta be them, right?
We're outsiders. Are you locking us up?
No, I'm not suggesting that.
This rain is fierce.
I can hardly go outside in my wheelchair in this weather.
Well, I'd better go patrol one more time and then catch up with my partners.
Be careful out there.
Your husband's shoes are remarkably muddy and wet.
As if he'd been spending time walking around in the rain.
I'd like to use your phone, if I may.
Huh?
Uh, it's just that lush.
Can't be him. He can't do anything at all.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hm?
What's wrong?
Are you out of gas?
Is it leaking oil?
I could radio for a mechanic.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hm?
[GUNSHOT]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
That was another gunshot.
All the phone lines must be down.
Is it too late for us to prevent the bloodshed around the corner?
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]