(rain pouring)
- You got left high and dry by your mom.
- Yeah, your mom threw out you and your drunk dad
like you were a big pile of trash.
- So don't try to come out of the garbage can again.
(laughing)
(choral music)
(dramatic music)
(horse neighing)
- Sorry, but I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
then pay off your tab first.
- Wait, wait, wait, I've got money.
Enough for today's drinks.
- Listen, I'm not gonna let you buy drinks here
with money that you stole from your son.
- What did you say?
- Just get out of here.
(spits)
- He's suspicious.
- You mean, how Conrad's missing?
- And Mrs. Hillman's dog, too.
Do you think he did it?
He's too gutless to shoot anything.
Yeah, he's a coward and a drunk.
Oh, man. We're not gonna find him here.
Hey, Merkle! Let's call off the search for today, yeah?
Hey, Merkle, you there?
(thunder rumbling)
- Hey, I found Mr. Conrad!
- Mirko, where'd you go?
- What the?
What happened?
(thunder rumbling)
This is Lopper! Emergency! Please respond!
Someone! Someone answer for God's sake!
You look surprised. I think I'd better take that gun of yours.
That drunk's too gutless to shoot anything.
You got that right.
Yeah, he's a coward and a drunk.
All over town there are countless corpses, it's like a war zone.
Oh my god, Vim, what just happened?
Easy now, you're alright.
It's me.
I just...
I...
Relax.
now let go of the gun I don't remember what happened did I really shoot them I
mean they were always bullying me so I
you didn't shoot them I didn't are you sure huh it's all right
Try to calm down. You're going to be fine.
There's nothing to be afraid of, Vim.
Now try to remember what happened.
Who did you get this gun from?
Try to stay conscious, Laufer.
It's amazing that you made it all the way here with your leg shot like that.
Please, just call the station.
The telephone doesn't work.
My God, the guy took it from me.
Was he somebody from around here?
I'd never seen this guy before.
We'd better do some first aid on that leg.
These are your friends, aren't they?
What do you mean by that?
How many of your friends have come here to this town?
Just what are you trying to suggest?
Only that you've scattered quite a few guns around.
You even went and forced a gun on this poor innocent boy.
Vim? A gun? Tell me you didn't use it!
You're definitely not trash, Vim.
Don't bother with those bullies.
You were born for a reason, I know it.
You told him all of those things to encourage Vim to feel good about himself.
You'll be glad to know he didn't shoot this gun.
All the bullets are still in it.
I would say Vim took that good advice of yours to heart.
You did the right thing.
It's alright, Vim. You're a good boy.
There are corpses all over town. They're just lying in the street.
I have a question for you.
How many guns did you give out around here?
Huh?
How many townspeople did you give out guns to?
You don't want to make me any angrier.
Now answer me before I break you in half!
All right. He was like our grandson.
Keep talking.
You see, he looked just like our dead grandson.
It was uncanny.
Who did?
I got the impression that he really knew us quite well.
That's how it was. He was just like our real grandson.
Tell me his name.
Earlier, you were writing to your dead grandson's replacement.
You were actually sending him information, isn't that so?
You tell me his name.
He's probably come here for me.
I'm the one that he's after.
That's true.
I would have to agree, Mr. Poppe.
You mean, Mr. Franz Bonaparta.
[explosion]
(thunder rumbling)
- Extremely heavy rain continues to fall
in southern Germany, and there have been fatalities
along the rivers in Bavaria.
(Dido coughing)
- You know what?
You smoke way too much.
- It helps with my nerves since I've quit drinking.
- Yeah, I think you should quit smoking too.
- Anyway, show me what you've been drawing
all this time, Dido.
- Does it look like him?
What do you think?
- Look like who?
- Well, it's supposed to be Tenma.
- Not bad.
Maybe I should give your drawing to the police.
Even when I offered information, they didn't believe it.
Not the important parts.
This is the man I'm talking about.
He's out there all by himself,
on a long journey to slay the monster.
- Eva, is he gonna come back?
Now, the latest news on the flood-damaged areas.
Due to the flooding of the Elgar River, many roads are closed and railways have been shut down in several areas.
Power and phone lines have also been affected as well, leading to dangerous conditions in many of the stricken areas.
This is an email that came three days ago.
Its content might be disturbing to you, but Dr. Gillen and I decided you should read it if you feel you're up to it, Nina.
I want to see it.
"To Nina, I'll be waiting for you in Ruhenheim, Johan."
So you think it's from him as well.
Earlier, you were describing what you felt Johan was attempting to do right now.
You called it a perfect suicide.
You thought many innocent people might wind up being killed too.
Ruhenheim. There is a village with that name in the south part of Germany.
There's a real possibility that Tenma is headed there as well.
I've got to go there. You have to let me go.
I really must admit this has been an unusual turn of events for me.
At first you were someone who only existed in a certain man's delusions.
It's true. It's as if you were an imaginary character straight out of one of your many story books.
For many years, I carried out my investigation, compiling only objective data.
But lately, I did something different. I ignored my methods and looked into that man's delusions.
I tugged at the loose ends of this case, mostly for fun.
In the Czech Republic, I met a young man who had visited the Red Rose Mansion frequently.
That young man was your own son.
This is a hand-drawn postcard he received.
It signed "KP" for Klaus Poppe, your real name.
Even though I've come to this place and you're sitting there right before my eyes,
it still feels unreal to me.
It really is as if a character from one of your picture books sprang to life.
But this is reality.
I did some research and found a list of refugees who had defected from Czechoslovakia
The name Klaus Poppe was listed there.
You escaped and resettled in this town after the fall of the Berlin Wall.
What were you trying to escape from?
Maybe from people like myself?
The orphanage known as 511 Kinderheim only existed because it was part of your plan.
That's where you created subjects like me.
When you ran away, it was to escape the reality you made.
I know what he's up to.
And now, Johan's warped plans are being manifested even as we speak.
And this quiet town is paying in blood for your sins.
Another gunshot?
What's happening? I saw a lot of dead people on the way over here.
Hey, do you have any idea what's going on?
Come on, why are we waiting?
Let's get out of town now.
We can't.
All transportation in and out of here has been shut down.
Well, that's great.
Where do you keep going?
You go out and then every time you come back to our room,
you take another shower.
This whole town smells of gunpowder, blood, and death.
It's disgusting.
You need to calm down, honey.
I've ordered you a pot of tea from the front desk, and that ought to help.
It's all right, baby. There's nothing to be afraid of.
By the time it stops raining, everything will disappear.
Disappear? What do you mean?
All those awful memories.
I'll allow you to go to Ruhenheim if you meet two conditions.
You must allow Dr. Gillen to accompany you.
Number two, he will not be allowed to bring a gun with you.
I won't. I don't need it.
If you'll excuse me, I need to get ready to go.
Dr. Reichwein, I'll need you to do what we talked about.
You, yourself, and Dieter, Eva, and Karl,
Mr. Schuwalt, and Lota,
Everyone that knows Johan must go into hiding.
Johan's trying to erase every last memory of himself.
That's long enough. Come on or Dieter will see you.
"My memories with Dieter, and with you, and with Lota and Karl, my memories with the Fortners and with Tenma. I have many memories I don't ever want to forget, even if there are many memories I do want to forget."
But with Johan, it's vital that Johan's memories...
...should not be erased.
A policeman.
And his gun's been taken.
Don't take another step!
Save the town. I beg of you.
Tell me, who shot you?
There have been gunfights everywhere.
At first, these men with guns quietly snuck their way into town and spread themselves around.
Before I or anyone realized what was going on, our own town people had guns and they began shooting each other.
I've got to call for help! Help me! I've got to find a way to save... to save the children!
Help!
(dramatic music)
- Johan, I remember clearly the first time
that I heard that name.
It was back in 1995,
in the statement of a certain neurosurgeon.
- Dr. Tenma.
You admit that your theory about this case
is incorrect now, don't you, Inspector?
- No.
You see, Dr. Tenma is still a very important witness to me,
and this Johan is still nothing but a fabrication.
A fabrication.
I found myself obsessed by that term throughout my so-called vacation.
What does a person that exists have to do to become a fabrication?
The answer is quite simple.
Erase all who knew him.
Erase everybody that knows his past.
Everything must disappear.
Isn't that right, Bonaparta, exactly like the ending in your picture book?
At last he had found a name, but there was no longer anyone around to call him by it.
Such a shame, because Johan was such a wonderful name.
That could explain what's happening right now in this town.
That's what I would do if I were in Johan's shoes, because I'm a fabrication as well.
I'm not really Neumeyer, the man whose name's written in the hotel's ledger, and I'm not really Wolfgang Grimmer either.
Actually, I'm nothing, a nobody.
I imagine I'll disappear someday, with the person who's taken my childhood memories and my real name.
I've been waiting for this. I've been waiting here, waiting all this time for my verdict.
"I am not afraid of death, yet I don't know how to atone for my deeds.
I willingly accept whatever happens to me now."
"You've been waiting for this?
You say you're not afraid to die?
Do you have any idea how terrible the things you did really were?
Do you understand what it means to destroy a human being's sense of good and evil?
comprehend what happens when you awaken the monster inside each of us people should know
in their hearts that food tastes good they should always look forward to having picnics
in wonderful places on their weekends they should think that beer tastes good after a
hard day's work people should know they should feel they're supposed to grieve from the bottom
from of their hearts if they have to bury their own child.
I won't let you die.
My only goal is to get you out of here safely
and have you go public with everything you've done.
I will see you reveal to the world the identity of the monster
that you awakened with your horrible deeds.
Until that day, I will protect you with my life.
(eerie music)
- Where is Johan now?
- I, I don't know.
- All of us know that there is a monster
orchestrating this massacre.
Now where is he?
- I just don't know.
- Don't lie to me.
- Another gunshot.
Is someone here?
Can you see me?
Look, I'm not holding a gun.
It's all right.
Don't be afraid.
I've come to get you all out of here. You can trust me.
It's too dangerous here. You must escape, or none of you will survive.
Stop crying. I'll lead you to the path so you can escape through the woods. Let's get moving.
Wait! I know there's this man who's giving orders from the Hotel Bergbach.
I see.
That means I'll need more firepower than just my pistol.
I found these two outside.
This is our fault.
I feel like all of this happened because I won the lottery.
We should have informed the police earlier, when we first found Conrad dead.
Back before the town completely lost its mind.
So then you bought all three of these guns.
I haven't fired a single shot with them, honestly!
Let me borrow these two.
You stay here and protect this hotel.
What about you?
Every person you'll see out there is carrying a gun.
I can tell who's trouble.
I'm a detective.
Oh.
By the way, Grimmer.
When we're done with all this, I would like to buy you a beer.
Fine by me.
Run! Get out of here! You have to survive!
[MUSIC]
(gentle music)