I don't like having to tie up a couple of elderly folks.
But you're both important witnesses.
We can't have the two of you running away or getting shot.
Well, we barricaded the back door and most of the windows with furniture as best we could.
So I'm telling you right now, if somebody really wants in, it's not gonna keep 'em
out for long.
It's better than nothing.
Head down to the first floor and defend the entrance.
Do you have any experience using a gun?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- I'm coming with you.
I have to go down there too.
- I'm not about to let anything happen to you.
You need to live through this so you can tell the world
what you did to all those children.
Listen, Vim, you stay in here and keep this door locked.
But, Mr. Grimmer, what if something happens to you?
There's nothing to worry about.
A really strong friend of mine is coming to help us.
Do you mean it?
Yeah, of course I mean it.
Whenever I get into a really bad scrape,
he shows up just in the nick of time.
He never lets evil go unpunished.
They call him the Magnificent Steiner.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
Run, as fast as you can!
Head north, just stick to the path.
I'm pretty sure most of the children in town have made it safe out of here by now.
Go, follow those kids.
But what if there are still some near the center of town?
I gotta check.
Don't worry, leave it to me.
You just get your group to safety.
Alright. Hold on, one more thing before you go.
Do you know a man by the name of Franz Bonaparta, or maybe Klaus Poppe?
Poppe? Well, of course I do. He's the proprietor of the Hotel Versteck.
What are you doing there?
Just remain calm.
I'm not going to hurt you.
I...
I ran away as fast as I could.
But there's dead bodies.
He's everywhere. I don't even know where to go anymore.
And where did you run away from?
His room. He's giving orders from in there. I heard him. I heard.
Heard who?
Him. Roberto. He kept leaving and coming back, and every time he'd take a shower and change his clothes.
They were covered in blood.
So where can I find this Roberto?
The fourth floor of the Hotel Bergbach.
I thought... I thought he was a nice guy who'd take me away.
I didn't know.
Listen to me.
A group of survivors are holed up in the Hotel Berchtek.
Can you get there by yourself?
Get there myself? I can't.
Come on. You can't just sit here.
I can't.
(rain pattering)
(dramatic music)
- Dr. Tenma.
- Inspector Lunge.
- My trip into imagination has finally become reality.
"Emergence, Dr. Tenma. My journey comes to an end as the realities of the situation demand my attention.
From here on out, I'll be acting as an officer of the law. I'm finally back on the job."
"Take this girl to the Hotel Versteck. You'll find who you're looking for. A certain picture book author..."
Franz Bonaparte, how'd you know?
Inspector Lungay, where are you going?
I told you, back to work.
Perhaps we can talk later.
There are many questions I want to ask.
Dr. Tenma...
I'm sorry.
Talk to me, Nina.
What's going on?
My memory.
It's trying to come out.
One of my most painful memories.
One of your most painful memories?
It's horrible.
I don't ever want to remember again.
This scene keeps replaying in my mind...
If Johan has brought this memory to light...
[FOOTSTEPS]
Show yourself.
Please, don't shoot me.
I-- I'm telling you, I'm not one of them.
I'm a local, I swear.
I want the man in charge. Where is he?
Where's Roberto? I'm not asking you again.
You need to stand up. Come on!
Dead people! Everywhere! I can't take it anymore! I feel like I'm going crazy!
I can get you to the hotel, but you need to be brave for just a little while longer.
I can't do it!
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING]
[SOBBING]
(sobbing)
- Open your eyes, Erika.
Please, honey.
Please, Erika.
Just open your eyes.
- She's your wife, isn't she?
You need to leave.
She's already gone.
You can't stay here, it's too dangerous.
You need to get to safety, I can help you.
- You wanna help me?
Give me your gun so I can shoot the bastard who did this!
Damn you! Give me the gun!
He destroyed our happiness in an instant, so I'm gonna go kill him!
Is that what your wife would have wanted?
Your wife would want you and your child to live through this.
Well, isn't that right?
I'll take you to a path that cuts through the northern woods, it'll lead you to safety.
If the hotel's too far away, at least go with this man to the woods.
I'm not moving one inch!
Alright, I'll be back for you.
Stay right where you are, okay?
(sobbing)
- It sure is quiet.
So, these guys shooting at us,
they're not really here 'cause of that jackpot
me and the missus won, are they?
- Afraid not.
- Honestly, these last couple days
What the hell's the matter with me anyway?
I win it big in the lottery, and the first thing I do
is run out and buy a bunch of these awful things.
A normal life is what's best of all.
-Sounds pretty good.
-I gotta let the wife know the good news.
You know, about this not being our fault.
Honey, can you hear me? Guess what!
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
Mr. Heydick!
I've got you.
[GROANING]
My wife, is she all right?
Damn it.
[GROANING]
Oh, God, it hurts.
(dramatic music)
- This way, quickly.
- It's coming from the building across the street.
- Is there a basement in here?
- There is a cellar underneath the kitchen.
- You hanging in there, okay?
- Me?
What about you?
- My dad's doing this.
It's all my fault.
I didn't buy him a bottle and now he's going crazy.
Your dad didn't shoot anyone.
But you don't know him.
It's just like when he hits me every day.
'Cause I make him mad.
Come on, Vim.
You know your dad wouldn't do anything this bad, don't you?
I can end this.
All I have to do is go outside.
It'll be quick.
I'm not going to tell you again.
You don't get to die today, that's final.
I'll tie you down if I have to.
You stay here. Let me deal with this.
But Mr. Grimmer...
Remember, Vim. When things are at their worst, the Magnificent Steiner will show up and save the day.
I saw a few cases of that during my experiments years ago.
By exposing a child to excessive stress from anger or sadness, a child will manifest a different personality.
Those children were exceptionally violent creatures.
Almost all of them took their own lives.
I'm surprised that you haven't.
I'm alone and I'm unarmed.
A minute of your time, that's all I'm asking for.
You're not here because you want to be, isn't that right?
to this? East Germans from the old days? Former secret police? I don't care! Look at me! I'm
just a nobody from nowhere! Are any of you listening to a single word I'm saying?
Don't just follow orders! You're men, not machines! In your hearts, you know what's right!
The answer is sitting there waiting for you! Are you brave enough to look inside yourselves?
Well, are you?
I think you are.
Who are you talking to?
Huh?
I was so frightened, but I made it over here after all.
God, am I ever glad to see you again!
Huh?
I tuned into The Magnificent Steiner every day, my face practically pressed to the TV
screen.
But I don't remember the final episode.
Come on.
Let's go.
Huh?
No!
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
That weak young man in the show, I wonder if he ever realized--
realized that his anger transformed him
into the Magnificent Steiner.
I wonder if that young man ever found happiness.
[GUNSHOTS]
(gun firing)
- That young man.
I wonder, did he ever find it?
(screaming)
- Here we go.
Just a little bit further and we'll be out of these woods.
- You came from Ruinheim, didn't you?
How did you know?
Something's happening in your town, right?
Bunch of folks I'd never seen before showed up with weapons.
Everyone in town started killing each other.
You're not with those guys, are you?
Calm down. We didn't come here to hurt anyone.
When you were back there, did you ever happen to see a Japanese man with long hair?
Wait, you two know him?
Then you did see him.
Yeah. He was doing his damnedest to get these kids out of harm's way.
He's still back there, making sure they all get to safety.
When we split up, he said he was headed to the Hotel Versteck.
Nina, wait!
I left my car at the beginning of the path, just outside the woods.
Get any of those kids who need treatment to a hospital,
and contact the authorities as soon as you possibly can!
Hey, what are you doing? Are you out of your mind?
You can't go back there! They'll shoot you dead!
Maybe so, but that Japanese man is my friend, Kenzo Tenma.
He needs my help. Now call the police before it's too late!
The Hotel Versteck...
Mr. Grimlock.
Hey, Doctor.
I figured you'd be coming.
I'm not surprised.
I got two in the building next door.
Another one of them downstairs.
And that one I threw out the window.
Not bad for a day's work, huh?
The Magnificent Steiner appeared and did all this, didn't he?
As a matter of fact, Steiner never did show up.
I did it all on my own.
I got angry and I killed four men with my bare hands.
I need to treat those wounds.
Oh, yeah.
Almost slipped my mind.
Take it. It's a letter.
I got it from Inspector Lungay. He found it back in the Red Rose Mansion.
You gotta... you gotta go help him. He headed to the Hotel Bergbach by himself.
I'm not leaving you like this.
I'm fine. It's nothing a little rest won't fix.
Where are my manners?
I'd like you to meet Franz Bonaparta.
Mr. Grimmer!
Everything's gonna be alright.
It's been pouring all day,
but when it's sunny out,
seen from a postcard.
Wouldn't you agree, Dr. Tenma?
- I would.
- When the rain lets up, we should take Vim on a picnic.
- All right.
- With a bottle of old wine,
the finest cheese money can buy.
- Yeah.
- I'm crying.
But it's not because I feel my life fading away.
These tears are streaming down my face
because I'm crying for my son.
You can't just erase people's feelings.
It's as if my emotions were lost somewhere
hundreds of miles away.
It's as if they were sent long ago in a letter that was always intended for me.
So this is what true sadness feels like.
It feels a lot like happiness.
I think I figured out how the show must have ended.
The Magnificent Steiner.
He probably became human again.
Oh, Mr. Grimmer, please wake up.
Mr. Grimmer!
What have I done?
I don't want to die.
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]