(suspenseful music)
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hm?
[GUNSHOT]
[GROANING]
[GASPING]
Unless I'm wrong, your name's
Oh, you're dead wrong. I have no name.
I'm sorry to hear that.
As a police officer, you might say I take a professional interest in the name of the man who kills me.
[MUSIC]
(dramatic music)
- Oh Lord.
- He was such a good man.
- He fought to protect us at the cost of his own life.
- Mr. Grimmer.
- Dr. Tenma, where are you going?
- I can't stay here right now.
- You're going to help Inspector Lunge, aren't you?
I'm going with you.
I have a gun.
I have the letter that Inspector Lungay left with Grimmer.
Seems the inspector found it, tucked away somewhere in the Red Rose Mansion.
I've been watching you.
I wanted to devour you whole.
But instead, everything about you consumed me.
When I was falling apart, how did I look to you?
When I was falling apart, the object that you gave me...
You left me...
You left me a beautiful jewel.
The twins who look as if they were blessed with eternal life.
The most sinful deed is to take away a person's name.
Let's get your name back.
I'll give you your name back.
"Your name is Anna. Right now, I'm just sad. Sad. Sad. Sad. Sad. Sad."
You wrote this letter, didn't you?
Unexpectedly, I fell in love with the twins' mother.
My whole way of thinking changed in an instant.
And so, I killed everyone who knew about her,
who knew about the twins,
who knew about the experiment.
That is all.
(rain pattering)
(thunder rumbling)
(grunting)
Stop playing games. Tell me now, who are you?
That gunshot wound will prove fatal in time.
Answer me if you want to live.
Where the hell is Johan?
Why do you go to such lengths for him?
Exactly what is your connection to Johan?
You're a sad and bitter man.
Pathetic man inspector Lungay
The brilliant BKA agent sniffing around this little town
without a friend in the world
on a long vacation without his police badge
Dug too deep into a Senate members dirty laundry, didn't you? Your boss has left you out to try
Chasing Tim is all you've got to live for and now you're obsessed with it
You did your homework
You know me very well.
Oh, there's more.
Your wife's living with another man.
Very happily, I might add.
Your grandchild thinks that your wife's new man is his grandfather.
The little boy's starting to talk now.
And he says, "Grandpa, my dear grandpa."
Shut up.
You must be dying to see him.
They grow up so fast.
Shut up.
You've never even met him, have you?
Shut up!
You've really lost your edge, Inspector.
The old Lungay would never have fallen for that one.
So, you want to know who I am and what my connection is to Johan?
I'll tell you again, I have no name.
country and no memories. The farthest back I can remember is going from the
orphanage to my job. That's all I knew. Then one day in walked Johan. And that's
when he awakened the one powerful memory I'd held on to. The only memory of my
childhood.
Tell me, what was his real name?
He said he didn't know.
He didn't know his own name?
Mm-hmm.
He was in an orphanage.
He forgot everything,
except the name of his friend,
a boy he was close to,
who was also living in that place.
Are you sure about this, Phim?
He forgot his own name,
but remembered his friends?
Yeah. His friend liked to draw,
and he liked to paint.
bugs but he hated killing them so he would release the bugs from the cages
that had been used to trap them. He even told me the boy's name. He said it was
Adolf Reinhardt and he loved the hot cocoa that was given to each of them
once a week.
Johan came to me that day at work and offered me a nice warm mug. It reminded
me. Of my childhood, the only pleasure I'd had. I remembered I loved the hot cocoa they
gave us once a week at the institution.
If only all of this rain would wash everything away. The fear, the evil, and sadness. But
And everything flared up instead and grows more powerful as the rain continues to pour.
Just like then, it was raining like this on that day.
We begin with our top story.
Mr. Liebert, former head of commerce in East Germany, has fled with his family to the West.
We go live now to Dusseldorf.
I'm here in Dusseldorf where the East German trade commissioner who fled to the West appeared
yesterday, along with his family.
(doorbell ringing)
- You're a refugee as well?
- Yes, from Czechoslovakia.
- And you say you know everything about them?
- Let me see them, even if it's only for an instant.
Just their sleeping faces.
(somber music)
- That night, something tragic occurred.
(dramatic music)
- There appears to be one survivor, a girl.
A man and a woman are dead.
critical condition. Where's the patient? Blood pressure 72 over 50. His pulse is
at 137. The bullet entered through his forehead.
I couldn't fathom what in the world happened on that fateful night. No,
Well, actually, I knew.
I knew about everything.
But I tried to escape.
I shut down.
I wasn't able to think about anything.
I just fled.
And then, I tried to draw them.
The picture-perfect twins,
surrounded by love and affection.
However, no matter how hard I sketched,
I captured it on paper, because deep down I knew only too well, I knew they didn't exist.
The Hotel Bergbach where the inspector went is up ahead of us, right?
That's right.
Let's go. Be careful. They could be aiming for us.
I...
I'm guilty. I'm the one who created the monster.
And I brought that monster back to life, I'm the one who saved him.
This isn't going to kill you, is it?
I don't have that much strength left in my right hand.
I was shot by Dr. Tenma in a library in Munich.
It would have been so easy to kill him right there and then, but I couldn't because it wasn't part of the plan.
You see, Dr. Tenma is the one who's to be left.
He'll be the only one left, and he'll be all alone.
He'll die alone, slowly, sadly, and without a name.
All part of Johan's master plan.
Dr. Tenma will be the one to be given a glimpse of what Johan saw.
You know something? I want to see it as well.
And I will.
Tragically, you will not, Inspector Lungay.
Sadly, you will die.
This is also...
Johan's master plan.
[GROANING]
[CRASH]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
His master plan?
According to the hard drive inside my head,
his master plan doesn't add up.
Answer me now.
Where the hell's Johan?
Unbelievable.
It looks like a war zone.
Johan isn't here.
How do you know that?
He's somewhere else, observing all this.
For him, it's like watching a line of ants.
Well, let's take a look inside anyway.
Tenma was headed here too.
Hello? Is anybody here?
I'll look upstairs.
A little boy?
Stay away!
Easy. It's all right. We're friends. We've come here to help you.
Look, I'm not holding anything. See? It's all right.
What?
Are you the girl in the drawings?
Drawings?
Drawings? What do you mean?
There's a whole big pile of drawings,
and you look exactly like the girl in them.
A big pile of drawings?
With a boy who has the same face.
Bunch of drawings of twins.
Where are they? Where did you see them?
Tell me where you saw them!
Um, the-- that big hill south of here.
They're in the vampire's house.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[rain pattering]
- Hey, anybody seen him?
Anybody seen my son?
Hey, where'd my boy, Vim, go?
Everybody... everybody's dead.
The devil did all this...
The devil...
The devil has come to this town!
Well, it sure doesn't look like there's anybody here.
"You're thinking that just before we arrived, Johan was standing there, doing what you're
doing right now.
The same drawings over and over.
They all seem to be attempts to draw you and your brother, but they're all unfinished.
Unfinished drawings of gentle, smiling faces, but did Franz Bonaparta really draw all these?
What must he have thought when Johan saw them?
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Nina?
I saw something frightening something very frightening a whole lot of people
died the red rose mansion every everyone in that room was drinking wine and then
And then they... they collapsed, writhing in agony, piling on top of each other!
Where did my mother go?
"I'm sorry. Why are you apologizing to me? Because at that time, the two of you had to
keep on living. The two of you had to live. Why are you crying? Why are you crying? Please.
Please don't cry. Please don't cry. Please don't cry. Please don't cry. Please don't
Don't cry! Please don't cry!
Nina!
Nina, are you...
Johan... He was crying...
Go on.
He was right here. He was in this room right before we arrived. All alone.
Crying the same as he did back then.
Back on that rainy night. If only I hadn't shot him.
If I had been able to forgive him instead,
maybe it wouldn't have gone this far.
All these innocent people wouldn't have had to die.
I don't know.
It might already be too late by now.
But it's time.
Do you know where Yohan is?
He's gone into town, to end this once and for all.
(static crackling)
(ethereal music)
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]