The devil did all this...
The devil...
The devil has come to this town!
Listen, I'm gonna go in first, alright?
You come in behind me and cover my back.
Our one and only priority here is saving Inspector Lungay.
Of course.
Dr. Tenma!
Him? What is it? What are you doing out here?
Dr. Tenma, a lady who came into the hotel was looking for you.
Who was it?
She was heading up to the vampire's house.
And she looked just like one of the twins from the drawings I saw up there.
Drawings of twins? Nina?
Nina...
I've always wondered what name she would have.
her Nina. Was that the name they gave to her? Yes, Nina, Nina Fortner.
It is a wonderful name. It's really important to cherish your name. That's
what you always told me, Mr. Pope.
Hey, did you see my dad?
I can't find him anywhere. Have you seen him?
Listen to me, Vim.
We have something very important to do here.
But when we're done, we'll help you look for him.
My dad wouldn't kill anyone, would he?
Dear boy, you know your father isn't that kind of person?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, now go hide in that store across the street.
Take them and find some cover now!
Well, we finally meet again, Dr. Kenzo Tenma.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANING]
[GUNSHOT]
Let's die.
You and me together...
(dramatic music)
(eerie music)
[EXPLOSION]
[WATER RUNNING]
[PANTING]
Nina, wait!
I have to look for him.
I have to find Franz Bonaparta.
That's him at the Red Rose Mansion.
He told me!
Listen to me very carefully.
Forget everything you just saw.
Run far away from here, as far away as you can.
People can become whatever they want to be.
You are beautiful shining jewels, both of you.
And that is why you mustn't ever become monsters.
That's what he told me! So I... I...
Mr. Povey! Mr. Povey! Mr. Povey!
Oh my god! Mr. Bonaparta!
(footsteps)
- Roberto.
(grunting)
Run away, Bim, now!
(sobbing)
(thunder rumbling)
I have to see it now, the scenery for a doomsday.
You can't see it now.
You are not able to.
[rain falling]
Vim! Get back!
Dr. Tenma, for you, all lives are created equal.
That's why I came back to life, but you've finally come to realize it now, haven't you?
Only one thing's equal for all, and that is death.
You can see it.
The scenery for a doomsday.
(wind howling)
(airplane engine roaring)
(explosion booms)
Stop, Dr. Jemma, don't do it, don't pull that trigger.
(sobbing)
- Johan, I forgive you for what you did.
Even if we were the only two people left in the whole world,
I'd forgive you.
This is what I can do, from me to you.
- It's no use.
Some things just cannot be undone.
There's no turning back.
Dr. Tenma will shoot me.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Isn't that right?
Stop!
You have to do it.
Tenma, no!
(water rushing)
It was the devil.
The devil has come to this town and killed everybody who lives here.
(sobbing)
That's for him.
No.
That's my son.
Stop.
(eerie music)
- What, what the hell is that?
(explosion booms)
It's a, it's a monster!
(man screams)
What the hell is that thing?
Get away!
Stop right now!
Stop, you get away from my son!
[GUNSHOT]
This is TKMIF.
We've landed on the west side of Rubenheim.
The situation here is under control.
We've secured the east side.
Provide aid to any residents you can
He's still alive!
This is terrible.
Are there any survivors left?
My D.N.N. news crew and I have finally been able to enter this remote,
rain-drenched area by taking a route through the hills south of here.
We bring you this shocking live report.
The entire populace has been annihilated in what looks to be a wanton massacre.
What could have happened in this quiet little southern German town?
Who is responsible?
Yes, as I said, we have one person in custody at this time, and he's our primary suspect.
Herbert Knaup, age 38, says he's currently unemployed.
My dad!
Yes, he's admitted his crime, said he shot a young man.
My dad only shot him because he was trying to protect me!
He appears to be a severe alcoholic, and by his behavior, I'd say he's quite drunk.
The reason he gave for his actions, he said there was a monster with seven heads and many
horns that was attacking his son.
It's really hard to make any sense out of his statements.
Huh?
Oh, Dad!
Hey!
Can you copy that?
Dammit.
Cut off again.
It's as I said, I've already told you what happened here.
Yes, I know you did.
But I'm having trouble understanding it.
You said a young man named Johan destroyed this entire town in order to commit suicide?
Please, Dr. Gillen, run this by me one more time so I can better comprehend it.
It's a long story. It'll take a while.
And after I'm done, you still might not fully understand it.
I was at the Hotel Versteck.
We found a wounded police officer in one of the rooms there.
How bad is he?
Well, I don't think there's any danger to his life,
but he seems to be delirious.
Damn it all!
Isn't there a single officer in this town who can explain what happened?
Yes, right here.
I know everything.
And you are?
Inspector Lunge of the BKA.
I'm afraid I don't have my ID.
headquarters Roberto is dead essentially he's the one responsible for what
happened here I tried to finish him off but he lost consciousness I turned
around to head for the stairs but when I did I suddenly heard his voice coming
from behind me in the next instant I was hit on the back of the head and I
But just as I was passing out, he said,
"I still can't see it, the scenery for a doomsday."
We'll want to hear more after you receive medical treatment.
Stop crying. Everything's going to be all right.
Excuse me. I need to get both your names.
Heine, I live on Erf Street, and this is my wife, Franka.
Can you prove your identity?
Yes.
What is it? Dear, what's wrong?
No. I can't find the lottery ticket.
I thought I had it tucked away in my vest pocket.
I've got to go back and look for it.
Honey, wait!
That must be what happened.
Honey, don't go! It's alright!
We're going to be fine without it.
Being alive is plenty.
We still have each other.
That's more than enough.
Sorry to interrupt, but I still need some ID.
Just take your time.
I'll come back a little later.
Well, let's see.
here. Ah, there are two right there. Excuse me, folks. I need to see some identification.
Search every building. There might still be survivors inside.
Got a minute?
Yeah, what is it?
I might be wrong, but... I can't believe it.
Johan... He's breathing, but will he live?
Well, it's hard to say. He's got a serious head injury.
Even if we had a really good neurosurgeon on hand.
You do. He's right here in town.
Get him, quickly.
Excuse me, there's something I'd like to ask.
You couldn't be, could you?
You are him! You're that doctor, aren't you?
Dr. Tenma!
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
I need you to come with me right away.
Hey! Wait a minute!
Inspector Lungay of the BKA is asking for you.
Look, he sent me to get you because we have a patient in critical condition who needs your help.
"Let him go! My dad isn't a murderer!"
"Now listen, son. We need to take your dad away in order to ask him some questions."
"My dad would never hurt anybody! He was only trying to save me!"
"I'm sorry."
"Dad!"
"I want to forgive him. I really want to do that."
Tenma...
You weren't wrong, you know.
Not then.
And you won't be now.
Give him back!
My father's not a murderer!
[music intensifies]
(helicopter blades whirring)
(heartbeat thumping)
(heart monitor beeping)
[Beeping]
All right, let's begin the operation.
[Music]
[MUSIC]