From Mount Olympus, Zeus commanded his mortal subjects to live off the land.
They obeyed, and--
Stop, Carl. Your recitation is so stilted.
Sorry, Father. I guess I was trying to be careful.
But you have improved.
When you first came, I thought to myself,
"Why in the world did such an unimpressive student show up here?"
Oh, yeah.
Whatever happened to him?
What happened to that Japanese doctor?
Actually, I've heard he's traveling quite a bit now, Father.
I see.
You know, I'd really like to meet Dr. Tenma one more time.
Me too.
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(bell tolling)
So you've started a job? Glad to hear it.
What kind of work are you doing?
I'm an interior designer these days.
Oh, I see. You do seem like someone
who would have a very keen eye for arranging a home.
I am working in homes,
but it's a little different from what you're thinking.
Hmm?
Well, I specialize in kitchens.
Ah.
Funny, isn't it?
A person like me who had no idea
I've never even stood in a kitchen before.
- Well, do you think you'd consider
remodeling my kitchen sometime?
- Sure, why not?
- But with your expensive tastes,
I bet your kitchens must come at quite a steep price.
- I like the best.
(laughing)
- You're not drinking anymore, are you?
- No, not a single drop.
- That's good news.
Try to take your time and enjoy your life.
Even if we rush, tomorrow we'll arrive
Same as always.
You've always said that's what real happiness is.
Haven't you?
That I have.
Happiness...
I can't forget his words.
He said that he was happy just knowing I was waiting for him at the station.
Ah, this is Martin you're talking about.
People are such strange beings.
The sad memories seem to just fade away
until all the persons left with are the happier ones.
People are certainly designed so conveniently.
That's the whole reason we can keep on living.
I'll introduce you. Meet Mr. Werdemann. He's a lawyer. He's the one who was ultimately
responsible for clearing your name, Mr. Grimmer.
I did do some research and found out as much as I could about you. You were one of the
children from 511 Kinderheim. You worked secretly as an intelligence agent for the East Germans
traveled the world posing as a freelance journalist.
After retiring, you used your skills
to investigate human rights violations.
Your duffel bag was bursting at the seams
with papers and documents supporting your work.
But in all your investigating,
the one mystery you were never able to unravel
was that of your real name.
- Wolfgang Grimmer.
- His name wasn't the only mystery.
He left without telling us anything about himself.
Inspector Lungay.
I'm no longer an inspector, Detective Suk.
Oh, well, sir, you haven't retired, though.
I heard that you're a professor at the police academy.
True, I have other priorities.
I talk to my daughter more now.
Well, email, technically.
We lived our lives without knowing anything about one another.
For years, we never discussed anything.
Only one thing matters to people.
It's all about how much we can communicate during our lives.
Grimmer probably had lots of things he wanted to talk about
over a good beer.
You're going back to live in Dusseldorf?
I am. The company that hired me is located there.
Oh, I see. Hmm. Are you comfortable with that?
After all, a lot of things happened to you there.
There's no use in running away.
You said what's important is to face the truth and move forward.
Didn't you?
Mm-hmm.
Could you dispose of this notebook properly for me, Doctor?
Sure.
Thank you.
You're welcome. And best of luck.
Please, call me if there's anything you need.
Remember that Dr. Gillen and I are always here to help you.
Dieter is, too. And him.
Do give him my regards.
The questioning of Dr. Tenma is still continuing, but the real truth is still unknown.
Inspector Lunge begins his testimony on the Tenma case.
Could this possibly be the worst multiple homicide case in European history?
Dr. Tenma is found innocent of any crimes.
a formal apology to Dr. Tenma.
The motive for these murders still remains unclear.
Just who is the mysterious young man
who's allegedly the real culprit?
Munster University's medical school
invites Dr. Tenma to become a professor.
Dr. Tenma declines the school's offer firmly.
Dr. Tenma joins the aid group Doctors Without Borders.
The articles become shorter and shorter.
People are certainly designed conveniently, huh?
Hey there, Deeter.
You've grown a lot since the last time I saw you.
Hey, Mr. Heckle.
You've gotten a lot sleazier since the last time I saw you.
I see you've still got that smart mouth, don't you?
Sorry, I can't chat now.
I've got soccer practice.
Hold on.
Hey, wait a second!
Isn't Tenma back in town yet?
He went and joined the MSF.
'Cause he's trying to make himself look good by doing something that doesn't make any money.
And I can't even get a hold of him.
What if he is back?
Then I'll tell him to his face.
The money he gave me for this job I'm doing for him isn't enough to cover all my expenses and labor.
He asked you to do a job for him?
He said he just needed me to look for somebody.
And it sounded like an easy job.
Confidential stuff from the police who knows what'll happen if they catch me
Hey
Dieter
You give this bill to tenma and if he doesn't pay it I'll see to it that he ends up an underground doctor again
Tell him I'm not kidding
We've been wondering where you went.
You haven't stopped by for quite a while.
I'm sorry, I've been out of the country lately.
Here, I brought this back to share with everybody.
My, my, you really shouldn't have.
Oh, thank you.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
(birds chirping)
- It's a beautiful day.
So many of the leaves are photosynthesizing.
That's life, all those countless genes.
Are you familiar with Mendel's work?
- Yes, he's a famous geneticist.
- That's correct.
I studied at the same university Mendel attended in his day.
in the Czech Republic.
It's down southeast in Moravia.
It's a nice city.
I'd like to see it someday.
I thank you.
You've come to visit me many times.
I've so enjoyed the time I've spent with you.
It's nothing.
I feel wonderful today.
I feel like I can talk about anything.
No matter how terrifying.
And you...
You have something you want to ask me, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You're the mother of the twins, aren't you?
Yes.
I loved him so much,
and he was killed by that man.
It was all part of his experiment.
I will never forgive him, not for what he did.
Even if I die, these children growing inside of me will punish that man for what he's done.
He will definitely pay for everything that he's done to us.
And don't let go of my... my hand.
Who is the real monster? Who is it?
Are the twins still... they're alive, aren't they?
Yes. They will.
I just remembered.
You can tell me if you like.
I might not remember this ever again if I don't say it now.
I gave names to both of those children.
And I'll tell you what their names are.
Yes, come in.
Well, as usual, I see that you are tardy.
You are ten minutes late for our appointment.
I'm sorry, Professor Kronecker.
Your apology is accepted.
You know why I called you in today, don't you?
It's about your senior thesis.
Without a good grade on it, you will not graduate.
Please come forward.
Yes.
I know a lot has happened to you this semester.
It's unrealistic to expect you'd be able to catch up with all the time you were gone.
I understand. But I know that that's no excuse for my grades.
You are quite right.
Now, regarding the matter of your thesis...
superb.
This thesis is far and away the best paper written by any of my students
I'm quite proud of you. You have done an exceptional job.
Thank you very much, Professor.
What do you want to become?
I want to become a lawyer, sir.
Well, I imagine that a great many people will be saved by your skills.
And now you may go.
Yes, sir.
However, don't think you'll be allowed to be tardy for court,
Fräulein Nina Fortner.
Right.
Yes, hello?
Oh, hey Dieter.
Will, are you graduating?
Even if you aren't, I'll stick with you.
Will, it's good to hear from you.
Sure that. The next time we're together, you can try and cheer me up.
You can't fool me. I can tell you did from your voice. Congratulations, Nina.
Thank you, Dieter. But once I'm in law school, the real studying begins.
Let's celebrate. Come home already.
I can't come home for at least another day. I've got work. And I've already made plans with my friends.
What are you talking about? Tenma's coming back to see us.
Nina? Tenma just called. He's heading abroad soon for the MSF, but first he's coming here.
When?
He said he'd be here by tomorrow. So you better hurry!
Oh, Nina! About our plans for tomorrow?
Sorry, won't be able to go!
Tenma! I'm going to see Tenma!
(panting)
- Oh, good afternoon, Doctor.
- Good afternoon.
You've been sleeping ever since that day you were shot.
Can you hear me?
I had the opportunity to talk with your mother.
She still loves you very much.
Sh-She told me what your real name is, Johan.
You have a name.
Dr. Tenma, there's something I want only you to hear.
That time, long ago, when the monster appeared in front of me.
Don't touch my children!
Don't you come near us!
This is an experiment.
We will leave one behind and take the other one with us.
Now, which one are we going to take?
Don't let go.
Don't let go...
This one...
No, wait...
This one!
No!
Was my mother really trying to save me that day, or did she confuse me with my sister?
Well, which is it? Which one of us didn't she need?
(breathing heavily)
- Well then, I guess this is goodbye.
(footsteps tapping)
[silence]
[door creaks open]
[door creaks closed]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(ethereal music)