It's over?
What do you mean
by "it's over", Mr. Schuwald?
It means the investigation
I hired you for is now over.
Wait a minute...
It's true that the investigation
on Karl Neuman is over.
He was your son.
I thank you for your work.
W-Wait a minute, that doesn't mean
that the matter is settled.
It's still possible that Edmond Fahren's
death was not a suicide.
We also don't know the identity of the
person who was behind Fahren either.
Everything has been settled.
The tea is ready, Dad.
Oh, is that so?
Hello.
Would you like to join us?
No. I'm fine, thanks.
Well, thank you for your work.
Please send us your bill.
It's nice weather outside, isn't it?
Yes...
Johan is here, too.
Is that so? Johan is here, too?
How can that icy man, who's never trusted
anyone or let anyone get close, become
such a softy because of his son?
That smile...
I can't believe that's the same man that
was called "the Vampire of Bayern."
"Is that so? Johan is here, too?", huh?
So you're currently trying to
find this puppy, right?
Just One Case
Yes.
It seems that my client's ex-husband
took it away after the divorce.
That's a difficult situation...
a custody battle over a puppy.
Indeed.
Excuse me, but I'll be having some wine.
It's fine, go ahead.
I'm okay with just water.
Even though you say that you're
free from your job,
it doesn't seem like you're
interested in drinking.
That's right. I'm fine in that respect.
"In that respect"?
Is there something else that
you're worried about?
Well, because I've got some free time,
I'm doing some silly things.
Oh?
I've been flipping though a scrapbook I made when
I was a detective. It's full of all my unsolved cases.
I see.
And when you look at that, what do you feel?
Frustrated...
That homicide, this homicide...
When I think about how the perpetrators
are living comfortably outside of prison,
I just can't take it...
I feel frustrated at my lack of ability.
You had the ability.
Richard, you tried so hard and became
too attached to your cases.
You became frustrated at your inability
to read the perpetrator's mind and...
And I turned to alcohol...
That's right.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh, the food's here.
But I don't necessarily think
that that's a bad thing.
I mean, the fact that you're flipping through
your scrapbook of past cases.
I'll just get frustrated again.
No, you should be fine now.
I'd like you to tell me what you think of
the cases when you look over them now.
You got drunk and killed that young
boy who was a serial killer.
You are now prepared to face
that fact head on,
yet you're still trying not to remember what went
through your mind when you pulled the trigger.
You still see that young boy's
ghost, don't you?
Yes...
When everything is clear,
and when it comes into broad daylight,
that ghost will go away too.
When everything comes into
broad daylight, huh?
The homicide of Holmar the accountant...
The victim, Joakim Holmar, had been
steadily building up his career.
He wasn't the type of person
who people would resent.
There was no indication that
it was a robbery.
The "Voice of God" homicide.
The victims were an
ex-housekeeper and a driver...
At both crime scenes,
a mysterious message proclaiming that the killer had
heard the voice of God was written on the wall.
The homicide of the Dornah Company CEO...
One of the leading investigators in Bayern, Ruto Gakushi, was found dead in the Hartoholtz forest.
The Spiras homicide...
A middle-aged couple drowned and was
found upstream in the Izar River.
The case was grouped with the serial
homicides of middle-aged couples.
The primary suspect, a Japanese doctor, is still on the run.
Man...
I started drinking more as the number
of unsolved cases rose.
But now, things are different.
I see.
It's just like the doctor said.
So this is what it's like to think while sober...
What?
W-Wait a minute.
Think.
Thi...
And?
What were you thinking about at that time?
Well, the thing is...
I was thinking about something but...
Your flash of insight disappeared when
you saw that young boy's ghost?
Yes...
There's no need to be impatient.
Your flash of insight will
come back to you someday.
What was my realization?
I felt as though it was an important key
to solving one of those unsolved cases...
Must have been my imagination.
Who is it?
Who's following me?
It's just like that one time...
That time, I was also...
I was also running through this hallway...
Chasing him...
Sorry for bothering you this
late at night, doctor.
It's fine. It seems like you finally feel
like telling me the entire story.
I'll listen to it.
That time, I saw it in the young boy.
I realized that it did exist in this world,
that true evil existed.
That's why...
That's why I...
shot the young boy dead.
Good. Good job telling me that.
You've finally been able to
get back on your feet.
There's more...
I see now...
That flash of insight I had...
Out of the many unsolved
cases that bothered me...
Really...
There was one case.
Dear Dr. Gillen,
I had the pleasure of reading your
work that you sent to me,
"A Summary of
Transcendental Criminal Psychology."
I'm pleased that one of my students...
from my days of teaching at the
University of Düsseldorf...
is having such success.
By the way, Dr. Gillen,
you told me before that during your interview
with the serial killer Peter Jurgens,
he told you that he'd committed the murders
because one of his friends had ordered him to.
Since my memory isn't certain,
could you tell me again...
what the name of Jurgen's friend was...?
P.S. You were a very good student in college,
but there was another who could compete
with you for the top rank.
He chose the path of neurosurgery,
but he is now the primary suspect
in a serial homicide case.
If you know anything about him,
please let me know.
What kind of man was he,
and where is he now...?
The man called Dr. Tenma...
Ah, you're that detective.
Now I'm just a private investigator
who barely scrapes by.
Forgive me for bringing up a hard subject,
but may I ask you questions regarding
the "Voice of God" homicide...
in which your mother was a victim?
Of course.
After four years, the police no longer
put any effort into the investigation.
Schuwald?
If I remember correctly, your mother
was a housekeeper, right?
Yes, but that was over 20 years ago.
What was the reason that she
stopped working for him?
Her health had declined,
so she stuck to working
around the neighborhood.
Could it be possible that she didn't
get along with Mr. Schuwald?
No! On the contrary,
my mother loved poetry, and while Mr.
Schuwald could still see, she and he...
used to read poetry to each other.
Oh, yes...
Please come this way.
Here, take a look.
I've kept these through the years because
mother thought much of them.
All these poetry books were presents
from Mr. Schuwald to my mother.
Who would have thought that the detective who
investigated the Dornah CEO homicide...
would now be a private investigator...?
As the CEO's secretary, I'd like to
ask you some questions again...
regarding the people who hated the CEO.
The CEO's enemies?
I told you before that there was
an endless number of them.
The police should have finished the analysis
of the list of companies that went
bankrupt because of CEO Gauk.
There is another notable
investigator in Bayern, right?
What was his relationship with him?
You're talking about Mr. Schuwald, right?
Well, those two were lifelong rivals.
Did you know about that?
Huh?
Schuwald went bankrupt twice in the past.
His second bankruptcy was a direct result
of fierce competition with CEO Gauk.
In other words, Schuwald was
crushed because of the CEO.
But the CEO had also been
hit by Mr. Schuwald.
They hated each other?
Of course.
Whenever they met at a party, there
would always be a big ruckus.
They would argue passionately.
Those two would?
Yes, those two cold people would.
They were the only ones who could
argue with each other on par.
Rather than being rivals,
They were actually friends.
Hey! Watch it!
Oh, Hans? I knew him well.
He was one of the two victims in
the "Voice of God" homicides.
It's too bad. He was a good guy.
Was Mr. Hans really such a good person?
Yeah, he would often buy me drinks.
He was Mr. Schuwald's driver, right?
I think so,
but that was over 30 years ago.
Do you know why he was fired?
It's because Mr. Schuwald went
bankrupt around then.
Oh, I see.
So it wasn't because of any trouble...
Listen up!
I'm telling you this to defend Hans's honor.
He was a good guy who could
get along with everyone,
be they rich people or poor people like us.
He used to often say...
that he taught the rich guy
how to enjoy bird watching.
Bird watching?
Yeah, he said that when he
took him to the forests,
that vampire would be as happy as a little kid.
It's already been two years,
but I still remember my husband.
My husband was a very serious man,
and no one had any real
reason to dislike him.
I still can't believe someone would
want to murder him.
My sympathies.
Pardon me, but your husband was a...
Yes.
He spent his childhood in an orphanage...
and lived with several foster parents.
After much difficulty,
he became an accountant.
Your husband was asked by Mr. Schuwald
to be his personal accountant, right?
Yes, many times.
He refused him every time, though.
There was the fact that he was busy
with what was then his job,
but he said that their philosophies
on money were different.
My husband was very strict
with money, so...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Do you think the perpetrator
will be caught?
I'll work hard on it.
He will definitely be caught.
Goodbye.
Oh,
by the way...
Do you know how your husband
and Mr. Schuwald met?
Oh, he said they met in the forest.
In the forest?
It was back when Mr. Schuwald could still see.
They happened to run across
each other in the forest.
Why in a place like that?
They were bird watching.
After that, he would go with
Mr. Schuwald many times.
Bird watching...
Happy like a kid...
Read poetry to each other...
Friends...
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yes, I'm fine. Thank you.
What a horrible driver.
Or rather, it seemed as though
he was targeting you.
Dr. Reichwein,
I've done my research.
It was just like I told you the other day.
The unsolved cases that bothered
me when I was a detective...
were all pointing in the same direction.
The "Voice of God" homicides,
the Dornah CEO homicide,
the accountant homicide...
At first glance, they seem totally unrelated.
The modus operandi of each murder
was completely different.
The victims were not related to each other.
In addition, there was no cash flow
linking them to each other...
Their connections did not go
into the records at all.
Even so, they were all connected
by one point.
All of these murders...
were committed to isolate Mr. Schuwald.
Also, there's another curious common point.
In the Dornah CEO homicide,
CEO Gauk left right before the crime,
saying that he had an important meeting.
The name of the person he went to see...
The name of the "God" that was written on
the wall in the "Voice of God" homicide...
And in the only one of my cases
that seemed unrelated,
the serial murder of the middle-aged couples in
which the prime suspect was that Japanese doctor,
the name that he mentioned
during his interrogation...
All of the names are the same.
"Johan."
A former student of mine,
a criminal psychologist,
researched a killer who murdered
because a friend ordered him to...
He told me by mail.
The name of the friend was also...
Johan.
It is a common name.
The connection between the cases
could just be coincidental.
However, if this were true,
then it means that someone named Johan
has committed these murders...
in the span of four years to
completely isolate Mr. Schuwald.
And the prostitute,
Margot Langer, who gave birth to Mr. Schuwald's
son, also conveniently died.
Fahren, the student who claimed
he was Mr. Schuwald's son...
also conveniently committed suicide
once the real son appeared.
If this man, Johan, does exist...
Where is he now?
This Johan...
Is that so?
Johan is here, too?
Hello, Johan.
It's nice weather outside, isn't it?
Yes, very.
He's right beside Mr. Schuwald.
Execution