Everyone's... dead.
The devil...
The devil has come to this town!
Okay. I'll go in first.
You cover me from the back.
Our top priority is to save Inspector Lunge.
Right.
Dr. Tenma.
Wim.
Why did you come here?
A woman came to see you.
A woman?
She went to the vampire's house.
A woman who looked just like one
of the twins in the pictures.
One of the twins in the pictures? Nina?!
Her name is Nina?
So now her name is Nina?
That girl is now known as Nina?
Yes. Nina Fortner.
What a nice name.
You always told me to cherish my name, Mr. Poppe.
Have you see my dad?
I can't find him anywhere.
Okay. We're doing something important right now,
but once it's over, we'll look for him right away.
My dad hasn't killed anyone, has he?
No, he hasn't, Wim.
Your dad isn't someone who would do that.
Yeah.
All right. Hide in that store over there.
Take Wim and find cover.
We finally meet again, Dr. Tenma.
Let us die.
Let us die...
together.
Scenery for a Doomsday
Wait, Nina!
I have to find him. Franz Bonaparta.
Back then, at the Red Rose Mansion, he...
Listen up, got it?
Everyone is going to forget what they just saw.
Run far away.
As far as you can.
People can become anything.
You two are beautiful treasures.
That's why you mustn't become monsters.
That's what he said to me.
That's why I... That's why...
Mr. Poppe!
Franz Bonaparta.
Roberto!
Run, Wim!
Show me...
the scenery of doomsday.
You...
will never see it.
Wim!
Get away from there.
Dr. Tenma.
According to you, lives are equal.
That's why I live today.
But, you must have realized it by now.
The only thing people are equal in...
is death.
You can see it.
The scenery of doomsday.
Don't!
Dr. Tenma, you mustn't shoot.
Don't shoot.
I...
I forgive you.
Even if we were the only people on Earth, I'd forgive you.
That is my message to you.
It's no good.
There's something you can never get back.
You can't go back.
Dr. Tenma's going to shoot me.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Isn't that right?
Stop!
The devil...
The devil has come to this town.
He has come to kill everyone.
Wim...
Stop...
My son.
Stop.
Who's that?
A ghost!
What is it?!
Stop! Let him go!
Get away from my son!
This is the D-KMIF. We've landed
on the west side of Ruhenheim.
We've confirmed that the east side is safe.
Secure any citizens that you see.
This is horrible.
Are there any survivors?
Our DNN news crew has finally made it
to town, located in the hills of the south.
This is a shocking incident.
This town has been wiped out in some sort of slaughter.
What happened in this quiet town in South Germany?
Yes. We currently have only one
person to press charges against.
Herbert Knaup, age 38, unemployed.
Dad!
He has confessed to a crime. He shot a young man.
Dad only shot him to save me!
It seems that he's pretty drunk
and he committed the crime because a monster
with horns and seven heads attacked his son.
He's been saying nothing but nonsense.
Dad!
Please respond.
Geez, it went out again.
It's just like I said.
It's just... I don't understand what you're saying.
A young man named Johan destroyed
this town in order to commit suicide?
Dr. Gillen, can you explain it so that we can understand?
It will take a long time to explain.
And even after that, you might still not understand.
We've secured an injured police
officer in the Versteck Hotel.
How is he?
Sir! I don't think his life is in danger,
but his sense is messed up.
Dammit. There's not a single officer who
can explain what happened here.
There is one.
I know everything.
Who are you?
I'm Inspector Lunge from the BKA.
I don't have my badge with me, but check with the BKA.
Roberto.
Is he dead?
He's the real culprit here.
I tried to deliver the final blow, but he lost consciousness.
I got away from him and headed downstairs.
I heard his voice from behind me.
In the next instant, he hit me in the back of the
head with his pistol and knocked me out.
He then said this,
"I still can't see it."
"The World of the End."
We'll talk later after you get treated.
Don't cry. We're safe now.
Excuse me. I need to confirm your identities.
We're the Hennigs from Erft Street.
This is my wife Franka.
Do you have any identification?
Yeah.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's gone.
The lotto ticket.
Huh?
I-I put it in my pocket.
I'm going to go look for it.
H-Honey.
I dropped it somewhere.
That's enough, honey.
We don't need it.
Just living here together...
is enough for me.
Um... That proof of identification...
I'll ask for it later.
Well, any more survivors?
There are some.
Excuse me.
I need to confirm your identities.
Go to every house.
There might still be survivors.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Hey, that guy...
What?!
Johan.
Is he alive?
No, with that head wound, he'll...
We couldn't save him even if we had
a brilliant brain surgeon here.
No. There is one.
Call him.
We have some questions to ask.
Are you...?
There's no doubt. He's the wanted criminal...
Dr. Tenma!
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
Could you come with me?
Hey, wait!
Inspector Lunge from the BKA asked for you.
He wanted me to tell you that there's
an important patient waiting for you.
My dad is not a murderer.
Hey, boy. We have a lot of questions for your dad.
My dad... My dad was just trying to save me.
Come on.
Dad!
I want to forgive him.
I want to forgive.
Tenma, you were not wrong...
in what you did back then and what you will do now.
My dad...
My dad is not a murderer!
Let's begin the operation.
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Real Monster