Formerly served in the French Foreign Legion
Then when freelance and fought in Nicaragua in 1979
From 1981 to 1984 assisted the Guerrilla rebels in Afghanistan
Then in 1987 you played a key role in the assassination of radical Islamic leaders in
Top secret moussard operation
It's quite an impressive resume I must admit
Isn't it Mr Hugo Bernhard
I have no doubt that a mercenary of your caliber must be quite a teacher and I'm sure a number of distinguished
Men must have been under your instruction
It might be a good idea to send some of our own officers to attend your seminar and have you with them into shape
That'd be great
Incidentally
Was this man here a good student by any chance
I believe he showed up at your training grounds about 5 months ago
We know that he is a genius with a scalpel
What I'm wondering about is whether he has any Talent with a gun
I don't divulge information about my pupils to anyone period
Of course you don't
So have you ever trained with a gun before
No I guess that means that you're self taught then
Actually
I've never shot a gun before
What you mean not even once right
I know I'm asking for the impossible
Matt said you're my only hope right now
It makes no difference
I make all my students forget everything they learned before they got here
But this
This is the first time I'll be teaching someone who's never shot a gun before
Jump rope
Regardless of your experience or lack of this is where everyone starts now jump like that child over there
Don't just stand there
Well get started yes sir
Faster now hurry it up
I said faster
Balance it's all about balance
Come on faster
I said faster
Well obviously I can't jump rope nearly as well as you do
Tell me something is this what you do you know always supervising student training like this
All right I understand you don't have to keep on staring at me like that
I'll do it
I know what I have to do
Hey it's a branding
I wonder if it's looking for food for its chicks
What's wrong are you too tired to eat
Yes
You can't train if you pass out
Yes sir
She your daughter
Or your granddaughter Maybe
Neither
That little girl is the daughter of a woman
I killed
Shut her down right before very
Backing me on
On Mission in the jungle I ran into a hut
For shelter
And there she was with her mother
If I'd have been a fraction of a second slower it would have been me that died that day
I brought the child back here with me I couldn't just leave her
From that moment on
She hasn't smiled once
That's why
She'll probably hate me for the rest of her life
That's the sort of thing that happens when you have a gun
Now if you can't handle that then I'd suggest you don't carry one
What a person sometimes it smells just like Daphne blossoms
Thanks
All right that's enough of that
So then
Time for some more running
Go
Yes sir
Right away then
When you're done running come to the bottom of the hill in the back
What's down there the firing range
The firing range
Remember
Two shots
You have to make sure that whenever you fire your gun you always pull the trigger twice if you can do that instinctively it better is
Chances of taking out your objective
If you can't do that
Then you're as good as Dad it's all over
What's this about
You're always preparing meals for me so I thought it would cook for you today it's a Japanese stew of meat and potatoes
It's called nicujaga go on dig in I think you'll both enjoy it those are chopstick
They're carved out of wood I made them I thought it would make our dining experience more authentic
Wow
You're really good at using Chopsticks aren't you
Again faster
Do it again
What's wrong
It's a baby brambling
I guess it fell out of its nest
No wait you have to put it back
That chick is going to die
It's very difficult to raise them like that they rarely survive for that long outside of the nest
Let's put it back
Back with its mother okay
3 seconds
That's all the time you've got
Find your target and pull the trigger cuz one mistake of the slightest bit of hesitation and you're dead
Tell me how well did he perform over those 5 months he was there training with you
Technically speaking he was a perfect student
He built up the necessary stamina
And his concentration while firing was extraordinary
However
Being able to actually shoot a person is another story
Really
Whether or not he is successful on his first kill
That's what it all comes down to
Either he's got what it takes
Already
Yes I see
I wonder which road this man will choose
Well it matters not
Tell me
Do you have any idea where he might have gone
Because if you do know where I would really like for you to tell me
Thanks for all you've done for me over the past 5 months
Here's the remaining tuition I owe
And please help yourself to the necojaga
Again
Thank you for everything
Damn it
So how about it you do know where this man was heading don't you
That I can't tell you
That's fine you can go now
This way sir
One man have a ball
Wait a second where's the Cherry
It's not a Manhattan without the Cherry
Yeah my mistake
I'll let it slide
This time
Business always goes well when I'm sucking on one of these
A lucky charm is a lucky charm
Come to Papa
I just hope there's still something of value we're taking
Well well look at what we've got here
It's a five finger free for all
Wonder if there's anything valuable enough for a connoisseur like Auto Hackle
You never know what's going to happen first year issue in Canada for governor next thing you and your
Can't get shot
LOL
Down to business
I'm guessing this is where they kept the safe
Why am I getting a chill this is creepy as hell I've never felt anything like this could
Could somebody be in there
What am I so scared about it ain't like me to be a chicken move
Put your hands behind your head
Oh man I can't believe this damn bartender at his fault
Forgot the Cherry
I said put your hands up all right all right all right give me a break on this one officer I
Taking anything yet I promise
I'm not a cop
No
So you're robbing the place too huh
Well in that case why don't you just put that thing away and we'll have ourselves behind your head now
James what's with this guy's a bigger boy scout than the freaking cops
Kidding me thanks for nothing buddy come out of here don't follow me someone like you just
It's in the way you call me down
That's right I thought I recognized you you're all over the papers you're the doctor wanted for questioning
Meaning connection with councilman Springs Missouri are you a thief
Go around killing people you wouldn't know anything about the murders that happened in that house would you no idea so get out of my
Face will you later
Hey doctor you're some sort of top notch surgeon aren't you my brilliant
Changes came up with a fantastic idea do you think that people meet by chance doctor they don't
Believe me I know I believe in fate I think people meet for a reason and my gut tells me
Destined to become Partners call me crazy but I think a lot of folks in the underground
Did he need someone like you you know guys who need to hide out so they can't go to regular doctors for help
Listen you leave the management to Old Heckle here I'll make you the world's best underground doctor in no time I'm
You'll be a millionaire before you know it hey hey
Do you think you're going there's something I have to do and it can't wait well I'd hold my
This is if I were you you want to know about the murders in that house don't you well I guess you'd like to
I hear that I saw the killer am I right what did you say are you telling me the truth
You want to know what's the Killer Blonde and about 20 years of age
Never mind you just tell me about who you saw there team up with me and I'd be happy to doctor
He's on the third floor
So how did you come to know all of this anyway
I spent a month checking out the councilman's house case in the joint I do my homework just when I'm ready to make a move
Killer beats me to it
15 minutes later I look in the window and they're dead worm food
And when I figured I might be able to Blackmail the murderer so I followed him here
This is all you really need to prove your innocence doc know what I'm saying all you have to do is call the police and tell him
After that we should go somewhere
Sit down relax talk over a drink about our future together as partners hey
Stop what are you doing what do you want to talk to him for what did you miss the part where he murders people
Man what is he thinking looking for trouble like that I'm out of here
However
A cash cow like him is a rare opportunity
Damn I usually make it a rule not to stick my neck out but
Another hot afternoon isn't it I
I'm actually looking for someone
There doctor what are you doing he's got a gun
Mother and I we often used to go walking together
On summer afternoons a lot like this one there was a long road we took and alongside of the
Field of sunflowers but mother's dead now this is important so I need you to listen did someone ask
To use that gun tell me was it a man was it a man it was one day
This young man came up to me at a local bar and was he about 20 years old with blonde hair
He was and he had a Big Bright Beautiful Smile called himself a
So he's going by Eric now
We met a few times and we eventually became very close friends
He invited me over to the place where he was staying
It was the estate of councilman Springer
Did he live in that Mansion until recently
Yes he did for a year in fact
He said they took good care of him he was like a son to them
Wait a minute I had my eye on that house for a month it never saw anyone who looked like that
They were a wonderful family
I have a picture
The councilman is wife and me
However
There was something I couldn't forgive them for
There was a beautiful area on their property a bit of sunflowers in their yard
But one day the councilman cleared it all up in order to build a bigger driveway
So when I mentioned to my young friend that I thought it was awful I was delighted to discover he agreed
Wait are you saying you actually killed them because of some flowers
Hardly
There was more to it
He also told me councilman Springer had a mistress
That's when my friend looked at me and said
I've decided I no longer wish to live with or be a member of the Springer household
From now on I'm not a part of that family anymore
Then he proceeded to request of me
That I erase
The family
Having a mistress is so an excusable
My mother was someone's mistress too she was a kept woman you know
Listen listen don't think about all that stuff by the way do you know where the safest in that house I believe
Leave on the second floor in the library
All right then
Talk to you probably shouldn't stick around here
You can erase your past did you know that if you don't like it you can erase everything
You can erase all of it and reset your entire life if you want sorry I don't
Don't agree with that at all you may try to forget but no one can simply erase their past like that
Yeah I guess you're right I wonder why I thought that it
Doesn't make any sense to me now why did I think I could erase the past by pulling the trigger
Looking back I wonder why I listened to him and did what he asked me
I think you should go now our talk is over I have nothing more to say
Oh that's right your name is
Isn't it he left a message behind for you to make sure you take
Good look at it you'll find it in the councilman's library he predicted that you would come
I'm here and he was correct about that Eric also mentioned to me your fate has already been
Decided for you so has mine
Doctor
I told you didn't I
Did you actually shoot this guy
Oh suicide I got you
What the hell
What's the use in dying
Everything's over when you're dead it makes no sense
Hey doctor there's nothing like living am I right you know I think I actually agree with you for a change hey what exactly
Really do you mean for a change
Anyway so you're after this killer named Johanna whatever I don't get it I really don't know why you do that
Hey why don't you forget about this nonsense in team up with me
Oh by the way I don't know why but when I try to open the door to this room before it kind of gave me the cre
What the
What's the matter you shaking like a leaf doc
Look at me look at me my monster inside me
Johansson mrso just a game to you isn't it
Hey Doc wait up oh come on wait listen to me hey Doc I'm talking
Do you oh for crying out loud I've got some really good news to tell you you're going to thank me for this
You'll keep your promise in team up with me right I never said a team up with you
I just thought you might need some money to run from the cops but I guess I was wrong
Just getting the car
This is our first client
The nice man will ask her to your patient doc
I'll hang on to your things for now if you want them back you'd better do your job get paid
The rest and meet up with me at Frank's Tavern on graston Street
So long now get out there and earn your keep
Now that's what I call a profitable business
Sincerity got in advance I suppose it's time to go and have a drink
Hey counselor I brought back a doctor for you
Thank you for coming
Hurry please stop the bleeding
It appears your auxiliary artery has been damaged did you get hit by a shotgun yeah
Get that far I could not operate on you here even if I had the proper equipment
He needs to be taken to a fully equipped Hospital
About how long ago was he wounded can the questions doctor
4 hours ago huh
Are you involved in the terrorist attack this morning and what does it matter if we were
Do it
What the hell did you say
I'm not helping people who took others lives and discriminately you
When you're in right now either you help him or you die
Calm down Carl
Listen daughter our friends will be coming to help us soon so it's simple all you need to do is stop
The bleeding to buy me some time
What the hell do you think you're doing do you want to die I already told you to come down
Counselor
I know you listen to me very carefully my life is in this doctor's hands right now
If I die
Then you can shoot them
We're not running a charity here no you are so you got to pay back
$250,000 marks we let you simple as that auto Heckle but Mr gloss I want to pay you back
Sir that's nice I'm glad you feel that way how considerate
Now go on ahead and break both his arms
Get it I'm getting them pay you back I will that's a good boy I just need you to give me one more month
Like both his legs too
They are Max steindorf and Carl blunt
Wait a minute it's them I can pay you back that money I know where those guys are I really do
And then I'll take care of what I owe you
This it better be the truth otherwise I'm going to break your scrawny necklace
Oh man that's right I forgot to miss
Get those guys oh well who cares
You called me a murderer who goes around killing people and discriminately
Well you're wrong doctor what I did have meaning there was a good reason for what I did
Now that
The president of gwe is dead I can finally die in peace
I really don't mind I achieved what I set out to do
Counselor
I used to be a lawyer in East Germany
My friend here was a political secretary
And when the Wall came down
We lost our jobs
Do you have any idea what it is like for us after the wall felt gwe came to the
With their big funding
They barged in and built these factories on our land
One after another
That was our country Our Land
They had no right to do that
They stepped all over our pride
Well I'm proud to have shot that bastard
I'm glad that I did it
Counselor
It's called
I'm cold
Hang on just hang on I'm friends will be here soon
They won't come
I have a feeling that our friends
Won't be joining us
Stop the bleeding
No doctor
Hurry I'll shoot you
Don't do it I don't want to die
I don't want to die
I don't want to
Are you afraid
Are you afraid of dying well now you know what they all felt like
The 12 people you killed that's how they died this is what they went through how do you know
Get scissors and disinfectant
Is that too much to ask
Arterial bleeding is pretty bad he's in a State of Shock from low blood pressure and I can keep my hand pressed against the wound
Stop the bleeding I'm going to have to suture the open flesh here needle and thread
We don't have that fine then a stapler will do what a stapler just go and get it yes sir
All right
What what do you think you're doing I've done what I can he needs to get to a hospital
What hospital no what are you thinking if
You don't put him down right now I'll tell you pull the trigger if you want but if you kill me know
Yes you're going to have to carry into the hospital yourself
Put me down right here just save yourself
I just realized I seen your face somewhere before you're the doctor wanted in connection with
Serial murders aren't you
Put me down dammit
What I did this morning was not an indiscriminate attack the men I killed
The president of gwe is lackeys and his bodyguards and they all had it coming
So you're telling me there were no innocent victims in that shooting
You're talking about that girl at the Newsstand
You already knew about it then
You knew you shot that girl didn't you
Why did you bother saving a man like me
It wasn't because you were afraid to get shot you weren't afraid to die I could tell by the look in your eyes
So why did you do it
Why save a terrorist like me why would you even bother
Because I believe in you I have faith in your Humanity
You should get going the police will be here soon
You hang in there
You tell
You are truly a great doctor
And the money what happened to the money Hey Duck don't tell me
Something come on without incident
Hey we ain't operating no charity outfit