Well Well you certainly have found an excellent piece of property
It's only a 20 minute drive to the center of Berlin perfectly situated in a convenient
Lovely neighborhood
It's rare to find a unique property of such caliber especially on the east side
I Can Only Imagine
If I'm not mistaken wasn't this the residence of Mr Liebert the former head of Commerce of East Germany
You Don't Know Her buyer you just came to investigate Mr Liebert is that all
Please forgive me but I just need some information
I don't know anything about an official who died almost 10 years ago
Apparently Mr Liebert and his wife adopted fraternal twins during the time that they were here I told you I don't know
Anything well who owns the property
Can you direct me to them
Listen a lot of the property in former East Germany used to be owned by Jews who had to flee during the Nazi regime
In some cases the government ended up borrowing land from people on the west side or in other countries
The owner of this property is overseas besides
My company is a Westside real estate firm that entered the Eastern Market after the wall hell
We don't know anything about the past now if you could please hurry and leave I'm locking up
Isn't there anyone who might remember
Could there possibly be someone who knew the lieberts
It's like I already told you this was a residential area where many high-ranking officials live
Most of them fled soon after the wall came down especially the officials from the ministry of the interior
Come to think of it
An ex-official from the East German Department of Commerce lives about 10 houses away
Yeah I remember Mr Liebert
I'll never understand why you decided to take such a risk if only he had waited just a little longer until East German
Collapsed
It makes you wonder why you went to a free country only to be killed in the end
It's a damn shame really
Do you remember if Mr Liebert had children twins perhaps did he have twins you say
Oh yes that's right
Mr Liebert adopted those twins from The Orphanage
Are you sure
That's right those two are such cute kids
Mr Liebert always did talk about wanting children
Which orphanage was it
Which one was it
Yes that's right I believe they came from 511 kinderheim
I'm sorry
511 kinderheim
They're planning on turning this old orphanage into a supermarket sometime soon
About time thank goodness they're finally going to destroy this creepy building
Excuse me ma'am by any chance do you know anyone from this place
The orphanage
Everyone from there is long since gone
I really prefer not to talk about it
It was such a tragedy
But if you want to find out more about it
There's a former official from the old Ministry of welfare named Hartman over on 47th Street
Hello there
Do you know if a man named Hartman lives around here
Wait what's wrong you're injured
Let me take a look
Don't be afraid I'm not going to hurt you
You reinjured an old wound
It's infected but this should help
Attabo
I know this stings but it'll help you get better
There you go all done
Be careful okay
You might get hurt again
Heart mon
After the fall of East Germany
I became the foster parent to all those kids you see photographed up on the wall
Foster parent yes well it just means that I took care of them until they were adopted or eventually able to go off
Up on their own
The boy in the middle was adopted by the president of an accessories company
And the last one on the left
Is enlisted in the army
I still have one left in my care right now it must be hard work for you to tell the truth I wouldn't call
Work
As the district official for the ministry of welfare I worked for many years dealing with orphans and I was Adam
Currently against the way the government handled them
After the fall of socialism I thought I'd try doing things my own way
I couldn't do any worse
Of course it isn't easy and I don't have many resources
But it's far better than the way they were living in that orphanage if you can call it that
The ministry of the interior and the ministry of welfare ran 511 kinderheim as a special
Well all these German orphanages were pretty severe places to be
But these special orphanages
We're particularly notorious
It wasn't just an institution for children with nowhere to go
It was the place where children of criminals and political prisoners are suspected dissidents were sent disc
Elimination and inhumane cruelty were part of everyday life for the children there
Those poor unfortunates were defenseless and couldn't do anything about their situation
Ironically it was a contradictory clash between socialism and total
The government claim they were reeducating them to be good citizens but in actuality behind closed doors
Wasn't away from the public eye those helpless children were treated like criminals even worse than criminals
The director and instructors were absolutely terrible
The worst of the bunch would confiscate care packages sent to the children and sell them for their own profit
Who then were the real criminals I ask you
Fear and violence rule the daily lives of those poor children and those special orphanages
You can't raise normal people that way
And then one day
That incident happened incident what exactly do you mean by that
Well when you came here you said that you wanted to ask me about the twins didn't you
Yes that's right can you tell me anything at all about them
I don't know much about the girl except that she was left at an orphanage in a different District but the boy
I'll always remember the brother Johan
Johan yes please tell me whatever there is to know
What happened they kept everyone
From finding out
The East German government placed a strict gag order on it well it is in the past
Also I suppose it's all right I guess there's no harm in talking to you about the incident so what are you talking
Talking about I need to know
What's your hun too
I didn't uprising
I'm home
Diet
We have company
Come here and say hello to him why don't you
Dieter
Where are your manners
Well are you going to greet the man or not oh it's okay we already met earlier out in front of the building
Remember
Please continue Mr Hartman
I'd like to hear more
No I'm sorry I can't not in front of the child
Understood
Well it's late can we continue this another time
Peter
Maybe you'd like to stay and have dinner with us
Sure if you don't mind
Mr Ten
You say that you're a freelance journalist does that mean you're going to write an article about the things we've been talking about
Eventually
When you do write your article
Please be sure to emphasize this
The moral development of a child all depends on the adult that raises him
It is essential that we encourage every child to follow the proper path
If we do
They'll be able to achieve their dreams and have a happy life
Dreams
Hey diet
What are your dreams
A soccer ball
I want a soccer ball
I see
Thank you for dinner I was hoping we could continue our conversation another time of course I am sorry
Maybe we couldn't finish it up tonight
I'll be back
Perhaps I can come by tomorrow
Well did
Hello I'm sorry may I still make a purchase
Mr Hartman
It's me Tim
Mr Hartman Mr Hartman what's wrong please open up
Mr Hartman
Mr Denmark
Teacher what happened to him he was playing
It was standing on a chair and you fell
My dear data
I would really hurts where does it hurt
It hurts everywhere
So hard man call an ambulance quick all right
Deter them take a look
My God
What are all these bruises
Does this hurt
What about here
Two of your ribs are fractured
And also
Your shoulder is dislocated how did you get this injury from falling off a chair
The ambulance is on the way and should be here soon so everything's going to be all right good
But where these bruises come from I said everything's all right
You can leave now Mr tinma but your hands just now it was like you're examining him
It's as if you are a doctor well 10 Ma I thought I heard that
Somewhere before you are a doctor aren't you the one wanted for murder
These bruises just how did he get these bruises all over
You shouldn't worry about the boy you've got your own problems don't you the police
Ambulance Mr Hartman what really happened to Peter how did he get
Well these injuries
What's it matter to you
I mean you're the one who's wanted for murder doctor
You're very short tempered just like a fugitive
You did this to him didn't you did what what do you mean you're the one who's been abusing
Why I'd never do such a thing to an innocent child
Right Dieter wait
What are you doing to the hospital first murder and now kidnapping
Don't move the police will catch you eventually
It's okay to
We'll be at the hospital soon I'm scared I'm scared of the hospital there's nothing to be afraid
The doctors will take good care of you but Mr Harmon is always the one who took care of me every
Time I got hurt before
What are you telling me
You're completely covered in scars and bruises and you've never been to a hospital
I'm scared
The world is full of bad things that's why I have to become stronger
If I'm going to fight all the bad things I have to become
Stronger is that what heart mom told you
The world is dark
The Futures bleak
And that isn't true
The world's not a dark place that's a lie
Really
Yes really
Oh I almost forgot
This soccer ball is for you
Tomorrow will be a good day
I promise
I'm sorry for coming so late thank you nurse
But the ER is pretty busy at the moment it might end up being a while before we can treat him
I can't move him up at all
There is a very big accident I'm sorry
So we need to ask the truck driver about the circumstances of the accident
You broke both his legs but he can still talk any
We have to treat him first
You can question him after we're done
All right then we'll wait right here until he's ready I see
I'll be back in 2 hours please just do what you can to take care of the boy
And whatever you do please be sure not to let anyone else take him away I will be coming back to get him
I owe you one is the accident site cleaned up yet no
Traffic still backed up okay what should I do now
First what to do with Dieter even if I call the police I can't go with him
I don't know much about the girl except that she was left at an orphan
Mention a different District
A different orphanage wait that's it
There's a child that you want me to take in
Well are you the child's parent
What are you doing coming here at this hour I'm sorry I know it's a strange request but this child needs you
Look I understand that the child is being abused
But if I don't know who you are then how can I
Well I I just I can't take in a child from a suspicious person who won't even identify himself
Wait
Did Anna Liebert live here with you with this orphanage by any chance
Hold on a second
Are you saying that you know Anna Liebert
That's right
So you do remember Anna
Yes of course I do
How is Anna is she doing well for herself
Yes
She's currently taking classes at Heidelberg University
Really then I guess she's doing very well
Thought it was such a nice girl
I heard she was adopted by Mr Liebert of the Commerce Ministry
Along with her twin brother
What was his name again Johan
That was it his name was Johan they were truly very close I felt so sorry for them when they had to be separated but they
They had to be placed in different orphanages
Before the two of them arrived here they only had each other they were truly alone in this world
They were found walking hand in hand near the border of Czechoslovakia
Just the two of them
Shivering all alone in the cold at first Mr Liebert was only going to adopt
Johann but Johan wouldn't go anywhere without his sister there was no separating them
Thankfully Anna was able to live a happy life because of her brother
I heard that the conditions and the orphanages in East Germany were pretty terrible not all orphanages were like
511 kinderheim
Anger deer the bathroom
The other way
Down the hall okay
It's all right it's all right there's nothing to be afraid of now you can go to the bathroom by yourself
Can't you
These poor children have never really felt the love of a parent in order to
To develop as a person the only thing you need is love
The orphanages of the East Side were truly horrible places for the children to grow up in everything was so
So impersonal even this place was only known by the number 47 you'd better believe we did everything
We could do within our power so that we wouldn't be controlled by the government we weren't going to be
Another 511 kinderheim it was a special orphanage controlled by the ministry of
Fair and the ministry of the Interior do you know what that means
No
The reality was it was a Ministry of the Interiors Pet Project East Germany was using
Thing that place for experimentation on the children
Experimentation
They were running a project that would turn the children into perfect soldiers
Mental reconstruction they made the children form factions to observe the aggression the fighting
I hate that resulted it was an experiment to claw every last bit of compassion out of those
Children and see what remained can you imagine what kind of
Adults those children grew up to be
And now the problem is there's no way to prove that anything like that ever went on
Any type of data or secret records all those documents were burned before the wall fell
Everyone who had anything at all to do with the project
Fled the country
However
I've heard rumors of someone who remain
He managed to clean his records
He stayed even though he was the last person in the world who deserved a second chance
He was the man who was in charge of overseeing the Abomination that was 511 kinderheim
And even though he was actually a pediatric psychiatrist closely affiliated with the ministry of the interior
Police
The man's real title was that of a district official with the ministry of welfare
A district official
History of welfare
Inga are you all done in the bathroom
Sweet dreams honey
All right
Play
Good night
They were careful to cover everything up
Especially after that
Incident incident
Tell me
I need to know what exactly happened at 511 kinderheim
I've said too much already
Such horrible
But I have to know you must tell me what happened there please
Where's my soccer ball
Where is it do you know where my soccer ball went to
Here you go
I have it right here
But you got to hold off on soccer until your wounds heal all right
Batman who brought you in earlier said he was going to pick you up soon
You just get some rest until then
I don't know what really happened there
No one
The East German government at the time placed a strict gag order on the event
It all began with the mysterious death of the director of 511 kinderheim
Soon after there was a power struggle among the instructors there as to who would succeed him
The place was thrown into Anarchy it was utter chaos
They couldn't even control the children it was every man for himself
It's a miracle Johan made it out of their alive then what what exactly happened at
511 kinderheim everybody there died what all of the instructors and
Every last orphan except Johan those people massacred each other
The world's not a dark place that's a lie tomorrow
I will be a good day I promise
Excuse me Mr Hartman but aren't we going to
Go home now no we're taking a little detour
Back there
Each other come on now be a good boy
What do you mean
I told you not to let Peter leave with anyone until I came back didn't I did was that person was the
Child's Foster father
And let me tell you he was very much a gentleman
Unlike you obviously
Look I'm sorry but that man I wouldn't worry
That boy seemed very happy to be going with him
Dana
They're not back yet
Hartman's Library
These photos were taking a different times
But they were all shot at the same location
So what am I looking at
Yohan
Who's the man in the photo next to
Yes that's it every single one of these photographs was taken at 511 kinderheim
And it looks like they were taking over 10 years ago
All of the instructors and every last orphan except Johan
Those people massacred each other
Dita could
Another
Just hold on Peter I'm coming
This child is blind to what I show him
Hot mom
He can't see it
He can't even comprehend what Johan saw
He's not like him
It's no good it is failed again
This boy is no Johan
Every single one of them died here did you know that
10 years ago
The instructors and the orphans all 50 people died
Johann is not here just watching it
All happen you just sat here and watched everything
You didn't lift a finger you just watch
I had to know his secret so I ask
Johan what he done and this was how he answered he
The piece of oil soap cloth Into the Fire like this
Do you get it do you know what he meant by that
I simply added a bit of fuel to the hatred born when people come together
It was easy
That's what he told me
Only 10 years old and he said that
And he did it with almost no effort at all
He was able to make 50 people kill each other
Without even moving a finger
It was you
It was you and your damned experiments that Twisted Johann into what he is
So you think it was us
I'm sorry
It wasn't us at all
We didn't make him that way
It's true that 511 kinderheim was an experimental project
Specifically created to transform orphans into perfect soldiers
Thinking back on it now it really was only a little experiment
As for Johan
He's no Soldier
Not at all
He was better
He was a natural born leader of men someone who was meant to stand at the very top of the world
There's no way we could have ever created such a work of art
He was beyond human from the beginning
A veritable monster
Johann made a prediction
He predicted that mankind would end up hating itself into Oblivion
And what do you think Johan's goal was
Do you want to know what he told me
He said he wanted to be the last person left in this world
He did
My poor teacher
The future is dark you must try harder to become
More like Johan it's a pity
Why are you such a failure
Why can't you be more like your house tell me why
Drop the gun or I'll shoot don't you lay a finger on him hard man get
This is our problem it's none of your business just leave
Come down from there sorry Dr Tim that's right
You were wanting to know more about Johan what were you planning to do
When you find Johann are you going to try and kill him that will
Possible don't look so mad
I'm going to let you in on a little secret but in exchange once you hear it you must leave immediately
You
Search out a general wolf he's the one who first discovered Johann and his abilities
I'm sure he's still alive somewhere so is he the man in the photograph the one in your study
General both the man standing next to Johan
He's the one who brought Johan to us he should be able to tell you something now
Get going
You can come with me or stay here
But you have to decide for yourself
There's nothing to worry about if heart mom does anything to try and stop
If you want to shoot him
Listen to me the choices her own nobody else can make
For you
Go ahead tell the doctor there's no way you leave me now would you you can't live without me
Because you're my child teacher
Now you see how it is Doctor tenba
You can leave
Where are you going it's all right it's okay
That's good nice and slow
Teacher come back here my dear little detail
You really think you can live without me no time
I love you so much Peter
The world is dark
The future is bleached the time
It's not true 10 minutes told me
Tomorrow will be a good day
Because he's wrong be brave
Don't be afraid
Feeders fly
Get on the bus here and take it to Conan Street
You got that
The orphanage is there by the bus stop
When you get there I want you to give this letter to Elna Tice
She runs the orphanage
I know she may look scary but she's a nice lady
Be a good boy okay
I can't stay in this town anymore
So I guess this is goodbye the bus will be along in a few minutes
Take care dear
Keep up the soccer practice
I'm sorry
You can't come with me
Here
Peter
I'm telling you don't come with me
I'm serious okay
You can't come with me dear