Did you get that dress
You're an unfamiliar face
Get yourself a permit if you're looking to do business here
Last thing I need is an unlicensed hooker
Can't make as much cash when you're legal
Yeah good luck with that
I just need permission from him don't I
You let me meet him
Sorry I got no idea who you mean
I'll keep coming back until I meet him
Until
I meet the baby
You can't catch the ball with your hands like that you're not the goalkeeper with your whining who died and made you rap
Where the hell did you go to go
Where'd you go
10 my dummy Tenma
He told me to stay with you for a while cuz he found the man he was looking for that's all
That's all
Who leaves a kid with someone like me
No way in hell thanks a lot of time I have to babysit
I hate kids first he drops off the face of the Earth and then he Saddles me with some random brat
Me and him had an agreement doesn't it mean nothing anymore what the hell kind of doctor doesn't want to make some easy money
Son of a
Did I look like I was ready to you hey
Remember what I said you can't use your hands that's a yellow card
I'm throwing this into traffic if you mentioned the rules one more time you keep talking like that you'll get a red card
Shut up
Why the hell are you so late
Hurry up and give me the stuff
Give me the stuff now
Long time no see detective Messner
That's right that's exactly what you called me back when we first met before I even got around to telling you what
My occupation was
But that was a long time ago my days in medicine are over
But I suppose you're no longer Detective
Detective suspended on narcotics charges
This article really came as a shock when I read it 6 months ago
Don't even think about running away
I have a gun trained on you under my jacket
All right what do you want with me
I need answers what happened in Heidelberg almost a year ago
And who was behind it all who ordered you to do such a terrible thing
I I don't know anything
You killed the foreigners and Mr Mauer from the post
It wasn't me that did it
I was hired as the lookout that's all
Detective Mueller also left the force soon after the murders
Yeah he did
I hear that he's very well off turns out he's doing good with his money
You on the other hand ended up wasting all of your money on your drug habit that sound about right
He was the one who took on the job and he was the one who committed the murders he ended up getting a larger portion of the reward
They even tried to get rid of me
They they tried to kill me to make sure I didn't go to the cops
I'm surprised you're still breathing
It was the organization that helped me
Organization
Enough I already told her too much as it is
Told her her who leave me alone already I can't I
I can't deal with you right now looks like you're going through withdrawal
And with me sitting here no dealer would come within 20 ft of you so I suggest you start talking
I thought I was
I was saved by
Baby
The baby
Go to a pub called candy you can find him there
Wait who's this baby you're talking about
He's all right wing extremist
He's also a high official and two of their major political parties
After the wall fell the baby tried to create a town of only pure-blooded Germans
But his plan failed and now he's come back
But why'd he do it
Why do you bother saving you
The darkness
After the Berlin Wall fell
A great Darkness was created
A monster
A monster was born
Now leave me alone I've already said everything to that girl you understand what girl Messner she came
Revenge had pointed a gun at me
She's the daughter of that older couple we murdered you're saying
I mean Nina Nina Fortner came to see you then
The baby said to me that I
But I was to send that girl to him if I ever saw or if she ever showed up around these parts
He said
That she's important to use as B
He's using
As base
You don't give up do you
You're getting to be a regular coming back all the time
How about I rent you for an hour or two so the night ain't a total waste
You're the one who said I'd get in trouble if I did business without the babies permission
Yeah not so clever now are you
Is this the girl who keeps asking to see the baby
Yes sir
It seems you're getting your wish
Don't keep him waiting
Please wait right here
Stand on that imot
If you'd be so kind
Directly over the iris please
Much better
Like we met I know I need
And if I had the chance
Resonate with you right down to the soles of
See I have to dance
The baby told me the day another Hitler
Born to us our country will be saved the girl will be the perfect
How is it that you know my name
The name of Anna leave with the former is just as false is the latter A Rose by Any Other Name does
Smell is sweet but they call me the baby so I'm biased come on let's cut the rug of it is
True that you know where my brother is right now good name
No don't you I'm going to do when you finally have your little family reunion
I'm going to take him down
You shouldn't ripped that out really really miss someone's liable to get hurt patients did
Why I'm sure Johan is searching for you even as we speak
I lived around here when I was your age no this place like the back of my
And there's a fella who buys Antiques and it's on this rug I stumbled across what do you mean don't you
Do you have any money left Mr Heckle shut your Yap already
I'm Hawking this rug so I can get the two of us something to eat I don't hear you coming up with
Son of a
There goes the neighborhood Turks
This whole area is full of Turks now
You are so called
It's a
What are you talking about
You can't pick this kind of quality
It's synthetic
Tell you what
I'll give you 100 marks for it out of sheer
More like s*** you Cannery the German guy who had this place would it give me 10 grand well you can take it
Don't you come crying to me when you realize my rug is the real deal
That one hanging on the wall is the real deal
It's a genuine headache rug
There's your hand woven silk
Look at the detail there in the patterns
It's perfect
$150,000
You sure got took for a ride
If you really can't tell the good stuff from that crap I feel sorry for you
We're out of here Peter
Hey
I'm getting kind of hungry
That runs real
It's a Hannah cake just like he said
Only
Grand I could get 800,000 for a rug is fancy as that
Come on let's get something to eat already shut up if I can get my hands on that rug we'll be able to eat
Anything we want
How you going to do that
What are you talking about I'm sure I'll think of something
Don't give me that look
You hungry ain't you whatever Thief
Hold on a second where do you think you're going
Sorry but I'm not looking to buy
That's not what I meant
Are you crazy and Asian like you is going to get killed if you walk into a place like that
They don't take kindly to foreigners in there but your Turkish aren't you is it all right for you to be doing business
Do you miss around here what are you stupid I wouldn't do business in a dump like this
A friend of mine was just abducted by a bunch of guys who are regulars there what
It seems like she found out a secret of theirs
A secret
I don't know what it's all about but I have to find her before something bad happens who knows what they're going to do to her
A woman I know is in there too I have to get her out
Does she have long blonde hair don't know I couldn't tell you what she looks like now
The young blonde girl away in a car
Hey how should I know
What color was it
It was big and red I don't know all right then I've got a track down that red car before it's too late
Wait you have to do something to help my friend too please help her she has a small baby if something
What happened to her please
You're
Alive this is my lucky day
This way please
Without your gun on this point I'm afraid I must insist
Thank you for your cooperation
Go ahead and sit wherever you like
So the baby brought you in
Eyes forward let me see your face
Goodness
But I should have known you'd be quite a beauty
After all you are a Johan's twin sister
My name is Professor guidlitz
And the man standing next to Johan in the picture is General
We created this organization along with a pair of other like-minded individuals
Where are my manners
Would you care for some fruit
No thank you
I want to see Johan
And see him you will
Once he knows that you're here no force on Earth could keep him away
The boys suffers mightily in your absence
You people don't know where Johan is either do you
We need him
His country needs him
We for shall help him fulfill his destiny
Do you have any idea how Hitler became possessed of such power
It's because he saw the three things a person would have to do to gain control of a country
Manipulate the banks feed the War Machine and take command of the military
I'm sure johans working on one of those things right now
What exactly do you plan to do with Johan think of it
Hitler been a weekend Nation to his will using nothing but raw Charisma all that from a man
Who only made Corporal a man whom Art School wouldn't Dane to let in his
My appeared after he hit his 30s
Not so with your brother Johan he was a leader of men even as a mere boy
Charisma of Messianic proportions but even Jesus Christ
That help consider the three Magi and John the Baptist who heralded the savior's arrival into the world
Are they ready the way for his glory
Likewise the four of us have been keeping track of your hands talents ever since he was a little boy
Exciting wouldn't you say
What is it that you want with me
Please accept our Hospitality until Johan comes looking for you at the very least
Actually I'm afraid I must insist you know too much for us to let you walk away now
Don't worry about that I came here of my own volition I will wait here for you hun
Then we agree
Now then
You should at least try the fruit
Good you're finally awake
Don't look so worried we're not going to hurt you
That's right away at least
So what brings you to my little slice of the world
Doctor ten
Wait how do you already know what my name is
Why don't you leave the questions to me
Now all you have to do is answer
Why exactly were you snooping around
I know you're looking for Johan but I can't figure out why where are you keeping Nina
I told you leave the questions to me did I not
What are you going to do with her
Why do you insist on texting me
Nina is our guest whereas you are just a metal some piece of trash to be disposed of
Is she okay
At the moment
But that'll change soon enough
She's determined to kill your heart and we simply can't have that
Always ashamed when a pretty girl dies before her time
You're just using Nina as bait to draw out Johann
What are you planning on doing
The hell are you pictures
The whole quarter indeed
The night sky tomorrow will be a thing of beauty of fiery cleansing
If I stay here
Then I'll find you
Please
Who are you
Where are you right now
It sounds like you're speaking with an accent
Where are you from
Let me escape
Tomorrow night we celebrate in honor of johann's homecoming
Only the members of the pure Master race like us deserve to survive everything
And she'll just burn away
Hey kid where the hell are you going
Come on give me a break
Leaving that rug in this town is a complete waste that guy doesn't know what it's worth
How many times do I got to tell you stop looking at me like that
Slime ball
Yes see if I care don't come crying to me when you're starving and I'm living like a king
And if you tell anybody about this you're going to pay for you got that
Who would want to be friends with a dirty Thief like him anyway I don't need him
I'm so hungry right now they're there don't cry be
Good boy mom is coming back soon I promise what's wrong doesn't he have a mom
Go home too
Hey I'm sorry if what I said hurt your feelings kid it's all right
I've got 10 more
Eat as much as you want it's nothing special but don't feel like you got to hold back
So you're just sitting on the steps waiting for that tender guy to come back and get you huh
That little guy is waiting too
Where's his mom why did she leave where'd she go
A bunch of bad guys came and took her away
We got to save her
It's just so dangerous out there
An Asian man I met said he was going to try and help her but then he got hit by a car right in front of me
An Asian man
Wait
You said 10 Mile was Japanese didn't you
But there's no way it could be the same person could it
Where are they I've got to help them
The man who hired me
On the phone
I heard him say that I'm going to burn the entire town tomorrow
Please you must help me
My baby
I don't want my baby to die
That's easy
Who is it
Professor guidlitz has asked me to bring you some fruit
Thank you very much
The professor also asked me to deliver a message
General vote will be here shortly and would like to meet with you
You mean the man in the photograph with my brother
That's right
General wolf is the person who knows Johann better than anyone
Probably even more than you do even though you're his twin sister
That's what Professor Gilead said
No don't go dying on me just yet
General Volks going to be here in a minute
And I want him to see what a wonderful job I've done of capturing you alive
Well if you say
That's General to you do you understand excuse me sir
We've assembled our members in the arson teams ready to set fire to the Turkish quarter
Shall we continue with the plan is scheduled
Yes proceed with the itinerary
I'm looking forward to dinner with a view of a beautiful creams in the sky
Be sure everything stays on schedule otherwise my perfect dinner will be ruin
And tell them that if anything goes wrong forgiveness will come at a very high price
Yes sir
He won't do it
Johan isn't going to lead you
He'll never be able to convince Johann to lead your organization are you out of your mind
Johan doesn't share your simple-minded views on racial Purity he's not just an ignorant bigot like all of you
He's different don't you see he looks down on all Humanity
Silence
Well well what do we have here
Hey get this gentleman a drink on me I'm thinking the usual
Right away
Well
Not bad for a little guy that kid's going to be serious trouble when he grows up
That was disgusting
How can they drink that stuff
This is 10 ms Jack
Where are you
Everything will be all right just calm down
I want to help you get out of here but
I can't really do anything right now
I'm going to sneak out of here and I warn everybody in your neighborhood
What's the name of the street
And what's your name
I don't want you to worry about anything okay
Promise you your baby is going to be just fine
I'm going to save you too
Hang in there
I forgot to ask you a name
Nina
And when this is over I hope we get to know each other better
I've had so many bad things happen to me since I came to Germany
I forgot to ask you what's your baby's name
Hey I say
Are you there
What's happening
Leave her alone
Tell me is the man sitting in that chair Dr Tema very own hand
So where is General wolf
General wolf is waiting
Will be taking the doctor to him
No wait what do you mean but I wanted to show General wolf my prize catch and then finish him off myself
So what do you want me to do with this kid
I found them walking around downstairs looking for Tenma it's a friend of yours
No of course not
Metro has nothing to do with this just let him go
You don't really expect me to take a filthy Street agent like this to General wolf do you
Dispose of him you heard me finish him off go ahead got the little bread
Already he bothers me yes sir
Stop no
One of my men
My apologies doctor please forgive us for the rude treatment you've received
It's very important to General wolf that you be treated as his guest
Poor I say
Please
Help me escape
I have to warn the other so my baby will die too
We are
Isn't that the
Yes we are I say
We are friends
What happened here
Everybody's dead
We should be arriving at General Volks Mansion momentarily
Tell me is Nina going to be there yes you can rest assured she is all so considered to be a special guest
List of General wolf what about the Turkish lady the baby's mom I don't know we don't know anything at all
We simply follow orders and nothing else
Burn Tonight We got to go back we have to let them know where the lady who gave me dinner last night and the baby are going to die
We're all going to die be that as it may young man I can't let you go we must take
The general Volks mansion
Think you can make it to the Turkish quarter on your own
I'll be there soon but right now it's important that I go with these men
But
You can do it I know you can if you go right now you'll be able to save everyone on Calvin Street go on
From here you should be able to get to the city in 30 minutes
I apologize but I had to do that I had no choice
Now I know you trusted me enough to give me back my gun and I may have just broken that trust but it didn't seem like you were going to stop
It's fine I'm sure General wolf will be pleased to know that you don't just carry a gun around
For show and that you're not afraid to use it when needed
If you would please follow me where's Nina I want to see her she is here isn't she
Pat
Before we do anything else we must see General wolf and Professor gilitz I just need to know for myself that she's safe
Professor against his
And it's not just katelets all of these men have
Also been killed we've disposed of the bodies
Everything's been taken care of
What about Nina when we first arrived with General volt we search the entire Mansion she was
Nowhere to be found
Your doctor tenmark corre
Wait do I know you
You wouldn't recognize me even if you saw my face
I don't recognize me but people call me for both
That means that you you don't look anything like the picture from 10 years ago
That's because
Fear has aged
Sir please hurry can't you go any faster you crazy
Pushing 200 here must be broken there's no way I'm going to make
Take it in time
I think people's names are very interesting mysterious
All the places I've been throughout my life
Everybody has referred to me
On the other hand
Every time I encounter someone new
I must tell them that my name is
I wonder
How can they really know that is
What's there to prove that I really am
You're the one who found Johan and his sister isn't that right
I did
It's happened 12 years ago
And that's when he was sent to 511 kinderheim they were going to tournament to a super soldier weren't they
But you had bigger plans for him
That's correct
He was supposed to become
Hot country safer before it's downfall and now you're trying to make sure he becomes the next Adolf Hitler so that he
Can lead the ultranationalist isn't that your plan
At the moment I'm only part of this organization because it benefits me
I did hear that the others are trying to make him into another
I think it's a stupid
Imagine if a man like Hitler was able to take things as far as he did
Johan could do more
Yes
I was the one who gave him the name Johann
We found the twins wondering near the check border
They had managed to evade the heavy security patrol somehow
They were dead on their feet
Malnourished to almost frozen to death
When we finally arrived the two of them simply coll
They both would have perished if we hadn't found them when we did
I too know what it's like to have saved Johannes life
When he became Consciousness I asked him a simple question
How do you feel I
And do you know what his reply was
He said
You will know very soon
I know there's no more proof I really
All the people who knew me have disappeared my wife
Children siblings relatives friends
Everybody from my life
Is dead all of them died one by one I have your heart
For
The money I brought with me back for me is Germany is the only proof I have
Good morning name is
Because of your heart I am a stranger to all you will
Very soon
No I understand what he
Loneliness
Take a look at this doctor
Come to the abandoned warehouse of hilden and Engels company in rombark
Johann was here this morning
He came here to slaughter he let's send his men yet
Other person who knew me has been murdered
I imagine Nina must have seen this and gone there
For
Please kill him my back of you
Calm down kid what are you talking about
Calvin street is going to burn tonight we have to hurry and tell everyone I can't believe this
This is amazing it must be my lucky day
This is great now I can grab that rug during the fire
What it's score how can you think that way
Keep it down you little brat if you tell anyone about this I swear out hey let me go
Kid I'm not just talking about all those Turks okay if any of the right Wingers find out what we know we're dead
What you didn't notice all the guys with the freaking she wants the good tattoos around here
One
What question was the Turkish woman being held hostage in there
We found a dead woman on the third floor based on what we saw I don't think Johan killed her look like it was the work
Professor gelitzman well General wolf do you
Really think you'll be able to kill Johan I don't know however he still has time
Maybe able to
What is this supposed to mean
She has a baby back there in the new Nazis are planning to burn the town
The Turkish woman was found dead up on the third floor
We are approaching the meeting place where Johan will be expecting you I'm not sure what will happen there
You do know how to use that gun right Calvin Street Frankfort now
My plans have changed why the sudden change of heart what about killing Johan I'll deal with him later now
Do as I say General wolf will be disappointed to hear this news he personally requested that you kill Johan
Believed you with a man for the job I don't care I don't take requests from anyone I'm going to
I killed Johann of my own accord now hurry up and get to Calvin Street
All ignition points are ready to go sir
Awaiting your orders to proceed
Well done
Time to celebrate our superiority with a little Firepower
Now what are we going to do with them these two are an insult to our race
This place is going to burn anyway leave them for the flames
Oh come on little one don't cry
Your mom is coming back real soon
I can't believe you're still alive
How'd you find me
It's all thanks to Dieter he told me that you lived in this building
Where is Teeter
Didn't he come by
Where do you go
Hey have you seen Aisha
He needs her he misses his mom a lot
It can't
It's not possible I don't believe it
What about this poor little child he's too young to be without a mother what am I going to do what do I do
She's the last
There mustn't be any more victims
I need to see the leaders of the Turkish quarter now
So what does everyone think
Set the town on fire huh
Not likely
We are rumors about the right wing extremists all the time
We can't overreact every time they threaten us
What's even more suspicious to me is this Japanese guy Waltzing in here though he says his life is
What's the matter with all of you I say it's dead don't you get it she was killed because she tried to warn all of us about this Danger
I wonder about that he was a prostitute like you right
You women go off with Germans all the time and end up missing
That's nothing new
You may call us Turks look bad
How do we really know whose kid that is anyway
You all know how hard it is to make a living you should know better than to act like this
If you want to live
You've got to listen to me
Forget it do what you want you can burn and go to hell for all I care
No we just one second
Are you suggesting Patrol groups
Maybe we should do is this Japanese man says we have nothing to lose Mr Denny's
Are you really going to listen to some Asian we don't know
He might be suspicious but there are certainly plenty of trustworthy Japanese people
In the world
General Logie for example
General Noki
You mean you don't know about him
General know he was a brave Japanese man who saved the Turkish navy when they were lost in the Pacific years
Years ago
Go ahead and gather all our man immediately
It looks so delicious let's dig in
Sally no need to be in such a hurry ladies
Take your
We wouldn't want to finish eating before the entertainment
I planned it so by the time the main course comes around the show will be reaching its climax
In the meantime let's enjoy the 76 Chateau Le Tour I saved especially for this night
The first dish we will indulge in is my
Raw Flounder with caviar
And does the feast begin
Voila the first fire
What a wonderful start
But like I told you that's still just an appetizer
Where is the main course
Remember what I said don't be impatient
If you Savor your dinner my show will be something you'll truly enjoy
Oh yeah because I don't know we need more fire extinguishers
Save the women and children what a lovely surprise and
What do we owe this honor
Don't even try it
Or kiss your boss goodbye dangerous thing away
Why don't we enjoy this meal together
Unfortunately it seems your appetizer is fizzling out
Don't worry that was just the beginning
This is your favorite right
Sorry about that
Don't be so contrary my dear
You see after all
This is a great celebration
In honor of your
Listen to me Johan doesn't want any of this
And tell me how can you be so
I saw it with my own eyes I followed his messages I know what he wants
Johan doesn't care about your plans
What exactly did you see
He doesn't want any of this don't you understand okay
Relax calm down just take it easy because of you
I won't let anybody else die tonight
So where's the main course what part of town are you going to sit on fire
Take
I hope you had any luck finding Dieter someone
Told me they saw a kid who looked like him near the park around noon
No just
Continue with my dinner is planned that girl sure is something I suppose it must run in the
The look she had in her eyes she was really going to
It's a good thing she didn't realize how close I was to giving her the actual location of the
Main course well shall we bring out the next dish
No make me some underwear first
A scary girl isn't she
Are you going to be just fine everything's okay all right thanks for getting
How did the two of you end up here anyway
You want to know what happened lady this bread almost got me killed
Forget this
I'm getting the hell out of here
If that was the smallest fire those skinheads said I wouldn't be a bit surprised
I grew up in this neighborhood I know the place like the back of my hand
If I wanted to burn down the town this wouldn't be the spot believe you me
This town ain't out of the woods just yet
There were three other fires up wind that were all so put out
We can't thank you enough for your help
Right everyone
Our next step is to take care of the injured
No I won't have any more victims not one more
Wait what are you talking about
Well the wind's going to change direction
It always happens every night around this time the wind just stops and it starts blowing towards town from where the
The wind
And now time for the main
To be served
You see them running away
Allow me to buy this round
That should take care of it thanks for patching me up doctor
Let me buy you a drink
What are you talking about you have to take it easy for a while
Oh come on loosen up Dr right
That's right it's thanks to you we were able to put out those fires and save the neighborhood I bet those Neon
No doubt they are that'll teach him never underestimate that text what are they tendon
All the other injured people
Hey doctor Tenma take a break and relax come on why don't you have a drink with us
Not until everyone's taken care of
If all of the fires up until now we're just diversions
Where do you think they're going to light the real fire how the hell would I know who cares about this stupid town anyway
Besides there's something much more important on my mind that I got to take care of wait I need you to tell me
And I need you to tell me now where would you start the real fire get your hands off of me
Like I already told you the wind's going to come from the river
The abandoned Factory down there would be a perfect place for a fire
If I'm not mistaken there should still be a bunch of chemicals in the warehouse
Long
Something I can sink my teeth into yeah this is going to be
We're right on schedule the celebration of the
The race is about to begin
It's you why did you follow me because I have to put out the fire I made a promise to
Is it it's the warehouse
Thank goodness looks like they haven't found this place yet these are all filled with chemicals
If all of this were to go up it'd be hopeless it'd be nothing left of the town
Check this place no matter what I'm not going to let those horrible people burn it down
What the heck is this
Smells like Castle
It looks like what's there
It's all right I'm fine
Hey you can walk on my own let's get you to a shelter so I can have a closer look at it
Hey twisted my ankle it probably happened when I was trying to get away from the fire
Now that I finally got this rug who gives a damn about this stinking town
I bet I can probably get $800,000 marks for this baby no a million
What happened to Dieter couldn't say he's probably where is he where did he go what happened to him
Last I saw he was going to the abandoned warehouse by the river
Why there
The wind's going to blow in from the river soon
So if the chemicals in that warehouse are set on fire it's all over for this town
This is what I was talking about
Tell everyone to evacuate from the Riverside shelters right away you're going to take me there
Who is
Who's back there
Please don't move
Can it be true
Are you really Johan's sister
Once I sent this trail of gasoline on fire
This Warehouse is going to go up in an instant
I'm going to shoot you in the head before that happens I can fire quicker than you can flick that lighter and I'm not afraid to do it
And what if you miss I haven't skipped a day of training in 6 months straight
So I know
I can hit you from here
You don't frighten me
Don't you know this is a celebration of the master race
This is our big welcome for Johan
But Johan doesn't want any of the things you want
Yes it's true that he was recently seen here in Frankfurt
The only reason he came was to kill one of your leaders and all of his subordinates
He left a message behind you know
What message
Listen to me Johan is not the person you think he is
The truth
Is much more complex than that what are you trying to say
It's worse
It must be terrifying for him
He's suffering he's an anguish and teetering on the edge of despair
You know I'm not so sure it's such a good idea to be making enemies of these guys which way to the warehouse
I didn't sign on for all of this I'm going to call it a day see you
The hell do you think you're going are you just going to let date or die like that tell me where the warehouse
Let me go you choking me you told me about your friend you said that his name is
Right would you believe that I know a man whose name is Tenma also for real
Is your timer Really Brave too
Yes but he must never fire a gun not if I can do it for him
I don't want him to kill anyone he's a good man killing people is always wrong you understand
Even if they're the bad guys
Right don't ever do what I'm about to do
Close your eyes don't look don't shoot
Quick I can put up the fire
1 million marks
Nina
Damn it all the cops are coming
Get out go I'll take care of things here there's a boat over by the river
Please tell me you have to leave now
My main course
It got
Thank you
Your cooperation young lady we'd appreciate it if you'd come down to the station
Wait one second okay I'll be right back
Mina you have to promise me something n
I
I'm heading there now the night I shot my brother
Now I understand
He's not alone there are two of them inside
That's why
It wasn't your fault you didn't do anything wrong
I must
I have no other choice
I have to shoot you hun again
Hey wait up
What the hell are we doing here anyway
Come on let's get out of here
There's no use for this guy
I guess I'll be starving and broke forever
If only I still had that
Damn it
The hell's that supposed to be
Message
The monster inside me
About to explode
Let's see if I got this straight
So you told us when you arrived at the warehouse you witnessed the Asian man in the arsonist engaging in
Verbal argument
According to your statement on it as soon as the Asian man saw you there he quickly fled
So Ms Liebert is that exactly how you saw it
Answer
Well it's good that Firebug ended up turning himself in
You confess that he's a right-wing extremist said he was celebrating his people when he let the fire
Anyway Ms Liebert your records clean so that's all we need from you today
We do appreciate your cooperation
So then you're saying that I can go home now detect
Yes ma'am
Oh
Hold on
There's one thing I forgot to ask about the townsfolk refer to the Asian man you mentioned is Dr Tenma
Ms Lieber
You wouldn't happen to know anything else about this guy would you
No I don't know anything about him
Tell me what are you thinking
I'd say from the way Ms Liebert was dressed she might just be a high-class call girl
That isn't what I meant
I'm talking about Dr Tim
When we first spoke to the church from that District all of them referred to our Asian guys Dr Tenma
But as soon as we told them the doctor was under investigation and suspected to be a serial killer
They got real tight lift all of the sudden none of them knew who he was
They told me I'm responsible for you now
Mr Russo
Yeah it's so great to see you I was worried about you when
Now that's more like it
There now you look more like the honor I've always known I like you better in casual clothes
Come on sit down and eat I ordered what you like enjoy
So aren't you going to eat
No thanks dear I've already eaten I'll just have me some coffee
Go on dig in thank you
I am pretty hungry
What's so funny
Well that's what tastes best I say coffee isn't any good at all if it isn't sweet
It's good to see you can smile
I know you're in the middle of a big job interview and up to now you've looked quite serious
But your smiled when you saw me put all that sugar in my coffee
Your names on
My name is Anna Liebert
So
Well Ms leebert the job's yours
Don't start today
Having a young lady like you waiting tables in my Cafe might give my business quite a boost
Except what
Do me a favor
Show off that smile a little more all right
When you smile it'll make everyone feel good
Thank you so much for the job
I work very hard really
Chances are you may not have to this is an Italian restaurant in a small town
Tables of folks is as busy as it gets
Donna come stand over here
I'll place all the orders here on the bar and you'll take them from here to the customer's tables
All used plates go on that side of the counter
The wine is right here
And the glassware is back here
You'll find more bottles of wine Above This Shelf
And you can hang the food orders on these little hooks
Some more wine is above the shelf and glassware is back there
This is for water
Morning Russo
So how are you today good morning and welcome
I'm starving
Nice to meet you sir my name is Anna
It's not possible I must still be dreaming no way someone is pretty as you could be a waitress in a place like this
Well you're awake and my place is classier than your thought introducing Anna our new waitress she'll
Serving here from now on like I said I'm pleased to meet you
You really mean it
Hey Anna how about a nice plate of carbonara hey Anna I think I'll have a Bolognese
Dear could you please get me some more water when you have a chance
Order up one Bolognese and one carbonara all right here you go sir
You're a gem Anna
The orders up
Okay hey Russo come on you got to tell us how you trick this cutie into working here
I didn't have to trick her guess I was just my charming so
Hey Anna if you're free tonight how about you let me take you out to a real restaurant it'll be fun
Hold on just forget about trying to make time with my Anna I'd hate to have to hurt you oh boy listen to the
Cry Baby Ross so everybody suddenly acting all tough hey where do you get a load of this last week he was at my house watch
Watching a TV Movie Falling like a baby
Another order of squidding risotto
Summertime is playing across the street
That old movie house is screening summertime see you there
What a city Frankfurt has
So many great old movie theaters that movie was on TV just last week
That one really brings me to tears
Have you ever seen summertime it's touching
The whole thing takes place in Italy actually in the city of Venice
Folks don't know the history of Venice it was a port city back in medieval days and everyone called it the city of
The entire city of Venice was originally built on a lagoon there are these canals that run through
The whole thing
I'd really like to go see it with you someday it's just beautiful
It sounds to me like you've been there before I have
The film soundtrack is great music it's very well composed I bet you've heard it's theme song I'd say
Most folks have heard it it was a popular very well-known song
Tell me how does it go
Let's see
Hey I know let's go across the street and see it right now we've missed some but they'll still let us in
Some other time it is kind of late and you're still eating
Sorry
Well I'm back
Great
So how was your break
Oh can I scrub that for you no thanks I can handle it
I appreciate you letting me take off a few hours from work every afternoon it's always
Flow around this time of the day
And I don't want to be nosy but
Where do you go everyday
Hey forget I asked it's your private time it's none of my
Business where you go
Oh learning to shoot
At Mr venkles firing range
You're learning at wrinkles Place huh
He's good people
Tell me Mr Russo have you ever shot a gun before
Me shooting guns no way honestly I get all nervous just looking at them
Here you go sir enjoy thank you very much
How do I do this time take a taste
No you should try it
Tell me what's it taste like
Like there's some garlic olive oil parsley and not much else
You're a gun right that just means you're having learned how to make it proper
This cooking stuff
Anything worth learning takes practice
I'm all done with the bathroom Mr Rosso I'm heading for bed now so
When I was younger I never realized that movies like this existed
Mr Rosso
Movies have always affected you deeply
That's true
When I was younger I always wanted to watch movies but with work I never had the time to
Back then I ate a lot of fabulous meals but to be really honest I never felt any of them had any tast
Flavor
I didn't even appreciate the taste of sugar then
Really is that the truth
You know my past
Isn't that right Anna
Well after you left I checked up on you and I know what happened
You really need a Fortner
And you disappeared 2 years ago after your parents were murdered
Exactly what were you looking for me to do what are you looking
Looking for me to do a hit or did you want me to teach you to kill
I guess I wanted to learn from you that was it
So how did you find out about me and what I did
From one of my professors at law school he had done research on you and all the cases you were involved in
The Ristorante Nino case
Osaka Milano case
A sub 18 murder case
You were called into court to testify in all three of those murder cases
And in each of those cases
All charges were dropped due to a complete lack of evidence
However my professor came up with a theory about it that made sense there was only one conclusion
A world class Hitman committed all three of the murders and
You were that man
I suppose you want to know how many people I killed
To be honest with you I can't even remember
I was never a good kid
And before I knew what was what I was in way over my head
Robbery blackmail
If you can name it then I did it
And eventually I became a hitman
I rewarded Myself by eating very well
I never had any feelings about it it was just my job
Just wondering I
Doing what I always did waiting to kill some faceless guy
It was sunny and he was
I've been doing it so long I was numb I didn't know how many I killed or who was next
I had him as good as Dad
He had ordered a coffee and as I watched he started putting sugar in it
One spoonful two spoonfuls
Four after
5th Spoonful they stopped black moment started me finally tasting the
I drink when I saw how he was
Doing that coffee I couldn't do it
That was the day I put my gun down for good
That part of my life is done
I know I can't kill people and steal their Simple Pleasures
After all the time we spent together I don't get it you never asked me to teach you how to kill someone
I decided
I decided that getting you involved wouldn't be right
Do you really have to go Nina
Goodby
Thank you for everything Mr Rosso
You should know killing is easier than you think
You just have to forget how sweet the sugar is