Old Karina why are your letters
Ever ever so short
As with you police The Scholar of the stars and his
Astrology that you drive my heart mad and such the gold of
Ideas it's colors faded while the work of the artists already
Well what are you waiting for put the book on the shelf and go if I
Something to offend me you're offending me right now
I'm not sure what I did to upset you sir but I'm sorry nonetheless if you can't wrap your tongue
Your brain around Latin you're of no use to me is a reader understood I'm sorry sir
I'll be more careful I told you to get out
He really tore into you back at the Mansion didn't he
Don't move Carl
Business major should have thicker skin than that
I'm sorry but
Do I know you
I'm loved to Frank a cultural anthropology major I'm guessing you work for him too are you another one of his
Part-time student readers whatever needs doing
He only lets boys do the reading
As I'm sure you already know
Anyway he's got a different reader each day of the week
Your Tuesdays of course
Hey so what do you think of our boss anyway the ever mysterious Hans gay York shuval
I was looking for work and the money was good honestly that's all I
I needed to know
Are you saying you've never heard the rumors about him
He works the stock market like a marionette one phone call from him leaves Banks across Germany quaking in their boots
Of Bavaria he has no family no close friends
It's just him and his money his fortune keeps growing and growing every year
On Earth is he spend it on anyway
Who knows
I didn't even get to the weird part yet
Other nickname is the vampire of Bavaria
How come
Just as the clock strikes 2:00 a.m. shoe volts manservant loads him into a car like
I've seen it myself
It's like something out of a horror movie
Maybe he's getting some air
I'll find out soon enough what else you've all up to
What do you mean you're going to find out
It's for my research paper silly
Mental activities of medieval and present-day Financial figures of Bavaria
I lucked out
So you look me up cuz he yelled at me is that it
Just your name and your major I'm not a snoop
Anyway I wouldn't lose any sleep over him chewing you out
He yells at all the guys who read to him
Yeah
Well I guess it's a good thing I'm used to getting yelled at
What do you mean
It's just I spent a lot of time in foster homes some of them weren't so nice
So that's why there's no record of you in any of the local high schools
You looked up more than my major in name
It's got to be rough
Growing up without your real parents like that
The truth is
I came to Munich for school because I thought maybe I could find my mother
She's here in Munich
That's great
Have you seen her yet
No
It wasn't meant to be
You just throw in the towel
Hey you don't happen to know your mom's name well go ahead
It wasn't meant to be okay
If you don't we both know I'm going to look her up anyway
Mar
Her name is Margo Langer
Silly you have her full name and you were ready to give up like that find her
What are you waiting for
It's too late for reunions
Here we go Margo Langer what do we got
Oh no
Like a chestnut Mare
At full stride
Passion Electric
Barking great way
Only beautiful things are deserving of my love
We are reading pains me
Why didn't you explain Carl
If only I had known
Now I understand why you gave up looking
I'm so sorry for your Los
I already said that it doesn't matter didn't I
Well listen
Carl if there's anything I can do just ask me that's sweet of you but
I'm fine
Hey Lott
You said you wanted to figure out where shoe Vault goes at night
You're going to follow him right
Would you mind if I came along for the ride
No not at all
Sure does beat sneaking through the darkness by myself
I'm telling you it's true our supernatural phenomena research group is finally hit Pay Dirt
There is no way
In any case
Listen up Bishop gropius one of the founders of our school wrote this poem in the year 1502 that much
Already know for sure
Now consider the following verse
On the second to the last big year
The boy of Thursday will arrive upon the land
And the book shall go up in flames
The entire world will be shrouded in sorrow crazy huh
So it's spooky what's your point again
Don't you get it guys
Look it says right here the second to the last big year
What year is it 1996 right
So that means this is the year
How do you figure
Listen The Big Year means leap year
And the only leap years left in this Century are this year and the year
He will arrive upon the land and the book should go up in flames
The part about the books in this land means that this University will go up in Flames okay then who is this
Thursday huh
Thursday
Well let's see
Don't understand comes from the word donor
Yeah and donor means Thunder
The god of thunder
You lost your damn mind hey this is going to be the front page story of our next newsletter it's no laughing matter
I'll run the article if it'll make you happy but come on nobody's going to buy this
Vampire of Bavaria he is
And this is what we find out
There he goes
Okay be careful I want to see
What do you think he was up to
Hey maybe this isn't such a good idea
You're probably right this is no place for a girl you should go home
Only beautiful things are deserving of my love
I need to know
I need to know how miserable of a man he really is
Yeah it's open
If you're looking for some fun you came knocking on the
Wrong door I got out of the business a long time ago kid
Who are you
Nice manners kid you want my name shouldn't we start with yours
Margo Langer Pleasures all mine
I bet your students from the University aren't you
And both of us have part-time jobs working for hanshuvalt congratulations what do you want
Tell me why
Why does he come here to see you in the middle of the night like he does
It's simple kid I make him feel better
But not in the way you're thinking just cuz he's up at this hour doesn't mean he's up at this hour if you catch my
He brings me money scads of it
And why shouldn't he
When I finally went to shoe volt and told him who I was he broke down crying and apologized on the spot
I had his son and he threw me out on the street like I was a piece of trash
Wait so
Carl is she saying that you're hunchew about son
How would you know you liar
How dare you
How dare you pretend to be Margo Langer
The real one was all over the papers a year ago former prostitute
Former prostitute Margo Langer murdered police say killer still at Large
The woman you call yourself is already dead
How could any human being stoop so low
You're using my dead mother's name to guilt shoes all that of his money and he's falling for it
Shoe ball knows the score
Well he knows I'm not the real thing but he still gives me money hand over fist
All the money in the world can't buy him forgiveness from the real Margo Langer that ship is sailed guess
I understand is the next best thing money money
That's all the bastards been living for
And the only way he knows how to say sorry
Don't look so terry-eyed kid you know Saint yourself
You and I both know shoe balls on his way out
Take a good look at him
If you're going to play the long lost Sun card better do it while we can change his will what are you giving me
Agree for being an imposter
But you didn't exactly Walt's in here with a positive paternity test
Just watch out for the competition boy you're not the only one who says he shoveled son
Yeah you came to see me a little while back told me the same sob story you did
No way it can't be
Excuse me if I don't take your word for it
For the record I think you're both full of it so this other guy who is he another student
A bunch of you take turns reading books to shuvall the different boy every day of the week ain't that right
You've got that in common Kyle he's the Thursday boy
You're his real son
What's the point
I was passed along from foster home to foster home from most of my life
Usually sending me from bad to worse
But I finally ended up with a couple who loved me as though I were there very own
They're everything I ever could have wanted
But they're being so wonderful made me want to meet my biological father even more
I thought that if I could see what a sad little man he was with my own eyes
I could finally return my foster parents love
That's all
I was trying to do
Hey look
Tell me something
Have you ever seen this Thursday boy that's one day of the week I always have off from work
But this one Thursday I wanted to grab something I'd forgotten
And he was there reading right tell me what he looked like
Let me think
I want to say he had blonde hair and a very beautiful face
Who is he
Someone in this University
Is pretending to be me
Carl are you listening to me this is important take this money
Get off at the 8th station
What about you Mom honey I already told you I can't go with you but
Home are you in trouble I don't want to go alone mom you have no choice if
Now go on what about my dad can't my dad make it better somehow his
Name is hanske York isn't it who told you that old Mrs Bella from across the street
My dad's Rich isn't he she said he abandoned us how come you would do something like that
He didn't abandon us Carl
I'll just go where he is and you can find us there no you can't so when can I see him
Oh Carl when you're all grown up you can meet your father if you want
Hate him if he turns you away please bye
Because Mommy doesn't hate him even now
Keep this with you always it was a gift from your father on the day you were born
Carl I know who he is
Earth to Carl I know who the Thursday boy is
His name is Edmund foreign he's a philosophy major
I'm sure he's the guy we're looking for he reads books to shove all the Mansion every Thursday
Edmond Farrah get ready
You should be coming out of that lecture hall any second hey
Hey you wouldn't happen to know Edmund foreign would you
Hey guys is Edmund here
Who had been foreign
I think he was a no-show today
There you go
Okay so he dodged the bullet today
But seriously
It's only a matter of time before we give that fraud what's coming to him
No imposter's going to cheat you out of shoe balls inheritance
It's not about the money
I couldn't care less if I see any part of his fortune no if they want to Rob
Duvet blind they can go right ahead
Who cares
Then why
Because
Because I can't stand the thought of this bastard far and pretending to be my mother's son there's no forgiving something like that
With the pedals of your silk flower swaying in the breeze The Cry of the Mockingbird rang through my heart
You haven't told me to stop reading yet
Why is that sir I berate you all the time why do you insist on
Coming back
Here's the money that good that isn't why
With all due respect sir it's nothing like that
Is money the only incentive to do something in your world
In my world or any other
What are they like
Your parents
Actually I was raised by a series of foster families
Forgive me for praying
Would you meet your Rio parents if you could
Well sir
Actually I'm yes this young man who reads to me just may be the one I've waited
It doesn't seem to be after my money
Who is
Never mind
I'm talking to myself
It's time we called it a day Norman
Oh one more thing regarding your Latin boy
It is much improved
Well thank you very much sir
Looks like Edmond Barnes playing hooky today too
Pictures laid up in bed with a bad cold or something like that
Tomorrow's Thursday he'll be there
He'll be at the mansion in so will I bust him as
Baker he is right in front of you right
That's awesome
Let's go get them already
I don't know sign of
It was supposed to be here an hour ago
If you were sick and stuck in bed at least then we would know where to find him
Hey
I want to barge into his room and confront him there
Hold on
Don't tell me you looked up Florence address
204 jackpot
Here we go
It's been so Grim around here
The whole school's talking about what happened to Edmund foreign
The school paper actually printed a suicide note didn't they
I can no longer continue to deceive
So that's what it was about
I guess so
Spending all that time with you all to acting like his son maybe the guilt just blindsided
If you known he was going to grow a conscience he'd have been better off not trying in the first place
Yesterday must have been tough
Hey
Don't you know it
Since we're the ones who discovered the body the police held us for questioning all day
Well I didn't end up reading today after all
Mr shoevall is taking the news very hard
Hey I'm being rude
This is Carl he's the Friday reader a pleasure to meet you the same here
I'm call Norman from the economics Department I'm Johan Liebert I study in the School of Law
And you haven't touched a drink since is that correct
Absolutely not even a drop
Well that's very good but you have to continue to stay away from booze to give yourself the chance to start over there's
No way I'm going to drink as long as I report to you once a week I don't want to incur your Wrath
Hey I just the thought of it makes me afraid what are you talking about I always conduct myself in a very calm Prof
Professional manner I was kidding I don't have time to drink anyway
I got my first big case since becoming a private investigator
Well that's very good news
Dr rifine
How would you judge this fellow
What do you mean
But using your knowledge of physiotomy I thought maybe you could tell me what kind of young man appears in this Photograph I
Practice physiotomy
Richard I'm afraid you're mistaking me for some kind of quack fortune teller a weirdo psychic
But you have a well acknowledged reputation
You're able to predict someone's behavioral traits from just a single glance right
That's the result of many years of accumulating information from observing patients
Then can you use all of those years of acquired wisdom to tell me if this guy looks like a con man
Con man
That's not possible
A man with a face like his couldn't fool anyone
Even if you tried some kind of con he'd be easily found out
Ah
What are the odds that he commit suicide
Absolutely none at all
People with faces like his would never kill themselves
Well I must say doctor your observation seem to be pretty convincing
Then give me quite a lot to think about
And they're based on experience
So who hired you if you don't mind my asking Hans gay York shoe Von
You're working for shoebox I take it you know who he is am I right yes I'm quite familiar
Here with him he's the wealthy vampire of Bavaria wow that immensely Rich gentleman is my client
The young man in the photograph is Edmund fahren
And in person at her who actually passed himself off as shoe volts son for a while you event
Actually gave himself away not really Mr Cheval bought every detail of his deception it
Isn't your typical run of the mill scam artist you know
I myself had a lot of trouble figuring out it was a complete fraud even though some pieces of the my
About I'm still remain how did foreign know so much about shoe volts missing son where do you get the information
Supplied it the only way is to go straight to the source and demand that foreign tell you
Yep normally I would but the boy committed suicide
They say
Come on now Martin think of it as a
Favor for an old friend at least let me take a look at the suicide note huh the handwriting's been analyzed
How to doubt the kid wrote it himself okay look you're an outsider now Richard I can't justify bending the rules
The two kids who found the body Carl Neumann and Loda Frank
Didn't they work at the same part time job as I've been Farin
They were just friends that's all well maybe they weren't such good friends
So how you doing anyway
Is it the same old grind yeah you know how it is we never have enough Personnel in fact I've had no time to
The rest since I took over your position so thanks a bunch Richard
Slowpoke Martin has become one of the big shots now you don't get to call me that anymore
When you have my boss anymore so I don't have to put up with your Wise Cracks oh come on Martin you just don't get it do you
You have no idea how much trouble you put us through
Believe me it was no picnic cleaning up your mess
Now if you'll excuse me I haven't got time to waste on simple suicides I'm a very busy investigator with
Important criminal cases
Yeah I want to check out the crime scene
I presume everything's been preserved right
I already gave the go ahead to have it cleared out since it's been determined that there was no crime
They'll be removing all of the deceased effects sometime today
Damn it when did Slowpoke Martin become so efficient
They're supposed to be arriving anytime now to take everything away don't worry I won't be more than a couple of
Most of hung is real from this pipe in the ceiling
It appears that he wrote a suicide note of this desk
Here's a paper he was in the middle of writing the birth of tragedy process
Reality World Views on psychology far for the course for our philosoph
These must be the materials he was using for his paper
Caesar's gallic Wars now what was he doing with this book seems
Place Spanish or it could be Latin I can't read a word of it
This is the only passage underlined in the book
Up here it is room 204
YouTube
Better go down and get a bunch of boxes
Okay
Start with the books
It's going to take a while
Hey don't work too hard guys hey what should we do with this desk
Let's just leave it there all right
Yeah
I'd like to ask you a few questions about your former neighbor
I have nothing more to say just leave me alone hold on I'm not with the local police I'm a private investigator I
Sure who you are Mister you're bothering me and I have a paper due tomorrow but I haven't been able to get it finished because of all the questioning and
Motion going on next door all right I'll be quick
Just one question then would you happen to know if these two were close friends of Edmund foreign
Couldn't say I'm too busy to hang out watching everybody around here but as far as I know that guy didn't seem to have
Any friends I ever saw really I've said enough go away hold on a second just one more little thing
Ah come on now what could you translate this passage for me the part that's underlined in red ink
This is just ridiculous it's going to be your fault if I flunked my class
Believe I'm doing this for you
And I appreciate it
It says I can no longer continue
To deceive
What was the last thing you said I don't know now if you don't mind I'm busy okay
So I can know
Longer continue to deceive
Where have I heard that before
You like coming here too
Hey
We met a few days ago Johan right why don't you come all the way up
You can get a much better view if you're standing up here at the very top
Right
Hey thanks for the hand
Oh man kind of scary up here huh
It's not scary at all
Johan come down from there
Come on stop it
I'm serious you're going to fall
Do you come up here a lot
Yeah
Around this time the lights start coming on and the neighborhood looks beautiful
Family members are returning home
And the delicious smells of dinner begin filling the air
It's something I've wanted for a long time
Really yeah
I guess because I never really had anything like that when I was growing up
So tell me what's your family like
Got it
Not something you want to talk about
Wish I could say the same
Being bounced from one foster home to another made it important
If you don't mind I'd like to hear your story
Tell me everything you remember
This is just sloppy police work
I can no longer continue to deceive and those words are supposed to be proof he was writing a suicide note
That wasn't a suicide note foreign was just working on translating a Latin phrase from this book
So anyway that's my story
I wish you weren't so depressing but it's all true
It's very strange but I feel like I can talk to you about almost anything in the world
Tell me one with thing
That rich father of yours
Are you talking about uvald
Those tears in your eyes are you crying for me
Listen
You got to do something Carl
I'm there every day tending to housekeeping chores and I see changes in him that really have me worried
Ever since Edmund committed suicide Mr shoebold hasn't been eating very much
If he continues to starve himself he's going to end up dying too
Carl why don't you try telling him that you're a real son
What have you got to lose
I want him to get to know me first and then maybe shoovald will grow to like me
If I tell him the truth now he won't believe it because he just doesn't trust me yet
He could completely reject me and think that the only reason I'm coming forward is because I'm after his money
Seems like money means everything to him
That's all he knows
So how can he understand how I feel
Well we can't just do nothing your father is in a deep depression and we have to come up with a way to get him
I see you're worried about him
But don't know what to do
I have an idea that I think might work
I can no longer continue to deceive
Edmund wrote these words but they weren't meant to be a suicide note
In his dorm room I found this Latin book
Caesar's gallic Wars and he was working on translating this underlined portion from it which means his death
Might not have been a suicide
I don't have conclusive proof it's just my gut feeling based on many years of police detective work
Have you been listening to a word I said
Anything at all
No
Not really
It doesn't matter now
Don't say that it does matter you have to believe me if I'm right that Edmund didn't commit suicide
There's a possibility that your life's in danger
That dear lad
He was my son and I can't bring him back nothing matters
I've already told you the facts everything about him including his birth was completely unrelated to you he was
That was a fake a con
I'll Grant you he wasn't a very good con and apparently he didn't make it a habit of fool people but
It's precisely what he did to you Mr scheuval he just saved you
I must ask you to leave now Mr schewold is tired and needs to rest
I'm not going to let this investigation end yet
And my decision has nothing to do with this being my first high profile Pi job
I can feel it there is a far greater evil lurking somewhere behind this case
Sometimes in life
Even if we want to
There are things we can't do over and we can't ever make right
They're gone can't you understand that
Yes I understand
Only too well
This isn't over yet
Good day to you sir
A children's rights treaty
Yes
I guess you could think of it as an international rights agreement to secure and protect the civil liberties of children in countries
All around the world
That's what I'm currently working on in my Law class anyway
But my volunteer job with the orphanage is completely unrelated to that project I do this because I know I can help
A difference in their lives
Hey guys
Can we get back to what we were discussing earlier
You said you've all went bankrupt three times in the past
Yes
After each one of them
He would just disappear
And when he'd reappear he'd start from scratch
And work to regain his fortune
Mr scheuval told me during one of our Friday reading sessions how this experience re-energized him
Gave him new strain
Well did you ask him where he went when he disappeared each time
Yes
I think I get it your plan is to take him there am I right
Everybody has a place to go where they can feel good
For you Carl it's the rooftop of the University building where you go to watch all the city lights
Mr Coons
I think there's something wrong with the bathroom sink it could be clogged
Do you mind taking a look please
There might be water dripping out of those pipes
Lota there's nothing wrong with the sink it's working
Open up come on open this door now
Stop playing around child
Open up this door now where are you going with Mr schumold open
Hey guys that's that mission accomplished all right let's go aren't you going to tell me where we're going
It's a surprise
Look lady I'm well aware that you're not the real Margo Langer
I just want information on Edmond Florida the boy who died recently
He came to see you not long ago didn't he
Foreign remind me which one he was
Which one
Apparently I'm very popular
I had two pairs of visitors each said he was shoe volt kid
Was he the blonde one
Or was he the one with the black hair
The black hair
Yeah the black haired one came with a girl isn't that funny I still can't believe it actually show up with a girl
Well in a place like black hair you say
Did the girl have glasses
I got photographs of them somewhere at least two
Yeah that's who I saw
You're positive about this
He said that he was hansgalaxivald's son
Are you sure this is the right spot yeah I'm absolutely certain it should be right around here
Had to tell me the name of the surprise
We brought you out to visit Ellenburg Webster
We were hoping this place would cheer you up I'm sorry
Just let me out of the car
Can you see the lake from here
Leaves here always gets so beautiful in the fall
Yeah very much so
Wait something
Is missing what happened to the wrens why don't I hear the chirping of the Reds
Yeah I know I'm so sorry this place has changed
They've turned it into a construction site you can't hear them Carl
If you listen very carefully you can make them out
Little birds delightfully chirping in the trees
Minneapolis have ripened and fall into the ground
And when you turn in this direction
He will see a spectacular sight
Autumn Leaves a blazing color in the afternoon sun reflected on the
On the surface of the water like in a huge mirror
You must see it
Don't you sir
It's hard to believe such wonders exist
I see it I can see
Back up a second I just remembered something
You told me that you had two pairs of visitors and you mentioned that the black haired boy brought a girl with him
So then that means the blonde brought someone
Oh yeah that's right he did have somebody with him
That kid kept mumbling his words I could barely understand what he was talking about
The gorgeous boy you came along with him and ended up doing the talking he was the one giving me the lowdown and
Play truth be told
If it's good looking pal would have turned around and claimed he was shoe vald Sun I wouldn't have had any trouble believing him
Who's the other guy tell me
You're looking very well
Thanks
And how's your job
Everything going smoothly
I'm happy you're doing well
Is Rosemary all right
How she adjusting
She's doing fine
She's made a lot of new friends
That's terrific
Sounds like she's fitting in
Yeah that's really good news
She's becoming used to her new school I'm sorry it's getting to be quite late
But right now before I forget
I brought you some pictures their new ones of Rosemary
I prefer to see her in person
How about 2 days from now
We can meet here again
Fact is I'm completely sober
My life's back to normal again well
Actually this may be the first time my life's been truly normal
It's finally clear to me how much I've screwed up
I'm going to let her decide whether she wants to see you or not
Yeah
I'm really hoping she will
Richard I have to go now or I'll be late
Yes sir
Just more coffee
Dr rifine
What's your impression of this man
Tell me something Richard
Precisely why do you think you're here
Well
You're here for counseling I asked a questions remember
And as I've told you before I'm a doctor not a fortune teller
Right you're inside comes from your years of experience with patience
So who's the boy in the photo this time
A person of interest in my case
He made the initial discovery of Edmond Farms body at the alleged suicide scene supposedly he's a friend of the
Deceased that's all I know well here's what I know Richard yeah
You're a dedicated workaholic
But you've got to learn to take time for yourself to relax I'm beginning to do just that
Will wonders never cease
And doctor I have news
About what
Rosemary
I might be able to see her very soon
Well you must be looking forward to that
Yeah but just remember
If you do get to see her
You can't get back the time you've lost you need to be emotionally prepared for changes in her
No matter what
And listen you must not touch a drop of alcohol am I clear
Don't worry I won't I suppose you're off to work on your case again yep
Don't leave yet
I think it's time to talk about the event that God you kicked off the police force tell me Richard what do you remember from that day
Well
I remember all of it
He was 16 years old
And a suspected murderer
I've been drinking on the job when I spotted him
My shot I'm dead
He died because I was drunk
You faced up to it
But that doesn't erase it it will always be there
And nothing can remove that memory from your head
So do you know what's important now
Giving myself permission to move on
That's correct
You may step to the Head of the Class
Do I get an A+ Professor not so fast I don't give out perfect scores easily I demand results and
Besides I'm not all that crazy about perfect patience they're boring frankly
Carl neum
A business admin student in the economics department at Munich University
Apparently he told that prostitute posing as Margo Langer that he too is shoe Vault real son
At this point I don't know whether he was telling the truth or not
However
I need to investigate that possibility
Yes
Excuse me I finished all the cleaning so I'll be going now
Yeah
Thanks for all your hard work
Cleaning for you is never hard work
It's pretty rare for a man living by himself to be so neat it makes my job here extremely Pleasant
Well lately I've been trying to clean up my act on all fronts
I couldn't help but notice
You've got a new picture of your daughter
Yes
I may be able to see her soon
Really that's just wonderful your daughter will be so delighted
Do you really think so of course what young girl wouldn't be happy to see her father
Yeah
It was a tough one
So were you able to turn your paper in on time
Carl nor
I can't figure you out
If you know for sure then why haven't you told shuvall that you're his son
Are you just another con man or are you the real deal
If you're legit
What is stopping you
Don't you realize that any parent would be overjoyed just to see their own child
I'm so sorry
She said
She doesn't want to see you
That's fine
She's made up her mind I didn't want to force her it's her decision hey that's okay
Don't worry about it
It's fine
I've got to go
Yeah
Yes
What can I get for you sir whiskey will do
Here you go
Then I'll just go where he is and you can find us there no you can't oh Carl
When you're all grown up you can meet your father if you want
Don't hate him if he turns you away
Promise me that no matter what because Mommy doesn't hate him
Keep this with you always it was a gift from your father on the day you were born
With none to admire them
The daffodils of Loris proudly bloom
With none to mind them
The Trees of Peoria Russell
The bloody tracks of the nameless man
That was wonderful
I must say Norman you come a long way and become an excellent reader
Thanks very much sir
I'm impressed by how much your Latin has improved in the short time you've been reading for me to be perfectly honest
I'm being tutored by someone
Well he certainly is an excellent teacher
Would he be anybody I know
Johan
Johan Liebert is my tutor
A proficient young man
Yes
And not only in Latin
He has an extensive knowledge of Law and economics and amazing aptitude in fact for whatever
Studies
He's a boy who's beautifully gifted at everything he's True Perfection
Mr Shoe V
What would you think if a boy like him
What if Yohan Liebert was actually your real son
Then he smiled
It was the first time I'd ever seen him smile
He made it clear
That you're worthy enough
To be his son Johan
To be honest I was jealous
No matter which way I looked at it you came off better than me
I'm ashamed to admit it but I do envy you
Why don't you just tell him
Come on Carl what have you got to lose go ahead and tell you his real son will you stop it
How many times must I tell you I have no intention of doing that
What would be the point if I did he would never believe me
And worse than that
Then he'll think of me as just another greedy Predator only interested in getting hold of his fortune
He'll despise me forever
How my mother lived her life until her death
And with everything I've gone through up till now
He knows nothing about me
And I won't stand for him thinking I'm after his fortune when he doesn't know a thing
That's exactly why you should go talk to him
You have to gain his Trust
Make him understand the truth about his son
He'll never believe that I miss son
Well don't you have something from your past that would prove it to him
Anything he might recognize or remember
You know something you both could recall
No
There's nothing
Far as I know
Think back
There must be something
I'm drawing a big blank it doesn't matter I don't want to tell him okay
If that's the case can you explain why you spend all that time having me tutor you in Latin
Wasn't it because you wanted to please him
Because you wanted to make him proud of you
I'm thinking that maybe
I should quit my job being his reader
Yeah
It's for the best
Thanks for all your concern I appreciate it
But I guess I'm done
Johan w
I feel you're entitled to know
The truth
I do have something that can prove who I am
Well what is it
It's dumb I don't know why I'm still holding on to it
I'm not going to convince him and I don't need to
My foster parents are coming to visit me next week
I've been fooling myself
I'm not the son he'd want to have
So I see
When your mind's made up it's important not to waver so for the time being Carl I think it would be a good idea
Idea to let me keep an eye on your proof
We're so happy to hear your studies are going well
Isn't that right mother
But I've been worried about you Carl I want to make sure you're eating right I'm always eating out
What's so I know I have to be careful not to gain any weight
Better stay away from your mother's cooking too but it's so delicious
Are you making a lot of new friends here
I've got some people I hang out with and can talk to you about anything terrific
It's always good to have friends yes that's very true and it looks to us like you're doing quite well
I'm extremely grateful to both of you
That I can even be here
Whoa what's this all of a sudden there's no need for thanks
For years I was shuttled from one foster home to another where no one cared about me
But you two have treated me with such kindness that's because you're a wonderful young man we both think so
That's right girl
Thank you for everything you've given me Mr and Mrs Lindner
Isn't it about time you stop calling us Mr and Mrs
We came here hoping that you would finally accept our offer
We know this is been hard for you
But now
With college treating you so well mother and I were wondering if you'd made up your mind
Have you decided to become our adopted son Carl
We believe in you and we want you to succeed
We trust you
Trust us don't you oh absolutely
We understand why you might still be a little hesit
There's a chance your real parents are still alive
No matter how much effort we make
We can never be your birth parents but maybe there's no maybe about it
Because the both of you
Or is real to me as my birth parents could ever be
Oh my
Let's have a toast
Feel like some expensive champagne son yeah
Waiter bring us to Champagne list we're celebrating today's a special day
Hello
Carl speaking
Hello Carl it's me
Do you know who this is
Mr shoe
That's correct
Now watch this I hear about you
Quitting your
Right sir
That's very disappointing
I'm sorry for any inconvenience this might cause
I just hate to see you abandon your lat
You put so much hard
Thank you for your concern sir
It really is a
I'm going to miss you you know
As a favor to me
If you don't mind
Would you read to me
One last time
Sure
It'll be my pleasure
How about the third chapter of
From EOS to lemnos
A splendid choice
That mysterious
Beckons for the death of even the god Phoebus
What other pleasure could there be
Than to wish death
Upon the Sons and Daughters of Cerberus
Now
Move forward softly whisper Zeus
Move forward move on
And dance in the temple that belongs to the dark gods
The gods of Juno who dwell in the sea
The Earth
And the heavens
From the summit of the Parthenon steal the forbidden apple of Campania
And bring forth the apple and everything
Everything to save my soul
Bring
Everything
Mr schufaul
But but your phone call
Magnificent
So heartfelt and meaningful the best I've heard in my whole life
Why did you keep this from me is
Is that mine
This rabbit's foot holds so many memories
I gave it to Margo a long time ago
A good luck
I wanted to pass that luck to you
This is yours Carl
My son
I've put you through so much
Oh Father I found
My son
This is all thanks to one person
He told me about everything his help was invaluable so from
Now on you'll be working for me as my secretary
He is a young man who can be trusted
That's good enough
When you say that just what exactly do you mean Mr shoevald
I've decided that I've learned enough I am calling off the investigation
But sir we had a breakthrough and I'm close to another I checked out Carl Norman and one thing certain that boys
Real son I'm quite grateful to you for all you've done now hold on there's still more to be done
You're still the Edmund foreign it should have figure out Edmund pretended to be your son but some evidence I am covered seems to indicate that
He didn't really commit suicide if that's really the case someone else is pulling the strings and may have killed foreign it
Father I made some tea would you care for some yes I would
Oh good afternoon Detective
Would you care to join us no thank you I'll be going
Once again good work just send me your bill
Good day it sure looks nice outside it does oh and Johan's
As well
What a surprise so Johan's decided to visit
Shoe volt it always been known as a distrustful man with a sour disposition who
Soul when he found his son
Well that smile of his who would have guessed that people still call him the vampire of Bavaria
What a surprise so your heart's decided to visit
How cute
So you're trying to track down this puppy huh
What a job
My client told me her ex-husband basically dognapped a little fella
I guess disputes over pets can be just as bad as one's over kids
You're right about that
I think I left some wine if that's quite all right with you
Are you go ahead I'll be sticking with a sparkling water
I'm glad to hear you say that I know it works scarce at the moment but it's a good choice on your part not to Cloud your life with
Alcohol and I'm doing okay at least I'm not account
What do you mean
Are you saying there's something else in your life that's bothering you
Well I find that with all the free time I have now I end up rehashing things a lot
Such as
I spend hours and hours pouring over this personal notebook I have of unsolved crimes cases I never saw this
Detective
How interesting
So tell me when you look at it how do you feel
I feel frustrated
There were so many murder cases I wasn't able to solve
It haunts me to think of those vicious Killers still out there walking around in our world
They're free because of my incompetence
Even now I can't seem to catch them
You're being too hard on yourself
You could have caught them you had the skills to solve those cases but yourself critical nature was impeding you Richard
You got frustrated that you couldn't read these murderer's minds and that caused you pain
So I turned to alcohol
Sure of course you did gentlemen
Dinner is served
Oh good it's time to eat
Actually I think it would be in your best interest for you to keep trying
I would encourage you to keep looking at your old police notebook
But why
I'll just become angry again
Stop thinking that way
You have to analyze what you did in the past in a new light
Your mind is clearer now that should help
Let's be frank with each other we both know that you shot a young serial killer when you were drunk
And I must say you are facing the reality of what happened that night admirably
But now Richard you face a far greater challenge
Facing your thoughts when you pull that trigger
You're still haunted by that boy
You see him in your mind everyday don't you
When you brought everything to light
All those things festering under the surface
That boys ghost will finally move on
I see when I've brought everything to light huh
The home of murder case is a good place to start
The victim you I came home or had a long and steady career as an accountant
It was never involved in anything shady and had no enemies and when he was murdered
There were no signs of a robbery
Then there were those two voice of God cases the victims were a former housekeeper and a chauffeur
What connected those two killings was that the words I have heard the voice of God were left
Scrolled on a wall at both crime scenes
The door knock company president case
Little girl cuz one of the wealthiest businessmen in Bavaria and his body was discovered in the heart told for
And then there's the spirit a couple case
Both were forcibly drowned at their bodies washed up along the Eastern river later on
This one's still being investigated is one of a string of murders involving middle-aged couples and material witness in
Case disappeared Japanese Doctor Who's still on the Run
Oh man and more unsolved
Places I had the more booze I drank
Then it felt good but it's different now this is tough it
I was just like the doctor said so I'm sober my mind is clear and I'm feeling calm
Hold on a second come on think
Playing card Richard
So
You tried doing it again and what was the result
I did I looked at all my notes
And I thought of something new but then I
You saw that boy's ghost again and once that happened you lost your train of thought right
There's no need to worry
When you have an important thought like that sooner or later it will come back to you
What was it that I realized
An idea flash through my mind it felt like it was a key to solving one of those cases
Just My Imagination
Who's there
Show Yourself whoever you are I'll catch you
This is like that time way back
I was running after that punk just like this I chased him down an alley
Sorry for coming here so late at night doc
Nonsense if you think you've figured things out and you're ready to share them go ahead then tell me everything
Back then I felt myself looking deep within that killer
That's when I knew it existed in this world
Later was true evil and once I saw it standing right there in front of me
I shot and killed him that's good thank you for sharing Richard
By telling me this you're well in the road to recovery there's still more doctor it just came to me
That idea that it flashed through my mind before all those unsolved cases I
I've been working to solve separately I realized
They are actually one single case huh
Greetings my dear Dr Gillen
I'm writing to thank you for sending me a copy of your recently published book
Transcendental criminal psychology
I found your book informative and a very interesting read and it pleases me to see that a student of mine from Duss
Dolph University
Has now become a leading Authority in the field of criminal psychology
Now I have a question for you regarding another matter
You told me in a phone conversation that you conducted the lengthy interview with the serial murderer Peter Jurgens
After you spoke with him you told me that Jergens claim that a friend of is it encouraged him to murder the victims
Sadly my memory isn't what it used to be so could you please tell me again
What was the name of jurgen's friend who he said told him to kill
I'd appreciate that information as it may Aiden associate of mine
PS
As I mentioned earlier you were quite a student in college and excelled in my class and you had a fell
Colleague who was equally bright you often competed with him for the best marks
He graduated and became a neurosurgeon
At any rate it seems that he's become a suspect in a Multiple homicide case
With your expertise I'm hoping you could help me get a better picture of who he is
Please tell me everything you might know about him
What kind of person is he and where do you think he might be right now this Dr Tenma
I remember you you're a detective
It will I used to be
And now I'm a private investigator
I'm sorry to show up unannounced here at your door man
And I hate to bring up a subject I know must be painful
For you but
I'd appreciate it if I could ask you some questions again
Of course you can it's been 4 years since I last spoke to the police and it seems like they're done with their investigation
Mr
Yes I believe your mother was actually employed by
Wasn't she once the head housekeeper at his mansion
20 years ago
Well at that time she became very ill
And after her sickness she only worked close to home in the neighborhood
Was that it or could it be she had some problem with Mr Chev
No not at all
They were actually quite good friends she told me that she used to read poetry to Mr schewald when he was still able to see
My mother just loved reading poems to him
Come along
I want to show you something
Look how generous he was to her
I've kept all of them because they remind me of my dear Mother
Every one of those books are collections of poetry that were given to my mother as a thank you from Mr schupold
How are things change they had detective and the door knock company president cases now just a private
You worked as Mr gox Chief business liaison and personal secretary
I asked you once again did anyone hold a grudge against him
You mean did anyone hate him
Turned enough hours in the day to count all the people who despise him
In business Mr God was such a fierce adversary that he personally forced some of our competition to go bankrupt
But there was another powerful and well-known businessman in Bavaria wasn't there
How did Mr gauch feel about him
I take it you mean Mr Shoe volt
Well they were lifelong rivals in business but of course you knew that right
They knew each other very well
When Mystic golf was still alive she was company went bankrupt two times
That second bankruptcy happened when Mr gauch undercut two volts prices for the purpose of ruining him
So what you're saying is the Mr gauch was consciously trying to crush him
Mr schewald made certain we suffered serious losses too
So then they both hated each other
Of course
A few times they happen to be at the same party and it looks could kill they both would have been dead
Oh it was very tense they had explosive fights
Like to Vipers
But those snakes understood each other's every move
Only those two tycoons could talk to each other on the same level
I never felt like they were enemies
This may sound weird but they were really more like friends
Hey careful up there
Oh yeah I knew Hans real well
Poor Hans was one of those two people that ended up being victims in that awful voice of God murder case that Hans was
A good guy he deserves better
Just what is it that makes you say Hans was such a good guy
He was nice always treated me to a drink or two
Generous huh
I heard that Hans used to work for Mr shoe ball as his driver
He told me that but he worked at Shoe volts driver almost 30 years ago
Did Hans say why he stopped driving for Mr shoevald well that was around the time old company went bankrupt
That's why he was fired huh so Hans never said that he and his boss didn't get along listen to me what I'm about to say
Get along with anybody and everybody it was Hans he
There's a prince even Rich bastards like that vampire of Bavaria shoe Vault he treated us
Folks like kings and Hans always said he was the one who taught you about bird watching a time about bird
He took him to the forest
It's hard to believe that was 2 years ago
But whenever I think of my dear husband
I just can't understand why such a kind and wonderful man ended up being murdered
It's unfair
He died so horribly
You have my sympathies
Pardon my asking
But I believe your husband grew up as an or
Yes he lived in an orphanage till he was six then with different Foster families until he was 18
After that he became an accountant
Is it true Mr scheuvo the business tycoon asked your husband to be his corporate accountant
He did many times
But my husband always turned him down
My husband was quite busy with work at the time but that wasn't why
He said Mr scheuvald had a different set of financial principles
When it came to money my husband was very honest
Again thank you so much I appreciate the help
My husband's killer
Will he ever be caught
I'll try my best
If I can do it
I swear I'll catch him
Well then
Yo one more thing
Yes
I forgot to ask you if you knew how your husband and Mr schuevault first met each other
Oh that
It seems they met in the forest
The forest
Yes they met in the forest back when Mr shoe ball could still see it was a total coincidence
Place like that
They were both their bird watching after they meant they went to the forest together all the time
Bird watching
More like a happy kid
Red poetry to Mr shoe vald
More like friends
Hey buddy you okay yeah I'm fine thanks
That guy was driving like an idiot
From what I saw look more like he was trying to run you over
Dr rakvine
I've re-examined all the evidence and what I found out supports what I told you before
Some of the key murder cases that I wasn't able to solve
I'll point to one killer having just one motive
There's the voice of God murder case
And the door knock company president murder case
The accountant murder case
Look at the three of them
They're all extremely different
The methods in which they were committed for example
And the victims were related to each other
None of them even knew each other
However
I have discovered that all of them shared one common Bond
There was a man who connected all the victims
And because they knew him they were all murdered
Every one of them was killed to further isolate Mr shoe
There's also another Connection in these cases that's rather curious in the door knock company president case
His secretary said there was a certain young man who was supposed to meet with Mr gauch right before he was murdered
And in the voice of God cases under I have heard the voice of God this name was scrawled there by the murderer
And then there's the spirit a couple murder case since both of them drowned that case seem to be unrelated to the others
But the name of the killer given by the Japanese Doctor Who was the only witness in that case was the same
It was the same name in every case
Yohan
I've been in touch with the former student of mine who's now a renowned criminal psychologist he interviewed a murderer who claim
And he committed his crimes on his friends orders in here he wrote that friend's name and the name that's in
In this letter is Johan joh
Is a common name but based on what you found it's also possible that all these cases could be related
If by chance you're findings are true this Johan has been systematically murdering people for the past 4 years
News I can't help but wonder why this man known as Johann is trying to force you've all into complete isolation
Oddly enough Margo Langer the woman who bore you both suck conveniently died as well
And there was that young student who was pretending to be shoe Ball's son he conveniently killed him
Self as soon as he made his claim if Yohan really does exist I wonder where he is
Right now perhaps he's close
What a surprise so johans decided to visit
Weather so beautiful
Yes isn't it sir
Right next to shoe volt
Rainbow Ranger
Hey that's not fair you're supposed to fall when I kick you
My evil empire is going to take over the world you're puny little kick isn't enough to stop me
The bad guys always losing the TV show don't you know anything hahaha well well how's
How's the global domination coming along
The big secret to breaking the rules is to make it look as though you're following them
So what sort of plans do you have for the Earth
Who knows why should I care I'm just going to destroy everything anyway
A lot more fun than being a stupid hero yeah forget being a rainbow
Well guys shall we start making our way back
Okay come on so did you have fun today
Time to go home
Finally starting to warm up a bit
That's good
I guess
Has Rosemary you know
Too busy romping around with her friends to get sick
That's good she used to get those fevers like clockwork
Hey remember that one time years ago rushing her to the doctor and the dead of night
Household pictures you always keep them on you
Of course I do I bet she's a lot bigger now they grow up so fast these photos of mine must be
The ancient history
But still
No matter how grown up she gets I'll always know it's her the moment I'll rise mate She'll always be
Oh almost forgot whenever she's ready please give Rosemary what's in the sandal up
The newspaper clippings mostly and the official Internal Affairs report
From when I shot that young man who killed all those people
I'm not asking you to defend me
You've done that enough
I shouldn't have shot him and I'll be the first to say
I just want our daughter to know to know the truth about her old man even if it's terrible
I understand
She said either way I'll ask her again if she
To see you if she's okay with it then so am I really oh thank you
Just give me a call at the latest time usually home by 9:00
The old you again like that when you first made detect
Remember that fire you had in your belly when you and I first met
We both had it
So what do you think if you enrolled today we can get you in at a lower premium the thing of it is we already
Already have insurance
We don't really need another policy let me just show you our rates Mr Liebert that's all I ask
The coverage we have right now is more than enough
I couldn't afford a whole new policy at the moment anyway
We've had our current one for 4 years ever since we moved into this neighborhood
4 years huh where were you living before
Well over near Manheim in Boone town
Bruton how about that
It's a nice area so are you folks from their originally
Yeah we are and the nice is an understatement
So do you folks have any kids
He's attending the University of Munich
Now that's what I like to hear as it turns out we're offering a new plan that's perfect for young adults hear me
This won't take a minute
Oh your son I presume
Well he sure was a handsome baby what's his name
His name is Johan would you like some tea
Yeah don't go to any trouble on my account
They must keep him pretty busy at school
Seems like he hasn't called us in a long time boys get like that when they leave the nest
Sounds like you speak from experience
Hello Dr rifine
I'm back
Yeah I went to Johan's folks house
That's the thing
They were normal as could be
Totally average
So what do you make
Richard
Hello back in my detective days I probably would have said there's nothing fishier than normalcy
Or something to that effect
Now I just don't know
Hard to tell
At any rain I'm going to keep checking out the people around you hun
Where's the flaw
Nobody's that perfect
You want to enjoyed a great reputation during his prep school days is grades were top-notch and is evaluations painting
Is a model student
The baby's face in the photo
There's no way he grew up to look like you're on
Here you go sir the birth certificate you asked about
Thank you
Johann Wilhelm Liebert date of birth
9th of February 1976
So it was definitely born in this town
Everything here reads pretty legit
Mr Hertz how many times do I have to tell you you cannot
Not light up in here just give me an ashtray I promise I'll smoke it real quick no way
And risk another fire like 4 years ago I am not replacing all those damn files again mister
You had to recreate your files from scratch
Well yeah we did have to ask people to resubmit their information it took a while but we're a small
Town so we got all our ducks in a row again eventually
Hey thank you so much for coming Dr Gillen
Good to see you again
It's been too long Dr reichvine
So I'm to understand that when Dr tenmark came to see you he was looking for a young man he called Johan
That's right but there was no evidence with which to corroborate his story
However if the young man in this photo is the friend who manipulated my current research subject
When Peter Jurgens a serial killer into committing another murder
Then Clues must exist that tie these three events together
I'm counting on you Dr Gillen right
I'll get clearance to interview Jurgens as soon as possible
I'll let him see this Photograph and monitor any reactions
If it might help prove 10 minutes innocence it's worth a try
So he's dead
That's right
The real Johan Liebert who was born in Boone Town died when he was 2 years old
Hold on
You're saying the liebert's replaced their dead sun with someone else and after that fire destroyed the original records They
Who's that chance to plug the other boy into that identity
I'm afraid so if they did
Then who's this young man masquerading is Johan Liebert alive and well
Beneath the lies
Who the hell is
At any
I did pass along Johan's photograph to Dr Gillen when he stopped in to see me
Hopefully he'll get to interview that killer of his again sometime soon
Now then
How about dinner sorry but it's getting late
Another time what's this you run around all day and now you're working through the night as well hard
I'm expecting a very important phone call
Cross your fingers
There's a chance I may get to see Rosemary
Really
Don't worry I'm okay
You're always telling me to focus on the road ahead aren't you
Of course
This is an important step in your recovery
Yes hello
Hi Daddy
It's
Hi Rosemary
Daddy's fine
Of course
I'd love to see you
You say when
And I'll be there
Mr Brown
It's Johan
Tell me you're against this young man
Do you recognize him
Maybe you've met him somewhere before
I don't know him
Best friend of yours Johan right
You only know him through his letters you've never actually met him isn't that correct
But Johan certainly seem to know a lot about you
Could I borrow your pen for a moment
What's
I'm sorry you know the rules here prohibit me from giving you anything
The park
That's where I was
Killed someone the day before
I remember thinking I'm going to stop killing people
I've had enough of office
That's what I told myself
He was there
With a bunch of kids
Wait hold on a second I should be recording this just start over again please
Come with us come with us
Come with us come with us comma
What are you doing here
We met at Mr schewald's estate
Remember
Johan Liebert sir
I've been trying to get in touch with you but to no avail so
I figured I'd drop by
Yes
Oh Dr Gillen it's you good
So did anything interesting happen when you showed Jurgens that photograph of Johan
Wait he's
Correct
I'm at the hospital right now
The police still aren't done questioning me
So I'm stuck here
Listen we lost a vital witness tonight because I was careless and handed a psychopath of ballpoint pen
But I do know one thing for sure
Jergens committed suicide
Because he saw that photograph of Johan
I'll be over there as soon as I finished up with
The police all right
All right
I'll give Richard a call and let him know
He'd better be home
The report for class huh
That's right
On the recent un convention on the rights of the child
And if the treatment of juvenile offenders holds up
Well how rude of me care for something to drink no thanks I'm fine
That's right you do abstain from alcohol
Yeah
Probably for the best
You did have quite a drinking problem
I mean you were drunk when you shot that boy isn't that right
Or so I've heard
Yes I was
Not that it matters
What I did is unforgivable drunk or not I have a few questions about what happened if you don't mind
Tell me about the victim
Stefan Yos age 17
Of what crimes did the child been accused
Don't be so naive son
Yours was a monster
He was old enough to rape and murder nine women and almost killed two more
So you executed him no I didn't pardon me
Speaking of
Article 40 of the UN convention
States every child is presumed to be innocent until proven guilty according to the law
Were you familiar with that
Yes of course I was I used to work in juvenile detention
And article 37
The one that goes you cannot impose capital punishment or life imprisonment without possibility of release on any person
Symbol of the age of 18 you know that one
The convention Agreements are considered basic human rights for adults and children Al
What kind of a fool do you take me for you really think I planned it all out in advance my shooting him was a drunken mistake
Look I know that what I have done can never be undone all right
And I accept the consequences of my actions
I'm not trying to antagonize you I just want to cover my topic from every angle
I'm very sorry sir I really should have used more tact
Shall we walk
The night am I doing some good
I'd like to purchase the bottle please
Just something to take the edge off of the night air
Oh Dr Gillen
I keep calling him but there's no answer
You know Richard did say he might be getting to see Rosemary soon but this hardly seems the hour for a father-daughter reunion
Well when you finally do get a hold of him let him know how dangerous that young man can be
And tell him that I'm in route to his apartment
Did you ever look into Stephanie's background
Of course he grew up in an East German orphanage or something like that there's more to it than
His crimes were to be expected
If you knew his past
To a child like Stephen
That orphanage was hell on Earth
He was a good boy
But that didn't save him from the horror that might have even made it worse
That orphanage devoured his mind
And then picked its teeth with his soul
The convention on the rights of children article 6 the right to life survival and development
Article 8 preservation of identity Article 19 protection from abuse to Stefan these were
So many fairy tales Eva there's no more fitting word for a place like that I can barely speak its name
Allowed 511 kinderheim still sends a chill down my spine
When will you be seeing your daughter
What did you say
How do you know about her
Before you answer the door you were on the phone with her
Isn't that so
When do you see her
Tomorrow maybe
Enough talk
What are you up to
I'm just doing research for my report
That's all no damn it I'm on to you kid you're going to tell me what you've got planned for shoe Vogue
So who are you
Who are you
Tell me
You got drunk and shot that boy to death that's what
Plenty of people did see you drinking in a bar that day but that was after you'd already killed
It's kind of odd Mr Brown
I've researched this case exhaustively and try as I might I can't find a single person who saw you drinking before
You murdered that young man not a one Mr Brown this charade has gone on long enough
Will you really drunk when you pulled the trigger
You are quite sober
And you are calm you executed Stephen Yos and you knew exact
Did I get it right
I'll wake the mind when it wants to forget maybe you didn't forget
Maybe you're lying is it a lie you tell everyone around you or perhaps a lie you tell yourself
Were you absolutely certain he committed those crimes certain enough to put him down like a
Dog you are guilty of murder do you think your lies can free you
That
Blood is on your hands how are you going to look Rosemary in the eye tomorrow isn't her daddy
Lowered and a murderer hiding behind an empty bottle
Well Richard how about a drink
Huh but Dr Gillen is that you
We're the police
We've come here regarding your patient Richard Brown
He's dead