Outstanding yes his skills are truly unmatched the aneurysm was in such a delicate
Location
Yet he clipped it off so effortless
ENT
Another perfect operation by the Peerless doctor
I was finally able to observe the genius surgeon at work for myself
No I couldn't have done it without your help
Thank you all very much
It's not midday already
Well you know that surgery did go on for almost six straight hours
We don't have any more patience today
You should go rest
Mommy where's Daddy what happened to Daddy
Wake up sleepy head
It's time to wake up after 10 minutes
Looks like rolls have been rever
It should be a princess like me who's awoken with a gentle kiss
Well I guess you did forget about our date didn't you cancel
I didn't forget
Appeared before the Press yesterday along with his family
Appeared to be in fine spirits
The family will remain in dusseldor
For an unknown period of time
Before moving to a home provided by local government authorities
We'll be following this story
With great
Feel like I'm still so exhausted
Hey wake up look at the TV
But seems to be recovering well after undergoing surgery
Is holding a press conference now
We take you there live
Mr rosenbach's diagnosis showed a ruptured aneurysm in his cranial artery
The operation went smoothly
Including the successful clipping
Of the patient's cerebral hemorrhage
Yes well we will certainly do whatever is necessary for him to be able to sing again
Isn't that wonderful Kenzo
It wasn't even about me
It was all about your father
But it's only because you did such a wonderful job last night working as part of Father's team
I'm sure he appreciates all your hard work
Since you're the one responsible for raising the hospital's reputation
No I'm the one who should be grateful
I mean after all it is thanks to your father that I'm actually able to work here in Germany
Hang in there Kenzo
It won't be long before father becomes chairman of the board
Soon after that you'll become chief of surgery
And then Chief director
Which means I'll be the director's wife
You better make me happy Kenzo cuz hardship doesn't suit me
You still want to go out on that
I said we just
Blood pressure 128 over 64
Spatula
I will now scrape the pyramus
As usual you did a magnificent job
Thank you very much
But it seems to me that your talents extend beyond the or
Well you're the head of neurosurgery it's such a young age
You've become the Golden Boy for both the director and the chief of surgery
And on top of that you've even captured the heart of the director's daughter
What exactly are you trying to say doctor sorry
I'm not suggesting you've done anything wrong here after all hospitals are ruled by politics
If he is using you then it must mean that you are gifted
When you do become successful don't forget about Good Old Becker
I'll buy you a drink next time
May I
Help you
Are you Dr Tim
I am
Give me back my husband
Me back my husband tell me just tell me what can you operate on
Who are you my husband was dying and he was brought to this emergency room first
He came in long before that stupid opera singer was here
But you made him wait to be operated on everyone says you're supposed to be the best surgeon
This entire Hospital
I remember now yes sir you shouldn't be here right now
Doctor get over to or one immediately these are the directors orders doctor so please hurry
Why if you had operated on him he would have survive
Bring him back to me bring him back
And then my friend and I started fighting over that dress
It was the only one they had in that size can you believe that
But don't worry about it of course it was mine in the end
Hey are you listening
Is there something wrong
You seem distracted
I checked the records
And the surgeon who operated on the Turkish man was Dr Becker
Why are you still talking about that
If you look back over the charts they clearly show what happened
Becker took too long to treat that man I don't know but I think if I had performed the surgery on him I might have been able to
Save his life
Do we have to talk about this at dinner
I was just following orders from the director when I performed surgery on that opera singer
I'm not responsible
Well am I
Well of course not
After all people's lives aren't created equal
Is that the house
Yes
One of the neighbors called in
How many shots were fire
Five or six sir
Who lives in this house
Well it seems
It seems to be the residents of the Levert family who recently fled here from East Germany
This is going to turn into a big mess
One
Someone's there
There appears to be
Survivor a girl
A man and a woman are dead a boy is in critical condition I repeat
One boy is in critical condition
A bullet to the head is that boy the only patient
Yes his parents were DOA it seems to have been a robbery all right then
I'm about 5 minutes out I should be there shortly
Oh Father
Evening Dr heinemann
I'm terribly sorry for keeping your precious daughter out so late what are you talking about Tenma
It's all right Ava is your fiance isn't she
Now what are we all doing standing here come in have some tea
So tell me something have you notified your parents in Japan about your wedding date yet
Yes sir
But my father runs a small Hospital back home so I'm not sure if he'll be able to take the time and come all the way out here to
Germany well wouldn't it be a good opportunity for him to take some time off and enjoy a Leisure trip overseas
They should come we're taking care of the expenses anyway
Thank you very much sir
I'm completely indebted to you for everything you've done for me
Did I ever tell you that when you first arrived here in Germany I thought you were a high school student
And now you're the best young doctor at Eisler Memorial Hospital
By the way Kenzo
I want to talk to you about your current research on cerebral vascular spasms and subarachnoid hemorrhages
Oh good I've been creating a model of a subarachnoid hemorrhage in a dog
I'm sorry but I'm going to have to cancel the project
I have been asked to speak at the next European medical convention
And of course that means preparing a sharp presentation
That's why I want to have you compile my manuscript
Sorry my research is very close to being completed I'm almost finished by the way Eva did I tell you what happened earlier
Later today
The suspicious group of civilians forced their way into the hospital
They were protesting the operation We performed on the opera singer
They claimed we pushed back the case of a Turkish man who'd arrived at the ER first
They got the whole thing wrong
That's not how it happened that Turkish man was operated on first there was not a thing wrong with our Pro
Right Tim
Yes
Apparently they think we're some kind of Charity or something
Our priority is to progress as medical Scholars before we save lives
Don't you agree
In any case I do want you to work on my manuscript
I have great expectations of you Doctor Tenma
I appreciate that sir
Where's the patient they just brought him in
How's he holding up
Blood pressure 72 over 50 his pulse is at 1:37 the bullet entered through his forehead
We need x-rays immediately yes doctor
Who's this
She's the twin sister of the little boy we just brought in
Any injuries no
But she seems to have sustained a serious psychological shock
Yes what is it
Dr Ten
The boys x-rays in CT scans are ready
I understand I'll be there shortly
It entered the front of the head and stopped deep in the center of the brain
Yes
This one is definitely going to be difficult
The bullet is touching the left side of the middle cerebral artery
Here
Will you look at that
Dr Tema is absolutely right
This one won't be easy
If you jostle the bullet even the slightest bit then they artery could rupture and cause a massive hemor
Hey so I'm late talk to Becker you're supposed to be on dut
I don't understand how you could be so late
Will do a full frontal craniotomy and remove the bone fragments and contaminated brain matter
Then we'll remove the bullet very carefully
And lastly repair the arterial wall
But with a little hard work and some luck I'm certain that we can pull it off
Blood pressure 120 over
Pulse 92
He's looking good
The anesthesia is taking effect
Oh there you are doctor yes
You shouldn't be here
You're needed in operating room 1 immediately
It's critically urgent mayor rudiger has suffered a cerebral blood clot
He's being transported here by helicopter they're scheduled to arrive in 10 minutes then
I think the best thing is to contact Dr Boyer there's a chance his carotid artery is blocked
If that's the case we want you to operate on him
But sir I can't do that I was just about to begin surgery on that young boy
It's an order from the director
Hello this is Tim
Hello tema
Take care of the mayor will you
I've contacted Dr Eisen and Dr Boyer
It'll be good to have that extra support
In case you
But Dr heinemann I was about to start another operation right now
Just let Dr Becker take over that
With all due respect sir the patient I'm about to operate on has a bullet up against his left middle cerebral
Ordering it could turn into a very complex surgery
But I am confident I can save him director
So I'm going to let Dr boy or take care of
I'm expecting you to do everything in your power to save the mayor
You need to understand something very important in the next review of medical facilities the mayor has promised our
Spittle a very generous increase in funds
We can't have him die just yet
Do you understand
I'm expecting you will do this
I'm counting on you Doctor Tenma
Yes sir
The mayor has just arrived on the heliport doctor
After the CT scans are done do the angiogram
We need to confirm where the arteries blocked
About time to get ready Dr timma
Yeah we're all counting on those brilliant skills of yours
Is something the matter doctor Tenma
I have
I have a surgery to perform in the other room
Hey where are you going Dr Tema but this is an order from the director
Mayor is having a CT scan done on him now doctors please report to the reading room on my way
Hang in there kid I'll save you no matter what
Blood pressure 120 over 80
Pulse 92
I will begin extracting the bull
Bullet is extracted
Removal process is completed
It's a little early to be relieved
We must still reinforce the walls of the damaged blood vessels
Right
80 Proline
His current blood pressure is 128 over 72 and his pulse is 88
It looks like he's still under the effects of the anesthesia
Live on kid
Survive and have a good life
Oh Dr Boyer how did everything go it looks
Looks like the procedure went smoothly on your side
Yes the surgery went well at least
The mayor wasn't so lucky
Really is that so
That's very unfortunate news
You act as though his dying has nothing to do with you
The truth is doctor that you're the one who abandoned our team
Just before surgery too
But wait that child was brought in before what does it matter is
Selfishly left us a man short we had to scramble to cover for you at the last minute and somebody died and then wait a minute just
Who sent the teamwork after 10 Mi you are aware that I followed the director's
And I clearly instructed you to perform that surgery on the mayor did I not however you chose to IGN
You decided to act on your own I've already given my
Report to the director
You deeply regrets this incident
This will greatly affect our Hospital's reputation
You have only yourself to blame
So wait please wait
Doctor Tenma things are looking very good at the moment the boys blood pressure is 114 over
82 pulse 84 overall sir the boys vitals are very stable
Well that's good to hear I just want to say Sir the operation was amazing
After collapsing on a holiday retreat
As soon as his sudden death was made public
Life of the May
They are Road Acres cause of death was a cerebral infarction
Caused by severe infractions of the inner carotid artery
We certainly did everything we could for him but the condition caused intense swelling of the brain and it resulted in the
Mayor's untimely death
A city official explained
I've got to get some sleep
Which took place late last night
Terrorist act against the
Who had recently fled here from the East
A full investigation is currently underway
The boy has not yet regained consciousness
And is still in critical condition
Now the weather
The whole country
It's a shame I wonder what it'll end up happening to the boy
On the way I'm just like him now
Mrs Reinhardt and ICU is complaining that she's having a hard time sleeping that said do you think we
We can give her something to help her sleep
Doctor Tenma
Are you listening to me
Oh I'm sorry yes in that case give a one house in tablet please that should help her get some sleep
What is with him today he's been spacing out all day
Hey
Dr Becker it's you Alex like you're going through a bit of a tough time there
Come on fish up have you heard anything from the director yet
I did try to warn you didn't I
I told you the hospital is ruled by politics
I knew what I was talking about and if you played your cards right I'm sure your future would have been smooth sailing
Oh well I guess what this means is you and I are on the same boat now my young friend
Come on 10 man don't be so depressed
I know you'll get a chance to redeem yourself sooner or later
What do you say we go get some drinks that'll put a smile on your face
Hold on a second nurse excuse me
I still need to get a statement from the girl would I be able to go in and question her now
Time
That girl has disappeared from her room what did you say
Seems like she's always slipping out of her room and wandering all over the hospital
And so the reason that Eisler Memorial
Royal Hospital has proven to be the nation's leading medical facility is first and foremost
Because we're blessed to have excellent Personnel such as yourself and I'd like to take this opportunity to thank
Every single one of you for that unfortunately as you
Oh no just yesterday the mayor passed away in our Hospital
Of course as always we did our utmost to save his life
And because of that this Hospital's reputation remains intact
And I appreciation let's have a round of applause for Dr Boyer and Dr Isen who strive to the very end to
Try and save the mayor's life
I looked over your thesis young man you did an excellent job please keep up the
Good work all right
Excuse me
Oh yeah I'm so sorry I apologize for what happened sir
Now now don't worry my boy what's done is done
Director
You did what you thought was best you followed your heart
Why don't we just leave it at that
Thank you sir
Ladies and gentlemen may I have your attention please now a word from the head of neurosurgery
Please excuse me it looks like I'm being called up there no you're not Timba
Allow me to introduce the newly appointed Dr Boyer please make your way to the microph
Come on but so what does this mean if you wish to remain at this
Hospital you may do so but you'd better give up any dreams of furthering your status it's not possible for irrespons
Possible people such as yourself
I recognize your skill as a surgeon but that is it and you can forget about presenting any research papers at future
Conferences
But sir please listen to me you decide to transfer to another hospital I have no intention of recommending
In other words it's useless for you to Harbor any Ambitions you have successfully tied The Noose around your own
Successful surgery requires teamwork it's only with everyone's help and cooperation that
Ava please you have to talk to your father for me
Spare me Kenzo You're such
Fool
Dr Norton you're looking very handsome this evening thank you you're looking especially beautiful tonight
Yourself Ava
It's quite ironic really
I came to Germany after I discovered one of director heineman's papers
And as soon as I get here it takes me under his wing
So now it all makes sense that paper I was so impressed with
It was probably written by someone else someone he was grooming just like he'd been doing with me this whole time
I knew that he was really just using me
But I was hoping that when I'd reached a certain status I'd be able to make my own choices
With what I wanted to work on
Our priority is to progress as medical Scholars before we save lives don't you agree
That's not true her doctor's priority is disabled every can after all people's lives
He tells me there's a flaw in my character what about him he says he's a doctor but he's just a greedy Bast
Bastard
He'd be better off dead
I have to thank you
I have to thank you because you helped me open up my eyes as a doctor
So survive and live a good life after all I did throw away everything in order to save you
That's how far I went to give you your life back and I would do it again
You know your name don't you
Your name is Anna Liebert
Isn't that right
I did try to warn you that all this was a bit too soon for her Detective
Isn't there anything we can do doctor
She saw her parents get shot to
She's fine physically and I think her trauma induced Amnesia is natural given the circumstances
Is there any chance you might be able to wait to get a statement from her after she gets better
Not really this is a very difficult case one of the victims was a former East German diplomat
If we're not able to solve this quickly the bka will be all over our back
Those guys always come here after the fact and try and steal the show from us
I haven't got time to take things easy
What if we do this yeah
We let her see her brother and then she'll probably be so relieved to see him that it might help her regain her memory
I cannot possibly agree to such a risky proposition that's completely out of the question besides I'm sure doctor Tenma would
Never permit such a thing
He's in charge of Johann her twin brother
Sure feels like I'm getting a run around
Hey Dr Tenma you seem a little bit out of it you all right I mean you are looking awfully tired this morning
I've been so busy with emergency surgeries
Wow it seems like they've been working you to the Bone
Well ever since you were demoted from Chief
Well I don't mind really it actually makes me feel better
How are you really doing doctor
I'm sorry I've just been paged I need to go
Are you so sure it's a good idea to keep on going like this
Hard work won't get you anywhere
Look at this doctor Heineman
Look at all the gifts and letters of encouragement
Yes there are mountains of them in his sister's room as well
The media keeps reporting on the twins heartbreaking soda after losing their parents and how they're now on
Grown and this is what we get
As far as this hospital is concerned with no one alive to pay their medical expenses and nothing but an inconvenient
Now so their story is a pitiful one that works for us
It only means this hospital is garnering attention think about it a moment doctor these kids
Very valuable to us am I right or aren't I
Yes sir why don't we do this we'll give the media a photo of the siblings together
They'll probably be thrilled to have something like that yes that's something the media has been requesting for some time now
But the thing is just do it don't be naive it'll be a picture of the orphan sibling struggling bravely
Survive under the warm hearted care of our Hospital staff however the boys attending physician says
It is still too early to allow them to see each other who's on this case
It's Dr Tenma not anymore
What's that
There's no need to leave him in a position that's getting so much attention
Just take doctor 10 Mile off the case
Yes sir
This is a heartfelt gift from the citizens yeah why don't you have one thank you
You're looking well Mrs Hank
How do you feel I'm feeling quite well doctor
And I owe it all to you thanks will be removing your stitches very soon so it won't be long until you
You mean I'll be able to go home soon
That's right just make sure you follow my instructions all you have to do is rest
You still need regular doses of anti-convulsants and anti-hypertensives okay
Anna wake up
What happened to her we brought her in to see her brother and
She just she just started screaming and why did you do that
Dr timma take her back to a room doctor Boyer
Telling me what this is about and why the camera we wanted to commemorate the emotional meeting of the
Twins and then release a picture to the media will allowed you to do such a thing I should have been consulted I'm the boys
You've been dismissed as the boys attending physician as of today he's
So I made my own judgment that it would be fine for the twins to see each other
Children were just following the
Disorders and I think it would be best for you not to fight him I seen this boy's life it's my duty to protect him until
Fully recovers well in that case just take a look
As soon as he saw his sister he reached
Down to her and began to cry you see he's regained Consciousness and is reacting normally to stimuli
Which means the surgery was a great success
So good job your work is done here
I'll get back to your post that's in order
So it was
Directors orders ha don't make me laugh we'll give us a damn about what the chief says bunch of
They're less for power and money screw them
I'm not wrong no matter what those bastards think of me
Hello
Father I'm home
Father
Are you in your room
Excuse me Dr Boyer are you still in a meeting at this time of night
Hello father are you sleeping already
I'm coming in
That bastard
Have a bastard be better off today
Hello sorry to bother you at this hour We're Here on Official Police business
Would you happen to be Dr tema
Can I help you pardon my asking
But were you home all last night
What
No I was out drinking until dawn
Why do you ask well sir Eisler Memorial Hospital
Battles director heinemann chief of surgery doctor oppenheim and Dr Boyer
They're All Dead
No one except the police are allowed to enter the scene of the crime
But you're interfering with the operation of this Hospital press is not allowed inside that patience in this kind of Chaos
Can you tell us please was it an accident or was it murder three people died at the same time of course it was murder
Are you part of the hospital staff tell us would you happen to know anything about this internet out of my way let me through
Hey no one's allowed in I work here I'm Dr Kenzo Tenma come on step back
I'm sorry sir but I don't think this is the time to be
Calm down everyone is the emergency room running smoothly well actually we're swapped with the emergency cases right
No doctor
Two patients are waiting to be operated on all right then I'll see what I can do can you take care of the car accident victim with the
First I'll go look over the X-rays how about the other case the patient collapsed with a stroke
Doctor
I'd like to ask you a couple of questions
I don't have time for this I understand but this initial investigation is vital
Do you know of anyone who could have possibly held a grudge against the director and the others
A grudge doctor
Did someone come to mind no
Sorry
We have a problem
Those kids
The twins the boy and the girl
They're gone sir we can't find them anywhere
And is the little girl's bed empty is well nurse
What's going on what the hell is going on
In his Mercy he lent a hand to many who were ill and suffering we will
Always remember his Great accomplishments farewell Dr Heideman may you
Amen
Ava
I know it's difficult but please try to hold yourself
This whole funeral business is just too sad Dr timma
Yeah
Up until now she was fed with a silver spoon as the director's daughter but now suddenly she's just another ordinary person
That's got to be quite a big shock how can you say that right now sorry about that
Dr Tenma
I am inspector Vise Bob the nordheim westfallen police department
Thank you for your efforts this was such a tragedy
Yes let me introduce you
Dr tanma
I am inspector Lungi I'm here from the bka
I've heard about your amazing abilities
No
I still have a long ways to go
Do you have any leads at all to the children's whereabouts no but we have determined the cause of death for the
The director and the other two doctors
We have discovered traces of nitrate inside all three of their bodies
Please that's a muscle relaxant exactly
I see you're not a doctor for nothing
How could something like that end up and was candy
Candy
It turns out the same candy wrapper was found beside each of the bodies
The same substance was also found in each of their stomachs
Tell me
Would you have any idea where they might have gotten this candy or something else of that sort
I wouldn't know where they got it from
If you don't mind me asking how was the search for the twins going
The bka is taking over jurisdiction on this particular case from the local authorities please don't worry
As it stands after investigating certain events we believe all this could be tied back to the moment the twins parents
Was shot to death
First their parents defect from East Germany and are murdered soon after that
Then staff from the hospital where the children were treated are also murdered political terrorism may be a possib
Those children might hold a major key to this whole mystery they need protection please do
Your best to find them inspector we certainly will
Excuse us
Interesting a Japanese doctor demoted by the director
And then his engagement at the director's daughter broken right before the incident
But the man was in the bar drinking at the time the crime was committed it checks out
No
I still have a long ways to go
Dr Timo was actually quite modest about it when I commented on his well-recognized talents earlier
The police huh
What are they think in your suspect
There's enough evidence to implicate me
Nothing I can do about it
I don't worry about it
They were persistent when they questioned me too
God I'm so exhausted
Once this whole thing gets settled
I think I'm going to go back to
And
I came to Germany to do research but
With everything that's happened I see again
Most important thing for a doctor is to save lives
Come on don't get all depressed on me now just tired
So so tired
Mr Buckner
You're making great progress
Thank you so very much Dr Tim I'm glad to hear it
Do you think I'll be able to work like I used to
Yes of course
Good because if I'm not there I'll have no choice but to close shop however
You mustn't overdo it and I'll stop by your restaurant for a drink after you released
Now that's just to make sure that you're not over working
See Dr Tim yes
I heard that you were leaving this Hospital
Is it true doctor
Don't quit
Please don't quit
Good doctors like you are so hard to find
Please stay please don't say you're quitting
Please
Mr
Doctor Tenma the chairman is asking for you
Right now he's in a meeting with the board discussing how to fill the open positions
Until now most of these posts were held by Dr heinemann's followers
Seems like they're going to be major changes for example the rumor is Dr eckner is being transferred to a small
I see
Chapter 10 now hold on
No matter what the chairman says please don't give up I want you to know we're all behind you
So please don't leave the hospital
Let me say this again
I'm performing so
And that's the reason
I'm making you chief of surgery
Oh God real life this is
I'm sorry for calling you out of the blue but I'd heard you'd been appointed chief of surgery
I'm truly happy for you
Thank you Eva
Kenzo
That day at my father's funeral
I remember you were trying to comfort me weren't you
It made me happy
A lot of things happened between us but I'd like to start over
Cancel
Listen please forgive me I was wrong let's start over
Patient is hospitalized for a spinal cord tumor
His paralysis has accelerated I understand I'll do the operation myself excellent
Doctor I'm glad to hear that make the arrangements for the procedure right
I've had it with this damn flood
I thought the world would change when the Berlin Wall came down 6 years ago
And it did
The worst
It's true
They talk about a unified Europe but we just keep getting dumped with the bad
The rate of unsolved crimes is definitely on the rise
Inspector we have arrived sir
Both victims had their throat slit
It isn't pretty
Their identities
Mr and Mrs reichmann from Stitch Drive
They were murdered in their home
We believe they were hidden away in a closet
But we're washed out into the open because of the rising flood waters
Another middle-aged couple murdered for greed
In the past two years there have been four other similar cases across the country
All murder the same way
Probably the same Thief
No
It's too premature to call these simple robberies
Judging from the data
For some reason none of these couples seem to have had any children
Well this couple didn't seem to have any children either
Don't you think there are too many factors in common here
To make the Assumption this is just a simple robbery well sir
I'm just going by the fact that money and goods were taken from all the victims homes it was all of it totally a small amount
Although this would make sense if it were the work of a single perpetrator
Hold on you're suggesting there's more than one two of the homes in question had extremely strong locks and sophisticated
Alarm systems
But the perpetrator bypass them and was able to enter without any trouble
Also
None of the couple showed any signs of struggle before they were killed
And the neighbors did not hear a single sound
The time the incident took place
Don't you think these were orchestrated all too well for just one suspect
Yeah maybe
Do you know this man
No
Adolf Yonkers 32 years old
He's been arrested twice for larceny
In a robbery he's the one who Gets You Through the front door
In other words a lock pick
It turns out
He was spotted near the area and three of those four double murder cases
Then he's got to be the man right
Or not
It's too early
Well
In any case detective your job here is done
The bka will take it from here
Sure
Oh well
It didn't fly after all sorry about that I've never flown a kite before in my life it was good you almost did it
Well doctor do tell how was your date last night
Oh well she seemed like a nice girl
She's the daughter of a director don't tell me you just had dinner and saw her home
Well actually there was an emergency call during dinner so I had to come back to the hospital hold on you did what
You'd better rethink that all work or no play doctrine you're going to lose a great catch and regret it
Do you hear me hey are you listening to a word I'm saying
Oh okay good morning doctor how are you
Is this yours Carl
My Grandpa gave it to me
But it won't fly I think it's broken
Maybe the alignment needs to be adjusted
Well doctor do you know how to fly a kite when I was a kid back in Japan I used to do this a lot
Hold it up in the air now all right you ready
How like this had a boy
Now here we
It's flying
All right
Oh man
If I were as smooth as that
I have at least five lovers hell maybe even 10
Seriously
That's so awesome Dr Tenma
Get better soon Carl
So that next time you can fly it yourself okay
Today's surgery is a paracellular meningioma extra patient
We'll proceed with a right tyrional approach yes
Everyone watch closely
The chief of surgery himself is heading up this one
Brilliant operation
Just look at
That is hardly retracted the brain at all
He is truly a surgical genius
New residents should learn to treat the brain with such care
This is terrible and ambulance
I didn't do it this wasn't my fault
This guy ran into the street all of a sudden out of nowhere
Is this the patient
Yes
How is
Well
We tried
But there isn't much we can do
This man is material witness in a case
It's important that we get his testimony since it may help us solve a string of Serial murders doctor
We can't have him die on us
But inspector this patient isn't very critical condition
Really there's nothing else we can do for him here
However there's a top-notch neurosurgeon at Eisler Memorial Hospital
If he comes here
He might be able to do
Neuros
That would be Dr tinma
Thanks for coming all the way out here Dr Tim
What's his condition right now he is conscious but a bit delirious
Also one of his pupils is Dil
It's been a while hasn't it Dr Tenma
Sorry but do I know you from somewhere sir it was 9 years ago
The director's funeral remember
Oh yes you were from the bka inspector lunge
Please do be sure to perform a successful operation for the sake of the bka
The thing is Doctor
This patient has to survive he holds the key to solving a very important case
The sake of the police I do it for the sake of the patient
Fair enough doctor now if you'll excuse me I have an operation
I hear you've become the chief of surgery
Well no doctor
You certainly become very successful
Yes and what about it
Nothing
That's your age it's quite an accomplishment aren't you next in line to become the
I still have a long way to go
Those murders years ago at Eisler Memorial Hospital due to a lack of evidence that investigation has seen
Very little progress
The only clue we found was the poison candy
This suggests it was a calculated act on the part of the Killer
In that kind of crime
The killer always has something to gain
From the victim's death
What are you getting at inspector
Nothing forgive me
In my line of work
The mind doesn't stop I'm always thinking like this
In any case rest assured
Of all the cases I've ever handled throughout my career not one is gone unsolved
Not a single one
Well I'm glad to hear it
Will perform a craniotomy to remove the hematoma
If we don't hurry the brain hernia will worsen
After the Eisler Memorial Hospital murders
No matter which way I looked at it
One person had everything to gain from the incident
And that is you
Doctor Tenma
Thank you again for going to all this trouble driving all this way
No don't worry how is the patient responding well he is still conscious but is right people does remain Dil
He's also got Paralysis on the left side
But he has already started rehab hasn't he
The paralysis should go away
He's on the right track listen I think the police want to interrogate him as soon as possible but that's out of the question
But doctor that detective Loom gay is a very persistent man
Right now the patients recovery is all I'm worrying about
How are you feeling Mr Yonkers everything okay
So
Tell me Mr Yonkers are you able to recognize me
Do you see this finger I'm holding up
How about it
Can you talk to me today
What's that
I'm sorry
What did you say
Coming
Mr Yonkers what's coming
Monsters coming the monster
Yonkers
I know you're able to speak
You have been identified at the scene of the crime of four murderers
Involving middle-aged couples in the past two years
There's no point denying
What do you say
All right okay I guess we had better tell you that we already know that you are just a lock pick
You couldn't have possibly slit their throats in one single slash with such cold blooded Grace Yonkers no
That wasn't your work
Now that means there had to be other accomplices involved
And I'm thinking there would have had to have been at least three of you in order to do both
Open a strong lock
And murder a middle-aged couple
Without resistance
That sound about right
We're almost through compiling a list of suspects who we already know our skillful with knives it's only a matter of time
And before we're able to narrow it down to one name
Whether you decide to cooperate with us or not
However I must confess that's not really what I wanted to ask you about
What I would really like to know Mr yunkers is why four couples from across Germany and every one of the couples
Middle-aged and without children money and items were stolen but we know the amounts were too small to just
Define murdering for a mere third of it
All right
So tell me are you up for some negotiation if you confess now we'll dismiss all charges against you
So tell me who is the person who hired you to do this
Mr Young Chris it's all right it's all right
I don't think so we're almost there get out of
That's a doctor I'm ordering you
Very well but I'll be coming back at a later time and just to make sure he isn't poisoned or that he doesn't
Pier I will assign a guard to watch him closely that shouldn't strike you
They're always seems to be so much trouble happening all around you Dr Tenma
We'll keep in touch
Hey hold on where are you going
Just going out for a walk it's not supposed to leave the room without permission
Patients need to get fresh air every so often
We're just going out into the garden
You're welcome to come with us if you like officer
Very
It's nice and warm out here today
You are able to talk aren't you
It's afternoons like this one that make you happy to be alive you know
If it weren't for times like today I don't think I'd be able to go on
Especially when you're here constantly seeing people having to fight for their lives
That's why it's easier for some doctors to think about their money their research or getting promoted
I used to be one of those guys myself
I wanted to get promoted and do my own research
I was positive that being successful in surgery was the way to the top
But have to performing a surgery on a certain little boy and everything changed for me
He was the older of twin siblings
Been shot in the head
Saving his life reminded me why I had become a doctor in the first place
It reminded me that all human lives should be regarded as equal
And that a doctor's job is to save those lives
Thank you
People start over all the time
It's never too late believe me
You know something
You and I are very close in age
But you're almost like a father to me
Well it looks like I landed myself one big kid huh
This one time when I was a little boy
I wanted this clock
You
I'm sure you've seen those before
Kind of have a little Nutcracker figuring popping out of it every hour
I would stare at it for a long time pressing my face against that display window at the store every afternoon
So I guess it's no surprise doctor that was the first lock I ever picked in my life
But I was caught in the act
And I never got that clock
However ever since that day picking locks sort of became my job
And it all started just because I wanted that stupid clock
Oh I wanted was that stupid clock
You should just tell them everything
Tell the police everything you know
Just make a fresh start of
Oh my
Who did it
Is it this monster
The one that you mentioned before
Do me a favor don't screw it up this time I went out of my way to set this one up for you
You know she's the daughter of a state legislator she is beautiful and intelligent all in one package in other words
Perfection well we'll see about that but you know what all kidding aside you're right
It is time for me to find someone of course I'm right the thing is that someone in your position
Is that a wife just seems like hey
I'm sure you've seen those before the kind that have a little Nutcracker figuring pop
But every hour
Excuse me about the clock in the window hey what's going on you're already late for your date what
What you doing
Oh no
See see she left because you were late and it's all because you had to stop in that store
Oh too bad I'm sorry about that can you do me a favor and apologize for me
Oh wait hey turn my
Maybe if you give her a call right now she might come back
Who knows I want to stop by the hospital for a quick minute what at this hour
I've had it with you
Officer
Excuse me
Officer are you out there
Hello
I'm ready to confess but I prefer if Dr tenmo were present
Where you could have gone
Listen I know it's late but can I go see one of my patients
I found something special
Hey what's the matter are you all right
Instead
Mr Yonkers
Mr young girls
It's the last time there's some candy my patience disappearing
Just like 9 years ago
Mr Yonkers
It's me
Dr tema
Stay away doctor
Let's go back to the hospital Mister Yonkers
Everything will be all right
Don't come any closer
I'm begging you please don't look at him
He's the one who killed my friends and I'll kill you too
Who are you oh God just run run away
Been a doctor
It's me 9 years ago
With my life
Have you forgotten already doctor about the twins
That's right
That twin
You remember
What do you think you're doing here Mr Jones is my patience let him go
What am I doing
In execution
We were hired by him he call us each time a large amount will be wired to our accounts after each job
Stop why it seems like we're taking the money and split it we had it all figured out
The murder of those four middle-aged couples was ordered by it was you
The police started suspecting me and following me
He wanted to get rid of us listen to me the other two friends the Slayer and big boys have already
It means nothing to him
Johan don't do this
Mr gunquest doesn't know your identity but I do
How was your attending physician
You are so hun Liebert the Elder of fraternal twins
You are the son of Michael Liebert
Former advisor of Commerce
Who fled East Germany in 1986
Has a political Refugee to the West
If we know this much about you
You can't possibly Escape
Don't add your crimes Johan
Johan huh
Yes there was a time when I went by that name
But you know something doctor Johan isn't my real name what are you talking about
You must never know about my past not about those four couples
For the Liberty but you're different doctor
You cared for me and you restored me to life so I feel as though you're like a father to
Like a father truth is if it weren't for you I wouldn't be standing
Here right now
Why not because a human life is precious don't you see that
What are you laughing at
I heard you were promoted to chief of surgery soon after that incident
I'm really happy doctor
That you were promoted to that position
What are you trying to tell me
You are where you are today because the director and the others died right
I'm so glad I was able to help
That was a good thing
My God isn't that what you wanted Doctor that's what you said
Right after I regained Consciousness that's what you told me
That you hated them so much you wish they were dead all that I did was
To your wish doctor
God
I was supposed to
To die that night you're the one who resurrected me doctor
What a miserable downpour
I just spies the wet weather
All it does is wash away the crime scene evidence when you need it the most
Well wouldn't you agree
Dr timma
All right
To summarize what you told me so far
Just to make sure that we piece it all together
Back in 1986 Liebert a high government official escape from East Germany with his wife
Children
Right after they arrive the Liebert family was attacked the couple was killed in the twin brothers suffered a critical gunshot
Got wound to the Head
You were the surgeon in charge of his operation
And subsequently save the boy's life
But to everyone surprises fate would have it
The boy kills the director the chief of surgery and the head of neurosurgery with poison candy and then dis
Pierce
And last night after 9 long years out of the clear blue the Libra boy reappears and kills a state
Police officer with poison candy yet again
And right in front of your eyes he shoots Adolf Younkers your patient
He is none other than the very man that hired you and curse and two others to murder the four middle-aged couples across
Germany
And his name is
Johan Liebert
I believe that's the entire story isn't it
Yes
I think we're finished with the doctor he can go
I don't think that someone with Dr tennis credentials or in his position could be responsible for such a crime
He has an alibi for the time the policeman was killed and we didn't find any gunpowder residue on his hand
So much for key evidence
There go all of our leads to solving those murders of the four middle-aged
Inspector lung
Should we get started on this Johan Liebert for the time being