No class
I want you to tell me what was the basis for the ruling the judge made in regards to the 19
CH Stuttgart case
Oh boy what is this silence why are we some kind of a monastery Mr eimer
I'd like to hear your answer if you have one
Well sir that is to say I anyone is there anyone
This room who can break this silence
So The Chronic light coming is here at last
You're 13 minutes tardy
Send your part-time pizza delivery job kept you off late busy today
I'm sorry Professor chronic
Let me ask you a question before you sit down do you have enough strength left to tell me the basis for the ruling
1968 Stuttgart case
Well
The defense claim
But the kidnapping was a sham
And the victim's death had been to the poisoning
After an investigation into the crime scene it was found that the victim's death had been accidental
And that there was no motive
So
Since the crime couldn't be proven to be an intentional murder
I believe a sentence of 15 years was handed down
Very good
You can take your seat Nina for tonight
Yes professor
Wow good job Nina
If no one had been able to give him the answer I have no doubt that kronecker would have probably demanded we ride a 50-page report
50 pages if we were lucky
I'll have to treat Our Savior Nina to something to eat
What are you say Nina a nice meal Just the Two of Us
Oh I'm sorry Peter but I have a club meeting today bye
She turned you down again hey Peter how many times was that
Come on shut up as if one of you losers could actually score date with her
I give
Oh my gosh if I'm late with my deliveries the manager is going to be furious
Hi I'm home
Boy am I hungry oh my the neighbors can probably hear you you are such a child go
Wash your hands de
Yes ma'am
Hey Mom you dyed your hair
What do you think
At your age
I don't think you should be dying your hair such a bright color
I don't agree with you dad I think mom looks great
Looks like she's going to some costume parade
It's nice to know mom is still young
Hi Dad
Oh and that reminds me speaking of costumes I saw some kids dressed up from head to toe today
Oh yes today is supposed to be the same Hadrian costume parade
I wish I had dressed up like that when I was a little girl they were so adorable
Yeah you did dress up in a costume once
Isn't that right dear that's right I completely forgotten really
Let's see it's around here
Oh look here it is you are so cute
Yes I did
You are so excited and made such a fuss
Isn't that right dear yeah I remember
Costume parade
Distance spring
I forlornly wait for a spring that will never come
Hannah
When you get over your break up already
I shall send you the most beautiful flowers
I was born to smother you with flowers
That's so beautiful
Wow
I wonder who sent this
I'm very impressed with you Peter
So
How have you been Nina
Well
I've been very well lately Dr guid
That's good to hear
But of course I could tell just by the look on your face when you came into this session that you were doing well
So
Tell me are you still having that nightmare
The one about the monster emerging from the darkness
No
I've been sleeping very well I've been so busy I don't have time to dream
I wonder why I was plagued by such a dream night after night
It's common for students to feel fear and anxiety
Expectations of the future mix up with other insecurities
People end up confused losing sight of who they are
But who you are is something you can spend your whole life trying to grasp and never figure out completely
We're always projecting and trying to look into the future
We spend our whole lives looking for the answers and we do the best we can
Right and that's what I'm doing
I want to become a federal prosecutor
That's very good
All right I think that brings us to the end of our session
Bye and thank you doctor
Nina fortun
Such a cheerful girl
I can't help thinking that she's overcompensating or running from something overwhelmingly dark
What do you mean what
Don't act so innocent what in the world are you going on about
I was born to smother you with flowers
I would never have guessed in a million years you had such talent for writing poetry I don't know what you're talking about
I wouldn't be able to come up with really stuff like that even if I stood on my head
Then who was it
I only give my email address to friends and no one else
Beats me
Damn it what this means is some Suave poetry guys honing in on my girl
How could it be
This was a bizarre murder that took place in Munich
After shooting the parents to death
The perpetrators strangled there to children with a rope
Grizzly really
No
I would like you to explain the verdict
Using the records from all of the hearings
Nina fortun
What do you not understand the question
No
The trial was focused mainly
On the cold-blooded murder of an entire family
The evidence so not even Nina
Has all the answers huh
Nina and what's wrong Nina
Are you all right
You want to go see the nurse
I'm all right
I just felt a little ill that's all
I was just
Listening to the professor
You mean that question about that murdered family
Is that it
I thought you were awfully brave but I guess
You're pretty sensitive too
Did you watch a horror movie that totally scared you when you were a kid or something
I know exactly what that counselor Dr guidel would say
If you get back to the root of it I think that you'll find
It was nothing significant now go back to your childhood
Am I right
That's it
I have no memories
I remember nothing before the age of 10
Where are my memories
My childhood memories
Yes
Those two were indeed a very nice couple
To think that they died in such a way
Children
Now that you mentioned it yes there was a son his name was Michael I do believe
He was there for a year or two
Let's see a boy
Do you remember if there was a boy
Yes there was
Wasn't his name Michael he was 14 give or take
Michael you say
Yeah I think I remember him
But
Why
Who are you the police
Michael Redman
I remember him vaguely but he was a student in my classroom
He didn't leave much of an impression I'm embarrassed to say it but honestly I don't remember him very well
I'm not sure if he had any friends
You see there are no records left from then
Everything went up in a fire about 6 years ago now
There definitely was a boy named Michael living here
And Michael's real name is
You hun huh yes there was a time when I went by that name
Are you what does it matter what's the use he's a serial killer
In order of twin siblings that's all there is to it nothing else
What am I doing
Twins
Where did his twin sister go I will pick you up very soon
Who is this
A child
Oh yes there was a boy about 7 or 8 years ago and Mrs hyena had taken a boy
In before they were killed
And what was he like
What was he like
That was quite a long time ago
And I think he only really lived with them for about a year or so
I honestly don't remember anything about him wait do you remember if this boy had a sister no only
Me the boy listen I just want to forget about what happened to that poor couple after all those horrible things happened
I almost moved away
I remember that boy very well
Why don't you come up
I was about to have some tea
Come in have a seat
Yes thank you
I was wondering just have a seat
Go ahead absentee
Thank you sir
You're a doctor right
That boy was the one who told me you are a doctor Tenma
He's coming to pick you up
Who is he I have no idea who he is
It was just an anonymous email
Aw you look so happy
You're not thinking this is Prince Charming on a white charger or a knight in shining armor coming for you are you
Why are you jealous
There you go Nina daydreaming again
It said I was born to smother you with flowers
Come on that's so corny how many boys do you know who write like that
Hold on wait
There is a new guy in our class you know who I'm talking about
Oh I've seen him
He's the guy who sits quietly in that legendary Seton room 12 where you're bound to be called by the instructor
But strangely enough he's never called on that's right and you want to know what else
He is always staring at Nina the entire class
He's the one what do you mean
Come on you know Prince Charming who else
All I know is that boy was extremely grateful to you yes Dr tema
He told me more than once it because you saved his life you meant more to him than his parents
What name did he go by then
Fronts
Then what he did tell me it wasn't his real name
If he opened up enough to tell you that much it means he must have really trusted you
He just showed up one day out of nowhere really
Mr and Mrs heinek who lived across the hall took him in
He lived with him for about a year
No actually it was it was a 14 months to be precise from March
1987 to April 1988
And then one day out of the blue he suddenly vanished it
It really was very bright that boy
Very well mannered
Did he visit you in your apartment very often
Everyday
I live alone so I always welcome to company
He said in that chair
And would spend most of his time studying
He was able to master the English and French that I taught him in no time
By the time he disappeared he was completely fluent in both languages
He was only 12 years old
Can you tell me if there's anything else you remember about him anything
You like my War Stories War Stories
During World War II
I was on the crew of a U-Boat the boy's favorite store it was about the time we
Attacked by a destroyer of the Allied Forces
We were the depth of 120 M that's when we were attacked by the enemy we had suffered
We just kept going we all waited and tears inside that creaking boat enduring
An hour after hour
We had to endure that hell for the day and a half
Any ordinary child would have probably looked at this as another adventure story
That boy was different what he was most interested in was my description of
Sia yes ultimate fear that reaction of people on the verge of death
Fascinated him that was all he was interested in he toyed with fear
So
What was the expression on his face as he listened he probably had a dream in his eye
Smile I imagine imagine well I cannot see Dr timma
So no I don't know the boys real name nor obviously do I have any idea
Looks like for that matter earlier you suggested the boy trusted me because he told me
Wasn't his real name I can assure you that he doesn't trust anyone there's only one
Always trusted in his life and that's his sister listen I need to help
Looking for that sister he said he would go get her when she turns 20
In Heidelberg
See you later
Be careful on your scooter honey
I will
Bye see you later Daddy
And drive safely okay
The time has come
Has
I know
Hold on a second I'm not sure I can do this what are you talking about you wanted to
Don't mess it up you're about to meet Prince Charming
Later wait Clara
How could they do this behind my back
It's him here we go
Hi how do you do your Nina Fortuner right oh good
Yeah my name is out of huberman
Can you hear me
And you've been wearing that same shirt for half a week
Quit nagging me will you
You have a visitor in the reception area
All right I'm going home
Listen you're going to have to make your own coffee okay
He hasn't had a bath either you'll like him he smells almost as bad as you do
Give it a rest
Yeah well whatever
Whose fault is it that I haven't been able to take a bath anyway
She's completely oblivious to the fact that it's cuz of me that we all still have work
Work even though this paper has no future
No hard is that to figure out
Sorry to keep you waiting
Hello my name is Tim masser
And I've come here to ask you for your help
She was right
He certainly looks filthy
I see so you're a doctor huh
Well you don't look like one
Let me get this straight
I just want to make sure that we're on the same page here
So what you're saying is that the infamous serial killer who's been executing middle-aged couples throughout Germany has his next Target
Heidelberg
This particular couple haven't adopted daughter and you're saying that when that girl turns 20 the killer will come to
Take her away
And when he does show up the foster parents are going to be killed
And you have no idea who that girl or her parents are but you want to save them
If that's not delusional I don't know what is I'm not joking
About this you have to believe me
What a load of hooey
Not even a third rate tabloid would buy that story look I didn't come here to sell you a story after the
Twins Escape they disappeared
It was at least 6 months that went by before the brother was seen in Munich so what's your point huh I
Believe that after leaving the hospital those children must have come here
To Heidelberg together you know this is just your theory
And then the two of them were raised by the twin sisters current foster parents but the brother ran away from home after
Short period leaving the sister behind
Why don't you write a novel
Probably won't sell though wait maybe the couple reported a missing child with the police
Or there might be a newspaper article about it from 9 years ago
All I'm asking is to look through your archives from the past 9 years I'm begging you
Wait please
There mustn't be any more victims The Killing has to stop
Listen to me
The boss is allergic to technology
Reduced versions as well as the original archives from 9 years ago
And the rest of these are the articles that never did make it to print
Thank you very much so said some sort of Japanese bow
Well domo arigato let me say this this doesn't mean that I believe you I just don't have time
Listen show yourself out when you're done looking you got that
God why do I always have to deal with the weirdos
Please please let me find it
Good morning Nina
Good morning
You're looking much better I'm so glad I was really scared when you fainted like that you know I guess
I really didn't like the boy we hooked you up with huh no that's not it at all I just felt sick all of a
I need to apologize to him I'll never mind you don't have to worry about him trust me
I found out he wasn't your prince charming on a white horse after all yeah we asked
And he said he didn't know anything at all about those email messages
Really
So you're saying that you fainted right after you saw this particular boy at your campus huh
Well what did this fellow look like
I only saw him for a second so I'm not really sure
And do you remember exactly what you felt at the moment when you saw him
I remember I felt nostalgic
Maybe not
I don't know
How to explain it
Go on
Just take it easy Don't force yourself
Absolute evil
I don't know how to put it but
It felt just like when I used to have that nightmare
Absolute evil eh it sounds more like it has to do with your religious beliefs
I don't think so I'm not really want to go to church regularly
I think if I see this young man again it might help to clarify things for me
You're thinking this might help you recover your memory is that it
I suppose that's one way to go about it
But I don't think you should allow this to disturb the peace you now have
It's important you continue to focus on your future and the road ahead
Don't worry
Just work up a sweat doing your Aikido and your anxiety should disappear
Hey mower so did you pull another all nighter
Yeah by the way
I'm just wondering were you the one who told that person he could use the file room
That weird guy
Yeah
I asked him what he was doing there and he said you would give him permission to look through the archives well you mean he's still in there
Hey you time to hit the road
Hey
Are you all right
Come on heat up
Thank you
Good isn't it
I always come here for breakfast
So don't you ever eat at home then
What about your family
Haven't got one
My wife walked out on me a while ago
I was always too busy with the work and before I knew it my wife left with our daughter and moved back with her parents
Do you ever think about trying to patch things up with her
Why would I do that she's the one who walked out on me why should I have to be the one to go after her
Well it just seems like you regretted spending so much time at work
That's complete nonsense
Work is priority number one you hear any woman who can't understand such a simple fact is welcome to leave whenever she wants
Sorry about that I didn't mean to pry
That's right
None of your business
Oh another thing please do forgive me
But you smoke too much as a doctor I recommend you cut back I told you already it's none of your business you're
Beginning to sound just like that wife of mine
Well what's so bad about that it means she cares about your health
Just mind your own damn business
Is that Nina's birthday present
Yes I was finally able to finish it
Goodness I remember when her sweaters used to be this tiny
Honey do we really have to tell her
Why not just leave it alone
You're right
There's no point in telling her that now
Nina's our daughter
That's all there is to it
I'm home
Welcome back
I am so hungry
All I have to do is focus on my future yeah maybe Dr guidel is right after all
See you tomorrow at 7:00 p.m. at Heidelberg Castle for your birthday
Tomorrow but Heidelberg Castle I'm a very busy man
Staring at newspaper clippings with you for 2 days
I admire your gumption but
Don't you think it's about time you gave up
Hey Doc
If
And I say if
I were to ask my wife to come home again
Do you really think she would give it another go
If you kick the habit one day
What is it
Found it
11-year-old boy goes missing there's a possibility the child has been abducted but there have been no Ransom
Man's made as of yet address 16 Necker Street someone named Fortuner filed a missing person
What that day there should be some more information in here somewhere
Oh here it is oh man
What is it what did you find Hey Duck you said that killer would come to take his sister away the day she turned 20 isn't
Is that right if the boy in this article is her twin brother well see for yourself his birthday
Those twins are turning 20 today
Hi Dad
It's me
I just finished up at work
I'm going to be meeting up with a friend and then I'll be coming home
Yeah it Heidelberg Castle
Really
Your mom is making a birthday cake so don't stay out too late
Was that Nina dear
Yeah
She's meeting a friend before coming home
I'm wondering who this friend is
Nina's a big girl now
Maybe this will help me
To remember things
I want to know
Well I really am
So dark what are you going to do if this girl is at the fortuner's residence whatever's going
Going on one thing's for sure they're in danger so I'll call the police and see if they can send over a car
And you think the police are just going to show up relax nothing's happened yet doctor but if we wait till then
And it'll be too late look nothing's going to happen come on this is all in your head
Hey Duck listen up I know what I'm talking about I actually went to the crime scene of the fourth middle-aged couple murdered
Cone there was something unusual about those crimes no motive
No Vengeance no bitterness nothing yeah it just seemed like whoever did this
Where to kill for killing sake I've been a reporter for a long time something tells me
Pay off base this time around duck honestly do you really think a 20 year old kid could be such a cold-blooded
Killer there's no way a kid would do something like that it's something a whole lot worse
How could it be any worse hell that's just it I have a hard time finding the words
Describe that case
Whenever I tried to describe it the whole thing just sounds so corny but the truth is how was the devil's work
One thing's for certain doc if I had half a chance I'd snuff that guy
China heartbeat
16 Necker Street this is it
Good evening
Sorry to bother you so late yes
I'm sorry to bother you sir my name is Mara I'm from the Heidelberg post
So you're a newspaper reporter
Yeah I'd like to ask you a few questions
What about well
The missing persons report that you filed for your son in 1986
I've got nothing to tell you
I'm sorry sir but you need to talk to us please listen we know that you have a girl living with you the TW
Sister of the boy who disappeared 9 years ago
This is important please answer me
Son of a gun
I saw a cake I just saw the mother in there she was holding a birthday cake
9 years ago you took in a set of twins and the sister is still living with you both
Frozen sheep please leave Nina's our daughter we are a family it's that simple
Please don't call us any unnecessary trouble just leave us alone please you took
A pair of twins 9 years ago the little boy at surgical scars on his head the girl at Amnesia and the boy
Disappeared isn't that right Mr Fortuner listen to me
You got to call the police now all your lives are in danger your daughters and your own
What what are you talking about what do you mean look it's very important we talk to your daughter well she isn't home with the moment
She's out
Where where did she go she's gone to Heidelberg Castle she said she was going to meet a friend there
Please let me borrow your car no way we got to call the police station first we don't have time to
Give me the keys quickly all right
You go on and I'll call them myself thank you they talk listen
Be careful like I told you before this guy's the devil don't die on me
You got that instrumental right you better come back alive if you hear me I promise
Follow your advice and I'll finally quit smoking so get back here quick your wife will be glad to hear
Oh boy how am I supposed to explain this to the police what's going on is our daughter all right
What is it what's happened
Don't worry she'll be fine but I need to use your phone what has happened to our daughter
Tell us already
Calm down lady
What the hell is this
It's dead
The phone lines been cut
Fleas on just hang in there hold on it's
I'm pretty late he's probably not coming well I guess that message must have been a prank after all
I'm going home you can't do that
You can't go you
Have to wait here
Who are you he told me
I'm supposed to make sure you wait right here
I just told you to wait don't you understand what I'm saying
Wait I'm supposed to keep you right here lady
It's my job to keep you here
I guess
They're calling you Nina now
Do you remember me
I'm Dr tema
My prince charming who the hell are you
Don't interfere you can't interfere in this
She needs to stay here that's all there is to it
If she doesn't I won't
I won't get paid you back there
He said no one else was supposed to show up
Hey are you all right
Yeah but how on Earth did you I need something to tie him up with quick
Tell me who put you up to this I don't know okay well when is he coming back here what did he say look
I don't know all he said was he would be back as soon as it was done with something very important he had to take care of
Oh God he's at your house
Come on we have to get back to your house right away I'll explain it all later we have got to hurry on
Let's go
You have to understand me
You got it wrong my name is not Anna I'm Nina no but that wasn't your name back when you were
Got into my Hospital you were Anna and your brother your brother's name
Johanna my brother
Mr Fortuner
Mr motor
Mr motor Mr Fortuner it's me Dr Tema I mean
She's here with me Mr Mara
It doesn't look like a police have a cane
Oh my God
Please come back you must live
Please
I'm begging you
What's tomorrow you don't have to quit smoking anymore all right
Back then
Killed him but now he's
Killed him I did I killed him I know
I killed my brother
It was me I was the one who brought your brother back to life
Instead the phone line has been cut we're getting out
He'll be coming back for you
You
Okay in there
Where would the police someone called earlier is there any trouble
If you don't mind sir
We're just going to have a quick look around
Good Lord
This is horrible
You two all right
Are you injured you hurt
Well that's a relief
Backup should arrive very soon
They'll take care of the crime scene and we'll take you over to headquarters for questioning so we can file a report on this
So are you the daughter of the victims
I'm sorry for your loss
I'm assuming neither of you saw the Intruder then
To think something like that could happen in such a peaceful town
Pardon my asking sir but where do you come from are you Chinese and no sir I'm Japanese my name is Kenzo tema
Okay you're Japanese yeah well seems to me you're quite a ways from home then aren't you
You're all right now it's going to be okay
Sorry but
Can you tell me where we're headed officer the police station remember but wait I don't understand
Heidelberg police station is in town yeah but we're from the station in Manheim the next town over
Yeah we're almost there just another 15 minutes or so okay
He said they got a call
But who could have called the
There were no Sirens when they first came
And they took us away before making sure the backup arrived at the scene but
Those badges those badges did look real
Excuse me
Police checkpoint
Thank goodness
We're searching for a hit-and-run suspect so please be alert excuse me it's
Well if it isn't detective messenger and detective Mueller good evening to you gentlemen are you two on your way back
Back to the station
I'm sure we'll get it banged up soon enough yeah we really give our rides a workout excuse me
Me Detective
She's not feeling so well back here can she get some fresh air for a minute
Oh
Sure you go ahead
Say detective what's up are these two in some kind of trouble
Trouble not at all it's nothing don't worry
What's going on here
I seem like real detectives
What about that blood
Who could have called them
There's Sirens weren't even on
What should we do
Hey what's wrong Dr Tina are you two okay
How do you know who I am
I found a grocery store nearby
I also got you some dry clothes
There's bread sausage and cheese
And I feel this thermos up with hot coffee too
You probably don't have much of an appetite but you really should eat
You're shivering
You should change out of those wet clothes
A
People were dead
My brother and I
We're walking
It was like
We are all alone in the world
Where were you when all of this happened can you remember anything else
We crossed the border
Uncle and auntie helped
They were so kind to
And my brother said
I have a good plan
Soon after that
My uncle and my dear auntie were both
Anyone who is ever good to us died
Without fail
All of them
But then one day
One day I discovered the reason why
Rainy day
You're talking about the incident with Mr and Mrs Liebert
My brother did it he shut them
My brother
He murdered them
He's the one who did all this my brother murdered them all
So I picked up the gun with both my hand
And then I I aimed it right at my brother
And that's when he
He was smiling
After you shoot me make sure that you throw the gun out the window
And he told me to aim for his head
So
I shot him like he said
I aim for his head like he told me
Why did you save him
If you hadn't saved your mom and dad would still be alive and wouldn't
Why did you have to say that
Stay here I'm going to the police
If those detectives last night were real
It means that some members of the police force are linked to Gohan if so we can't just wait
Wait here like this
Nina I need you to listen to me I know that Johan is going to come after you if anyone comes
I was looking for you just hide
Why don't you have some food drink some hot coffee and then try to get a couple hours of rest
One step at a time that's how we'll get through all this
You're alive you must think about the future
Your future
Were there any clues left by the Killer is there any connection to the serial murders through
About Germany like I said we're doing everything we can to investigate this case but I can't
And make any comments or talk about details
This time or is she presumed dead as well we're trying to figure out her whereabouts why was that newspaper reporter with them Mr Ma
Who is it he sounds suspicious quick question Chief is this murder at all related to the one that took place
I said Heidelberg Castle around the same time so he was killing joke that's
It's all for now we'll release additional details in due time
Do you like one more question excuse me sir of course we
Appreciate all the support we're getting from Manheim like detectives Messner and Mueller thank you both for coming out this afternoon
We're at your disposal to Aid in the investigation anything we can do to help so how
Everything's coming along sir please come inside that way we will be able to speak freely
Hello Heidelberg post
What I can't hear you we're really busy in here
Just final Japanese
I'm bringing an important witness to your office at
5:00
But you must not tell the police
Hello
If I can't trust the police only they can help Nina now
Western power
I'm sorry but you just can't come in here without permission he's right
Besides the bka is only working on the serial murders of the middle-aged couples
All that you're going to find in this room is material for the murder of the castle inspector long gay
Sir
Please forgive me
I was just a bit curious but the crime you're investigating in this one happened at the same time Detective
I mean it couldn't have been the same murder
So I see
It appears that this man had been tied up
You didn't happen to find a rope or anything nearby did you
No
Seems the body had already been untied by the time the police arrived on the scene
I see
Yes
There are four possible routes of Escape From The Scene he also had to stay well out of sight
How crowded was the area where he'd come out and how much light was there
Here it is
Nina it's me Tema I'm back Nina you can come out now
It's all right hey Nina
Oh no
Nina
Where are you
He came for you
Disney Nina
I never should have left you here all alone
Doctor tena
I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore
You did what you had to do as a doctor
It wasn't your fault
Please eat the sandwiches
Get some rest too
Please live on
And continue to save as many people as you are able to
Nina Fortner
Nina what are you planning to do are you going to kill
Your brother second time I did it I brought him back
Back to life that monster it was me
I brought him back to life
There are a lot of blood vessels in this arterial venous malformation
Cutting all arteries
And now the veins
Extraction of the night is just complete
That went very well yes as usual
He's remarkably quick with the clipping
An amazing operation
Doctor Tema how is it possible that even after a long break the work of a genius like you only gets better and better
It's over
Never mind it is an important
You better make me happy Kenzo cuz hardship doesn't suit
Please
Sir Madam is resting at the moment
I won't need much
Overtime this shouldn't take
You really need to make an appointment with Madam
What's all the racket
I'm terribly sorry to bother you mad
But there's a police officer here
Miss Ava Heine
It's been a while hasn't it
And how are you supposed to be
I worked on your father's case
Exactly nine years ago
I'm inspector Lungi of the bka
Loon gay
Oh I see
You may leave us holes
I do remember you all too well
And you were that good for nothing detective you couldn't even close my father's case so tell me what on Earth do you want from me now
I'm quite impressed
You've been able to maintain this residence exactly the same even after your father's death
Actually it appears that the decor might have gotten even more extravagant than before
So then if you come to see how much money I've made from The Inheritance my father left me and all my divorce settlements
As you can see detective I live in Absolute Comfort
If you see anything you like please feel free to take it with you
As long as I have my liquor by my side I'm fine
I've come today because there is something I'd like to show you
Here take a look at this necktie
A necktie does it look familiar
Perhaps you don't remember
It's a design from 9 years ago
It has a very simple print
But if you look at it carefully
It's a Wonderful piece
With an extremely elaborate weave
So what what about it
Tracing it back was quite a task after all it was purchased 9 years ago
But luckily this was a limited edition offering especially made for a particular stores higher-end
Science
And your name was on that list Miss Ava Heine
So what exactly is your point
You see
I was wondering if you might have purchased this and given it to someone as a gift
This necktie is a key piece of evidence and another murder case
A murder
Who knows
I've given gifts to so many men I couldn't possibly keep track of them all now could I
They're not interested in me anyway the only thing thereafter is my money
Please try to remember
I told you I don't remember these men are all after my money
There isn't a single person who truly loves me for who I am
That's why I always stick it to them when it's time for the divorce settlement I did not tell all three of them
Damn Bast
Do you want something too
You want something
Just tell me
Michelle pay a high price for it
I'll be back ma'am
If you remember anything please give me a call
Next time you stop by detective be sure to bring me something to drink
Excuse me
Dr Norton you're looking very handsome this evening thank you you're looking especially beautiful tonight
House have my car ready
Well Mr Hess you're certainly looking better today
At this rate I'm guessing you should be able to go home sometime later this week all right
Thank you very much Dr Timmy you did a great job
By the way my daughter is getting married next month do you think I'll be able to attend her wedding yes that should be fine
You just have to promise me that you won't get too wild at the reception
Thanks doctor
I had resigned myself
To not going but thanks to you
Hey come on it's because you toughed it out
With you looking after me I feel as though I'll even live to see my grandchildren get married
You truly are a wonderful doctor I really hope they keep you with this Hospital forever
Excuse me Dr tema
You have a visitor
Oh I'm doing my rounds right now tell them I'm too busy at the moment would you please
Okay but
It's been a while hasn't it Kenzo
That ass
Both of us
Have gone through so much
You look worn out you're much thinner
I guess
I hear that you took some vacation time
Well I think that's great you should take a break every once in awhile
He always wore such a workaholic
Seems like you've lost a little wait yourself
I've had a rough couple of years
I'm sure you've heard all the rumors
I've heard a few
Spring
You remember
Almost 10 years ago how the two of us would often go out for a drive
We were so young
It was this time of the year when you tried to swim in that River
I panicked and tried to stop you
But you insisted and you just
Luck Eva I can't deal with this now
Cancel
I want to start over
After three failed marriages I finally realized
That the only one who ever truly loved me
Was you
It was you Kenzo
That was a long time ago
Please cancel
I want you to know that I'm very flattered Ava but there's no going back
Goodbye
Please cancel I kept quiet I didn't say a word the police came to my house and asked about your time
It seems to me that necktie of yours has gotten you in some kind of trouble I'm
Absolutely positive that's the one I gave you as a gift when we were together
If you do as I say I'll keep quiet about it I promise you
There's something very important that only I can accomplish
I'll tell the police about your time I'll tell them everything
You hear me I'll tell them how you killed my father 9 years ago you killed him
Oh I see
Let's bring Dr 10 my in for an interrogation right away
That's not what I'm referring to I'm talking about the killing at
Cooper Castle thank you very much for your Cooper
This could prove to be very helpful in solving several of our open cases
Resignation
But what is the meaning of this doctor ten
I'm very sorry director but I've already made up my mind about this
There have been various odd rumors going around about you recently but I want to be clear I don't believe
Leave any of
Please think this over you
Hey wait
Dr Tamma
Yeah speaking
Excuse me the police
Close up all the exits don't forget the back doors
Where is Dr Tenma
Why are you just
What is it
Get out of the way you people are interfering with the police like hell doctor would never be capable of killing anyone
Anything wrong though go to jail he would never do anything like that
Who is this
Wow I wonder what's going on in the front
Does police cars over there Dr temma man ain't that a site is that right well I wonder what's going on
Anyway can you drop me off at the station no problem hey doctor are you always this busy
Looks like another scorcher today hey
Why are you all bundled up on a hot summer day like this aren't you broiling huh you're reading an old paper
That one's at least 3 days old yeah a couple inverted and got themselves murdered they say
Doctor did it if you can believe that hey buddy you said you were headed for burden wasn't that right
What you know somebody over there yeah I do I'm not even sure if he'll still be there now
I have to try and find them