Petra open up Petra you're going in for a check
And that's final stop wasting your time coming here
Waste of my time you know that look who's talking to you
I've never been to a doctor in my entire life and I'm a healthy woman I'm very healthy Woman as a matter of fact
Now leave me alone
Yes what is it it's a drunk thing he got hit by a car out on the highway
Why when you left it was he still awake I'm not sure but some
I was treating them when I left somebody who just happened to be passing by I guess some
Nearby
So mind telling me what happened here oh he
Sister did he I'm so sorry I tried to stop him but he said he needed to take emergency measures because the patient
My choke to
Well who did he say he was
I don't know he never did tell me his name
Oh he did write something on the chart though
The patient kept pleading with me not to bring him to this Clinic because he said he had no money to pay for a doctor
Please take this to cover any medical expenses
Bastard who does he think he is
Doctor where you going this fella what did he look like
He was an Asian man and he had a little boy with him
Doctor what about Mr Fink there's nothing more I can do for him
Only took emergency measures to prevent choking yeah emergency measures my eyes that's stranger
Listen
Dieter
You can't keep following me around like this it isn't going to work
I can never stay in just one place and you can't go to school like this
You won't make any friends and who is that
That isn't what I meant
Was it you well were you the one showing me up in my
Clinic
Keep your damn money maybe I'm just a country doctor but I take care of my own
I would never stoop so low as to charge that poor drunkard for treatment
Sir I just you're probably some big city doctor out on vacation I bet you're
Please dispatch you got to go show us Yokel some charity hey
How's it going come on Peter let's go
I'm not finished with you yet I'm terribly sorry
We're in a hurry we have to get going now thank God injured in a hit-and-run
Guy who drinks too much we're looking for any Witnesses
Good luck with that one
Oh hey there Dr Schumann
So how's things doing
Looks like he's going to pull through
I'm more worried about the bottle doing them in
And you are
Who am I
Dr Chan
We're alumni from the same medical school he figured he dropped by The Village while he's on vacation
Have you and I met somewhere before
He took care of Fink actually since I was out making house calls
Good thing he was here yes sir speaking of house calls guess where I went again today where Heinz isn't it
Yes I'm talking about your mother Petra my mother
You need to tell her to come down to the clinic right away
There's no telling what may be wrong with her without a checkup there's no way she's too stubborn come on you know that
That woman won't listen to anybody
Don't worry doc
Trust me mom's not going to die that easily what besides she raised me so what's left to do
When it's time she won't have any regrets what did you say bite your tongue
Petra has plenty of living to do do you hear me
Why did you lie to him
Because I never would have made it to think in time
No he'd be dead right now if you hadn't stepped in like you did
Thank you very much sir
You turned white as a sheet when you saw Heinz how come
Never mind
Least now I know you're not some hot shot doctor from the city
I'm in your debt sir I really do mean it
I don't know how I can ever pay you back is that so
Hop in the car I've got an idea
Your splint is misaligned I'll straighten it
This may hurt a bit but just hang in there
There you go I should do the trick don't let me cat
Since you not wearing that in the next two weeks hey Doc I made some smooth apple wine how about we drink to my new
I think that's an awful idea but I'll have a drink with you in the cast comes off
You should be fine 5 days and you can go back to the fields
Good news hi Mr Shawna why don't you take some potatoes we had a good crop this year
Afternoon with a truck
Thanks for the help my specialties internal medicine but I have to be a jack of all trades out here
I'm all the doctoring these folks get and there's only one of me it's wonderful
Tranquility is the one thing this place has in Spain no I didn't mean to land I mean
I mean how much you love all the people in this Village and at the same time how much they all seem to love you back
Love huh that ship sailed a long time ago
This is my job and that's why I do it well one last stop
You're a free man I save the best for last
Quit do you quit I don't even know the meaning of the word
How many times you come back just leave you quack
Like I'm talking to a mule mattress the mother of that officer who had you spooked
She collapsed 3 days ago working in the fields I talked her into coming down to the clinic but she changed her mind on the way
Stay over she's been holed up in there ever since that is worrisome
Not to butt in but do you mind if I try talking to her it's not going to make a look a difference
Don't tell me you're still standing out there you idiots
You have to come down she'll never come out if you keep yelling at her like that
Understand the possibility of losing you
What I mean is I wouldn't have anyone to fight with anymore also I wouldn't be able to eat that gou
Clash of hers if that stubborn old thing passed on
Hey mister how come your face is red what did you say you little brat
Please miss Petra open the door
What did I say it's a waste of time
So tell me why do you hate doctors
Why do I hate doctors
I'll tell you why
You play God with people's lives that's why
God
So I wish
Sometimes I think it would be great if we were
And try our best but we make mistakes too
Wouldn't it be great
If doctors could be perfect like God and just heal people
When I see my patience it's always the same on the inside I'm trembling like a leaf
Please miss Petra let me at least see you
Is that I'm smelling you're cooking up some goulash in here aren't you why you asking you like
Goulash or something I do but it seems that Dr Schumann is a particularly big fan of it at least
That's what he told me anyway well that's news to me I always make it for him and he eats it but he never says a word
He's very shy this looks really delicious my goodness my shoulders are so
And I still have a lot of food to prepare for tonight's dinner Miss Petra
Can you touch your chin down to your chest of course I can't easy enough to do watch
Let me just check something man
Four fingers wide oh nothing
How is she
It isn't good
A subarachnoid hemorrhage what did you say
Hey Hines the fax came in for a murder suspect make some copies
Is your mom okay I heard that she had a fading spell three days ago she's all right
Yeah that tough old lady is going to outlive all of us
The first stroke occurred less than three days ago
We can still make it but we need to operate immediately can we get a helicopter here in time
Can you do it please if you can perform this operation
Then do it if you can't they're my feelings will have lost me the woman I love for a second
Time
Are you sure that it's Kensington positive all right he probably hasn't gone far set up checkpoints
Along the highway if we catch this guy it'll be big Hines yes sir prepare for emergency
Deployment great if things go well I'll get promoted
Have a call this is speaking
No the nurse from the clinic are you kidding me my mother collapsed again
God why didn't I drag her into town if they had checked her at the state hospital I wouldn't have come to this
You're the only one who can save her
Just as I suspected it's an aneurysm of the middle cerebral artery
We don't even have a surgical microscope or a cranial here
I can still do it as long as I have an aneurysm clip
No it's too difficult even for someone of your caliber
We've got no other option here
If the aneurysm ruptures I'm afraid she's not going to survive the night
It's my fault this is happening again
What are you talking about Dr Schumann those aren't the words of a man who single-handedly taken care of this entire town
I don't know what happened in the past but
You have to do the best job you can do right now that's all we as doctors can do
Yeah
Hey kid Dr schumann's inside isn't he he's operating
Why are they doing it here at this Clinic instead of taking her to the hospital in town hey don't worry
How's her blood pressure and pulse blood pressure
Propulses 88
Amazing he's so fast and efficient even without the benefit of a craniotone
What the hell are you doing we're operating on your mother isn't that
Obvious what are you doing with that gun put your hands up do it if he stops
He killed a man in Heidelberg and he's the prime suspect in
Cereal murders of those couples who would have thought that I'd find you here
Leave it to good old mom always looking for new ways to help out our boy now put your hands up Timba
If you don't I'll shoot like hell you will
This is a sterile operating room or it was until you came barging in do you want your mother to die of meningitis
Cuz it's very likely to happen if you keep standing there then stop the operation
If we don't save her now she dies
Now get out of here Hines no way I'm on to you just
Waiting on using my mom is a hostage so you can run away from here all right now please
Aneurysm clip in forceps now that's my mother on that table I won't
Did anyone hurt her yes Petra is your mother and you're her son
But what kind of sun have you been to her these past 5 years I know you didn't visit her once since you left for the city
Years later Petra sets out a dish for you
I should know I'm the one who eats it
Remember how delicious it is
He's giving it everything he's got so if you ever
I want to taste that goulash again you'll get out of here now
C10 was there so it's okay
Blood pressure 140 over 86 pulse 82
Good
Her Vital Signs have stabilized
Why don't you get some rest Misty on you
God like you haven't I'll be just fine
Yes sir you did well today
Dr Tama you should get some rest too
Don't worry about me I'm fine you're fine that was a grueling operation you must be dead on your feet I want
Stay and make sure she pulls through
That way when Miss Petra has recovered enough you can go ahead and finally propose to her
What do you mean for pose
Hey I thought you were supposed to be asleep
I'm not sleeping not until I take him down to the station
What's he talking about anyway
You're not thinking about marrying my mom are you of course not
Don't be stupid
Even if I did
I'm not the kind of man who's worthy of proposing to anyone
I used to work at the University Hospital didn't give a damn about any of my patients
All I cared about what a cliche
Well I moved up that damn ladder all right and ignored her like the wrong she was if
I had been a real doctor or showing her the least bit of attention I'd have known in a moment
My wife came down with a simple cold at least that's what I wrote it off as
If only I had looked at her I would have seen it an intern would have seen it severe liver
Before she died she said I finally have your
Define detention
I don't deserve to love anybody after what I did to that poor woman
That's not true you have been paying attention doctor you've been watching over the people of this
Petra is going to survive this because you were watching
Do you still plan on taking this man to jail he did everything in his power last night to save
What kind of murderer would do that
Heights
This is Hines get me the chief chief I made a mistake
I'm sorry we should cancel this search the man I saw before was not Tenma
He was another doctor by the name of Chan I thought it was him because he was Asian
Yes that's right
Yes yes sir I'm very sorry
The doctor from the state hospital sure did
Being surprised well of course he did he probably never expected to see such amazing results from a little clinic in
Dr Schumann are you really going to let that young doctor leave
I was making him something to eat but he packed his bags and left with the kid
Don't go this town is safe for you there's no need to run away
Dr Schumann what are you
This is a nice Village isn't it you're right this Village may be a very good place for a boy like Peter here
But not only for him you could stop running you'll be off the radar if you stay
The folks in this Village need more than I can give them on my own together there's no end to the good we could do
I can't I'm sorry but I really have to be moving on but why
Take care of Peter he's better off here
What's more important than that
Save countless lives before I do that
As a man whose life I have to end what what are you
You can't mean that no damage you're a good man 10
You fought like hell to say Petra's life why you're not a killer
Tim was going to go no matter what you say to him
Go take care of him Peter
If you stay with 10 amount maybe you can keep him from going down the wrong path go with him and look after him
How many times do you plan on coming here you can ask me until you're blue in the face I'm always going to tell you the same thing
Look councilman boltzmann didn't have sex with that woman that prostitute
This had better be your last visit
I would hate to have to take action against you take action
Are you going to sue for defamation
No
You wouldn't dare
You're a secretary
You wouldn't want councilman boltzman's name to come up in a case like this
Inspector are you threatening me
No of course not
I simply want to know the truth of the matter that's all
John
Have you decoded her client list for me actually we're still working on cracking that code it's a lot
Tougher than we thought
I'll do it myself just give me the disc great but don't you already have a bunch of
Much of other cases on your plate it doesn't matter give it to me
There's something I've been meaning to ask you for a while what is it
Well how do you find the time to sleep what does that have to do with the case
It's an irrelevant question Detective
Well have you gotten the chance to talk to him it doesn't really matter when we tell
He doesn't listen he stopped listening to me a long time ago I know but the sooner you tell him the
Better keep it down you're being too loud
He's here you know working in his office yeah I wonder why
Damn it are you still trying to connect councilman boltzmann to the
The murder of that prostitute is there a problem with that chief
From the ministry of the Interior you're just going to have to smooth things out like you usually do no I can't
It's too big do whatever you can chief
Give me a break here Loom gay you're good but you're only human sometimes you're going to be wrong
Are you going to risk your entire career on a dead hooker
Come on do you need another feather in your cap
Oh
Don't tell me you're doing this for the principle of the thing
Justice
I'm not interested in either
All I know is a woman was murdered in Cold Blood
I'm just interested in finding the killer nothing else matters to me
Excuse me inspector you have a visitor got it
I managed to figure out the encryption that she was using use this formula to get all the names on our Client List
Oh that woman is here again sir you know the one
Hey you can't just come back here we've been over this before
When will 10 be arrested you have all you need
It seems like you've been drinking quite a bit this morning just so you know
I've already figured out the case regarding Dr Tenma
He insists that everything is the work of a man called Johan
But this Johann is just another personality within 10ma's mind
If you think about it with this hypothesis what seemed illogical now makes sense
Well we have to do at this point is just wait for the police to capture him
So that means it's not your problem once you got an arrest warrant is that what you're saying there are a lot of things I would like to
To ask him when we finally meet
Doctor Tenma
What an interesting individual he is
However I have so many other cases piling up on my desk as we speak
If you'll excuse me
Don't you people ever let up
I told you councilman boltzman has an alibi for that night
Of course he did
The murder was a professional
I'm sorry
Are you honestly suggesting that my employer hired a hit man to kill that girl ridiculous I've cracked the
Code on the list of clients of the woman who was killed councilman boltzman's name was on that
That list
You know even if that were the case it still doesn't prove that he had her killed
Right come to think of it that's as far as we've gotten I'm sure you'll be in touch now leave
We're dead in the water without a Smoking Gun wouldn't you say are you familiar with a Publishing House called
Longhorn
They're not a major company but they stay in business by publishing tell all books on famous people like Pol
Petitions
They're known to play very dirty
They hire unscrupulous women to build relationships with famous men in order to create scandals
To write about
If I were you
I'd watch out for people like that
Check and mate you should have seen it it was great boltzman's guy just stared at him like what
Blunque is unbelievable near as I can tell all he does is work
He's a robot I'm telling you
Man I hear you
The guy barely seems human to me
All right speaking of Checkmate there it is what the hell hey don't put into our game buddy
You shouldn't waste your time with my numbing games it seems after a simple little threat the
President of the Publishing Company chose to confess
Write a report
Here
What do you think you're looking at
It's at call girls notebook it records the date and time and other details of encounters with a certain
Client I can't really tell you the man's name
He's only referred to here by the initial b
Not to mention shellhorn publishing also made arrangements with the woman to release her autobiography
Interesting
Don't you think
Oh by the way
Have you ever been in contact with a man named yanker you may be aware that he is a professional Hitman
I want you to leave
You get the hell out of here now
We're moving out both of us right now level with me you never
Or even noticed I was pregnant not even now did you are you going to the man or father to your child what
Care I bet you didn't even notice that I was having an affair with another man did you
Understood
I have to go we can talk about this later
Inspector what just happened here
Councilman Boltzmann's an innocent man
Not much of a suicide note but that's all we got
Looney
I'm handing this one over to inspector Kaminski
I'm giving him the reichner park in gallon murder cases too given what happened I think it's for the best
So then what am I supposed to do now
Get your head together
Then we'll talk about work
Well Dr Tenma it seems there's nothing left to distract me
Sorry inspector you have
Have a visitor it's a behind a man but I could tell her to come back another day if you know
No sure in
I had a great time Eva
How long until next time not sure babe
Maybe when I return from my next business trip
All right
I'll give you a call
No you won't be coming back not after getting in trouble for that perfumed handkerchief that I carefully placed
Suitcase you stupid bastard
You were eavesdropping again weren't you
You must see all the different men I'm with isn't that right well what then you want to join in the
Fun is that it no of course not you pervert you're wrong but I mean I just I
Get how nice it is it's beautiful I really love this Garden
Looking at all this Greenery helps me forget about the distasteful things out there
I'm so glad that you like it I'm going to plant some mimosas here and over there I'm planning to put up an arch for
When summer gets here it's going to be beautiful like you could be up to the
So what do you think do you think you can make me happy
Hey Dad are you listening to me
Dad
Oh how is my cooking today am I getting any better
You haven't heard a single word I said have you Dad
How come you're always daydreaming I bet you that's why Mom ran off with another man
I'm sorry
It's fine
Really
Actually
Colet
Yeah
If Daddy found
Someone he really liked
No forget it it's nothing
My cooking is pretty awful right come on tell the truth
It's not so bad
I see
Not bad huh
Sorry for the trouble
You're a gardener but I'm asking you to do all these odd jobs no problem
My handyman kept asking for time off and then quit
Well I'll do everything I can to help
So how about dinner tonight
Well
Okay
Why are you nervous
Well I'm not used to expensive restaurants like this you must be
Confident wherever you go just pretend you're working in my garden right now yes
That's right I do feel pretty confident when I'm out there working on something new in the yard I Feel So Satisfied
You want a garden turns out the way I envisioned it I just love being out there you know people who like Gardens can't
Be all that bad and you did say you like that Garden the other day you're trying to say that I'm a good person
Yeah of course but you well go on
You seem you know kind of lonely
I'm not the only one
I'm guessing that you're lonely too
I'm sorry
My daughter's probably worried about me so I should get going
Cancel
It's almost Christmas Coletta he doesn't have to come this year
Hey come on sweetie don't say things like that Dad celebrating Christmas
Let's not do anything okay just be the two of us celebrating this year you know
The man you're looking at in those photographs ruined my life
Sorry I was just cleaning up
His name is Kenzo tema
He's my ex fiance
You're drinking again at this time of day well of course I've been drinking I just went to see inspector
Can you believe that useless incompetent inspector sent me away
All I want to know is when they're going to arrest them
The pka
The rest
He killed my father and then ran away oh he says he's innocent but he's not fooling anybody
My future should have been gilded and gold as the daughter of the director of a large hospital and my three divorces
Everything is his fault and he blames the murders on your home this is Johan with my father do
Think that this child could kill anyone
Is that really what timma told you
Have you ever shown this Photograph to the police I don't know it
Be important evidence Maybe
Lego says he has a split personality dammit
Then tell me
Why do you still keep framed pictures of them like this around the house years later
I figured deep down
You think Tema is innocent
You still have
Feelings for him
You watch too many so
Out of all the men I've ever met Kenzo satisfied the most of my requirements his position suited me
He was an elite neurosurgeon who many considered a genius besides he spoiled me and best of all he never
Contradicted me he just listened to my every single request yes yes he was the man who
Well we said yes to me that man could have made me the happiest person in the world do you understand what I'm saying
Do you think
I would ever be able to fill his shoes I'd be willing to tend your Gardens for the
Rest of my life
If that would help to ease your pain any
Knocked out flatter yourself just because I slept with you once you were just something to pass the time I was bored
I was playing with you and you fell for it you fool who Do You Think You Are
Truly a sad and lonely person
So are you
On Christmas Day I'm having a party at my house with my daughter you're welcome to join us
Well Dad everything looks delicious
Did you really make this all by yourself
Yep I can't guarantee it'll be good
Do you think so
Mom's coming home for Christmas
Charlotte
Mommy
I'm so sorry to
I'm sorry
Who cares about mimosas or about Frozen or beautiful gardens
Devastate none of it means anything to me now just let it burn
Welcome back
So inspector loon gay you finally decided to listen to me
I had some time open up that's all this man was my only hope I must see to it that his life
Is ruined or I can never be happy again