You wake up
Leave me alone
Yeah like that's going to happen
Now get up
We can still do this the easy way come on this isn't a hotel
Don't touch me
How dare you
Do you have any idea who I am
All right
Here's all the stuff you came in with
If everything's in order you can sign here
Ms Heineman
I don't ever want to see you tossed in the cooler again
Passing out drunk alone in the dark alley be thankful something horrible didn't happen to you
You got a cigarette
I'm just asking if you've got a cigarette
There's no smoking in the station go outside if you want to smoke
Later
Where is my lighter
My bag
I want to know what you did with my bag
And I already told you it's the only bag you had
You liar I know you're not telling me the truth I had another shoulder bag where is it
Probably with whoever stole it from you when you passed out drunk in the all
What are you going to do about it I have valuables important things in there
I tell you what
You can fill out a theft report if you like
But I really wouldn't get your hopes up
How the hell did you lose your key
My bag was still in last night just hurry up and open the room for me
What what happened here
Somebody really want to town
Oh man this is awful
I got to change the lock now
Which reminds me Miss Heineman you still owe me back rent
I don't want to have to ask you again the deposit you put down is already run out I'm going to need the rest of what you
These people even broke into my damn suitcase are you listening
You have to pay for a new lock and all that back rent
Well I don't have any money
What
Fine I'll get out don't worry
You're such a tragic story still I don't know what you expect me to do about
Any of it you know I seem to remember you being the one who storm that on me oh come on that's
Ancient history now so I know buy me a drink
It's just a stolen purse for God's sake you must have had some extra cash checked away somewhere
Honestly have yet to meet another woman who could burn through money the way you do and here you are finally coming to me for
This is it welcome to Rock Bottom baby
I'll sleep with you you know
I'm asking you how much you'd be willing to pay honey as
General rule most men won't pay to have sex with women they've already had a bunch of times
You can at least buy me a drink you'll find yourself a street corner to work who
She might get lucky and meet some Sad Sack is not too picky desperate and middle-aged and drunk must be someone's type
Yeah I'm positive you didn't leave any
Papers here last night maybe you left it wherever you went next
I don't remember anything after I left this ball
If it's worth any money you might as well Kiss It Goodbye
No it's not it's not worth anything at all
Not any money that is
Hey
I've been looking for you
I asked for you at the pub back there
And they told me you just headed in this direction
Yeah and who are you
Are you serious
We had such a good time drinking last night
I was drinking with you
Your bag
That's why I was looking for you
I guess this means I have to make
Awkward introductions again
I'm Roberto
So should we grab a little something to eat
Your hotel room
Really
That's terrible I'm so sorry I mean it's not like you did it
Well no obviously not
I didn't even dare look in your back
Oh look my hotel keys are still in here
A little late for those
I don't need them anymore
I'm sorry it's all my fault
If I'd return your bag sooner you wouldn't have been kicked out of your room in the first place
Besides I'm very grateful that you gave me back my back
Honestly I'm kind of grateful that you lost it
Well last night as I watched you leave the pub I sat there thinking to myself
You shouldn't let this person slip away
And now thanks to your bag
Here you are and here I am
You have something very important in there don't you
I do
This is all that I have left in the world
A photo album
May I take a look
That's my father
He looks just like I imagine
He was a hospital director right
Yeah did I talk about him last night
You did you spoke very highly of
You mentioned that he died 10 years ago
I could tell that you still miss him
Let's see
The ex-fiance
Please don't tell me I told you about him
I believe his name was Tem
Quite a guy
This Tenma
I really want to know what I said last night
Well I wouldn't make a habit of it
It might end up making other men jealous
On this page is empty
Is that so
The photos that were on this page looks like somebody tore them out
Well I guess I didn't need those pictures anymore
So I see
Hey
Let's get a drink
Sounds good
So you were running a security company
I'm impressed yeah
In the south of France
Then we had a bad day and one of our better clients was killed on my watch
So that was the end of that
We're both going through tough times forget it let's drink to the hearing now enjoy yourself
You know
It's good stuff huh
So you like this song too
Of course
Let's Dance
Come on
I don't really know how to dance
God
I know a man who love this song he wasn't a very good dancer either
So you'd end up dancing like this
That's right
How fun
How about another drink
Just one more
Thanks but I'm good
Lightweight
Time for bed
Sounds good to me babe
There's just one more thing
What's that
Pictures
Where are they
What pictures
Stop playing stuff
Those photographs you took out of the album
Where'd you hide them tell me see I'm
Your little secret you're looking for Tenma aren't you
I know you get those photos from burning and I'm sure you have them with you somewhere
Know where 10 -
Photographs that you're talking about
May the ones with father in that boy am I right
Wasn't it
Him you know blonde Charming handsome he's grown up well I
A year ago and Dusseldorf
So
What are you up to these days
I've heard all sorts of rumors
The rumors are probably true
I've been married and divorced three times now
Between my father's inheritance and my alimony I'm living pretty comfortably
But enough about me how is life been treating you Dr Becker
I don't know
Well nothing's changed with me I still have no chance of moving up in the world
Speaking of which 10 must now chief of surgery
Where it is he's on his way to becoming Hospital director
Love to be in his shoes let me tell you
But please who am I kidding it ain't so bad I still managed to have a good time there's more to life
Promotions I never want to be like 10 men have no time for women or fun what's the point
Is Kenzo
Do you know by any chance if Dr Tenma ever did settle down
No not yet and to be completely honest I've introduced him to quite a few very nice women but you know him no
No interest at all his work comes first
As a matter of fact I'm about to set him up with a new girl God only knows if it's going to work out
She's the daughter of a state senator and she is absolutely beautiful if she can't keep his attention that
I give up
Anyway you called me about something how can I be of service Ava
You know
Back when you were the daughter of the hospital director you never even gave me the time of day
Who would have thought that you'd even think to call
I understand you're well off
But really
I think you're getting lonely aren't you
I mean it when I say it Eva I'm more than happy to listen anytime
Look I don't want you to let them meet up
Dr tenman the state senators daughter
Don't let him meet her
Man I should have known
You're still in love with him
Don't let him
Do me a favor don't screw it up this time I went out of my way to set this one up for you Tim
Well we'll see about that
This is it this is the clock that Mr Yonkers was talking about at the hospital
Excuse me about the clock what's going on what what are you doing
That's a very beautiful watch
Why thank you
I mean I wear a watch but mine is nothing a trinket
Honestly I don't even check the time anymore
I wonder why
Time seems to be moving faster and faster
Excuse me but who are you
I'm sorry I don't mean to be rude but are you Senator Burgers daughter Angelica
Goodness
You're a pretty little thing well aren't you thank you I think
And you're convinced that the entire world revolves around you am I right
Going through life thinking that there's nothing you can't have it must be very pleasant
I'm sorry what are you trying to say I'm confused who are you exactly
I have this tiny little birthmark on my inner thigh
He used to kiss it
How he used to love kissing me there
Dr Tena that is
You know him
Oh no
See see she left because you were late and it's all because you had to stop in that store
Oh too bad
I'm sorry about that
Can you do me a favor and apologize for me
Hey timer
Maybe if you give her a call right now she might come back
I want to stop by the hospital for a quick minute what at this hour
I've had it with you fine leave
Enzo
You're mine
You're all mine
Mr Yonkers
Please wait
Kenzo
What's going on
Mr Yonkers
Cancel
Oh great I broke my heel
I saw him you know oh yes a year ago
Dusseldorf I saw him it was Johann I'm sure of it
He saw you on Guess
I have to kill you
Yes I've seen something that I wasn't supposed to see
I'm thinking it was that sweet looking blonde boy I saw in Dusseldorf a year ago
Because I've seen Johann this is how it ends up that's how it works with you
It was dark and raining when I heard those three gunshots
I was there alone and got scared so I ran away
At the time I was pretty certain it was tedma who'd been shot dead
But the next day there was this big article in the newspaper saying that a man named Yonkers had been found dead in the same location
And that he'd been shot three times
So then that boy did it didn't
Might want to rethink holding that trigger
If you kill me you'll never get what you really want
That photograph you've been looking for the one of Johann as a young boy
Let me tell you what will happen if you do decide to kill me
If I die I've arranged for that photo you want so much to be delivered directly to the bka
If you want to see that photograph you need to tell me exactly where Tenma can be found
Just what is so funny your whole body is quivering
You talk tough but your legs are shaking so hard you can barely stand
You really do amuse me
I'll tell you where he is still working
The doctor but our friend is gone on the ground
How's this older guy in Hanover who was the number two man in a certain organized crime family
Guys boss kind of freaked out and put out a hit on him but the job got botched the guy got all shut up
But he didn't die September is at this remote Alpine estate patching him up it's up on
Mountain near foosen
Excuse me but why did you just stand there like that
Hey mister it's almost time for lunch
Why in the world are we eating outside
I just
The weather looks so nice this afternoon
Why not mix up our routine and eat outside
Why have our lunch out here
Dieter
Go ahead and bring the plates out here
Okay
Oh your wounds are healing nicely
And this fresh air will do you good
I have to say doctor
If you hadn't been there I doubt I would have made it
That country Clinic was pathetic
But the masterful skills you possess allowed you to save my life
Maybe the one bullet just grazed your head and the other one went into your leg and passed through cleanly
Just be thankful it didn't catch your femoral artery
To be honest you are quite lucky
Lucky huh
Alrighty guys lunches served wow that smells good heckle
Surprising isn't it it tast
Delicious Heckle may look more like a pickpocket but he's actually quite the chef don't you agree
Did you mean by that
This my friends is chicken Marengo the key to the dish is the sauce you have to get it just right it's based on a recipe
Keep from a three-star French restaurant called La Petite men
Appreciate the subtleties of fine cuisine you know this would say Steven better with a dash of soy sauce soy sauce
Not that again you put soy sauce on everything thank you this is dining
When you sit down to eat this is how it should be
What a waste
All my life everything I did was to make money
But while I was earning all those Millions I lost things much more valuable
Both of my parents and my only brother disowned me
Even my wife and son were murdered
I always wanted to live peacefully
Dying like we're doing right now
Money can really change the way people act
Allow me to share a good example with you
5 years ago a covert banking organization was formed to facilitate the underground funds flowing throughout Germany
But these guys pulled off was absolutely amazing
Within days of the Dirty Money flowing in through Shady companies it would come out the other side perfectly clean
A money laundering operation
Exactly
On top of that this organization functioned in many ways like a real Bank
Making loans and investing in speculative transactions
And a girl unbelievably fast
In five short years they made a fortune
But that all changed this year because the man who'd been running the show suddenly vanished he hasn't been seen in months and
Windows where he went
Guess what happened then
I fell apart
The entire operation imploded
The associates that remains started fighting over who would get what was left and who would be in charge
Most of them ended up killing each other
The entire operation disappeared
If only
I've been sensible and talk things out while sharing a fine dinner
You think that guy got murdered or did he just run off
Keep up doc I mean the head honcho guy who disappeared
So kidnapped murder
What do you think
I don't know
I'm quite sure he's still alive
In fact he might even be posing as a student somewhere
A student
That's right
I forgot to tell you
I left out something important
According to my sources the guy who created that money laundering organization 5 years ago was just a kid
15 years old
15 years old you sources must be nuts no way it could pull off something
Like that but it's true this kid did it
Tenses if he was conducting his own experiment to see how adults deal with money
As though he were a child playing around with a line of ants
Where was all this do you know where this covert banking operation was based
The organization was headquartered in Dusseldorf but the kid at the top was constantly on the move
He controlled the entire operation from wherever he was you know
And did anybody figure out the last place that he was seen before he disappeared
I saw the details I know but I heard right after their young boss went missing all of his money hungry underlings went
Washington Munich
Communicate
Hey Doc why the long face what's going on
I know
Let's invite that man down the hell up here for lunch sure why not that's a good idea
Sorry doctor but that means my body God he needs to stay down there
But haven't you been officially declared dead already
You still think there are people out there who want to do you harm
Are you planning to live the rest of your life and fear hiding behind a bodyguard
How much has been with me for a very long time indeed
Go ahead son
Go and get helmet so that's his name I bet
Go and tell him that his duties is My Bodyguard her over
Is the only one left is like family to me
Ask him to join us
Have him come here so we can discuss our future at this table
Okay
Mr Helmut lunch time they want you to come up and join us
Time is right up there in the mountain Villa
You do want to kill him don't you
It's something that matter that was a
Unfortunately I
He's already dead wait someone's coming after you there's no telling but
I'd say someone's heading up here even as we speak
Go tell him
You have to tell him to run away
Hurry go until 10 minutes now
Tell him damn it
I said go tell him
But your leg you've been shot don't worry about me go
Hang on
Who's shooting at us
Did you get him
I'm not sure but now's your chance to run for it get going but I can't go you're out here in the
I can handle this just go no you can't go
Time
Well well
Looks like I was wrong
She didn't want to kill him after all
You going to be all right man
I'll be fine
But I think
He's already heading up the hill on his way to the villa
Not a chance I would have seen him from here there's really only one path to get all the way up to that house
What are you talking about
I've explored this whole mountain and this path is the only way up there all the other pass lead to Cliffs no one can climb
So then if we guard this Trail there's no other way Roberto will be able to get far enough of the mountain to get to the villa
You mean you know this guy
I know him too well
Roberto's after 10 money he wants to kill him
You know Tenma so who are you ma'am are you a friend of his
What you laughing about ma'am don't make me sound so old stop calling me man
Now get out of here kid
You get up there until 10
Tell him to run away quick
But man I mean lady you're bleeding I'll be all right
You just get up there and warn him but your leg looks like it's bleeding a lot
10 my mustard those gunshots I bet he's headed down here to take care of that guy
It's not good
Roberta wants 10 minutes come down here and try to save us so we can kill him
Don't you see it's a trap and where the bait to bring him here
But what can we do man if we try to make a run for it with your leg you might bleed to death stop calling me ma'am what did
What did I tell you
So just what are you did anyway I miss friend
What about you
I mean lady
Aren't you a friend of tennis too you must because even though you're hurt really bad you're still trying to save him
I'm not trying to be nosy but
You like 10 but don't you
Are you his girlfriend
Do you like 10
Yeah I like him a whole lot
What exactly do you like about him
Lots of things
What do you like about him
I know you're there crawl around all you want
You'd be pretty stupid to shoot me again I already told you if I die that picture of Johann is a child
So that you want so badly will automatically be sent straight to the bka I mean it this is your last warning
So that photo you've got is something you really want it's a lie and it might not work
He's too smart to fall for such
Lady are you feeling all right
Starting to fade I've lost a lot of blood
Now go we'll get out of here save yourself
Leave you 10 minutes on his way he would have been here by now he's got to be headed here I mean it
Look there's no way he would ever come to save me
Nothing but a waste of time
Dinner where are you
I'm over here just stay there
I'm coming to get you Peter
Don't move
If you try to come get us there's a man here that's going to shoot you
That's why he's come here 10
To kill you
I know that voice but it can't be
Denmark this lady is a friend of yours
Been shot and she's bleeding a lot
You can't die now not what I'm so close I'm handing you over to the police
I want every waking moment to hurt for dumping me stop shouting you're straining
Yourself
Just tell me if you can hear me okay can you tell me the shooter is
No I don't know
I've got no clue where is he still here
Stop yelling to him I need 10 more
Hang in there he's getting close he's not coming to you wrong
He would never come to my rescue
It's all over for me don't die please
Why would she ever
What's all this why did you bring me out here
It's time for lunch
Your leg has been healing up nicely
And I thought you'd enjoy eating lunch outside in this beautiful sunshine
You're a lucky woman you know
What do you mean lucky
Just that
A guy who shot you was a real Pro you know what he was doing
He understood how difficult it would be for him to infiltrate this mountain Villa
There's only one path to get up here
And there are security cameras everywhere
He also knew this Villa would be guided by experienced men so it would be like he was attacking an Alpine Fortress
That was the reason he used you
Hold on what do you mean he used me
It's simple
He must have figured that a pretty woman making an unexpected visit would have a much better chance of getting all the way up here than
But when you betrayed him his old plan was sunk
He had no plan B there were no other options for him
So he got out of here quick and cut his losses
So then he got away
That's right
We search the whole Mountain
This is a special dish it's called chicken Marengo
I tried to recreate the recipe but I can't guarantee it'll be any good
You know there's another way you were very lucky
You were lucky to have a great doctor like Dr tender treating you
So is Tim still here
He already left where to
Thank you said something about going to Munich
Munich a
Let's see if you and I can enjoy this chicken I got a feeling you're like me and I bet
Long time since you sat down and enjoyed a meal in peace