My wife and I divorced about 3 years ago
No that's a
She divorced
3 years ago
She said that I stopped listening to her and I suppose she was right about that
This was the only thing I did really listen to by that point
My wife said I was broken
She said it was a Voyer peeking through the window and people's innermost thoughts
Crazy
You're abnormal
Maybe you're right about that
I became transfixed obsessively gazing into the abyss of the human heart I suppose it's possibly hibiscus back
Into me the depths of the human mind are filled with treacherous landscapes
Your fourth victim was an 18 year old girl in Munich I believe
I'm curious
Did you experience any form of sexual arousal when you cut her up
I don't want to talk about her today doctor I want to talk about my 12th victim
Fair enough then
That would be Mrs Hunter Kemp from crupp House
52 years old
At that time
I was in
I'm not prepared to talk about her
I promise we will eventually get to Mrs Kemp but for the moment I would really like to focus on victim number 11
Is that all right
No then
The peak of your arousal
Does that come before or after you commit a murder
The victims were all girls with long hair
Ages 16 to 18
Clear these murders should all be categorized as acts of sexual homicide
But then he confesses to the murder of his 12th victim
Mrs Kem
Mrs Kemp was 52
And showed no signs of sexual assault
He claims to have killed Mrs Camp as a favor for a friend
And obvious in Desperate last ditch attempt to disrupt the investigation
Who is it
Who is it I know that you're in there
It's me Rudy
This is a surprise yeah I know
I'm sorry for barging in on you like this Rudy
You've heard about my situation
That's putting it mildly
Well
Do you think I'm a serial killer
I don't know
But from what I've heard
Both the newspapers and our old classmates think you're as guilty as Sin
So the question is
What are you doing here
Why come to me
We were never exactly what you'd call close
I know for a fact you despise me
I could tell from the way you looked at me
I saw the contempt burning behind your eyes
Haha that's what this is all about
You've come to collect what you think I owe you
Is that it it's not like that at all you've become a noted specialist in criminal psychology
I have something
I'd like you to take a look at it
My dear Dr Tim
Look at me
The monster inside me is getting bigger
Help
The Munster inside me is about to explode
What on Earth is this
Quite a story
So 10 years ago you saved Boys Life who went on to kill the hospital directors some staff and his foster parents
Then he's gone leaving no Trace other than a series of cryptic messages addressed to you
Which is why it's so urgent that I find out where he is now
Because you think by finding him you'll also find something that might prove your innocence
20 years ago
There was a young man attending a prestigious medical school
He was driven to be top of his class one day a Japanese transfer student came and changed
Everything
This new student was Charming quickly gaining the respective peers and teachers alike he had a brilliant mind as well
No claiming his position as the top of his class within his first semester much to the men's dismay by the
The next semester he had become obsessed with regaining his title he had managed to earn full marks and all his classes so
So far however his last test was in his weakest subject Medical
The law
If he failed this test then all of his efforts would go to waste
So he resorted to Desperate Measures measures
I thought would put them back on top but he was caught
The Japanese student
Never told anyone about what he had seen
As a result
The man regained his throne
So is there anything you can tell me about this man based on the contents of these letters
You think it may be multiple personality disorder
And you've come to the conclusion that one of the personalities is committing these murders while the other personality is trying to get
Yes instances of serial killers leaving these sorts of notes or not unheard
Just as often these notes are fabricated as legal proof
Of their insan
Separating The Pretender from the genuine article is the art of the criminal psychologist
I believe you me this is no easy task the introverted shifty-eyed serial killer is more or less a Hollywood fabrication
Many killers are highly intelligent intuitive and extremely Charming they are
Adoptive and skillful Liars
So that's it
You think he might be toying with me well let's not add to the mounting pile of conjecture just yet
Why don't you tell me a little bit more about this Johan
My wife and I got divorced about 3 years ago
What I mean to say is my wife divorced Me 3 years ago
Thank you rud
I need to do some research give me a call next week
Do you have an opinion about this person
Seems like my kind of guy
Can you elaborate on that
The monster
I get all that
That's interesting
You
The monster
Makes sense of course
There's a monster inside both of you
To be fair there's even a monster inside of me
Shut your mouth
That's nothing but textbook garbage
Why is that
What I'm telling you doctor is at a real monster does exist
What do you think you're doing just stop looking at me like that
Don't you dare look at me
What are you doing
I'm feeling the guards
Are you scared
Because there are things out there that would turn your blood to ice
I'm going to tell you a secret thank you for your Cooper
Operation
You really still convinced that Tim was going to try and contact you again
I'm sure of it
And when he does he'll notify you immediately
However
Well go on
After his arrest I would like to get permission to use him and his case in my research
Doctor Turner would make a compelling subject
He has a complex Criminal Mind
I'm going to tell you a secret go to Miss Hannah Kim
Towson group house make your way to the basement you're going to find all of your answers down there
Down there you'll find proof proof the monster
Really does exist
This is Rudy
Cinema
I've been waiting for your call
Yeah all right
Excellent I'll see you there
Officer call Tim I just called we've arranged for a meeting tonight
Odell Park tonight at 8:00
By the fountain that's right
Goodbye then
I'm currently retracing Jurgen steps on the day of his 12th confessed murder
According to our interviews he broke into the basement
And stayed hidden there for several hours
Later when Mrs Kemp returned home
He made his way into the upstairs bedroom and murdered her there
There's nothing out of the ordinary
Except
There are framed photos
All over the basement
Their own pictures of Mrs Kem
Just a doll
Almost gave me a heart attack
Evidence of this so-called monster Jurgen sent me to find clearly isn't here
The supports my theory that Jurgens committed the 12th murder to confuse investigators
His first explanation was that he committed the murder as a favor for a friend
One he Associates with a primal monster archetyp
When I was a kid
What she would do
It was dark
She had this big dog
Where
What does it mean exact in every detail
Is it possible did Jergens actually recreate the basement from his childhood
Boy next to Mrs Kemp is
Perkins it can't be there's no evidence connecting young Jurgens to Mrs Kemp
Something is not right here
This one
This one and another all of these Mrs Kemp never
So who is this boy
Who are you down there you'll find proof proof the monster really
Does exist
I followed all of the instructions and my friend left me in the letter perfectly
Just listen
The first letter came in a blank envelope without a name or return address
He understood me
Sympathize with me crap like that
I was annoyed
Angry at first
But then another one came
And then another the next day
And again and so on
He's a letter freak
But before I knew it I started to expect the letters
Even enjoy them a bit
Then I thought
Maybe it's possible he might actually be a friend to me
And then one day one of his letters asked me for something
He asked me to go down to the basement of this house
And did the basement belong to Mrs Kemp
I still don't know how he could have known
There's no way he could possibly have known what happened to me down there when I was a kid
Somehow he got everything right down to the smallest detail
How do you do that
I just got so confused
The next thing I knew I was upstairs and Mrs Camp was dead
He's a letter freak as well
What is this another
And this another one
Look at me
Let's try inside me is getting bigger
Help me the monster inside of me is about to explode
These are the messages that Johan left me
They're the same
Jergens's friend and your hot he's real
Anything yet it's way past eight already
Inspector call
Target in sight
Asian male
Long hair
I appreciate you making time for this Rudy
I want you to know I did research what you gave me
But I thought you were making it up
I thought that Johan was just a ruse a scapegoat you created to buy you time once you were caught
You've got to believe me
Rudy
I've been conducting research on a serial killer named Jurgens and something he said caught my attention
One of his victims is off pattern showing no connection to profile or ritual
It doesn't matter Rudy please just listen to me okay listen up everyone will finish for today
We'll see you tomorrow seems like the carnival is wrapping up
Everyone in position
Make sure they're ready to move in on my mark
Yes sir
I want every detail of their conversation
You hated me didn't you
You've hated me ever since you caught me cheating on that exam in college
I could feel your disdain
Go ahead say it
Inspector call
This doesn't look good
Dr Gillian and Tenma are headed toward the west exit
Damn we'll lose them and that crowd that's leaving
You'll be well within your right
A man like me doesn't deserve your respect Rudy this isn't the time to remin listen to me
Now then I looked up the answers and wrote them all down on a cheat sheet
She just like this one
Run we're surrounded by the police
Don't look just walk
Is Doctor timer threatening Gillen
I'm not sure sir there's too much background noise for me to hear
Jurgen's recently confessed to me that he had killed Mrs Kemp at the request of a friend
Booty what is this
Something I found in Mrs Kemp's basement
But Mrs Kemp never had any children
I have found compelling evidence to suggest that jurgens' friend and your Johan are both
Same
They've passed through the West exit should we move in tell everyone
I found a letter from Johann and Mrs Kemp's house it was almost identical to the one you brought me
I believe that Johan had been in the care of Mrs Kemp at some point in his life that would explain
Motivation for orchestrating her death you're an innocent man
I'm sorry I can't give you as much detail as perhaps you'd like but here's what I've worked out on
Johan so far
I don't know how he does it but Johan can somehow identify other killers
He finds them worms his way in beguiles them then manipulates them
It is worth noting that to the best of our knowledge he hasn't killed the foster parents who cared for him as a
Probably because by the time he reached that age he no longer found himself dependent on anyone perhaps
But I have another theory
What if Yohan found himself his ideal family
And then became a part of it
But my work so hard to erase his past
Was there an ulterior motive
If that is indeed the case did he make his way into the family for a specific
Purpose
And what would that purpose be
Well
We're at the bus terminal
Yes confirm which bus Tim is getting on
They get a car over to the terminal and have him follow yes sir
At least I can do is buy you a bus ticket
You know
There's still time for you to turn yourself in and prove your innocence
I promise I can help you
The truth is I'm not chasing after your hunt just so I can prove my innocence
Thank you for all your help Rudy
You don't have to become him to end this that reminds me
I really didn't despise you back in college Rudy
I mean it I thought you were brilliant and it was a shame we never had a chance to talk I'm glad that I
I'm finally count you as a friend but I know you caught me cheating on that medical logs and there's no doubt about it
I saw you looking directly at me and my cheat sheet oh yeah cheated on the medical
Typical exam too
Be careful timma
What did that sign back that say I missed it
I've been trying to figure out this map is it this way or that way I'm not quite sure
Sure we're headed in the right direction really where did you find that map lying in the street
You know me better than that you were right beside me when I picked it up at the car rental place
You picking anything up you must have grabbed it when I went up to use the facilities
Names with such small print at my age it's almost impossible to read your glasses at the
Is weapon housing and amputs housing and he's got two
That's quite a mouthful dad he's German names all sound like don't they they are
Using I wonder if Germans think that about our towns when they read British Maps
Now we need to know when the next Crossroads coming up
There's a pedestrian let's ask him for directions
Ourselves
Let's give him a ride if you ask me we're looking for trouble giving a ride to complete stranger
Maybe so oh wait a minute he's traveling with a small child
I feel sorry for them let's pick them up all right fine
Hey look 10 of those people just stopped for us
Couldn't talk better
Sorry we don't speak German
Do you understand me
Oh are you both from England
We're trying to get to freiheim and would really appreciate your help
Could I see that map
So where is this place the place you're traveling to
Oh well all right
We're around this area now so it's just a bit further south from here
I suppose
Duncan
You're quite an Odd Couple on you
I mean I don't believe you're his father you appear to be Asian and the boy
Clearly German Caucasian yes in fact he's my best friend's son and
Some sort of well-educated professional man it's the way
I must apologize for him sorry it's not personal he just enjo
Is observing people now that he's retired from the police force
Nothing she just said that he used to be a cop
Let's get out of here 10 months easy so
I've been thinking I'll bet this is the first real vacation the two of you have taken since your husband retired
Yes you're right my husband was such a workaholic I never truly believe we'd be able to take a big
Put together but here we both are so I'm sorry we're imposing on this time you plan to spend with your wife
We'd be happy to catch another ride if we're being a nuisance here sorry the biggest nuisance has been
Getting lost cuz we can't read directions not to mention the trouble we've been having ordering food it might help
You traveling with us if I need to interpret the bloody language
Well what should we do now de
There's nothing we can do I'm afraid
Except find a gas station and bring some back
Look here comes the truck
Hey stop hey over here
What's wrong
We're out of gas
That's kind of a problem out here in the middle of No Man's Land huh
Well I've got room for two of you in my cab
Is that okay somebody should take the trip up on his offer
Don't worry about us we'll be all right we'll work something out
Listen as soon as I see a gas station I'll get them to send somebody out here with a can of gas for you
Thank you that would be most helpful and we really appreciate it
This is great thank goodness right then everything worked out perfectly
How long do you think it will be before we come to a gas station
Don't remember there being any around
He's been quite a while now
Indeed it has my dear
With that nice young man let them know that we're stranded out here on the motorway
The petrol station will send someone out won't they
There is another possibility
He might just have left us and forgotten about us
I don't believe it
He's not that kind of person
He struck me as a very caring man
Maybe not
What a beautiful scar
I'm not really in the mood to enjoy a sunset tonight
See one you've seen them all
I will not talking about the sunset
The sun's already disappeared
But just look at the lovely pastel colors the sun has left behind
It's like a watercolor painting in the sky
I wonder if Roberts watching it now
We be seeing it together
My goodness
I think it is do you better take a look my ass might be deceiving me
Someone's coming this way
It's getting bright and closer
It must be him I just knew it
Couldn't find
Gas station
I borrowed the gas and a lamp from a farmer
See I told you
Oh that was a delicious meal wasn't it dear
Thanks to your excellent translation of the German menu we were actually able to order something we could enjoy tonight
Especially that one
Oh it was forcedur
It's from the palatnet region
That liver dish was just scrumptious
The liver canoodle
That Cyrus pronounced
Melted in my mouth
If you hadn't been with us we had passed all these wonderful places without a clue as to what we were missing
I want to thank you for treating us to dinner
You're almost finished
Would you like some more to take with you
Thanks but if he has any more he'll burst
Do you think this plug looks like a criminal
For this chapter these are the trial for murdering his wife and there's a big picture of him in the paper see for yourself
What's your opinion
Do you think you did
Well who can tell really before I retired from the full so I was a detective with
Watch a long list of criminals that I put on
Oh come on dear we're enjoying the evening it's really not appropriate to brag about all your past exploits
Well
I would look at a person's face and I'd know if he'd done the crime
I possessed an uncanny neck for spotting the guilt that a person tries to hide
I see
Let's talk about something else now de
I think you've had a little too much wine
However
After years on the job I couldn't tell anymore
Was one person good and another bad
Was he guilty or innoc
I couldn't Spot the Difference that it won't seem so clear
I probably means I wasn't such a hot shot detective after all
Enough said
Maybe I did have a little too much to drink
Tell me once more
What was the name of that wine
It was fosterone
Excellent bouquet
How cute they each
A friend
When this trip is over Dieter and you move to a new place I hope you make lots of friends
Oh
Sure that'd be great
Everyone should have a happy childhood
They should enjoy every minute
It goes by so fast
Yes
Sorry
Should be somewhere right around here what are you looking for
Is the address dear
Almost there
Sorry but we have to make a stop before continuing that's fine
Oh here we are
The police
We won't be very dumb if you don't mind
Might as well wait in the car
What should we do tema
Let's run away
What's wrong someone's parked in one of the officers only spaces again he looks foreign guess I should
Nah don't worry about it
What are we going to do
Mr Jones we want to get to freiheim
I don't know if you're aware of it but you're heading in the opposite direction
It's a brief teacher I want to stop at Steinbach castle for a bit but dear
Stand by Castle or something I want to see for myself
How are you doing are you all right
Oh thank you
My son wrote us a letter about Steinbeck
He said the view from this Castle is truly breathtaking
He wanted to bring us here so we could both see it
Oh does your son live in Germany now
We're on our way to see
It's just that we have a few details to make along the way
This is the view he sold on that fightful day
My
I am flashing blood killed a
We came to this country to visit him because he'll never leave
Well we'll be okay from here
Thank you so much for everything thank you
For your kindness and the pleasure of your company
Chariot
Look after yourself
Such a nice young
Yes isn't he it's hard to believe that he's wanted is the Prime Suspect
A series of murders you must be mistaken no I'm
Not it's him he's on The Wanted suspects list I'm afraid so and when
You're at the station to speak to the detective arrested Robert 10 was photo was prominently posted on the wall
Unbelievable
There's so much good in him
I know
I thought so too and yet everyone seems convinced that he's guilty but my instincts keep
Telling me
He's an innocent man
A good amount why is the bad I'm sure of it
It was unbelievable to think the rubber that committed murder but he
And the fact that I couldn't sense what was going on with my own son made me realize it was time for me to turn in my bad
But you know something dear I just want to be able to trust my instincts again
Robert may have committed to try and true but I know he's a good boy at heart
Come on let's go in and see our son
Oh dear Robert