Hey honey can I trust you in this Moscow mule
Oh thank you Michael my pleasure
And for you A big glass of juice on the rocks
Come on Fred's now be polite and thank your father
Thanks Mr Mueller
Stop it Fritz
Leaving B Barbara
Mom wasn't built in a day you know
It's the same deal with my new antique business rough start then smooth sailing
Well for me everything is really happened so quickly
I suddenly get to live in this gorgeous house
And I have a wonderful and caring husband
Who makes me great cocktails
Hey honey
Did you see something just then
There in the window
I get this feeling sometimes
Like we're being watched
What honey that house has been empty for a while
Yeah I know
It's OD
Actually
I talked to Mrs Daughtry from across the street
What about
She said
The 20 years ago
A couple was brutally murdered in that house
Anyone who moves in never stays for long they say the place is haunted
Michael dear what's the matter
Wait a minute now don't tell me that you believe in ghosts too do you darling
Of course not what do you take me for
Are you going out sir
Yeah
I'll get the car
Not this time
I thought it might be a nice change of pace to go out just the three of us
Don't worry no one's going to try anything
I get it
Unless I'm mistaken you're wanting a little father son time with the boy
You're a smart Buddy Guy you know that
Best of luck to you Daddy
Have a good time
All right off we go
So Detective
Why don't you dig up
Regarding Dr Tenma
Everything checked out exactly as you told me
He's the main suspect in the murder of the Fortuner couple but the police have no idea where he is at the moment
Here's a transcript of 10 statement
He made it back during that first questioning
He operated on a boy at Eisler Memorial Hospital 10 years ago
Saved his life
Kid went on to kill the hospital director and two other doctors
The boy's name was Johan
He was already a young man the next time 10 men encountered him turns out Johann executed a patient in his care
Next up Nina Fortuner
She was the murdered couples foster daughter
No one seen her since the night they were killed either
Messner was a tougher nut to crack
But I did finally track him down in Frankfurt
Well
What did you find
The grave with his name on it
Turns out he was stabbed to death about 2 months ago
The official police version is that he was on the wrong side of a drug deal gone bad
Back when I was a detective on the
Force Messner was my partner
Sorry for your Los
They caught Messner with confiscated narcotics and booted him off the force
After that he got some help from a man called the baby
Bring any bells
He's the spokesman for some nationalist group in Frank
How is this relevant
You remember hearing those news reports about how it's Turkish quarter almost burned down last winter right
Word on the street is the whole thing was the babies brainchild
And the Turks credit an Asian stranger with having saved their neighborhood
Turns out that stranger's name was Tenma
What are the odds
I'm thinking it was the doctor
And what's more people are saying the baby had those fires set to commemorate the introduction of a new leader into their
Some Wonder can they were all really excited about he was going to change everything
Who is this guy
I've already told you
What was the name of that boy Dr Tana saved a decade ago
Johan
Well that young man who was supposed to take the reins of the babies organization in Frankfort
He was your hun too
You should have seen that one coming
Call me crazy Robert
But I feel like one of the ponds on this chess
Waiting for the
Goodness
What's going you looking so pensive all of a sudden thinking about the past
Everything was going straight to hell for me at the time
But after that phone call it change was like night and day
Back then my partner Messner and I were selling drugs
Whatever we confiscated off of the dealers we busted
The voice in the other end knew everything
He said it would be our little secret
If we did him a favor kill some couple in Heidelberg
The fortuners
And I didn't know him from Adam
But there was another guy there that night a newspaper reporter or
We killed all three of them
No choice
After that somebody wired money to the both of us when I left the police force The Syndicate was waiting
With a great offer
They gave me a plum job and the pay was top-notch
I had everything I wanted out of life or so I thought that's when you met your wife and decided to go straight or
So I would wager yeah but I still can't figure out why they let me just walk away
Who was it
Who called me that day
I got to know who transferred all that money over to us who the hell is manipulating my life oh
Damn it
Robert
I want to be sure that you know
I really appreciate your help
Well if that's how you feel
Take back that last move
Sorry my friend no can do
Ouch now you're being harsh
All right honey we're leaving
Okay
Have fun you guys
Lots of them maybe but first say goodbye to your father Fritz
We even be honey
He's got toys on the
Bye-bye Daddy
Roberto
Were there any calls from the detective
He should have come by now
Roberto
Roberto get up here listen to detective oh God he's
But
Yes I'm the daughter of the foreigners the couple you murdered
You shot him in Cold Blood
I was watching from next door
Your bodyguard's the one who killed him
Roberto that's right
I saw it all through the window no he couldn't have
I know Roberto I trust that man with my life
You murdered him
You came here for revenge and he got in the way right
Damn you
Roberto
Help me
I'm taking this bag
Stay here run for it I don't give a damn just don't be surprised if you're the next person who dies here you bastard
Was that you shouting just now Mr Mueller
Is everything all right
Start this car right now move it
You've been watching me all this time from the house next
Store real isn't that right so what happens to me now
Give me one good reason not to shoot you but he knew we had to do whatever
Said if we didn't kill your folks like he asked he was going to tell the cops about the drugs we were selling
On the side don't you get it we had to do it we didn't
Have any other choice
You didn't have any other choice
Stop the car
Stop the car God damn it
My parents were wonderful people
The kindest couple I'll ever know
Mom and dad love me
You love me with all their heart and soul
Please don't do this it didn't even matter to them that I wasn't there real daughter
They love me all the same
My mom and dad were angels
They were Angels I'm sorry please don't shoot Angel and
Like you
Barbara
You're crying for your family
What about mine
So this is what it feels like
Right before somebody kills you
Fritz
He called me Daddy today
For the first time don't take that from me please please let me live
I finally found someone worth living for Barbara
Impressed
I met them at half past 8:00 in the morning
At a cafe in Dussel
I quit the force and joined the syndicate
My boss told me to act like a businessman
Made for a nice cover
Every morning this woman and her little boy would walk by
They were my daily reminder
The regular
Honest life I've given up
Hey so how you doing
I'm fine thanks for asking
Tell me something what did you hire that detective for
I was hoping he could find you in 10
And my former partner
I wanted to know what he was up to
Messenger's dead
Whatever it's worth
Stabbed to death
When I heard about that I asked the detective to find out more information
Last night I got a phone call from him
I've been digging around
It's strange what do you mean strange
From Dusseldorf I'll give you all the details when I see you in person
Here it is
The draft of the report
Messner's killer
Robert
Look at this
Do you know what this means
Yes hello
Hey boss
I need that bag
Roberto
Your
Some Fritz are already home
What are you saying
If you hurt them I might be hurrying right back
A lot of accidents happen at home
Give me a gun
Look there's something I got
Remember
That model is intended for close range work
Only got four shots so make them count don't worry about me
I was an officer Once Upon a Time
Can have me dying before you take me to the police and have me confess to killing your parents
That's right so don't even think of dying on me
I'll cover you from the empty house next door good luck
Hi Daddy
I had to go fishing with his daddy
Barbara thank God
Where's your bear now
Oh that reminds me
The gentleman from his security team are here
He said something happened while we were out
Team
There's no need to worry he said everything's fine and no one was hurt
Oh Roberto look Michaels come home
Everything's all right
It was nothing important just a broken window
Probably just a kid from the neighborhood
Nothing to worry about
Nothing at all
Where's the body what have you done with him damn it a body what are you
Talking about what's going on Roberto who the hell are you
Fritz and the little wifey are heading inside don't be stupid hand over the bag
Now there you go
All right gentlemen nothing ever happened here understood just another boring day in paradise right
Like yesterday and tomorrow
Nina
She is such a beautiful girl but
What did you do to her don't look at me like that Nina's Fine my employer considers her a
Important cast your employer well that young man he was Yohan too
Johan Johan Johan everywhere I look Yohan is there who the hell is he who the
What the hell are you talk you want to live happily ever after with Barber and Fritz don't you come back to your
Fairy Tail trust me leave it alone as an employers go you weren't
Too bad but this is where we say goodbye
What are you going to do with Nina he's going to die
You take care now
Hey Daddy can you make a fishing sometime soon
Oh yeah
If it's sunny
How about tomorrow
It's over
I don't see ghosts anymore
You have very nice eyes
You're definitely Johan sister
I let you take me in without a fight because you promised I'd get to see him
I did indeed
He's really looking forward to catching up with you right now if you must know he's living Happ
Probably in Munich
You know you really have very nice eyes Such a Pity I just
Bring myself to do it
What's next
Ah yes Dr Tina
But why
Why did you come
It's like I told you
For Better or For Worse
I did used to be a cop
Don't worry you're almost home I know
I told Fritz that we'd go fishing tomorrow I promised
Good I hope it's sunny
I'm sure
It will
Excuse me sir sir just a couple of questions please stay there stay right there
Interfering with a crime scene can you please tell us what the police are thinking what are your views on this situation
No matter how you look at it it's obvious this incident is exactly like the other cases of murdered middle-aged couples across Germany
No comment at this time
I've heard that the bka is sending an agent to look into this is that true
Does that mean there's a connection to the serial murders
No comment oh man
I think I have better luck talking to a bka suit directly than trying to get this guy to give me anything
Just trust me all right
I promise you will be the first ones with the story just make sure you leave plenty of space on the front page
Just dude I got to go
Excuse me sir
My name is Kipper I'm with the Hamburg dog
You've been sent here by the bka to investigate this murder
Correct me if I'm wrong
I was wondering
Is this case somehow connected to the others here real murders well Kipper of the Hamburg to
You're right on both counts
Get your pen ready
Because here's my statement
A middle-aged couple was murdered and it appears to be another serial slaying
I knew it
And it's a suspect that Japanese doctor
Yes I just saw the report
It's his Mo the murders were carried out the same way
Thank you for the sco
Got to run oh one more thing
I'm aware the Hamburg talk is a leading local newspaper
But I expect you to make sure your story gets published in every major newspaper in the country as well
Hey consider it done thanks again for all your help friend
I have become the Killer
I think to myself as I approach
What's the best way to get into their house
Should I knock
I don't want to startle the Yoke pays by walking in on them
Such a friendly
They greet me
And show me to the living room
These folks aren't the least bit suspicious as they Lead Me In
The husband's chair naturally I sit on the sofa facing him
A few minutes later the husband will die on the floor
There but I haven't made that movie yet
So I have to decide when to eliminate him
I'll do it when the wife leaves a room where did she go to the kitchen to
Tea she is stabbed in the back before she even has a chance to serve it obviously
Play that I need to make my move on the husband while she's occupied in the kitchen I reach in pull out
The knife the husband sees this panics tries to stand up by stab him but I miss and end up
The husband runs off with blood dripping from his wounded left hand so I try to get him again
Swing the night this time I only puncture his right shoulder I'm such a clumsy amateur desperately the
Husband yells his wife's name only she can't hear him from out in the kitchen recently she's developed a
Turns out I knew about that didn't I go on shout all you want I
My time to kill you and then your wife you're trapped there's your left handprint on the wall
You can't get away from me I've got you pinned against this table you're finished
But then
Something prevents me from completing the task
5 m from this point where the husband dies
How come why not just eliminate them here and be done with it
My weight
I've never seen him
Murdered my neighbors
For the moment I can only say he's a person of interest but I'm asking everybody in the neighborhood for their cooperation in this
If you see this man just act normal I don't want him to become suspicious
Then get in touch with me as soon as you possibly can
That would be all I need for you to do
I personally assure you you won't be in any danger
Hard to imagine such a tragic event like this happening here it's such a pleasant quiet neighborhood
It really is
Any old pays for such nice people just the best
When I call out to her from my doorstep Mrs yopay would always greet me cheerfully
That's very interesting
I've been told Mrs yopé lost her hearing about a year ago and refused to hearing aid
Huh are you sure
It was in her medical record
If I had to guess
She really couldn't hear any of your greetings
Well knowing the type of person she was she probably sensed my presence and wanted to make me feel good
So then in your opinion nobody else in the neighborhood knew about her hearing loss either
No I wouldn't think so
It certainly appears that your business is booming
You made rapid progress at an early age
It's not easy for a young man to achieve such quick success Mr
You're right
The contracts I made with the car manufacturers just happened to work out
Before we begin I'd like to extend my deepest condolences for the recent loss of your aunt and uncle
Thank you
They're passing was a great loss they were the only relatives I had left in the world
It appears they never had any children of Their Own
So they must have taken good care of you since you were there only nephew
Yes
They treated me as if I were their son
Sir tell me you'll be able to catch the murderer
I will I'm pretty sure I know who's behind it me too I bet it was that Japanese doctor wasn't it sounds like
Very well informed
Well of course I am
As a matter of fact I've heard he's been linked to other murders similar to this
I'm curious
Just how much do you stand to inherit
You see
I found out that Mr yopay was quite a wealthy man
So what
His wealth has nothing to do with the serial murder case
Sir I presume you are the sole heir to their considerable estate
Seeing as how you are they're only nephew
It's inappropriate to be discussing my inheritance in these circumstances
A company can appear to be booming on the surface but underneath may have serious cash flow problems that have gotten out
Of hand it's a common occurrence in the business world
Just a minute you're implying I murdered them when there's a serial killer on the loose how dare you
What are you so worried about you have a perfect Alibi for the time in question
And you have plenty of witnesses you bought your secretary and some others a nice dinner after a long meeting
What exactly are you getting at
That it appears that you could not be the murderer
I'm sure you agree
Inspector Lungi well
What do you want Kipper what the hell is going on
Going on with what
Don't play dumb inspector
I've been out digging up stuff on that nephew for the last couple days
His company looks profitable at first glance but turns out to be holding a lot of bad stocks and bonds Cash Wise it's in the world of hurt
And now
I found out you've been investigating the same company
I want the truth
Who killed those folks Looney
In light of what you've uncovered do you still think this case is related to the other middle-aged murders
All of the newspapers have printed A variation of my story if the cases aren't related then it's just Sensational journalism
My reputation could be damaged
Your instincts are correct
It's the work of a copycat it was set up to look like the serial killer
That's just great I've got to publish retraction right away no it's fine as it is
Huh you'll continue writing your follow-up stories as if this case where another one of the middle-aged couple murders
It's not ethical no way I won't do it I tell you oh but you will I'm an honest journalist who believes
Reporting the whole truth and you're not going to tell me what I can write well let me give you the truth we have good tast
Really she's quite lovely you have a pleasant home with a devoted wife
Daughter who both adore you but it was impossible for you to resist the charms of that attractive other
Wasn't it
Continuous before no beef it up a little
Write a special report about the serial murders if you do as I've asked
He'll most certainly come I'm counting on you
Yes who is it
Excuse me ma'am may I ask you some questions
Well
Sounds like the your pace we're really a wonderful couple
They were
I see
And you're absolutely certain they didn't have any adopted children
Did any children children that you never seen before live with them even for a short time
No never
But they took very good care of their nephew he was the apple of their eye
Would you like more tea it won't take a minute
I'm fine
A little more tea won't hurt you
There's no mistaking
Nothing to worry about
Thanks for your cooperation
Inspect a long day someone's here to see you
Well who is it
He says he's the nephew of the L
That couple that was killed
Inspector you believe I'm the one who murdered them
I'm your suspect right
You think I killed my aunt and uncle for their money
That's what you hinted at the other day
Let's face it we both know that I have many debts right now
And the inheritance money they ended up leaving me will more than likely get me out of this whole mess
However that's not the kind of person I am
Is that really all you came here to tell me
All I came here
Wait a minute how dare you speak to me in such a condescending way
Well if you'll excuse me there's somewhere I have to be right at the moment
Don't you walk away I demand an apology for your disrespectful Behavior
Perhaps you weren't aware that the police had been following you well now that order has been canceled
Your local law enforcement thinks that you're innocent
Isn't that good enough for you Mr geebel
You want to know if I think you are guilty
That really doesn't matter to me at the moment
My chief concern is to catch the man I've been after
The blood stain over there can only mean one thing
He must have missed then am I to assume that you're convinced the
Never assume anything I've concluded it
Copycat murder made to look like the middle-aged couples homicides but how can you be so certain about that
Because there's one element this case has it makes it different from all the others
The killer Corner the victim here but he doesn't finish him off
He waits till his victim gets over there before delivering the final blow but why why
It's not him
That element
Is emotion
Emotion
Yes you see the man I'm after always take small valuables
He tries to make his crimes look like robberies
He murders quickly without hesitation or emotion
At least that's his goal
But this crime scene is full of emotions the killer panicked when he saw his face
Victims face together in the mirror
You needn't worry
From what I've observed the police in this town are totally incompet
This crime was definitely not committed by Johann
But somebody wants the police
Depended on him
How much longer is this all going to continue
When will it end
Hello it's been a while
So we finally meet again doctor Tenma
I've been looking all over for you
For a very long time I've been hoping to have a quiet chat with you
There's no use in
Away anymore stop trying to escape and talk to me period that is
No place you can hide Dr Tenna
Yes you're all mine
That's so hard couldn't you just leave it alone
Profession
Nothing to me just stay out of my way
Come on
He's been seriously wounded
I've got to do something now or he's going to bleed to death
Who could have stop
I'll drop him off in front of the hospital and get away
How are
I need the keys to the handcuffs tell me where you put them inspector
Don't bother reaching for your gun
I took it off you while you were unconscious
Don't be so stubborn just give me the keys I'm a doctor but I can't help you like this
How you examined your wound the best I could
It appears that only your muscles sustain the damage
But you're losing an awful lot of blood if we don't stop the bleeding you're going to die
Come on confess
Do it Dr Tim
Best to what
That you murdered the director of Isler Memorial Hospital along with three others
And that you've been on a 3-year Killing Spree targeting middle-aged couples
It's time to come clean and admit what
Done
If you keep this up you'll be a Deadman
Come on
Don't try to fool me
You're only fooling yourself by running around chasing this elusive Johan
Johan doesn't exist
Admit it you made him up
You're a Yohan
Own up to it
Inspector right now you require emergency treatment I have everything I need to do the procedure
Except for my hands and I can't save your life when I'm chained together yes
When you're the
Dr Tema those are the hands of a highly skilled surgeon was saved many lives
But how many people have you killed with those hands
You've got it wrong I'm not a killer
No but you change into Johan
When does the good doctor
Turn into the bad monster
I already told you he mistaken
Let me tell you
I never make mistakes
Your blood pressure is falling you're going to lose Consciousness soon
Your CR
Always
No more talking it'll weaken you
Your crime scenes are always lacking in something
An emotional Factor
Save your strength
Dealing with
Day forces doctors to check
Right doctor t
You develop a cold exterior
That coldness I always find it's your crime SC
Cold
Emotionless taking of life
I am not that kind of man
Every time I operate a thousand emotions go through my head
I affect my every decision
Has my diagnosis accurate
Will there be any unforeseen complications
Well my patient even survive
How can I become when I hold a person's life in my hands
How in the hell can I become
Closer
Stop I can save you
I will shoot I need my hands to stop the bleeding are the keys in your pants pocket tell me
I will
You really had us worried for a while
But you're looking quite well
Lots better than when you're running around investigating crimes
I guess this means you're not rid of me yet
Yeah you'll be back on your feet in no time
That emergency procedure you received before you got here was done perfectly
Your doctor said you wouldn't be alive without it
I'm assuming that
Got his hands-free and used them to save my life
Yeah well he got away but we got Gmail
He confessed a murdering the you'll pick couple
He stabbed you because you were on to him
You did good Lungi
Thank you
Well
What do you think
About what
It's quite clear that 10 must save Luna's life
So I'm worried Lungi might have a problem pursuing him now
I'm wondering if I should remove them from the 10la case
I'm sorry did he call for you again inspector loon get can be very demanding
Oh he really isn't that difficult at all in fact I find him to be very pleasant
I keep telling him not to rush through the recovery process but he's quite determined
He's already working on strengthening his grip and he's taking long walks down the hall
He seems to be having a really fun time recovering fun
Yes he's always telling me that nothing has been more enjoyable for him than what was the suspect
What's the name again oh yes the most
It's funny you could ever have