Dr. Tenma, it wasn't your fault.
You just did what you had to do as a doctor...
It wasn't your fault.
Please eat the sandwiches
and get some rest.
I want you to survive,
and save as many people as you can.
Nina Fortner.
Nina... What do you intend to do?
Do you intend to try to kill him again?!
I brought him back to life...
I...
brought that monster
back to life...
This arteriovenous malformation contains many blood vessels...
Cut away all of the inflowing arteries!
Treat all of the outflowing veins.
The removal of the nidus is complete.
Well... that certainly went well.
Yes. He did the clipping
very quickly, as usual.
That was a magnificent operation.
It was his first surgery after
an extended leave,
but the talent of this genius
keeps growing...
It's over...
Huh?!
It's nothing...
Pursued
That was wonderful, Kenzo.
That wasn't news about me,
but about your father.
That's true...
But that's because you did such a perfect job last night, as part of Father's team.
I'm sure Father is grateful to you.
After all, you're the one who has
raised the fame of the hospital.
I'm the one who is grateful.
It's thanks to your father that
I am able to work here in Germany.
Hang in there, Kenzo.
If you stick with Father,
your future is guaranteed.
It won't be long before Father
becomes Chairman of the hospital.
Then you'll quickly become
Chief of Surgery,
and in time, Hospital Director...
And then, I will be the Director's wife!
You must make me happy, now.
Hardships do not become me.
You want to go out on a date?
Or...
I-I'm afraid you cannot...
The mistress is resting...
I won't take much of her time.
I will leave very shortly.
B-But, please return again
after making an appointment.
What's all that noise?
Oh, I'm terribly sorry, Ma'am.
It's the police...
Police?
It's good to see you again,
Miss Eva Heinemann.
Who are you?
I thank you for the help you gave me
on your father's case, nine years ago.
I'm Lunge of the Federal Police.
Lunge...
You may leave us, Horst.
Yes, ma'am.
I remember you now.
You were just a useless detective
who couldn't even close that case.
What do you want with me now?
You've been able to maintain this residence
even after your father's death.
I am impressed.
No, I do believe all of the furnishing
is even grander than it was before.
Have you come to see how wealthy
I've become with
my inheritance from my father
and settlements from my divorces?
As you can see, I lack nothing.
If you see anything you want
please help yourself to it.
I'm fine, as long as I have my liquor.
Today... I would like you to have a look at something...
This necktie...
Necktie?
Have you seen it before?
Perhaps you don't remember...
It's something from nine years ago.
It's a simple print,
but if you look at it carefully, it's a wonderful piece with a complex weave.
What about it?
This really gave me a hard time.
After all, it's been nine years...
But luckily, this comes from a shop
that had a limited number of these
made for their best customers.
And on their list...
I found your name...
As I said, what about it?
Didn't you purchase this
and give it to someone?
This plays a key role
in another murder, you see...
Murder?
Who knows?
I've given countless gifts to men,
so I can't remember them all.
The men who approach me
are all after my money...
Please think carefully.
I said I don't remember!
They're all after my money!
There isn't a single person
who truly loves me...
That's why I took each one
to the cleaners with each divorce.
All three of them.
Good for them!
Do you want something too?
You want something? Tell me!
Just remember it'll cost you!
I'll come again.
If you remember anything,
please give me a call.
Next time you come,
be sure to bring a bottle of liquor.
Excuse me.
Eva...
Eva, won't you talk to
your father for me?
I haven't done anything wrong!
I just operated on an emergency case in the order in which he was brought in!
That's... your engagement ring.
You're such a fool.
Huh?
Eva!
Why, Dr. Norden,
don't you look elegant?
As do you!
You're more beautiful than ever tonight, Eva.
Horst, have my car readied!
Well, Mr. Hess, you seem to be much better.
Your color is good.
I think you'll be able to go home
sometime this week.
Thank you very much, Dr. Tenma.
My daughter is getting married next month.
Will I be able to attend her wedding?
Yes, that should be fine.
Just don't overdo it at the reception.
Thank you. I had resigned myself to not going,
but thanks to you, Dr. Tenma...
It was due to your own efforts.
With you at my side,
I feel as though I can be there,
not only at my daughter's,
but at my grand children's weddings, too.
You are truly an excellent doctor.
Please stay here at this hospital.
Uh, Dr. Tenma... You have a visitor.
I must make my rounds now.
I'm too busy. Please turn them away.
B-But...
Eva...
It's been a while, Kenzo...
Yeah...
We've gone through so much,
haven't we?
Father... Are you asleep?
I'm coming in.
Father!
Eva...
Eva!
I know it's hard, but you must
pull yourself together...
Let go of me!
Give me back my father!
Father!
Kenzo!
Please, I was wrong.
Kenzo...
Kenzo!
You've lost some weight, haven't you?
Not really...
I hear you were on extended leave.
Yes, you should rest yourself
from time to time.
You're such a glutton for work...
You've lost some weight too,
haven't you?
So much has happened...
You've heard the rumors,
haven't you?
Yeah...
Spring... Do you remember?
Ten years ago, in spring...
We often went driving together...
We were so young.
You tried to swim in the river
in that season...
I hurriedly stopped you...
And then you...
I'm sorry, but...
Eva, I haven't got time...
Kenzo?
I want us to start over!
After three failed marriages,
I finally realized...
the only one who truly loved me
was you, Kenzo.
I'm sorry.
Kenzo!
Please, Kenzo!
I appreciate your feelings,
but I just can't accept them...
Good-bye.
Wait, Kenzo! I didn't say a word!
When the police came
to ask about your necktie!
Isn't there something bad
connected with that necktie of yours?
I'm sure that's the tie that I gave you.
If you do as I say,
I'll keep quiet about it!
I have something I must do.
In that case, I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell the police about that necktie!
I'll tell them everything!
The person who killed my father
nine years ago...
I'll tell them you did it!
I see... Bring Dr. Tenma in
as a person of interest.
B-But there isn't enough evidence in the Fortner couple and Maurer murders.
I'm talking about
the killing at Heidelberg Castle.
Y-Yes, sir!
Thank you for your cooperation.
This might allow us
to solve a lot of murders.
Resignation?
What is the meaning of this,
Dr. Tenma?
I'm sorry if I'm acting selfishly, sir...
There seem to be various
strange rumors about you, recently,
but I don't believe any of them.
Please think this over...
Oh... T-Tenma!?
Dr. Tenma!
Yes! I'm me...
What?! The police?!
Dr. Tenma is a murder suspect?!
Close off the exits from each wing!
Don't forget the back exits!
Yes, sir!
Where is Dr. Tenma?!
I-I don't know!
What's going on there?
Hurry up and search the place!
Oh, but Inspector...
What is it?
Get out of the way!
You're interfering with the police!
Dr. Tenma would never kill anyone!
That's right!
We're indebted to him
for saving our lives!
Dr. Tenma is innocent!
Go away, police!
That's right, go away!
Go away! Go away!
Something seems to be going on.
There's a whole bunch
of patrol cars, Dr. Tenma.
I-I see... I wonder what's going on...
Anyway, just drop me off
in front of the station.
Yes, sir.
You're busy as always,
aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
I... I have a surgery waiting for me.
Wait! Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
Don't worry.
Hang in there!
I'll save you...
I am not wrong!
You say there's
a flaw in my character?
What about you?!
You call yourself a doctor,
but you're just money hungry!
That bastard... That bastard...
He's better off dead...
Oh, no!
The twins are nowhere to be found!
W-What is this?
What in the world happened?
Long time no see, Doctor.
It's me.
Have you already forgotten
about those twins?
Johan!
Save me, Doctor... I don't want to die!
Doctor!
I was supposed to have died that day.
You brought me back to life.
Five Months Later
It looks like another scorcher today.
Hey, it's summer, yet you're all
bundled up. Aren't you hot?
What's that?
That paper's three days old.
They say this time a middle-aged couple
in Verden was killed.
I hear the killer is a doctor.
Oh, yeah... You said you're going
to Verden, didn't you?
You know someone there?
Yeah...
I don't know if I can meet up with him or not, but...
I have to go there...
And slowly, you come to realize
It's all as it should be
You can only do so much
If you're game enough
You could place your trust in me
For the love of life
There's a trade off
We could lose it all
But we'll go down fighting
The Girl and the Seasoned Soldier