Munich
(Germany)
Thank you very much. We look
forward to your cooperation.
No... We should be thanking you.
I would really enjoy a round of
golf with you guys next time.
No, no, if that happens, please go easy on us.
We look forward to your cooperation.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you.
"Thank you," huh?
Words lose their meaning when they use them.
Ah, hello, hello.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Our business talk went on longer than we expected.
I'm Iwai, from the Munich branch of
the Kadofuku Commercial Company.
I'm Lunge, from the BKA.
Please, do take one of these...
Thank you.
A thank you and a bow...
You're even more polite than me.
One coffee,
and another one for him also.
About that person, Yamamoto,
that the police wanted to see...
He's currently on a business trip to the Czech Republic.
He is scheduled to return tomorrow.
He seems to be very busy.
Do you know Mr. Schubert of the great financial combine?
Ever since he came out of retirement
and resumed his economic activities,
all of the industries in Germany that he worked with and
other affiliated companies are paying attention to him.
All of the Japanese firms are getting
involved with Mr. Schubert as well.
Why does he laugh?
Anyways, Yamamoto cannot help you today, but...
He and I both know Mr. Kenzo Tenma equally well.
I see.
But I am really surprised
that you guys are still investigating him.
Yes, because we haven't solved the case yet.
I was really surprised when
Mr. Tenma was marked as a suspect!
You were surprised?
Was it that unexpected?
It was beyond any expectation.
To think that he killed someone...
To tell you the truth, I didn't think
he could do such a thing.
Although we only went out drinking
about twice three years ago...
He was not a bad person.
If you say that he was not a bad person,
does that make him a good person?
A good person...
He was more of the type of person
who didn't like to stand out.
So a person who doesn't like to stand out is a good person.
Well, all I'm saying is that he wasn't an unpleasant person.
My Nameless Hero
Japanese people don't usually wear these things.
Japanese people use chopsticks skillfully.
I am Japanese.
Thank you.
I am...
Tenma.
Ah, Father?
Hi.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I called you because I heard that you were in Munich.
I'm living here now.
The thing is, Father...
I gave birth to a healthy child...
I see...
Congratulations.
Even though we've been through a lot,
I'd still like you to see your grandson.
Will you come see him?
Of course.
Then, is tomorrow okay?
Yes, I should be free after 6 PM.
Where shall we meet?
Yes...
The Marienplatz.
Yes, I got it.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Wow, you're pretty skillful with chopsticks.
You think so?
Although lately, there are many foreigners who
use chopsticks better than Japanese people.
So, Dr. Takahashi...
From the perspective of someone who had the
same job, what kind of person was Tenma?
What kind, eh?
Hm... let's see...
He wasn't too anti-social...
though he was indecisive at times...
Except...
Except?
He turned into a completely different
person when he held a scalpel.
Although everyone called him a genius neurosurgeon,
it really wasn't an exaggeration.
What about his parents?
He never really talked about them.
He did say that both his father and
older brother were doctors...
I guess he had no choice but to become one.
Speaking of which...
I heard he didn't return to Japan once
after he became a doctor in Germany.
His parents didn't come to Germany
during that incident either...
and they didn't seem too concerned about
proving their son's innocence.
I guess he wasn't all that close with his family.
I'm terribly sorry.
Yamamoto just contacted me.
He did arrive in Munich from Prague, but...
it seems he has to go to his next
business meeting immediately.
He sounds extremely busy.
He did say he will be joining us later on at
the restaurant that we are heading to now.
The restaurant...?
Oh yes! Why don't you come with us, Inspector Lunge?
This surely must be some sort of fate,
and we don't know when well need your help next so...
I'm sorry, I cannot today.
I guess he wasn't all that close with his family.
I am...
Tenma.
Huh?
That sounds great.
Please let me join you.
Karaoke Bar Oedo
Farewell...
I will be going now...
I've been waiting for this, Iwai-chan.
How about it? Would you like to
sing one too, Inspector Lunge?
Yeah!
Oops, the next song is mine!
Nice!
I've been waiting for this.
Love letter from Canada.
If you were here with me.
Nice! Nice!
That would be a wonderful trip.
I am Tenma.
Love letter from Canada.
I cannot blend into Japanese Society.
I don't ask for their help...
I don't have a place to go home to...
I am...
alone.
Oh! Sorry for being late!
Hey! We've been waiting for you, Yamamoto!
This is Inspector Lunge, the man
I mentioned over the phone.
Oh! Hello.
I'm Yamamoto from the Munich branch of Kadofuku.
Hello.
How were your negotiations with
Mr. Kohou in the Czech Republic?
Oh, he was a tough one.
Oh yes! By the way, I found it!
Found what?
The thing that Mr. Schubert's right-hand
man, that blond-haired boy, asked of us.
Oh? You found it?
Because getting on that secretary's good side now,
is the best way of getting Mr. Schubert
to do business with us.
I had to search a lot of used book stores in Prague,
but I finally found a copy!
Oh? So this is the picture book?
The cover's fallen off, and it's pretty beat up too,
but if we wrap it up nicely, it'll be okay.
Excuse me!
Can I get a beer?
May I?
Oh, go ahead.
Oh, it's in Czech?
All right? The next song is mine!
Nice! Nice!
We've been waiting for this...
for this person.
Nice!
Munich Police
Inspector, what are you looking up in the dictionary?
Czech words.
Czech words?
Does this have anything to do with your investigation?
No, absolutely nothing.
I can't believe you're looking up something
that is unrelated to the investigation...
It's something from a picture book. I liked the picture,
and I wanted to know what it said.
The inspector reading a picture book?
That is certainly rare...
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"The monster within me has gotten this big!"
I see...
So Johan has finally gotten around
to manipulating that big company?
For a while now, I've been hearing a lot of stories
about Johan from you, Dr. Gillen, but...
seriously, that Johan is quite a monster.
A monster?
Yeah.
I, myself, have killed many people, but...
he's become something that I wanted to be, but couldn't.
Man, Johan is my hero.
I see.
There is something else I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
If you were Johan, what would you do next?
Do next?
Well, that's obvious!
Kill his current parents, the Lieberts.
Mr. Liebert?
Why would you do that?
Why?
Because I would be bored of them.
Mr. Liebert? Mr. Liebert?!
Mr. Liebert!
Yes, who is it?
A psychologist?
And what business do you have with us, Dr. Reichwine?
I have no intention of telling you the entire story.
Johan? Adopted?
What are you talking about?
He's our real son and...
Playing dumb is useless.
The grave of your real son lies in Bruntal.
You took advantage of the town hall's files being burned,
and turned in a birth certificate
to resurrect your dead child.
Who are you?
It wasn't my intent to come here and threaten you.
I came here for your sake.
I want you to read this.
It's a report of information we collected on Johan.
On Johan?
A certain man investigated all of this.
This man is...
He came by here before trying to sell us insurance.
He was Richard Brown, an ex-detective.
An ex-detective?
He... passed away.
Now please, read it.
The story begins in 1986...
when a high official of East Germany
defected to West Germany.
Is his goal money?
Money?
He holds no interest in money.
Then why has he gotten close to a wealthy man?
You did it when you were small too, didn't you?
Did what?
Taking an ant line like this...
and to that ant line...
you mess it up like this.
No way...
I cannot believe such a frightening story.
How can such a crazy story...?
I understand your disbelief of the story.
You lost your son at an early age.
After that, even though you were
not blessed with another child...
A young boy about the same age
as your dead son appeared.
On top of that, he had money.
He gave you a wonderful house.
He gave you a beautiful garden.
And then... he gave you love.
I understand very well that you want to believe him.
However, what's written here is the truth!
What kind of man is this Johan?
Just who is he?
Johan... is a good boy.
Johan is a kind boy.
He is very smart...
and outgoing.
He's...
our reason for living.
Is that all?
You have had a parent-child relationship
for nearly five years,
and that's all you can say?
You don't know anything about him.
Please, help me.
Because of him, my friend, Richard, is dead.
And right now, a man named Dr. Tenma...
is trying to set right what cannot be righted.
Please, help me.
No, more important than that...
You will,
like the middle-aged couples in here,
like those who raised Johan as an adopted son,
be killed.
Let's leave here. Leave with me.
The apple tree has produced some small apples.
Yeah...
Next year, it will produce bigger ones.
I look forward to it.
Yes... I look forward to it too.
You say he's going to be killed by a Japanese man soon?
Johan said that to some children?
Yeah.
What do you think of what he said?
I'll tell you straight out, he doesn't have a death wish.
Then what did he mean?
Who knows?
A hero's thoughts are complicated.
However...
However, I can tell you this much.
Even if the world was wiped out by a nuclear war,
he would still survive.
So he's saying that there's nothing we can do?
It's true that everything we've done
so far has led to nowhere.
I couldn't help Richard either...
Dr. Reichwine...
And we have not found Dr. Tenma either...
We can't even stop him from killing Johan.
Everything has been useless!
Dr. Reichwine, let's calm down and think things through.
I'm sorry...
Mess up an ant line, eh?
Even ants have souls.
Doctor... where are you going?
Now that it has come to this, I have no choice
but to engage in life-risking close combat.
I'll meet him face-to-face and tell him everything.
That big mogul, Schubert.
Huh? Add another fifty chairs?
Man, they keep adding things.
You mean tomorrow's Mr. Schubert's donation ceremony?
Yeah.
People just keep coming one after another
and we've run out of seats.
Nowadays, whenever Mr. Schubert does
something, it becomes a big thing.
The library will be closing soon.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry,
can you get that for me?
That Czech dictionary.
I can't reach it.
Y-Yes. This one?
Ah, sorry for bothering you.
Thank you.
I borrowed a Czech picture book, but I don't understand it.
I see...
My friend suddenly fainted after reading this picture book.
Really?
I thought it might have had something
to do with the picture book's contents.
Is your friend better now?
Yes. Completely.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Let's see...
"Once upon a time, in a land far, far away..."
"There was a monster without a name."
"The monster wanted a name so
badly that he couldn't stand it."
"So then, the monster went on a journey."
What a strange book.
It's closing time.
Okay.
We'll be closed tomorrow because of the ceremony.
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Monster of Chaos