What's going on?
What's wrong?
The books!
They're on fire!
Put out the fire!
Hurry up!
What's going on?
My job was to shoot Schubert.
I see.
So you've changed your mind, Johan.
I like it better this way. It's much better.
They're all running around in circles,
like ants running from a fire.
This is great. It's great, Johan.
It's great.
Take a look at this.
The books... The books are burning!
They're all running around.
They're all scrambling to escape.
Can you feel it?
The fear.
Whether you can shoot first or not
that is where the path diverges.
That determines whether you can use a gun or not.
What have you learned about guns before?
Nothing.
So you're simply a natural then?
No.
I've never shot one.
Not even once?
That's right.
When you fire a gun, always fire twice.
If you fire twice, the probability that you will deliver
the finishing blow increases by 100 times.
If you can't do that,
then it's as if you've just been killed.
I have to shoot.
You can't do it.
You can't shoot anyone.
I have to shoot...
You're just a doctor.
You can only give people life.
Taking someone's life is my job.
You can't do it.
Always shoot twice.
The Demon In My Eyes
He didn't shoot me.
The trembling... has stopped.
Johan.
The smoke's in the way!
Hurry! If I don't then...
I won't let him get away.
Save us.
We can't get out of here.
Open up, please.
Please calm down.
Everyone, please calm down.
Follow the security guards and get in line.
I-It's no good!
The doors are all locked.
What?
Then escort Mr. Schubert.
Yes, sir.
Do you have a safe place prepared for him?
Or do you plan to take Mr. Schubert
through this sea of flames?
Knock the doors down!
Yes, sir.
There are a lot of books burning.
The flames will burn everything.
Is this all you wanted to do?
Are you satisfied using this way to convey
the pictures of hell in the books
that I had you read to me?
So what you wanted wasn't to become like me?
I've decided not to do that.
A different idea popped into my head.
You're not afraid, are you?
Where did you come from?
Who are you?
Can you see me?
Even though your eyes are getting worse and worse,
if I'm this close, you should be able to see me.
Can you see what's reflected in my eyes?
I was born in a town that was straight out of a fairytale.
Many people died.
I held the hand of my other half and walked.
There were only two like us.
We didn't have names.
Lady!
It's you.
Dieter, do you know this woman?
A fire.
Karl, I have a document I want you to get for me.
Go back to the estate and get it.
Is this it?
Mom...
Th-This is...
A Report on the Investigation Concerning
the Death of Margot Langer.
Herflich Detective Services.
Margot Langer.
Real name, Helenka Novakova.
Born August 12, 1955, in Prague, Czechoslovakia.
In 1970, at the age of 15, immigrated
illegally into former West Germany.
As a high-class call girl in Munich,
she had clients from the center of the business and political worlds
and her name was well know among the social elites.
Furthermore, one of her clients was Hans Georg Schubert.
Dad, you were still investigating mom's death.
At the age of 23, she had Schubert's child.
That boy's name was Karl.
Got it, Karl? Listen carefully to what your mom has to say.
Take this money and get on the train on Line 5.
But what about you, Mom?
I told you I can't come with you.
I'll stay with you.
No!
If you stay with me, if you stay here, they'll
keep on calling you the son of a whore.
So hurry.
Dad...
They say dad abandoned me.
He didn't abandoned you...
because I don't hate him.
Mom!
He stayed in a number of foster homes...
and suffered many hardships.
He had some wonderful parents, but he was alone.
Always alone.
Although it's not in this report...
Although she was a high-class
prostitute, she retired in 1992.
There was some information that soon after, she was
involved with the head of the black market bank,
but that has never been confirmed to be true.
Somewhat related to that, the black market bank
has been involved in money laundering for the
German criminal underworld for about
the last five years, since '91.
In other words, they were an organization
that single-handedly monopolized
the process of taking illegal funds from the underworld
and converting it into legal money.
After retiring from being a prostitute, Margot
Langer lived in Offenbach, Hessen.
The picture is of the apartment she stayed in.
She lived with a young man who was around
18, but their relationship was unknown.
November 2, '95, Margot Langer is discovered on Heide St.
According to the police file, the murder was
random and the culprit was never found.
Mom...
Furthermore, three months before Margot Langer's
death, she sent a letter to a friend.
I have a copy of what was written here.
This is my mom's hand-writing.
I quit my job and I'm now living a quiet lifestyle.
The things I think about in my peaceful life are...
the son that I am separated from and my friend who
tried to cross the Czechoslovakian border with me.
My friend was captured at the border
and was taken back to Prague.
Afterwards, she gave birth to twins
and is now living happily.
Yes. Recently I met a young man who's
the same age as the son I left behind.
His face looks exactly like the face of my Czech friend.
Talking to him feels like I'm talking to my son.
He must have been raised to be a fine young man.
He must be living happily somewhere.
That's what I believe.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm not alone anymore.
Dad wanted me to read this letter.
I finally understand what mom meant
when she said she didn't hate him.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm already...
Dammit! All the doors are locked.
Dieter, did you contact the fire department?
I did already!
Damn it!
What's happening inside this library?
Out of the way. Move away from the door.
It's open!
Don't rush. Carefully, one at a time.
Make a line and get out in an orderly fashion.
Women and elderly people first.
Thank you. I don't know how to repay you.
Two more shots left.
Wait. Hey, you!
Johan.
Stop!
Dr. Tenma.
You mustn't shoot!
Nina!
D-Don't, Nina!
Don't do it!
Damn it!
Are you... going to shoot him?
Nina!
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Hell In His Eyes