Deutsche Zukunft Newspaper Publishing
Company - Czech Branch
Contact
it's about time we finish them off.
No, let's wait a little longer.
Right!
Circle around to the right!
We need another guy over here!
Tape!
Let's just bust in now!
I'm getting hungry.
I haven't eaten lunch yet.
Me neither!
Let's just break through the floor.
Let's see, what should we eat?
Hey, pass me the tools.
I found a good Italian restaurant.
Anyone got a smoke?!
I'm not in the mood for Italian.
Hey, this drill's not working!
This cigarette sucks... I can't smoke this!
What, Chinese food again?!
Get me a bigger tool, something like that!
It's not Chinese, it's Vietnamese!
"Who are you!?"
"Monster..."
The Door to Nightmares