You were abandoned by your mom.
You were thrown away like trash,
just like your alcoholic dad.
Next time you're at the dump, don't come back!
The Town Massacre
I'm sorry. Could you please leave?
If you want a drink, you're going to have to pay your tab.
If you want money, here it is.
There's at least enough for today.
I don't have any alcohol that you can buy with the money you got from making your kid work.
What?
Get out
He's so weird.
You know what happened to Conrad,
and Mrs. Hillman's dog is dead.
He doesn't have the guts to fire a gun.
That's true.
He's just a cowardly drunk.
How are we supposed to conduct a search in this rain?
Hey, Merckel!
We should just call this off.
I've found him!
Merckel!
Mer-
Merckel...
This is Laufer.
Please respond.
S-Someone answer!
I'm going to take your gun as well.
He doesn't have the guts to fire a gun.
That's true.
He's just a cowardly drunk.
There are countless bodies scattered around town.
It looks like a battlefield.
Wim!
What's wrong, Wim?
It's okay. Calm down.
It's me.
I-I...
Calm down.
Give me the gun.
I can't remember.
I shot them, didn't I?
They were always picking on me.
So I...
Wim, you...
Don't worry.
Calm down. Everything is all right.
Don't be scared.
Calm down and gather your thoughts.
Who did you get this gun from?
Hang on!
You did well to make it here with that leg.
C-Call the station.
The phones don't work.
H-He took my gun.
Was it someone who lives here?
I didn't know him. It was an outsider
I had never seen before.
First things first, we have to get you treated.
Was he one of your friends?
What are you talking about?
How many men do you have here?
What are you trying to say?
It seems that quite a few guns were
distributed around town.
They even gave a gun to this kid.
Wim!
A gun! You didn't!
"You're not trash."
"Don't pay any attention to those creeps."
"You were put on this Earth for a reason."
You empowered him with those words.
He didn't shoot his gun.
All the bullets are still in it.
He held on to everything you taught him.
You're amazing, Wim.
It's okay.
Everything's all right, Wim.
Either way, there are dead bodies all over town.
How many did you hand out?
How many guns did you give out in this town?
How many people took your guns?!
You better not make me angrier!
Bad things happen when I get angry.
Just like our grandson.
What?
He was just like our dead grandson.
He?
Our grandson knew us so well.
He was just like our real grandson.
Who is he?
When you wrote a letter to your dead grandson,
you were really sending him information.
Who is he?
He is probably after me.
It's me.
Yeah.
That's right Mr. Poppe.
Or should we say, Franz Bonaparta.
The heavy rain in the middle of South Germany
continues to cause damage to Bayern and other surrounding regions.
You smoke too much.
It's fine. I need something now that I've stopped drinking.
You should quit smoking, too.
Dieter, what have you been drawing?
What do you think? Do you see the resemblance?
To whom?
It's Tenma! Tenma!
I'll give it to the police the next time they question me.
They never believe the important parts.
That's why I'm going to tell them.
"I'm telling you this is the man. This is the man who is going to kill a monster by himself."
Tenma's going to come back, right?
Here's a list of some of the damages.
The Elgar River has run over it's banks,
and is stopping traffic in a few areas.
The trains to and from those regions
have also been stopped.
In addition, the phone connections
are weak in all the regions.
I got this e-mail three days ago.
After talking with Dr. Gillen, we've decided that you should see it.
Please show it to me.
To Nina.
I'm waiting for you in Ruhenheim.
Johan.
Do you think this is it?
You gave a name to what Johan is trying to do.
"The perfect suicide."
Many innocent people will die.
Ruhenheim. There is a town in
South Germany by that name.
Tenma is probably headed there.
I have to go.
Please let me go there.
This is an odd feeling, Mr. Franz Bonaparta.
At first, I thought you were just
a part of a man's imagination.
Just like one of the characters in your picture books.
I've conducted investigations by gathering
objective data for many years.
But this time, I ignored the facts and took a
journey through that man's imagination.
As I put all the clues together, half for fun,
I met a man in the Czech Republic who made
frequent visits to the Red Rose Mansion.
It was your son.
This is a hand drawn post card you sent him,
signed with your real name, Klaus Poppe, KP.
When I found this place and found you,
I got an odd feeling,
like one of the characters from your
books had escaped from the pages.
But this is reality.
During my research, on the list of people
who assisted Czech Republic refugees,
there was the name, Klaus Poppe.
You fled here just before the Berlin Wall came down.
What were you running from?
Someone like me?
In East Germany, at 511 Kinderheim
a place based on your design...
That is where I was made.
Did you try to run away from people like me?
I understand him.
I understand what Johan's trying to do.
And now it's actually happening in this town.
Another gunshot!
There were a lot of dead people when we came here.
What happened to this town?
Hurry up and take me away from here!
It's impossible now. All the traffic's been shut down.
What have you been doing? You leave and come back and then take a shower.
The smell of blood and gunpowder in this town makes me sick.
Calm down. I ordered us some hot tea at the front desk.
It's okay. There's nothing to be afraid of.
It will all disappear when the rain stops.
What will disappear?
All of the memories.
There are some conditions to letting you go.
Dr. Gillen is coming with you, and we're not letting you have a gun.
I don't need a gun.
I'm going to get ready.
And please do as I just told you.
Dieter and Eva, and you, Dr. Reichwine.
Mr. Schubert, Karl and Lotte.
Please hide all the people that Johan knows about.
He's trying to erase all memories of himself.
You'd better go before Dieter notices.
Memories of Dieter...
Memories of you, Dr. Reichwein...
Memories of Lotte and Carl...
Memories of the Fortners...
Memories of Tenma...
I have memories that I don't want to forget.
No matter how much I want to forget about the memories...
Johan... What about your memories of him?
I can't let them disappear.
A police officer.
His gun has been taken.
Don't move.
Save the town...
Who shot you?
There was gun fire all over town.
Some men came to arm the people.
At some point, the people of the town...
all got guns and started shooting each other.
You have to... go... get help.
At least save the children.
Save...
Johan.
The first time I heard that name...
was in 1995 from that brain surgeon's statement.
Dr. Tenma.
So you acknowledge that your logic was wrong.
No, he's still the prime suspect in my mind.
Johan is still just an imaginary person.
An imaginary person.
During this vacation, the words that
caught my attention are these,
"How does a real person become an imaginary one?"
The answer is simple.
Eliminate all those who know the person and
all those who know of that person's past.
In the end, he will become like the end
of your books, Franz Bonaparta.
"He finally had a name, but all the people who could call him by that name disappeared."
"And Johan was such a wonderful name, too."
What if that's what's happening in this town?
That's what I'd do if I was Johan.
I'm also an imaginary person.
I'm not the man called Mr. Neumeyer,
who signed the hotel registry,
nor am I the man known as Wolfgang Grimmer.
I'm not anyone.
So I'll disappear, as well.
Along with all the others whom had their
memories and names taken from them.
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting here for my judgment.
I'm not scared of dying.
But, I don't know how to pay for what I've done.
I've decided to just accept everything that happens here.
You were waiting?
Aren't you scared of dying?
Do you understand how serious your crime is?
Do you understand what it means to destroy
a person's sense of good and evil?
Do you know what happens when you
awaken the monster inside of people?
People need to think that food is delicious.
People need to enjoy a picnic on their day off.
People need to cherish the beer they have after work.
People... People are supposed to feel sorrow from
the bottom of their heart when a child dies.
I won't let you die.
I'm going to get you out of this town and make
you tell everyone all that you know.
I'm going to show the world the true nature
of the monster you have awakened.
I'll protect you until then.
Where is Johan?
I-I don't know.
There has to be someone orchestrating this carnage.
Where is he?
I-I don't know.
Another gunshot.
Is there someone here?
See. I don't have anything.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
I've come to help.
Relax.
It's dangerous here. Got it?
You have to get out of town.
Don't cry. I'll take you to the road.
You can run, can't you?
The man giving the orders is at the Bergbach Hotel.
I see.
But I only have one gun.
These two were outside.
We're sorry.
All I did was win the lotto.
If we had told people earlier that we found Conrad's body...
Before this town went mad...
You bought all of these?
I haven't shot any of them even once. I swear.
Let me borrow these.
You protect this hotel.
What are you doing?
The residents have guns, too.
I'm a detective. I can tell the difference.
Oh, Mr. Grimmer.
When this job is over, buy me a beer.
I sure will.
Move, now!
Run!
Live!
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Wrath of the Magnificent Steiner