I don't like doing this to such old folks,
but you're very important witnesses.
I'd be in trouble if you died or ran off.
I've barricaded the back door and
the windows with furniture.
But if they really wanted to, it wouldn't
be too hard for them to break through.
It's better than nothing.
Let's go down to the first floor.
You know how to fire a gun, don't you?
Yeah, I think so.
I'll go, too.
I have to go.
I'd hate it if anything happened to you.
You have to survive and tell everyone everything.
Wim. Stay in the room.
If anything happens to you...
Don't worry.
A strong ally is coming to save us.
Really?
Yes.
If you're in a pinch, no matter where
you are, he'll come and save you.
He'll punish any wrong.
He is the invincible Magnificent Steiner.
The Wrath of the Magnificent Steiner
Move! Run!
Go north along the road.
I think the children can make it out safely from here on.
You should go, too!
We haven't checked the center of town.
Leave the rest to me. You have to lead the others.
O-Okay.
Just let me ask you one thing.
Do you know a man named Bonaparta, no, Klaus Poppe?
Poppe?
Yeah, he's the owner of the Versteck Hotel.
What are you doing there?
Relax. I'm a friend.
I've been running.
There are bodies everywhere.
Where can I run to?
Where did you run from?
Him. He was giving orders from the hotel room.
I overheard him.
Him?
Roberto! I thought it was weird that he
kept on going in and out of the room.
Every time he came back, he took
a shower and changed clothes.
Where is he?
In a room on the 4th floor of the Bergbach Hotel.
I never would have thought he was like that.
There are a bunch of people hiding at the Versteck Hotel.
Can you get there by yourself?
On my own?!
I'm scared.
Come on now. Get up.
I'm scared!
Dr. Tenma.
Inspector Lunge.
The illusion has finally become reality.
And now that you are here, the vacation I took to pull
the threads of that illusion together is now over.
As of now, I'm on duty as an officer of the law.
It's been a long time since I've been on duty.
Take this girl.
The man you're after is at the Versteck Hotel.
Franz Bonaparta.
Inspector Lunge, where are you going?
I told you, work.
If I make it back, I want to talk with you.
I have a lot of questions I want to ask you.
Dr. Tenma.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, Nina?
My memories...
are running through my head.
The memory in the farthest recesses of my mind...
Your deepest memory?
I don't want to remember it.
If Johan has this memory... If he can remember it...
Come out.
D-Don't shoot.
I'm from the town.
Please don't shoot.
Where is the man who's giving the orders?
I'm asking you where Roberto is!
Please stand up!
We need to get going.
I can't stand it. There are bodies everywhere!
I'll go insane if I stay here!
That's why we have to get to the Versteck Hotel as soon as possible.
No!
Open your eyes, Erika.
Please, Erika!
She's your wife, right?
I'm sorry, but she's...
I'm a friend.
It's dangerous here. Let's go somewhere safe.
Please let me have your gun!
I'm going to kill the guy who shot Erika.
Give me a gun!
The guy who ruined my life... I'm going to...!
Your wife wouldn't have wanted that.
Your wife would have wanted you to keep your child safe.
Am I wrong?
I'll show you the way.
There's a route by the north road
that will lead you out of here.
You should forget about the hotel and take the road as well.
No! I don't want to go anywhere.
Okay. I'll be back. Don't go anywhere.
Okay?
It sure is quiet.
So they aren't after our lotto winnings at all, are they?
No.
These last few days have been a living hell.
I really went crazy for a while.
I bought all these guns because of that money.
A normal life is the best.
Normal?
I have to tell my wife that this isn't our fault.
Can you hear me, honey?
Mr. Hennig!
My wife...
Mrs. Hennig!
It hurts.
This way.
They're shooting from the building across the road.
Is there a basement in this hotel?
There's a storage room under the kitchen.
Are you okay?
I should be asking you that.
My dad's doing this.
My dad ran out of alcohol and went mad.
No, he's not, Wim.
It's just like when he beats me up. He's...
Do you think he'd go this far?
It will end if I give myself up.
If I...
Don't make me say it again.
I won't let you die.
If you say that again, I'll tie you up down here.
Stay here.
I'll come up with something.
Mr. Grimmer.
Didn't I tell you?
When I'm in trouble, the invincible Magnificent Steiner will appear.
I've seen some cases of experiments like that.
After experiencing overwhelming rage, grief, or intense stress,
different personalities would appear in the children.
Such children tended to be extremely violent, but many of them committed suicide.
You've done well to live this long.
Look, I'm unarmed.
Give me a second and let's talk.
Why are you doing this?
Who's giving the orders?
I don't care if you were former Stasi.
I don't care who you are.
I'm not from anywhere.
Are you listening?
Listen with your own ears.
Don't take orders. Listen to your own heart.
Think with your own mind about what you're doing.
You can do that, can't you?
You can.
What are you doing?
I was so scared, but I made it here by myself.
I'm so glad you're here.
Magnificent Steiner!
Are you gathered around the tube, kids?
Everyday, I watched TV intensely.
What adventure awaits us today?
But I have no memory of the final episode.
If you're in trouble, call out his name.
Lets go.
No! I don't want to!
No!
Did that weak young man ever realize that he turned
into the Magnificent Steiner whenever he got angry?
Did that young man live happily ever after?
Did that young man...
Did that young man... live happily...
Just a little farther.
If we go just a little farther, we'll be out of these woods.
You're from Ruhenheim, aren't you?
Who are you?
Something's happening in the town, isn't it?
There are many armed men in the town.
The whole town has turned into a blood bath.
Don't tell me that you...
Calm down. Were friends.
Did you see an oriental Japanese man with long hair?
Do you know him?
You've seen him?!
Yes, he helped us escape.
He stayed behind to try and save the other people in town.
He was headed to the Versteck Hotel when we parted.
Hey, Nina!
My car is parked at the end of the woods.
Use it to take the injured to a hospital,
and contact the authorities as soon as possible.
Are you headed to town? You shouldn't go.
They'll kill you.
Tenma, that Asian man, is my friend.
I'm going to save him. Please hurry and call the authorities.
Versteck Hotel.
Mr. Grimmer.
Hey there.
I knew you'd come, Dr. Tenma.
Two in the other building, one on the floor below us, and one here.
I got four of them.
So, the Magnificent Steiner appeared.
No, he didn't.
I did it on my own.
I did it with my own anger.
Either way, those wounds...
Oh, yeah. Before I forget, take this letter.
I got it from Inspector Lunge.
He said he found it at the Red Rose Mansion.
Please go help him.
He's headed to the Bergbach Hotel by himself.
We have to take care of you first.
I'm fine.
Just let me rest for a while.
Let me introduce you.
This is Franz Bonaparta.
Mr. Grimmer.
Don't worry, Wim.
It's been raining for quite some time.
It'd be much nicer here if it cleared up.
Right, Dr. Tenma?
Yeah.
When it gets sunny out, let's take Wim on a picnic together.
We'll have good wine and good cheese.
Yeah.
I'm sad.
I'm not sad that I'm dying.
I'm finally sad that my child died.
People don't lose their emotions.
My emotions just wandered around in an unknown place.
It's like a letter that was addressed to
me decades ago has finally arrived.
Is this true sadness?
Or is it happiness?
In the final episode of the Magnificent Steiner,
I bet he became human again.
Mr. Grimmer.
Mr. Grimmer!
I...
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
A Nameless Man