The year 1986.
Düsseldorf.
That was the beginning of this incident.
What's his condition?
Dr. Kenzo Tenma
Blood pressure, 72/50.
Pulse, 137.
So the bullet entered his skull from the front...
We need X-rays immediately!
Yes, sir!
Oh, Dr. Tenma!
Who's this girl?
She's the twin sister of that boy just now.
What is it?
Kill... him...
Dr. Tenma!
Yes?
This isn't your operation.
The Mayor, Mr. Roedecker, has collapsed
from a cerebral thrombosis!
But I was about to start the
operation on that child!
It's an order from the director.
We can't have him die yet.
Director Heinemann
I'm counting on you, Tenma.
I expect a great deal from you.
Hey, you better make preparations, Dr. Tenma.
We're relying on those brilliant skills of yours.
They think doctors are some
kind of volunteers or something...
Even before saving lives,
we doctors value academics first.
Isn't that right?
I merely operated on that opera singer
like the director told me to.
It's not my fault
Of course.
Because people's lives aren't equal.
Give him back!
If only you had operated on him,
he would have survived!
Give him back!
Give him back! Give him back!
What's wrong, Dr. Tenma?
I...
I have an operation waiting for me in there.
H-Hey, Dr. Tenma
This is an order from the director!
Wait, Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
You'll be okay.
Hang in there!
I'll save you!
The Beginning
Blood pressure, 128/72.
Pulse, 88.
Looks like there are still some residual
effects from the anesthesia.
Looks like it went smoothly on your side.
The mayor passed away.
After going against the director's orders...
Tenma was removed from his position
as chief neurosurgeon...
and his engagement to the director's
daughter, Eva, was cancelled.
It's impossible for someone with
an attitude problem, like you.
The path of being the doctor you
dreamed of is closed to you.
Eva Heinemann
You really are a fool.
Eva!
The hell with all of them!
Director's orders my ass!
Chief's orders my ass!
All they care about are money
and their stupid positions!
Damn it!
I...
I'm not wrong...
Yes?
I'm sorry for disturbing you so
early in the morning.
We're from the county police.
Can I help you?
The truth is that Director Heinemann, Surgical Director
Oppenheim, and Dr. Boyer of Eisler Memorial Hospital...
have all passed away.
This is terrible!
Those kids!
The twins!
I can't find them anywhere!
W-What is this?
What the hell... happened here...?!
What?
Let me repeat.
Dr. Tenma...
I'm appointing you as the head
of the surgical department.
What a life!
What a...
Kenzo!
Please, I'm sorry!
Kenzo...
Kenzo!
9 Years Later
The deaths of Director Heinemann and two
others at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
The disappearance of the twins...
And then, nine years later...
a new incident occurred.
The monster... is coming...
Mr. Junkers!
It's the same as back then!
Poisoned by candy!
My patient disappearing!
This is just like what happened nine years ago!
Mr. Junkers!
It's me, Tenma!
No, Doctor!
You can't come here!
It's been a long time, Doctor.
It's me.
You saved my life nine years ago, remember?
You probably already forgot
about those two little twins...
Johan?!
You're in that position today because the director,
head surgeon, and chief are dead, right?
I'm really glad.
You said it when I regained consciousness.
You hated them so much that
you wanted to kill them.
I only did what you wished for.
I should have died back then.
But you brought me back to life, Doctor.
I see.
His name is Johan Liebert.
Inspector Lunge
Hey...
Y-Yes?
Let's let him go for now.
After the murders at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
I can see only one person who benefited from the
incident, no matter how much I think about it.
Dr. Tenma, you're the only one.
I...
I was the one who brought that
monster... back to life...
"Tomorrow at 7pm, on the night of your birthday,
we'll meet at Heidelberg Castle."
Tomorrow...
At Heidelberg Castle...
Heidelberg
Oh, Papa. It's me.
I just got off work.
Nina Fortner
I'm going to meet up with a friend now, so...
Johan's twin sister, Anna...
had lost her memory after the
incident nine years ago...
Yeah, at Heidelberg Castle.
and was living with foster parents in Heidelberg.
She called herself Nina Fortner.
On her twentieth birthday...
she received an anonymous email...
and headed for Heidelberg Castle.
It's way past the time we were supposed to meet...
I guess it was a prank after all.
You can't.
You have to wait here.
I said wait.
Wait!
You have to wait here!
He told me so!
Anna!
Anna...
No, you're Nina Fortner, right?
Do you remember me?
I'm Doctor Tenma.
Thank God you're safe!
Anna...
Dr. Tenma...
Don't interfere...
Don't interfere!
She has to wait here.
Otherwise, I...
I won't get my money!
He said no one would come!
Damn it!
Who hired you?
I... I don't know!
When did he say he was coming?
I don't know!
He only said that he'll come here after he's
taken care of something important!
Oh, no...
Your house!
We have to hurry back to your house!
W-What do you mean?
I'll explain later.
Hurry, Anna!
Anna?
Hurry!
Please!
Come back to life!
Please come back to life!
Please...
I beg you
Please!
Mr. Mauler!
I killed him...
I...
...killed him...
I killed my brother back then!
For some reason, those who are kind to us...
...everyone of them...
...just dies.
But on that night...
...I finally found out why.
On that rainy night...
My brother shot them.
He... shot all of those people...
That's why... I picked up the gun.
That's why I aimed it at my brother.
Then, he said it...
He was laughing when he said it...
He said to aim straight for his head.
Why did you save him?
If only you hadn't saved my brother...
Papa and Mama wouldn't have been killed!
I have something I have to do.
Then I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell the police about the necktie!
I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell them that the incident where my father and the others were killed...
...was all your fault too!
Close off all entrances to the ward!
Don't forget the rear entrances as well!
Yes, sir!
Where is Dr. Tenma?
I... I don't know!
Looks like there's a huge commotion over there.
There are a lot of police cars out there, Dr. Tenma.
Is that so?
I wonder what happened.
Anyway, please drop me off in front of the station.
Okay.
You're busy as usual Dr. Tenma.
Dr. Tenma, it's not your fault.
You only performed your duty as a doctor.
It's not your fault
Please eat the sandwiches.
And please, get some sleep.
Please stay alive.
And... please save as many lives as you can.
Nina Fortner.
Nina...
What are you planning to do now?
Are you going to kill him again?
5 Months Later
Tenma was on the run as
a suspect in the murder case.
However, that was the beginning of the
long journey to hunt down Johan.
They said another middle-aged couple
was murdered, this time in Verden.
They said a doctor did it, didn't they?
Speaking of which, you said you were
going to Verden, didn't you?
Do you know someone living
there or something?
Yeah...
I don't know if I'll meet him there...
but I have to go.
Berlin
You said you wanted to ask
me about those twins, right?
I know a good deal about her brother, Johan.
Johan...
That's right! I want to ask you about Johan!
T-That was...
That was top secret.
Johan...
What did Johan do?
He led a revolution.
Everyone died.
Every member of the orphanage,
including the instructors...
killed each other.
It was ten years ago.
The instructors, and even the orphans...
All fifty took their last breath here.
And Johan...
He just gazed upon it.
Johan just gazed upon it.
I asked Johan...
What...
I asked him just what he had done.
And he answered me.
"Hatred is born when people gather together."
"I merely poured some oil onto this."
That's what he said!
A boy of only ten years old!
And he did it!
He made fifty people kill each other without
lifting one finger of his own!
This isn't what Johan wanted!
Frankfurt
How do you know that?
I saw it.
I went to the place he indicated.
Johan didn't wish for this!
W-What did you see?
He...
He didn't wish for anything!
He's not the kind of person you think he is!
He's much more complicated...
He's much more frightening than that...
He's... writhing in pain in an abyss of grief!
Tenma!
Nina!
Nina, promise me!
Don't shoot!
You mustn't shoot people!
I saw Johan's message!
Back then...
ten years ago...
when I shot Johan...
I finally figured out why he wanted
me to shoot him in the head!
Johan...
isn't alone!
There are two Johans!
So... Dr. Tenma...
That's why... it's not your fault...
I...
Once again, I'll...
aim at Johan's head, and...
Leaving numerous mysteries behind him...
Johan disappeared.
Who is Johan?
Where did he go?
What is his goal?
Tenma and Nina's journey...
hasn't come to an end yet.
"Help me!"
"The monster inside me is about to explode!"
Then, inside Johan...
there are two personalities?
And slowly, you come to realize
It's all as it should be
You can only do so much
If you're game enough
You could place your trust in me
For the love of life
There's a trade off
We could lose it all
But we'll go down fighting