How are you feeling, Mr. Junkers?
Mr. Junkers, do you recognize me?
Can you see this finger?
How about it? Can you answer me?
What's that?
The monster... is coming...
What's that, Mr. Junkers?
Coming? What's coming?
The monster is coming...
The monster... is coming...
The monster?!
Night of the Execution
Junkers...
I know you're able to speak.
Of the four murders
of middle-aged couples
in the past two years,
you were seen near the scene
of three of them, you see.
How about it, Adolph Junkers?
Never mind. We know that
you are a lock picker.
Your job is just to open locks.
Slitting throats
in a single stroke...
is not something you could do.
That means there were
other perpetrators
in addition to yourself.
I think that there would have to be
at least three people
in order to open a strong lock,
and murder a middle-aged couple
without resistance...
We're almost finished
making a list of men who use knives.
It's just a matter of time
before we pinpoint your colleagues.
Whether you talk, or not.
But that is not what
I really want to know.
Why four couples
from across Germany?
And why only kill
middle-aged ones without children?
Money and items were stolen,
but the amounts were too small
to split three ways to justify murder.
How about it?
Want to make a plea bargain?
If you make a statement,
you can escape prosecution...
Who asked you to do this?
Mr. Junkers. that's enough.
That's enough!
I'll have to ask you to
end this questioning!
No, just a little bit more.
Please leave this room!
That's an order from
his attending physician!
Oh, all right.
I'll come again another day.
But I will place a guard
to watch him closely
so that he isn't poisoned
or that he doesn't disappear.
Dr. Tenma, for some reason,
all kinds of trouble
seems to happen around you.
What are you trying to say?!
It's just a joke.
Excuse me.
Hey! You, where are you going?!
A walk.
Doing things without permission
is going to get me in trouble!
Even patients need recreation.
We're just going out into the garden.
If you're worried,
do you want to come with us?
It's a warm and pleasant day.
You can talk, can't you?
On days like this,
it makes you glad you're alive...
I need days like this,
or else it becomes unbearable.
I see people in
life and death situations every day...
That's why it's easier for doctors to
focus on fame and research.
I used to be like that...
I tried to gain a reputation
and do my own research...
I thought that succeeding in surgery
was a way to fortify my status...
But after performing surgery
on a certain boy, I changed.
He was the elder of fraternal twins.
He'd been shot in the head.
Because I saved him, I was able to
return to being a real doctor...
The weight of people's lives
are all the same...
A doctor's work
is to save those lives...
Thank you.
You can start over.
It's not too late.
Doctor...
You and I are close in age,
but you're like my old man.
You saved my life...
I feel like you're my parent...
I suddenly have a big kid, huh?
When I was little,
I wanted a mechanical clock...
Huh?!
You know...
The kind where a nutcracker doll
would stroll out on the hour...
Every day,
I would press my face against
the show window of the watch store...
My first break in was that store...
They caught me right away
and I didn't get the clock...
But, after that,
break ins became my job...
At first, it was only because
I wanted that clock...
I only wanted the clock...
I...
Tell them everything...
Tell the police everything
and start over from scratch...
Killed...
My associates, all of them...
They were all killed...
Who killed them?!
The one you called "the monster"?
Make this one yours, now.
I went through a lot of trouble
to set this up.
She's the daughter of a member of
the state parliament, you know.
She is beautiful and intelligent.
She's really something...
I'll have to meet her first.
But... I guess...
I should do as you say
and settle down...
You should!
For someone with your prestige
to not have a wife... Huh?
Hey!
The kind where a nutcracker doll
would pop out every hour...
This is it!
Excuse me!
About the clock in the window...
Hey! What's going on?!
It's already time for your date! Hey!
You can start over.
It's not too late.
Officer... Policeman on watch...
You're there, aren't you?
I'll tell you everything.
But can you call Dr. Tenma, too?
Officer?
It's late, but can I visit
one of the rooms?
Yes, of course, Dr. Tenma.
What is that?
I found something good.
Hey! What's the matter?!
Get a hold of yourself!
He's dead!
Candy...
Mr. Junkers!
It's the same as the last time!
Poisoned by candy!
My patient's disappeared!
It's the same thing that happened
nine years ago!
Mr. Junkers!
It's me, Tenma!
Doctor!
You mustn't come, Doctor!
Let's go back to the hospital,
Mr. Junkers.
Everything will be all right.
Don't, Doctor. You mustn't come!
You mustn't see him, Doctor!
"Him?"
He's the one
who killed my accomplices!
You'll be killed, too!
Wh-Who's there?!
Don't, Doctor! You mustn't come!
It's been a long time, Doctor.
It's me.
Nine years ago, you saved my life,
didn't you?
Nine years ago?!
Have you already forgotten
about those twins?
Johan!
That's right, those twins...
You remembered.
Run!
You'll be killed!
Wh-What do you intend to do?
Mr. Junkers is my patient!
What am I going to do?
Execute him.
Don't do it!
Doctor, run!
He killed my friends!
Wha?!
We were hired by him!
He always called us on the phone!
A large reward
was transferred into our account
after each job was done...
And we'd split it between the three of us!
Could it be?
The one who ordered the murders
of the four middle-aged couples
was you?
The police were watching me,
so we became a hindrance!
He's already killed Fritz, the Slayer,
and Big Boy Boris!
Just before he died, Fritz said,
"We've been hired by a monster."
He doesn't think anything of
killing people!
Run! Doctor, you'll be killed!
Run, Doctor!
You talk too much, Junkers...
Don't!
Don't do it, Johan!
Mr. Junkers doesn't seem to know
who you are, but I do.
I was your attending physician!
You are Johan Leibert, the elder of twins.
You are the son of Michael Leibert,
former advisor of Commerce
in East Germany,
who defected to West Germany
in 1986.
If we know this much about you,
you can't possibly escape!
Don't add to your crimes, Johan!
Johan?
I used that name before...
But that is not my real name...
What do you mean?
My past must not be known...
Those four couples
and the Leiberts, too...
But you're different, Doctor...
You saved my life...
You're like my parent, after all...
Parent... me?!
After all, if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be here.
Stop it!
You mustn't kill!
Why not?
"Why not?"
What do you think a human life is?!
Because I saved your life,
I was able to go back to being
what a doctor should be!
By saving your life,
I realized that
the weight of each life is equal.
No one has the right to
take another person's life!
I've lived for many years as a doctor
with that in mind.
What's so funny?!
Doctor, after that incident,
I heard you soon became
the Chief of Surgery...
I'm so glad that you were selected
as the Chief of Surgery.
What is it you want to say?
You're here now because
the Director, the Chief of Surgery
and the Chief died, right?
That's really good...
It can't be... You did it?
After all, you said it yourself...
This is what you wanted.
When I became conscious,
that's what you said
That you hated them so much
you could kill them.
I am not wrong!
That bastard... That bastard...
He's better off dead.
...off dead... off dead...
I did just as you wished, you know.
Doctor... I'm afraid, Doctor...
Doctor... Save me, Doctor...
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
I was supposed to have died back then.
You brought me back to life, Doctor.
Honestly, this rain is terrible.
I hate the rain. It washes away
all the evidence.
What about you, Dr. Tenma?
Let's see... That means,
from what you said...
In 1986, right after the Leiberts
defected from East Germany
with their twin children,
the Leibert family was shot
and the parents died.
The elder of the twins, the boy,
was hit in the head
and in serious condition.
You operated on the boy
and saved his life.
But, surprisingly, the boy,
killed the director, chief of surgery
and head of neurosurgery
with poisoned candy and ran away...
And last night, he appeared
after nine years
and killed a state police officer,
once again with poisoned candy...
And shot Adolph Junkers
right in front of your eyes.
He is the one who hired
Junkers and two others
to kill the four middle-aged couples.
His name is Johan Leibert.
And that's all of it?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Let him go for today.
Would you ever think that someone with
Dr. Tenma's credentials
would ever commit such a crime?
He has an alibi for the time
the policeman was killed,
and there was no gunpowder residue
on his hands.
With this, the clue to solving
the murders
of the four middle-aged couples
is gone.
For the time being, shall we
go after the guy, Johan Leibert?
Inspector Lunge...
The Girl of Heidelberg