Now, class...
Tell me what the decision
in the 1968 Stuttgart case
was based upon.
Now, now, what is this silence?
Is this a Zen temple in the Orient?
Mr. Eimer... I would like to
hear your answer.
Huh?!
Well... uh... That is...
Anyone! Is there anyone
who will break this silence?
So, the chronic latecomer is here at last.
You're 13 minutes late...
Seems your part-time pizza delivery job
was awfully busy today.
I'm sorry... Professor... Kronecker...
Now, then, let me ask you a question
before you sit down.
Do you have enough strength
to tell me what the basis was
for the decision in the Stuttgart case?
Huh? Uh... yes. Well...
The accused claimed that
the kidnapping was a sham
and that the victim's death
had been due to an accident.
After an investigation
of the crime scene
it was found that the victim's death
had indeed been accidental.
And so, based on the fact that the intent
to kill must be proven in a murder
I believe that a sentence
of 15 years was handed down.
Very good.
Sit down, Nina Fortner.
Yes, Professor!
Heidelberg,
(Germany)
You saved us, Nina.
The Girl of Heidelberg
If no one had been able to
give him the answer,
Kronecker would have probably
demanded 50-page reports.
50 pages, if we were lucky.
I have to treat Nina, to whom we're
greatly indebted, to something to eat.
You can come, can't you Nina?
Just the two of us...
Nina Fortner
I'm sorry, Peter.
I have a club meeting today.
See you!
She turned you down again...
Peter, how many times was that?
Shut up! I'd like to see if there's anyone
who can get Nina to agree to a date.
I-I give up!
Oh, no! If I'm late with my deliveries,
I'm going to get it
from the manager again!
I'm home!
Boy, am I hungry!
Oh, my, the neighbors
can probably hear you.
You're a young lady now.
It's not becoming.
Go and wash your hands.
Yes, ma'am!
Oh! Mom, did you
color your hair?
It looks good, doesn't it?
Honestly! You shouldn't be dying
your hair so bright, at your age!
You're wrong, Dad.
She looks lovely.
She's not going to
a masquerade party, after all.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
for Mom to be young forever?
Hi, Dad...
Oh, yes... Speaking of masquerades...
I saw some kids in costumes today.
Oh, yes...
It's the St. Hadrian Costume Parade.
I wish I had dressed up like that
when I was little. They were so cute!
Huh? Oh... you did dress up
in a costume.
Isn't that right, dear?
O-Oh... that's right.
Huh?
Let's see... It's around here...
Oh, here it is!
Here, look at this!
It's true...
You were so excited
and made such a fuss.
Isn't that right, dear?
Huh? Oh, that's right.
A costume parade?
Distant spring.
I forlornly wait for a spring
that will never come... Hannah.
Oh, Hannah... Will you hurry
and get over your broken heart?!
Huh?!
Let me send you
the world's most beautiful flower.
I was born to blanket you in flowers...
Wow... I wonder who sent this.
Aha!
I'm very impressed, Peter!
How have you been, Nina?
Yes, well, I've been very well,
thankfully, Dr. Gaitel.
That's good.
Of course, I could tell by the look
on your face when you entered
this counseling room
that your were doing well.
And do you no longer
have that dream?
Of that monster appearing
out of the darkness...
Yes! I've been sleeping so well,
I have no time to dream.
I wonder why I was plagued by
such a dream night after night.
It's common for people to become
insecure during their student years.
Dreams of the future become
confused with other insecurities,
and you lose sight of who you are.
But what you are is something
you can spend your whole life
trying to learn, and never discover.
All you can do now is be prepared
to spend your whole life searching,
and do only what you can do
toward your future.
Yes. I will do my best.
I want to become a public prosecutor.
That's good. All right, I think we can
end our counseling session for today.
Thank you very much.
Nina Fortner... Such a cheerful girl...
But I can't help but feel
that her cheerfulness
is a reaction to something
she's running away from.
Some... vast... darkness...
What?
Don't say that.
Don't act so innocent.
What in the world
are you talking about?
"I was born to
blanket you in flowers..."
I never thought you had
the makings of a poet.
I don't know anything about that.
I wouldn't be able to come up with words
like those even if I stood on my head.
Huh? Then, who was it?
I've given my email address
to only my friends.
Who knows?
Damn. All I know is that
I have another rival in love!
Who in the world could it be?
This bizarre murder
that took place in Munich...
The perpetrator,
after shooting the parents to death,
strangled the two children with a rope.
Now, I'd like you to explain the ruling
of the judge from the court records...
Nina Fortner.
Huh?
Do you not understand the question?
N-No... uh...
The trial was focused on
the cold-blooded murder
of a whole family...
- Huh?
- The evidence...
The evidence...
Oh? There are times
you can't answer either, Nina?
Nina!
What's wrong, Nina?
Nina!?
Are you all right?
You want to go to the infirmary?
I-I'm all right.
I just felt a little ill...
After listening to the professor's story...
suddenly...
Huh? You mean that bizarre
massacre of that family?
Stop it!
Is that it?
I thought you were awfully brave,
but you're more sensitive
than I expected.
Did you see a horror movie
that terrified you as a child?
I know! I'll bet that counselor,
Dr. Gaitel, would probably say...
"If you look back on
why this happened,
you'll find it was nothing significant.
Now, why don't you think back
on your childhood..."
I don't remember...
Huh?
I don't remember anything
before the age of ten...
My memories...
My childhood memories...
Huh?!
Köln,
(Germany)
Yes...
They were a very nice couple...
To think they were killed like that...
Huh? Children?
Oh, now that you mention it,
they had a son.
His name was Michael, I think.
They lived together about two years.
A boy? Was there a boy?
Yes, there was.
Wasn't his name Michael?
He was around fourteen.
Michael, you say?
I seem to remember him.
Why? Are you the police?
Yes. Michael Reichmann.
He was a student in my class.
But he didn't leave
much of an impression.
I'm embarrassed to say this,
but I don't remember him well.
I'm not sure if he had any friends.
And, there are no records...
Everything burned
in a fire six years ago.
There definitely was a boy
named Michael living here
in Cologne until six years ago...
And... Michael's real name...
Johan... I've used that name before...
Who... are you?
But what's the use in knowing that?
What's the use?
He is a serial-killer who is a twin...
That's all there is.
What am I doing?
A twin! What about his sister?
Where did his twin sister go?!
"I will come for you soon..."
Who is this?
You'll come for me soon?
What does that mean?
A child? Yes, there was...
about 7 or 8 years ago.
So Mr. and Mrs. Heinemann,
who were killed, were fostering a boy?
What was he like?
That was a long time ago.
And he only lived with them
about a year.
I don't remember
anything about him.
Didn't that boy have a sister?
It was only that boy.
Listen, I just want to forget about
what happened to that couple.
I even thought about moving away
after it happened.
I know about that boy.
Come on in. I was just about to
fix some tea.
Have a seat.
Uh... yes. Thank you.
Uh... I...
Have a seat.
Please have some tea.
Thank you very much.
You're a doctor, aren't you?
That boy told me.
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
He's coming for you?
Who?
I have no idea.
It was an anonymous message.
You look so happy.
You're not thinking a prince
on a white horse
will be coming for you, are you?
Are you jealous?
There you go,
daydreaming again, Nina.
"I was born to blanket you in flowers..."
There aren't any kids
who talk like that today.
Oh!
Say, listen. Haven't you noticed
a strange boy in class recently?
Oh! Yes, I have!
The one who calmly sits in
that "legendary seat"in Room 12,
where you're bound to be called on
by the teacher.
And yet, he's never called on.
That's right. And do you know,
he stares at Nina all through class!
- Huh?
- He's the one!
What?
You know!
Your prince on the white horse!
That boy was extremely grateful
to you, Dr. Tenma.
He said you were the one
who saved him;
you meant more to him than a parent.
What name did he go by?
Franz... But he said
it wasn't his real name.
He trusted you enough
to tell you that?
That Franz, who had shown up
out of the blue,
was cared for by
Mr. and Mrs. Heinemann,
who lived in the flat across the hall,
for a year.
No, actually, it was 14 months
from March 1987 to April 1988.
Then, one day, he suddenly vanished.
He was very bright.
And he was well-mannered.
Did he used to
come to this apartment?
Every day. I lived alone
so I always welcomed him.
He sat in that seat
and spent his time studying.
In no time, he had mastered
the English and French
that I taught him.
By the time he disappeared,
he was fluent in both.
That 12-year-old boy...
Is there anything else
you remember about him?
He always listened closely
to my stories.
What stories do you think
he was most interested in?
Well...
War stories.
War?
During World War II,
I was on the crew of a U-boat.
His favorite story
was about the time
we were attacked by a destroyer
of the Allied Forces...
We were at a depth of 120 meters...
We were attacked by the enemy
and although we had suffered
a fatal blow, we kept going.
Inside that groaning ship,
we all waited in terror.
We returned from that living hell
38 hours later.
An ordinary child would probably
look at this as
another adventure story...
But that boy was different.
What he was
most interested in was...
the terror.
Extreme terror.
What is the reaction of a person
standing on the edge of death?
That was his only interest.
He took pleasure in terror!
Wh-What sort of expression
did he have while
listening to your stories?
Probably had a gleam in his eye,
and a smile on his face.
Probably?
I am blind, you see.
Yes. I know neither his real name,
nor what he looks like.
Earlier, you said that boy
trusted me, didn't you?
He never trusts anybody.
There's only one person
he's ever trusted... his sister.
I-I'm looking for that sister!!
He said he would go and collect her
when she turned twenty.
Go where?
To Heidelberg.
See you later!
Ride carefully on your scooter.
I will!
Bye, Dad!
Be careful.
Good bye!
I guess it's time...
But...
We decided, didn't we?
That we'd tell her on her 20th birthday
that she's not our child.
Hey, wait, I can't...
What are you saying?
You wanted to meet him.
We told him you'd wait for him here.
Don't screw up,
with your "prince on a white horse."
See you later!
Oh... Clara! Beata!
How could they do this
behind my back!
Oh, look!
He's here!
H-How do you do...
You're Nina Fortner?
Y-Yes...
Uh... I'm Otto Hubermann...
Oh, hello...
Who is he...?
Who is he?
I've seen him... somewhere... before...
Who are you?
Huh? Huh?
- Nina!
Nina! What's wrong?
Are you all right?
- Nina, wake up!
- Nina! Nina!?
- Nina!
- Hey, Nina!
Nina, are you all right?!
The Missing