Please tell me the runners are you Dr Tema you got it wrong my name is not
Now but that wasn't your name back when you were brought into my Hospital you were on
Brother your brother's name was Johann
Mr fort
She's here with me Mr Mara
Alright you go on and I'll call them myself
It does look like a police ever came
Please come back
I'm begging you
You don't have to quit smoking anymore
Christopher
Back then
I brought your brother back to life
We're getting out of here
Back for you
You okay in there
Where would the police someone called earlier is there any trouble
If you don't mind sir
We're just going to have a quick look around
Good Lord
This is horrible
You two all right
Are you injured you hurt
Well that's a relief
Backup should arrive very soon
They'll take care of the crime scene and will take you over to headquarters for questioning so we can file a report on this
So are you the daughter of the victims
I'm sorry for your loss
I'm assuming neither of you saw the intruder
To think something like that could happen in such a peaceful.
Pardon my asking sir but where do you come from are you Chinese and no sir I'm Japanese my name is
Okay you Japanese yeah well seems to me you're quite a ways from home
You're all right now it's going to be
Okay
Sorry but can you tell me
Officer the police station remember but I don't understand
Smtown yeah but we're from the station in Manheim the next town over
Why are they taking us so far yeah we're
Almost there just another 15 minutes or so
He said they got a call they came
I got a call but who could have caught the phone
No no Sirens when they first came and
They took us away before making sure the backup arrived at the scene but
Dispatches that look real
It can't be
Could these men have
Excuse me
These trick question
Goodness
We're searching for a hit-and-run suspect so please be alert excuse me it's you
Well if it isn't detective Messner detective Mueller good evening
Are you two on your way back to the station
I'm sure we'll get it banged up soon enough
Yeah we really give our rides a workout
Excuse me Detective
She's not feeling so well back here can she get some fresh air for a minute
Oh
Sure you go ahead
Detective what's up I just doing some kind of trouble
Not at all it's nothing don't worry
Going on here
Who could have called them
Are Sirens weren't even on
What should we do
Hey what's wrong doctor Tenma are you two okay
How do you know who I am
I gave you my name but I never told you not once that I would the doctor tell me how did you know that
I found a grocery store nearby
I also got you some dry clothes
There's bread sausage and cheese
I filled this thermos of hot coffee too
You probably don't have much of an appetite but you really should eat
You're shivering
You should change out of those wet clothes
A lot of people were dead
My brother and I
Walking
It was like
Alone in the world
Where were you when all of this happened can you remember anything else
We crossed the border
Uncle and auntie help.
They were so kind to us
And my brother said
I have a good plan
Soon after that
And my dear auntie were both dead
Anyone who has ever good to us died
Without fail
Awesome
But then one day
One day I discovered the reason why
Rainy day
I'm talking about the incident with mr. and mrs. Libra
My brother did it he shut them
Brother
Murdered
My brother
So I picked up the gun with both my hands
And that night I aimed it right at my brother
And that's when he said
Can you shoot me make sure that you throw the gun out the window
And he told me to aim for his head
Like head
I aim for his head like he told me
Why did you save him
If you had anything to Mom and Dad would still be alive
Stay here I'm going to the police
If those detectives last night were real
Jeans with some members of the police force are linked to Johan if so we can't just
Wait here like this
Nina I need you to listen to me I know that Johann is going to come after you if anyone comes look
Just hide
Why don't you have some food drink some hot coffee and then try to get a couple hours of rest
One step at a time and that's how we'll get through all this
Your life
Future future
Were there any clues left by the Killer is there any connection to the serial murders throughout
Like I said we're doing everything we can to investigate this case but I can't make
Any comments or talk about details
Timer she presumed that is what we're trying to figure out her whereabouts why was that newspaper reporter with them
One question please man who is over here
Who is he he sounds suspicious
Quick question Chief is this murder at all related to the one that took place at Heidelberg Castle around the same time
So he was able to
That's all for now will release additional details in due time please let me through
Excuse me sir
Of course we appreciate all the support we're getting from Manheim like detectives Messner and Mueller thank you
You both for coming out this afternoon
We're at your disposal to Aid in the investigation anything we can do to help
So how are things coming along sir
Please come inside that way we'll be able to speak freely
Those guys were with the police there actual cops
I do
Hello Heidelberg post
What I can't hear you were really busy in here
Just hold on
I'm bringing an important witness to your office 5
But you must not tell the police
If I can't trust the police then the newspaper is my only option
Only they can help me on that now
Mr. Miller
I'm sorry but you just can't come in here without permission
He's right besides
The bka is only working on the serial murders of the middle-aged couples all that you're going to find in this room is material for the murder at the
Castle inspector
Sir
Please forgive me
I was just a bit curious what the crime you're investigating in this one happened at the same time Detective
I mean it couldn't have been the same murderer
So icy
It appears that this man had been tied up
You didn't happen to find a rope or anything nearby did you
No
Seems the body's already been untied by the time the police arrived on the scene
Nicey
Yes
There are four possible routes of Escape From The Scene he also had to stay well out of sight
How crowded was the area where you come out and how much light was there
Here it is
Nina's me I'm back Nina she can come out now
Oh no
Moon
Where are you
He came for you
I never should have left you here all of them
Dr. tena
I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore
You did what you had to do is a doctor
It wasn't your fault
Please eat the sandwiches
Get some rest too
Please leave on
And continue to save as many people as you are able to
Nina Fortner
Nina
Are you planning to do
Are you going to kill your brother second time
I did it I brought him back to life that monster
It was me
To
And slowly you come
Inside
You can only do so much
A game in
You good place
Other lover
But we'll go down