What's this?
It's okay now.
Never again...
Never again will blood flow through this forest.
Isn't that right?
A Child's View
"The falling deaths of children...
Is it suicide or murder?!"
"Was it just dangerous child's play?
Or is this the next victim!!"
"A fifth victim... Entry Restrictions to
Building Rooftops to be Reinforced!!"
Ralph Ludwich Memorial Hospital
You don't remember anything?
What happened on the roof back then?
What did you do? Could you tell
me anything you remember?
Spit it out, Martin!
If you hadn't hit the first floor awning and landed
in the bushes, you might be dead right now.
Tell the doctor like a good boy,
so that stupid things like this won't keep on happening.
Calm down, ma'am.
But... If he died, I... I...
Listen to me, ma'am.
I've come to counsel the boy here.
I know... I know, but Doctor...
Let's talk outside, okay?
Dieter, be a good boy and stay there.
Don't wander into the rooms.
Is he your grandchild?
No, I'm just watching over him.
H-Hey there.
Hey.
I'm Dieter.
I'm Martin.
Does it hurt?
Does what hurt?
Your injuries... Your bandaged injuries?
Were you scared when you fell from the roof?
Stop! What are you doing?
There are some shoes in that bag. Get them for me.
What are you doing? You should rest.
Get my shoes.
Where are you going to go?
They'll get mad at you.
So what?
I'm not scared of them getting mad at me at all.
Just like he said...
"If you make it back, go outside."
"The world will change."
It's not that the world changed. I'm the one who changed.
Because I've been chosen.
It's so boring.
I can't believe the world is so boring.
Watch out!
You should come too.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
What'd you do that for?
Look at him, he's scared.
Stop it.
I told you to look at him!
"Save me."
"I don't want to die! Save me!"
Is that what you're thinking?
Fine, I'll spare your life.
I'll answer your question from before.
Huh?
You asked me if I was scared when I fell from the roof, didn't you?
Yeah.
I couldn't be afraid, since I was just playing around.
Playing? People have died!
It was so much fun. It was just play.
The two of us stood on an abandoned building.
We'd close our eyes and walk towards
each other, one step at a time.
It was a duel.
Whether you fell or whatever happened,
if you could survive, you'd win.
Why would you do that?
It's like making a wager with fate.
The one who survives was chosen.
You might not understand what I'm saying.
The person who survives can play again.
Play? What do you mean?
The world is boring.
This is fun. Only the ones chosen
by fate can keep on playing.
Don't you get it?
I thought you were one of us.
Come. I'll show you.
If you don't understand after you
see it, you truly are a moron.
Hey, you aren't thinking of going up to the roof, are you?
The chosen...
The superior people will survive.
Just like "that person."
Who's "that person?"
The person who taught me this game.
Who is he?
He's our friend.
The friend of us superior children.
Hurry up!
No, thanks.
C'mon. You're coming with me.
Let go of me.
You should be able to understand. So just come on!
Stop!
Who beat you up?
Your parents?
Are you going to be on their side?
Even though they did that to you, do you still
intend to be buried in this stupid world?
Come. Take a look for yourself.
How is the view from here?
How does it feel?
Stand up. What are you afraid of?
Stand up, close your eyes, and try walking.
Stand up!
I understand it...
I understand everything you've been saying.
I thought the world was pitch black.
I thought the future was pitch black.
What's your favorite food?
I just ate some delicious sausage, but
if I died, I'd never get to eat it again.
Scaredy cat!
I like soccer.
But if I died, I wouldn't kick a ball ever again.
Weakling.
I like Dr. Reichwine.
His secretary, Ms. Mereth, is kind.
If I died, I'd never see them again.
There will always be things to be scared of.
That's why he said to become an adult.
Tomorrow is a good day.
That's what Tenma taught me.
If I died, I'd never see Tenma again.
I'm scared!
Don't panic.
Carefully, bend your knees.
I can't be like him...
I can't be like Johan.
Johan.
Johan is playing even better games.
Johan said that he's going to be killed soon.
He said he's going to be shot by a Japanese man real soon.
I closed my eyes and walked on the edge of the roof.
It's true. I walked up there.
I wasn't scared at all.
When I opened my eyes, Joachim, who should
have been right in front of me, was gone!
I saw it. I saw the instant when someone
dies with my own eyes.
People really die.
Please have some tea.
Thank you.
I can't believe this kid. It's like he doesn't
even know what he's doing.
I'm glad he's alive, but when I think of
how Joachim's parents must feel...
Please talk some sense into him.
It seems like he'd listen to whatever you say.
She annoys me like that every day.
She doesn't let me out of the house.
TV and comics are off-limits for me, too.
That sounds pretty boring.
I'll come bring you something.
Really?
If you can't have comics, then how about a picture book?
A picture book? That sounds boring, too.
This great game you told me about... have you played it yet?
You said you might be shot soon, didn't you?
I'm so excited.
When?
When is that Japanese person going to shoot you?
Tell me, Johan.
Herman Hesse's Der Steppenwolf, first edition.
And this...
Hoffman's Nachtstucke, first edition.
You have an entire collection of Goethe's poems.
It's a book collection big enough to make even me,
the head librarian at Munich University's
Fredrich Emannuel Library, dizzy.
I made it this far in life with self-study.
I didn't go to college.
I thought that I'd just read books
to learn, and this is the result.
To have such a large collection of
books donated to my library, I..
I don't have enough words to thank you with.
My eyesight is getting worse, so soon
I won't be able to read them at all.
I think they'd do more good in the hands of students
rather than being allowed to sleep here in this room.
Yes, many of the books are valuable, but they
should be accessible to normal people too.
I've already set aside a place for them.
There will be a ceremony, so if
you could please speak at it...
What about security?
Ever since Mr. Schubert has taken control of his
companies, I've been worried about his safety.
Please make sure that the invited guests
are checked out thoroughly.
Isn't that right, Johan?
Yes.
Karl and Johan, who suggested that
I donate these books, will go.
I'm the Head Librarian, Gerhmann.
Nice to meet you.
Good to meet you, too.
Munich University Library
This will be the room where we are going to
put the books that Mr. Schubert is donating.
Regular visitors are not able to come back this far.
You probably have never been here either, have you?
The temperature and humidity are at optimum levels for storage
and, of course, this place is safe from fire or theft.
What a collection of great books!
This is truly a treasure of humanity.
Don't you think so, Johan?
A treasure of humanity, huh?
And we'll hold the donation ceremony in this center hall.
Just as your butler said, the security will be very tight.
I'd like Mr. Schubert to feel at ease.
Yeah.
I'm sure Dad will love it.
Isn't that right, Johan?
What's wrong Johan?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Are you looking for something?
Yes, I'm looking for a nice picture book for a friend.
A friend?
Yes, a friend.
Let's see. How about this one?
Isn't that a nice picture?
Yes, it is.
But it's a little too adult for him.
So your friend isn't a grown-up?
How about this one then?
Oh, no!
Thank you.
I'm a bit clumsy, so I'm always like this.
Ah, this is it.
This is the book I was going to suggest to you.
Do you like that one?
Oh, it has nice pictures. I wonder whose book that is.
Let me take a look.
Emil Scherbe...
The publisher is Moravia...
That publisher is located in Prague.
There are a lot of good picture book
artists in the Czech Republic.
But I've never heard of Scherbe.
He must not be very famous.
What's wrong?
Someone!
Someone come now!
This summer is so hot!
It's vicious!
"Announcing Mr. Hans Georg Schubert's Book
Collection Donation Ceremony and Speech."
This is the place.
From here, I'll kill him.
Yes... Gazing at what is known now in this world...
Yes... Your eyes believe in kindness...
Make it home... to your land of harmony...
Make it home... to your land of purity...
At the Edge of Darkness