What would you like?
The usual.
What was your usual again?
Why don't you remember it already, Robby?
A hamburger with extra cheese...
lots of ketchup, and thick tomatoes.
I'll kill you if you put pickles on it.
How am I supposed to remember that?
That Chinese or Vietnamese person...
He's been sniffing around about you.
That customer has been in here a lot lately.
He was asking me who you were.
He's not Chinese or Vietnamese.
He's probably Japanese.
On top of that, he's a brain surgeon.
With excellent skills.
Right?
Am I right, Dr. Tenma?
Answer me!
And he's the former fiancé of a
hospital director's daughter.
What are you trying to make Eva do?
Eva?
You're being too familiar with her.
How long do you plan on playing the fiancé?
From what I hear...
not only aren't you a doctor anymore,
but you're a fugitive, too.
Go to where you belong and fix yourself up!
You might be released someday,
if you're an exemplary inmate.
Release Eva!
Release her?
I'm not holding her or anything.
Not only that...
she's going to parties every day.
Let me see Eva.
See her?
Hey! Hey!
Don't mess up my diner!
Stop hanging around here. Get lost.
E-Eva...
Get lost.
The Man Who Saw the Devil
You met kenzo?
Yeah, two days ago.
Well, I thought I should let you know.
He wanted to see you.
I hope you didn't punch him.
N-No.
I wouldn't do something like that.
We're leaving.
You're done with today's party?
Not just today's party...
The party's over.
Probably.
Nice work, Eva.
Would you like to have dinner?
I'll go.
So...
you took her to the restaurant...
and you're having your dinner here?
Compared to the food served at parties
or high-class restaurants...
the hamburgers here are much better.
I don't know if that's a compliment or an insult.
You're persistent, aren't you?
You want to get hurt again?
Didn't you get it when I told you to...
Don't move, Manager!
I'll shoot if you do!
What a dangerous doctor.
Who hired you?
I know you work for The Baby.
However, the one who ordered you to look after Eva...
was someone even higher in the organization.
Who gave you the order?!
I don't know who it was.
But I do know his face.
He wears glasses.
A man that wears glasses?
What is he forcing Eva to do?
I told you already.
He's only making her appear at parties.
She drinks, eats, and then goes home.
That's all.
That can't be everything!
Eva must be doing something special there!
Nothing.
Actually, today...
Today?
No, it's nothing.
That woman pointed at someone.
Pointed at someone?
At a young man.
A young man...
Like this.
At a blond...
young man with a pretty face.
That's all she did, though.
Where is Eva right now?
She's having dinner with my glasses-wearing boss.
W-Where?!
Tell me!
Where are they?
Eva's job is probably over!
After I've finished this job....
I'll surely be killed.
The party's over.
Where is Eva?!
Wait!
W-Where is she?
I sent her back to her hotel.
Do you have a gun?
No.
I decided not to carry a gun with me.
Then use this.
Kill her.
Back then...
The party was going normally.
The smell of alcohol.
The fragrance of perfumes.
Meaningless laughter.
Everything was the same.
Except for that moment.
Eva pointed at a young man.
And then the glasses guy appeared...
bringing with him another well-dressed young man.
And then the two young men...
shook hands.
I didn't notice it at the time, but...
it appears that with that...
Eva's job was over.
So you're the one who's assigned to kill me.
Go ahead.
The alcohol is starting to kick in...
and I don't have anything left.
Oh, that's right.
I guess you can't shoot me in this hotel.
You said you shot your girlfriend before...
and stood in a sea of blood.
Then take me outside and shoot me.
Or else you'll have to pay for making the room all dirty.
There is one thing left that I'm attached to...
Oh, well. It doesn't really matter.
I wonder what I did today.
You saw me pointing at someone, didn't you?
I probably did something terrible.
I lured someone horrible to the devil.
I lured Mephisto and Faust together.
It doesn't matter to me.
Even though I don't have to attend parties anymore...
I still have invitations for upcoming parties here.
If you'd like, after I die...
would you fill in for me and see what I did?
Now then...
would you please finish me off?
Let's run away.
Let's run away together.
You must've gotten the wrong idea or something!
Run away with you?
You've gotta be kidding!
Since when did we become that close?
I...
can't kill people anymore.
You can't kill people?
Then can you kill devils?
I'm a devil!
That suit and tie I bought you...
looks exactly like what Kenzo used to wear!
Don't you get it?
I was just dressing you up to look like Kenzo Tenma!
kill me!
Hurry up and kill me!
Hurry up!
Hurry up and kill me.
If you don't hurry up and kill me...
you'll be killed.
Can I kill devils?
Hey, wake up!
It's okay.
I just want to sleep off this buzz a little.
You can't!
You'll die if you sleep in a place like this!
It's okay. Just leave me here.
You look grim.
I always look grim.
Did someone come looking for me?
No, no one.
Actually, the Japanese guy from last night left this.
Hellblau Hotel, room 205.
He said to contact him there if anything happens.
What'll you have?
The usual?
No thanks.
If I get full on shitty hamburgers...
I'll lose my will to go.
Where are you going?
A party.
It's strange.
I can get into anywhere with just one necktie.
Just one.
There he is.
So, is he a devil?
He shook so many hands...
that his hand should have been swollen.
And then he left the party hall.
Sixth floor, huh?
But which room?
Please come inside.
Please, have a seat here.
You don't have to be modest.
You want to see him as well, correct?
Him?
I'm waiting for him, too.
He'll be here soon.
Let's talk about something until he arrives.
What should we talk about?
Oh, I know.
Let's talk about the world coming to an end.
That kid kept talking like a machine.
It was just like...
a child telling his parents all the fun things
that happened at school today.
That was how he talked to me.
The story of the world coming to an end, my ass.
It was just some nonsense this crazy kid was spouting.
That's what I thought at the time.
What do you think?
Wasn't it an interesting story?
Did you enjoy listening, Mr. Martin?
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know.
Let's talk about you next.
You've been working for The Baby for three years now.
Did you investigate me?
You were in prison before that.
Those eight years must have been tough.
You were a model inmate, right?
You were able to get out of the place,
even though you committed murder.
Was it fun?
Living with her.
The woman you killed, I mean.
Her name was Edda.
You sure have poor taste, kid.
She was a terrible drug addict.
You tried your best to get her off the drugs.
It's not something that's easy to do.
Was it love?
Do you want to get hurt?
She got back on her feet.
She cooked dinner and waited for you to return.
A happy life started.
I'm asking if you want to get beat up.
But on that night...
you saw a terrible sight when
you returned to your room.
Her old boyfriend was in the room.
She was doing drugs again.
She looked at you...
and mumbled something.
She kept repeating to herself.
I'm sorry.
But you shot and killed her, along with the man.
That's what was determined at the trial, wasn't it?
Why did you lie?
She killed herself, didn't she?
Your attorney found gunpowder on her hands...
so he deduced that she committed suicide.
However, you still confessed to killing her.
She begged you to kill her, didn't she?
I was right!
I was right, wasn't I?
I knew it!
You're not the one who shot her!
She asked you, didn't she?
To shoot her.
Shoot me.
Don't look at me like that!
kill me!
Martin!
It wasn't me!
She shot herself!
It wasn't me, right? Right?
I knew it.
That's amazing! I was right, wasn't I?
You're wrong.
You deserted her.
That's how you made her desire come true.
No!
Then what about your mother?
Your mother.
She froze to death when you were ten, correct?
You deserted your mother back then, too.
I was right again?
Amazing!
This is amazing!
I'm surprised I was actually right!
You carried your alcoholic mother home
on your back every day, right?
And your mother kept telling you...
to leave her.
Even so, you still carried your mother back every day.
However, that night...
You can't sleep in a place like this!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Leave me here.
Wake up!
You left her there.
Am I right?
You left your mother there, didn't you?
The next morning, you were told...
that your mother froze to death.
But at the time, you thought to yourself...
that it wasn't your fault.
You only left her there because she asked you to.
That's exactly right.
It wasn't your fault.
Both your mother and your drug-addicted
girlfriend wanted to die.
You only let those who wanted to die, die.
You aren't wrong. You're right!
You set them free from the misery of living.
Eva wants to die, too.
Just then, the devil arrived.
I passed by, making sure not to look at the devil.
I can't look...
I must not look at him.
I recited that to myself, like a child.
Yes
Ima kono seka de
Gazing at what is known
wakaru koto
mitsumeta
now in this world
Yes
Anata no hitomi no
Your eyes believe in kindness
yasashisa wo
shinjite
Make it home
to your land of harmony
to your land of purity
Make it home
The Man Who Knew Too Much