TENMA
That was amazing!
Yeah, he's as good as ever!
He could clip such a difficult part of the brain tumor at such a speed!
Yeah.
That was a great operation, Dr. Tenma.
I've confirmed once again that Tenma Kenzo is a genius.
No, it's all thanks to you all.
Thank you.
It's already getting so hot.
Yeah.
After all, it was a six-hour operation.
There's no visitors today.
Get some rest.
Hey, where's Dad?
What happened to Dad?
Tenma, Tenma, Tenma!
Tenma, Tenma!
Tenma!
Hey, get up.
Get up, Dr. Tenma.
It's the other way around, isn't it?
A princess like me is supposed to wake up with a kiss.
Eva, you're here.
You forgot your date, didn't you, Tenzo?
No, I didn't forget.
I don't think she's asleep.
Hey, you can't get up.
It's your news.
Rosenbacher's diagnosis is a ruptured cerebral artery.
The operation itself went as planned.
The clipping went very well.
Mr. Rosenbacher has a lot of fans.
Is there a possibility of his recovery?
Yes.
I'll do my best to revive his singing voice.
It's a team of Dr. Heinemann who have succeeded in many difficult operations so far.
With this operation,
you can say that they have made their position in the medical world of our country unwavering again.
That's great, Tenzo.
It's not my news.
It's your dad's news.
That's true.
But that's because you had a perfect operation on your father's team last night.
I'm sure your father is grateful.
You're the one who raised the reputation of the hospital.
I'm the one who should be grateful.
I can do this in Germany because of your father.
Do your best, Tenzo.
If you follow your father, you'll be fine.
It's only a matter of time before your father becomes the chairman of the hospital.
Then you'll be the head of the department soon.
You'll be the director soon.
And I'll be the director's wife.
Be happy.
I don't like hard work.
Do you want to go out?
Or...
Blood pressure is 128-64.
Novela.
I'm going to cut the pyramids from now on.
It was still a great operation, Dr. Tenma.
Thank you very much.
It seems that you're not only good at surgery.
At that young age, you sat in the position of the chief.
The director and the head of the department are your favorites.
And you even solved the heart of the director's daughter.
What do you want to say, Dr. Becker?
I'm sorry.
I'm not saying anything in a bad way.
The hospital is a world of politics.
You know you're being used by the director, don't you?
The operation of the opera house you succeeded in.
It's like you did it yourself.
It's a press conference on TV.
Well, being used means that you have the ability.
If you succeed, please take care of me.
I'll treat you to a drink next time.
What is it?
Are you Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
Give me back my husband.
Give me back my husband!
Why didn't you operate on my husband?
You are...
My husband was brought to this hospital earlier.
He was brought in before the opera house.
But you made him a fool.
You are the best doctor in this hospital.
Why?
At that time, I was certainly...
I was about to be hit by the operation of the opera house.
Dr. Tenma.
Yes.
You're not here.
Please go to the first operating room.
I'm the director.
Please hurry.
You...
If you had operated on me, I would have been saved.
Mom!
Give me back my husband.
My husband!
Mom!
So,
I'm going to steal that dress with my friend.
I only have one of that size.
But don't worry.
I made it mine.
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
What happened?
I saw Karte.
Dr. Becker was the one who stole the Turkish opera house.
I don't want to talk about that.
It's obvious that it's taking too long to start the treatment.
If I had stolen it,
I might have been able to save the Turkish opera house.
Stop it.
But what am I supposed to do?
I only did what the director told me to do.
I only operated on that opera singer.
I'm not responsible for it.
Right?
Of course you are.
People's lives are not equal.
Give it back!
Give my husband back!
Is that the house?
Yes.
The car is nearby.
How many shots were fired?
Five or six.
Who lives in this house?
Well...
It's the house of Mr. Lieber,
who has been missing from East Germany.
This is going to be troublesome.
I'll break in after I count to three.
One, two, three.
What's going on?
Someone's there!
Survivors confirmed.
One girl.
Two boys.
One boy.
One more time.
It's a traffic jam.
It's an emergency.
A bullet in the head?
Is that the only boy in the Klan family?
Yes.
His parents died instantly.
It looks like a robbery.
All right.
I'll be at the hospital in five minutes.
Oh, father.
I'm sorry, Director Heineman.
I didn't know you were so important.
What are you talking about, Tenma?
Eva is your fiancée.
How is it?
Would you like to have a cup of tea?
Did you contact your Japanese parents on the day of the wedding?
Oh, yes.
But, my father works at a small hospital.
I don't know if I'll have time to come to Germany.
It's a good opportunity.
Why don't you enjoy your trip abroad?
That's right.
I'll invite you to my house.
Thank you.
I owe you so much.
When I came to Germany, I thought you were a high school boy.
But now, you're the youngest doctor in the Aisler Memorial Hospital.
By the way, Kenzo.
Are you doing a brain hemorrhage research on the hematoma?
Yes.
I'm making a model of a dog's hematoma.
But, that research is canceled.
What?
I'm going to announce it as a symposium at the next meeting of the European Association of Emergencies.
I want you to organize the research.
Ah...
But, the research will be organized soon.
But, I can't do it this afternoon.
What happened, father?
A suspicious private organization came to the hospital.
They are making a fuss about the operation of the opera singer the other day.
They said that they postponed the operation of the injured Turkish man who was brought in first.
It's a complete misunderstanding.
The operation was done by the Turkish man first.
There is no problem with our continuation.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
They are mistaken that the doctor is a volunteer or something.
Before we save people's lives, we have to...
Isn't that right?
Anyway, I'm counting on you to organize my presentation.
I'm expecting you, Tenma.
Thank you.
Huh!
Damn it!
Where is Clank?
He just went inside.
What's the situation?
Blood pressure is 72 to 50.
The pulse is 137.
The bullet is from the front of the head.
Take a X-ray picture immediately.
Yes.
Ah, Dr. Tenma.
Who is this girl?
She is the twin sister of the boy.
What's her name?
I don't know.
But she seems to have a psychological shock.
What is it?
Kill me.
Dr. Tenma.
The head picture and CT scan are done.
I got it. I'm going now.
It's from the front of the head to the center of the brain.
Yes.
This is difficult.
What?
The bullet is piercing the left ventricle.
I see.
Dr. Tenma is right.
This is troublesome.
If the bullet is moved even a little, it may explode and bleed.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Dr. Becker.
What are you doing so late?
We will remove the skull and brain by removing the front of the head.
And carefully remove the bullet.
Finally, we will form a damaged blood vessel.
It will take some time.
Let's do our best.
Blood pressure is 120 to 80.
Blood pressure is 92.
He is anesthetized.
Dr. Tenma.
Yes.
You are not here.
Please go to the first operating room at once.
Dr. Becker collapsed in a brain hemorrhage.
He is heading here by helicopter.
He will arrive in 10 minutes.
Please contact Dr. Boyer.
There is a possibility of a hemorrhage.
If so, you will go.
But I was just about to start the operation for that child.
This is a message from the director.
Yes.
This is Tenma.
Oh, Tenma.
Please take care of the mayor.
I also contacted Dr. Eisen and Dr. Boyer.
This is perfect.
But, director.
I was just about to start another operation.
You can leave it to Dr. Becker.
I am sorry to say this.
The operation we are about to start is a very difficult operation.
But I am confident that I can do it.
I will leave the mayor to Dr. Boyer.
I can't do the operation for that child unless I go.
Tenma.
Please do your best to save the mayor.
The mayor has promised to increase the amount of money for our hospital for the next medical examination.
I can't let him die yet.
I'm counting on you, Tenma.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
The mayor has arrived at the heliport.
The operation will start soon after the CT scan.
Please confirm the blood clot.
Now, get ready, Dr. Tenma.
I'm counting on your genius skills.
I think the doctor is a volunteer.
We have to save people's lives.
Right?
I just did the operation as the mayor ordered.
I have no responsibility.
Of course.
People's lives are not equal.
Give it back to me.
I would have been saved if you did the operation.
What's wrong, Dr. Tenma?
I...
I'm waiting for the operation over there.
Hey, Dr. Tenma.
It's the director's order.
The mayor is having a CT scan now.
The doctor is in a hurry to the infirmary.
Okay.
Wait, Dr. Tenma.
Dr. Tenma.
It's okay.
Hang in there.
I'll save you.
Kill me.