No class
I want you to tell me what was the basis for the ruling the judge made in regards to the 19
The age Stuttgart
Oh boy what is this silence why are we some kind of a monastery
Mr Reimer
I'd like to hear your answer if you have one
Well sir
That is to say I anyone
Is there anyone in this room who can break this silence
So The Chronic light coming is here at last
You're 13 minutes tardy
Send your part-time pizza delivery job kept you awfully busy today
I'm sorry
Professor
Well let me ask you a question before you sit down
Do you have enough strength left to tell me the basis for the ruling in the 1968 Stuttgart case
Oh yes
Well
The defense claim
That the kidnapping was a sham
And the victim's death have been to the poisoning
After an investigation into the crime scene
It was found that the victim's death had been accidental
And that there was no motive
So
Since the crime couldn't be proven to be an intentional murder
I believe a sentence of 15 years was handed down
Very good
You can take your seat Nina for tonight
Yes professor
Wow good job Nina
If no one had been able to give him the answer I have no doubt that kronecker would have probably demanded we write a 50 page report
50 pages if we were lucky
I'll have to treat Our Savior Nina to something to eat
What are you say Nina a nice meal Just the Two of Us
Oh I'm sorry Peter but I have a club meeting today bye
She turned you down again
Hey Peter how many times was that come on shut up as if one of you losers could actually score a date with her
Oh my gosh if I'm late
My deliveries the manager is going to be furious
Hi I'm home
Boy am I hungry oh my the neighbors can probably hear you you are such a child
Go and wash your hands dear
Yes ma'am
Hey Mom you dyed your hair
What do you think
At your age
I don't think you should be dying your hair such a bright color I don't agree with you dad I think mom looks great
Looks like she's going to some costume parade
It's nice to know mom is still young
Hi Dad
Oh and that reminds me speaking of costumes
I saw some kids dressed up from head to toe today
Oh yes today supposed to be the same Hadrian costume parade
I wish I had dressed up like that when I was a little girl
They were so adorable
Yeah you did dress up in a costume once
Isn't that right dear that's right I completely forgotten really
Let's see it's around here
Oh look here it is
He was so cute
Yes I did
You are so excited and made such a fuss
Isn't that right dear yeah I remember
Costume parade huh
Distance spring
I forlornly wait for a spring that will never come
Hannah
Moana
When you get over your break up already
I shall send you the most beautiful flowers
I was born to smother you with flowers
So beautiful
Wow
I wonder who sent this
Ah
I'm very impressed with you Peter
So
How have you been Nina
Well
I've been very well lately Dr guidel
That's good to hear
But of course I could tell just by the look on your face when you came into this session that you were doing well
So
Tell me are you still having that nightmare
The one about the monster emerging from the darkness
I've been sleeping very well I've been so busy I don't have time to dream
I wonder why I was playing by such a dream night after night
It's common for students to feel fear and anxiety
Expectations of the future mix up with other insecurities
People end up confused losing sight of who they are
But who you are is something you can spend your whole life trying to grasp and never figure out completely
We're always projecting and trying to look into the future
We spend our whole lives looking for the answers and we do the best we can
Right and that's what I'm doing
I want to become a federal prosecutor
That's very good
All right I think that brings us to the end of our session
Bye and thank you doctor
Nina Fortuner
Such a cheerful girl
I can't help thinking that she's overcompensating or running from something
Something
Overwhelmingly dark
What do you mean what
Don't act so innocent
What in the world are you going on about
I was born to smother you with flowers
I would never have guessed in a million years you had such talent for writing poetry
I don't know what you're talking about
I wouldn't be able to come up with really stuff like that even if I stood on my head
Then who was it
I only give my email address to friends and no one else
Beats me
Damn it what this means is some Suave poetry guys honing in on my girl
Hello
How could it be
This was a bizarre murder that took place in Munich
After shooting the parents to death
The perpetrators strangled there to children with a rope
Grizzly really
No I would like you to explain the verdict
Using the records from all of the hearings
Nina Fortuner
What do you not understand the question
No
The trial was focused mainly
On the cold blooded murder
Of an entire family
So not even Nina has all the answers huh
Nina and what's wrong Nina
Are you all right
You want to go see the nurse
I'm all right
I just felt a little ill that's all
I was just
Listening to the professor
You mean that question about that murdered family
Don't say that
Is that it
I thought you were awfully brave but I guess
You're pretty sensitive too
Did you watch a horror movie that totally scared you when you were a kid or something
I know exactly what that counselor Dr guidel would say
If you get back to the root of it I think that you'll find
It was nothing significant now go back to your childhood
Am I right
That's it
I have no
I remember nothing before the age of 10
Where are my memories
My childhood memories
Yes
Those two were indeed a very nice couple
To think that they died in such a way
Children
Now that you mentioned it yes there was a son his name was Michael I do believe
He was there for a year or two
Let's see a boy
Do you remember if there was a boy
Yes there was
Wasn't his name Michael
He was 14 give or take
Michael you say
Yeah I think I remember him
But
Why
Who are you the police
Yes Michael Redman
I remember him vaguely but he was a student in my classroom
He didn't leave much of an impression I'm embarrassed to say it but honestly I don't remember him very well
I'm not sure if he had any friends
You see there are no records left from then
Everything went up in a fire about 6 years ago now
They're definitely was a boy named Michael living here in
Until 6 years ago and Michael's real name is
You hun huh yes there was a time when I went by that name
Are you what does it matter what's the use he's a serial killer
In order of twin siblings that's all there is to it nothing else
What am I doing
Twins his sister where did his twin sister go
I will pick you up very soon who is this he'll be picking me up very soon
But what does that mean
A child
Oh yes there was a boy about seven or eight years ago and Mrs hyena had taken a boy in
Before they were killed
And what was he like
What was he like
That was quite a long time ago
And I think he only really lived with them for about a year or so
I honestly don't remember anything about him
Wait do you remember if this boy had a sister no only the boy listen I just want to forget about
What happened to that poor couple after all those horrible things happened I almost moved away
I remember that boy very well
Why don't you come up
I was about to have some tea
Come in have a
Yes thank you
I was wondering just have a seat
Go ahead absentee
Thank you sir
You're a doctor right that boy was the one who told me you are
Dr tinma
He's coming to pick you up
Who is he
I have no idea who he is
It was just an anonymous email
Aw you look so happy
You're not thinking this is Prince Charming on a white charger or a knight in shining armor coming for you are you
Why are you jealous
There you go Nina daydreaming again
It said I was born to smother you with flowers
Come on that's so corny how many boys do you know who write like that
Oh
Hold on wait
There is a new guy in our class you know who I'm talking about
Oh I've seen him
He's the guy who sits quietly in that legendary Seton room 12 where you're bound to be called
That's right and you want to know what else
He is always staring at Nina the entire class
He's the one what do you mean
Come on you know Prince Charming who else
All I know is that boy was extremely grateful to you yes Dr tema
He told me more than once it because you saved his life you meant more to him than his parents
What name did he go by then
Fronts
Then what he did tell me it wasn't his real name
If he opened up enough to tell you that much it means he must have really trusted you
He just showed up one day out of nowhere really
Mr and Mrs heinek who lived across the hole took him in
He lived with them for about a year
No
Actually it was it was a 14 months to be precise from March 1987
Happened to April 1988
And then one day out of the blue he suddenly vanished it
It really was very bright that boy
Very well manner
Did he visit you in your apartment very often
Everyday
I live alone so I always welcome to company
He said in that chair
And would spend most of his time studying
He was able to master the English and French that I taught him in no time
By the time he disappeared he was completely fluent in both languages
He was only 12 years old
Can you tell me if there's anything else you remember about him anything
He was always interested in listening to my stories
And what kind of stories do you think he liked best to go on take a wild guess
You like my War Stories War Stories
During World War II
I was on the crew of a U-Boat the boy's favorite store it was about the time we
We were attacked by a destroyer of the Allied Forces
We were the depth of 120 M that's when we were attacked by the enemy
We had suffered a mortal blow that we just kept going we all waited and teared inside that cre
Boat enduring hour after hour
We had to endure that hell for the day and a half
Any ordinary child would have probably looked at this as another adventure story but
That boy was different what he was most interested in was my description of ultim
Sia yes ultimate fear that reaction of people on the verge of death
He toyed with fear
So what
What was the expression on his face as he listened he probably had it gleam in his eye
Smile I imagine imagine well I cannot see Dr Denmark
So no I don't know the boys real name nor obviously do I have any idea
Looks like for that matter earlier you suggested the boy trusted me because he told me fr
Wasn't his real name I can assure you that he doesn't trust anyone there's only one person
Boys trusted in his life and that's his sister listen I need to help I'm
Looking for that sister he said he would go get her when she turns 20
In Heidelberg
See you later
Be careful on your scooter honey
I will
Bye see you later Daddy
And drive safely okay
See you later
The time has come
Has
I know
We made an agreement
We said we'd tell her on her 20th birthday
That she isn't our real daughter
Hold on a second I'm not sure I can do this what are you talking about you wanted to meet
He told him you wait from here it's better you didn't know don't mess it up you're about to meet Prince Charming
Later wait Clara
How could they do this behind my back
It's him here we go
Hi how do you
You do your Nina Fortuner right oh good yeah my name is out
Huberman
Who are you seen that face somewhere before
Who
Who are you
Can you hear me