It looks like another scorcher today hey
Why are you all bundled up on a hot summer day like this aren't you broiling huh you're reading an old paper
That one's at least 3 days old yeah a couple inverted got themselves murdered they say
Doctor did it if you can believe that hey buddy you said you were headed for burden wasn't that right
What you know somebody over there yeah I do I'm not even sure if he'll still be there now
I have to try and find them
Formerly served in the French Foreign Legion
Then when freelance and fought in Nicaragua in 1979
From 1981 to 1984 assisted the Guerrilla rebels in Afghanistan
Then in 1987 you played a key role in the assassination of radical Islamic leaders in
Top secret moussard operation
It's quite an impressive resume I must admit
Isn't it Mr Hugo Bernhardt
I have no doubt that a mercenary of your caliber must be quite a teacher and I'm sure a number of distinguished
Men must have been under your instruction
It might be a good idea to send some of our own officers to attend your seminar and have you with them into shape
That'd be great
Incidentally
Was this man here a good student by any chance I believe he showed up at your training grounds about 5 months
Months ago
We know that he is a genius with a scalpel
What I'm wondering about is whether he has any Talent with a gun
I don't divulge information about my pupils to anyone period
Of course you don't
So have you ever trained with a gun before no I guess that means that yourself taught then
Actually
I've never shot a gun before
What you mean not even once right
I know I'm asking for the impossible
Matt said you're my only hope right now
It makes no difference
I make all my students forget everything they learned before they got here
But this
This is the first time I'll be teaching someone who's never shot a gun before
Jump rope
Regardless of your experience or lack of this is where everyone starts now jump like that child over there
Don't just stand there
Well get started
Yes sir
Faster now hurry it up
I said faster
Balance it's all about balance
Come on faster
I said faster
Well obviously I can't jump rope nearly as well as you do
Tell me something is this what you do you know always supervising
Student training like this all right I understand you don't have to
To keep on staring at me like that
I'll do it
I know what I have to do
Hey it's a brandling I wonder
Wonder if it's looking for food for its chicks
What's wrong are you too tired to eat
Yes
You can't train if you pass out
Yes sir
She your daughter
Or your granddaughter Maybe
Neither
That little girl is the daughter of a woman I killed
Shut it down right before very eyes
Backing me on my
On Mission in the jungle I ran into a hut for shelter
And there she was with her mother
Her mother was holding a gun if I'd have been a fraction of a second slower it would have been me that
Not that day
I brought the child back here with me I couldn't just leave her
From that moment on
She hasn't smiled once
That's why
She'll probably hate me for the rest of her life
That's the sort of thing that happens when you have
A gun now if you can't handle that then I'd suggest you don't carry one
What's that what a person sometimes it smells just like Daphne blossom
Thanks
All right that's enough of that
So then
Time for some more running go
Yes sir
Right away then
When you're done running come to the bottom of the hill in the back
What's down there the firing range
The firing range
Remember
Two shots
You have to make sure that whenever you fire your gun you always pull the trigger twice if you can do that instinctively it better is your
Chances of taking out your objective
If you can't do that
Then you're as good as Dad it's all over
What's this about you're always preparing meals for me so I thought it would cook for you today
It's a Japanese stew of meat and potatoes it's called nikujaga go on dig in I think you'll both enjoy it
Those are chopsticks they're carved out of wood I made them I thought it would make
Our dining experience more authentic
Wow you're really good at using Chopsticks aren't you
Again faster
Do it again
What's wrong
It's a baby brambling I guess it fell out of its nest huh no wait
You have to put it back and that chick is going to die it's very difficult to
Erase them like that they rarely survive for that long outside of the nest
Let's put it back
With its mother okay
3 seconds
That's all the time you've got
Find your target and pull the trigger cuz one mistake of the slightest bit of hesitation and you're dead
Tell me how well did he perform over those 5 months he was there training
With you
Technically speaking he was a perfect student
He built up the necessary stamina
And his concentration while firing was extraordinary
However
Being able to actually shoot a person is another story
Really
Whether or not he is successful on his first kill
That's what it all comes down to
Either he's got what it takes or he doesn't yes I see
I wonder which road this man will choose
Well it matters not
Tell me
Do you have any idea where he might have gone
Because if you do know where I would really like for you to tell me
Thanks for all you've done for me over the past 5 months
Here's the remaining tuition I owe
And please help yourself to the necojaga
Again
Thank you for everything
Damn it
She's laughing
So how about it you do know where this man was heading don't you
That I can't tell you
That's
Fine you can go now
This way sir