One man
Have a
Wait a second where's the Cherry
It's not a Manhattan without the Cherry
Yeah my
I'll let it
This time
Business always goes well when I'm sucking on one of these
A lucky charm is a lucky char
Come to Papa
I just hope there's still something of value we're taking
Well well
Looking what we've got here
It's a five finger free for all
Wonder if there's anything valuable enough for a connoisseur like Auto Hackle
You never know what's going to happen first year issue in Canada for governor next thing you and your wife get shot
LOL
Down to business
I'm guessing this is where they kept it safe
Am I getting the chills this is creepy as hell I've never felt anything like this could
Could somebody be in there as
What am I so scared about it ain't like me to be a chicken move
Put your hands behind your head
Oh man I can't believe this damn bartender at his fault he forgot the Cherry
I said put your hands up all right all right all right
Give me a break on this one officer I haven't taken anything yet I promise
I'm not a cop
No
So you're robbing the place too huh
Well in that case why don't you just put that thing away and we'll have our hands behind your head now
Geez what's with this guy's a bigger boy scout than the freaking cops
You got to be kidding me thanks for nothing buddy come out of here don't follow me
Someone like you just get in the way you'll call me down
That's right I thought I recognized you you're all over the
You're the doctor wanted for questioning and connection with councilman Springs Missouri are you a thief
But I got something called morals I don't go around killing people you wouldn't know anything about the murders that happened in that house would
No idea so get out of my face will you later
Hey doctor
You're some sort of top notch surgeon aren't you
My brilliant brain just came up with a fantastic idea
Do you think that people meet by chance doctor they don't
Believe me I know
I believe in fate
I think people meet for a reason
And my gut tells me you and I were destined to become partners
Call me crazy but I think a lot of folks in the underground Community need someone like you
You know guys who need to hide out so they can't go to regular doctors for help
Listen you leave the management to Old Heckle here
I'll make you the world's best underground doctor in no time I'm telling you that you're going to make a lot of money you'll be
Hey hey doctor what do you think you're going
There's something I have to do and it can't wait
Well I'd hold my horses if I were you you want to know about the murders in that house don't you
Well I guess you'd like to hear that I saw the killer am I right
What did you say
Are you telling me the truth you want to know what did he look like I need to know what's the Killer Blonde and about 20 years of age
What do you want about
Never mind you just tell me about who you saw there
Team up with me and I'd be happy to doctor
He's on the third floor
So how did you come to know all of this anyway
I spent a month checking out the councilman's
Case in the joint I do my home
Just when I'm ready to make a move the killer beats me to it
15 minutes later I look in the window and they're dead worm food
And when I figured I might be able to Blackmail the murderer so I followed him here
This is all you really need to prove your innocence doc know what I'm saying all you have to do is call the police and tell him
After that we should go somewhere
Sit down relax talk over a drink about our future together as partners
Hey
Stop what are you doing what do you want to talk to him for what did you miss the part where he murders people
Man what is he thinking looking for trouble like that I'm out of here
However
A cash cow like him is a rare opportunity
Damn I usually make it a rule not to stick my neck out but
Another hot afternoon isn't it
I have I'm actually looking for someone
Doctor
What are you doing he's got a gun dummy mother and I
We often used to go walking together
On summer afternoon's a lot like this one there was a long road we took
And alongside of the field of sunflowers but mother's dead now
This is important so I need you to listen did someone ask you to use that gun tell me was it a man
Implicit a man it was one day this young man came up to me at a local bar and was he
About 20 years old with blonde hair
He was
And he had a Big Bright Beautiful Smile
Called himself
So he's going by
We met a few times and we eventually became very close friends
He invited me over to the
The place where he was staying
It was the estate of councilman Springer
Did he live in that Mansion until recently
Yes he did for a year
He said they took
Took good care
He was like a son to
Wait a minute I had my eye on that house for a month it never saw anyone who looked like that
They were a wonderful family
I have a picture
The councilman
His wife and me
However
There was something I couldn't forgive them for
There was a beautiful area on their property
A bit of sunflowers in their yard
But one day the councilman cleared it all up in order to build a big
Driveway
So when I mentioned to my young friend that I thought it was awful I was delighted to discover he agreed
Wait are you saying you actually killed them because of some flowers
Hardly
There was more to it
He also told me
Councilman Springer had a mistress
That's when my friend looked at me and said
I've decided I no longer wish to live with or be a member of the Springer house
From now on I'm not a part of that family anymore
Then he proceeded to request of me
That I erase
The family
Having a mistress is so an excusable
My mother was someone's mistress too
She was kept woman you know
Listen listen don't think about all that stuff by the way did or the safest in that house
I believe
On the second floor in the library
All right then
Talk to you probably shouldn't stick around here
You can erase your past did you know that
If you don't like it you can erase everything you can erase all of it
You can reset your entire life if you want sorry I don't agree with that at all you may try to
Forget but no one can simply erase their past like that
Yeah I guess you're right
I wonder why I thought
Doesn't make any sense to me now
Why did I think I could erase the past by pulling the trigger
Looking back I wonder why I listened to him and did what he ask
I think you should go now our talk is over I have nothing more to say
Oh that's right
Your name is Dr Tena isn't it
He left a message behind for you
Do make sure you take a good look at it
You'll find it in the councilman's library
He predicted that you would come here and he was correct about that Eric also mentioned to me
Your Fate has already been decided for you so has mine
Doctor
I told you didn't I
Did you actually shoot this guy
Oh suicide I got you
What the hell
Everything's over when you're dead it makes no sense
Hey doctor there's nothing like living am I right
You know I think I actually agree with you for a change hey what exactly do you mean for a change
Anyway so you're after this killer named Johanna whatever I don't get it I really don't know why you do that
Hey why don't you forget about this nonsense in team up with me
Oh by the way I don't know why but when I try to open the door to this room before it kind of gave me the creeps
What the
What's the matter you shaking like a leaf dog
Look at me look at me the monster inside me
Johansson mrso just a game to you isn't it
Hey Doc wait up
Oh come on wait listen to me hey Doc I'm talking to you oh for crying out loud
I've got some really good news to tell you you're going to thank me for this
You'll keep your promise in team up with me right
I never said I came up with you
Hey
I just thought you might need some money to run from the cops but I guess I was wrong
Just getting the car
This is our first client
The nice man will escort you to your patient doc
I'll hang on to your things for now if you want them back you'd better do your job get paid the rest and meet up with me at
So long now get out there and earn your keep
Now that's what I call a profitable business
Sincerity got in advance I suppose it's time to go and have a drink
Hey counselor I brought back a doctor for you
Thank you for coming doctor
Hurry
Please stop the bleeding
It appears your auxiliary artery has been damaged
Did you get hit by a shotgun
Yeah
Hey the doctor is empty-handed did you get the surgical equipment
It was too dangerous in the city I couldn't get that far
I could not operate on you here even if I had the proper equipment he needs to be
Equipped Hospital
About how long ago was he wounded can the questions doctor
4 hours ago huh
Are you involved in the terrorist attack this morning and what does it matter if we were
I won't do it
What the hell did you say
I'm not helping people who took others lives and discriminately
When you're in right now either you help him or you die
Calm down Carl
Listen daughter our friends will be coming to help us soon so it's simple
All you need to do is stop the bleeding to buy me some time
What the hell do you think you're doing do you want to die I already told you to come down
Counsel
I know you listen to me very carefully
My life is in this doctor's hands right now
If I die
You can shoot
We're not running a charity here no you are so you got to pay back the $250,000 marks
Simple as that auto Heckle but Mr gloss I want to pay you back sir that's nice I'm
Glad you feel that way
How cons
Now go on ahead and break both his
No I'll get it I'm getting them pay you back I will
That's a good boy
Take both his legs too
They are Max steindor
Oh please please wait
For any information
Leading to the arrest of the terrorists
Wait a minute it's them
I can pay you back that money I know where those guys are I really do and that'll take care of what I owe you
This it better
The truth otherwise I'm going to break your scrawny necklace
Oh man that's right I forgot to understand with those guys
Oh well who cares
You called me a murderer who goes around killing people and discriminately
Well you're wrong doctor
What I did had meaning there was a good reason for what I did
Now
The president of gwe is dead I can finally die in peace
I really don't mind
I achieved what I set out to do
Counselor
I used to be a lawyer in East Germany
My friend here
Political
And when the Wall came down
We lost our jobs
Do you have any idea what it is like for us
After the wall felt gwe came to the east with their big funding
They barged in and built these factories on our land
One after another
That was our country Our Land
Bad no right to do that
They stepped all over our pride
Well I'm proud to have shot that bastard
I'm glad that
Counselor
It's called
Hang
Just hang on our friends will be here soon
They won't come
I have a feeling that our
Won't be joining us
Stop the bleeding
No doctor
Hurry I'll shoot you
Don't do
I don't want to die
I don't want
Are you afraid are you afraid of dying
Well now you know what they all felt like the 12 people you killed that's how they died this is what they
Through
Now do you know what it means to kill someone get
Disinfectant is that too much to ask
Ontario bleeding is pretty bad he's in a State of Shock from low blood pressure and I can keep my
My hand pressed against the wound to stop the bleeding I'm going to have to suture the open flesh here
Needle and thread we don't have that fine then a stapler will do what a stapler
Yes sir
All right
What what do you think you're doing you have done what I can he needs to get to a hospital
What the hospital no
What are you thinking if you don't put him down right now I'll tell you pull the trigger if you want but
If you kill me know this you're going to have to carry into the hospital yourself
Put me down
Right here
Save yourself
I just realized I seen your face somewhere before
You're the doctor wanted in connection with the serial murders aren't you
Put me down dammit
What I did this morning was not an indiscriminate attack
The men I killed for the president of gwe
His luckiest
And his bodyguard
And they all had it coming
So you're telling me there were no innocent victims in that shooting
You're talking about that girl at the new
You already knew about it then
You knew you shot that girl didn't you
Why did you bother saving a man like me
It wasn't because you were afraid to get shot you weren't afraid to die I could tell by the look in your eyes
So why did you do it
Why save a terrorist like me why would you even bother
Because I believe in you
I have faith in your Humanity
You should get going the police will be here soon
You hang in there
You
You are truly a great doctor
And the money
What happened to the money
Hey Doc don't tell me you fixed him and just left without getting paid
What did you say something come on
Hey we ain't operating no charity outfit here doc