Well Well you certainly have found an excellent piece of property
It's only a 20 minute drive to the center of Berlin perfectly situated in a convenient and love
Lovely neighborhood
It's rare to find a unique property of such caliber especially on the east side
I Can Only Imagine
If I'm not mistaken wasn't this the residents of Mr Liebert the former head of Commerce of East Germany
You don't know how buyer you just came to investigate Mr Liebert is that all
Please forgive me but I just need some information
I don't know anything about an official who died almost 10 years ago
Apparently Mr Liebert and his wife adopted fraternal twins during the time that they were here I told you I don't know
Anything well who owns the property
Can you direct me to them
Listen a lot of the property in former East Germany used to be owned by Jews who had to flee during the Nazi regime
In some cases the government ended up borrowing land from people on the west side or in other countries
The owner of this property is overseas
Besides
My company is a Westside real estate firm that entered the Eastern Market after the wall hell
We don't know anything about the past now if you could please hurry and leave I'm locking up
Isn't there anyone who might remember
Could there possibly be someone who knew the leverts
It's like I already told you this was a residential area where many high-ranking officials live
Most of them fled soon after the wall came down
Especially the officials from the ministry of the interior
Come to think of it
An ex-official from the East German Department of Commerce lives about 10 houses away
Yeah I remember Mr Liebert
I'll never understand why you decided to take such a risk if only he had waited just a little longer until East Germany
Collapsed
It makes you wonder why you went to a free country only to be killed in the end
It's a damn shame really
Do you remember if Mr Liebert had children twins perhaps
Did he have twins you say
Oh yes that's right
Mr Liebert adopted those twins from The Orphanage are you sure
That's right those two are such cute kids
Mr Liebert always did talk about wanting children
Which orphanage was it
Which one was it
Yes that's right I believe they came from 511 kinderheim
I'm sorry
511 kinderheim
They're planning on turning this old orphanage into a supermarket sometime soon
About time thank goodness they're finally going to destroy this creepy building
Excuse me ma'am by any chance do you know anyone from this place
The orphanage
Everyone from there is long since gone
I really prefer not to talk about it
It was such a tragedy
But I if you want to find out more about it
There's a former official from the old Ministry of welfare named Hartman over on 47th Street
Hello there
Do you know if a man named Hartman lives around here
Wait what's wrong you're injured
Let me take a look
Don't be afraid I'm not going to hurt you
You reinjured an old wound
It's infected but this should help
Attaboy
I know this stings but it'll help you get better
There you go all done
Be careful okay
You might get hurt again
Heart mon
After the fall of East Germany I became the foster parent to all those kids you see photographed up on the wall
Foster parent yes well it just means that I took care of them until they were adopted or eventually able to go
Go off on their own
The boy in the middle was adopted by the president of an accessories company
And the last one on the left
Is enlisted in the army
I still have one left in my care right now and it must be hard work for you to tell the truth
I wouldn't call it
As the district official for the ministry of welfare I worked for many years dealing with orphans and I was Adam
Easily against the way the government handled them
After the fall of socialism I thought I'd try doing things my own way
I couldn't do any worse
Of course it isn't easy and I don't have many resources
But it's far better than the way they were living in that orphanage if you can call it that
The ministry of the interior and the ministry of welfare ran 511 kinderheim as a special or
Well all these German orphanages were pretty severe places to be
But these special orphanages were particularly notorious
It wasn't just an institution for children with nowhere to go
It was the place where children of criminals and political prisoners
Suspected dissidents were sent
Discrimination and inhumane cruelty
What part of everyday life for the children there
Those poor unfortunates were defenseless and couldn't do anything about their situation
Ironically it was a contradictory clash between socialism
And totalitarianism
The government claim they were reeducating them to be good citizens but in actuality behind closed doors
I wasn't away from the public eye those helpless children were treated like criminals even worse than criminals
The director and instructors were absolutely terrible
The worst of the bunch would confiscate care packages sent to the children and sell them to their own profit
Who then were the real criminals I ask you
Fear and violence rule the daily lives of those poor children and those special orphanages
You can't raise normal people that way
And then one day that incident happened incident what exactly do you mean by that
Well when you came here you said that you wanted to ask me about the twins didn't you
Yes that's right can you tell me anything at all about them
I don't know much about the girl except that she was left at an orphanage in a different District but the boy
I'll always remember the brother Johan
Johan yes please tell me whatever there is to know
What happened they kept everyone
From finding out
The East German government placed a strict gag order on it well it is in the past
So I suppose it's all right I guess there's no harm in talking to you about the incident so what are you talking
Talking about I need to know
What's your hun too
Then uprising
I'm home
Diet
We have company come here and say hello to him why don't you
Where are your manners
Well are you going to greet the man or not oh it's okay
We already met earlier out in front of the building
Remember
Please continue Mr Hartman
I'd like to hear more
No I'm sorry I can't not in front of the child
Understood
Well it's late can we continue this another time
Maybe you'd like to stay and have dinner with us
Sure
If you don't mind
Mr 10
You say that you're a freelance journalist does that mean you're going to write an article about the things we've been talking about
Eventually when you do write your article please be sure to emphasize this
The moral development of a child all depends on the adult that raises him
It is essential that we encourage every child to follow the proper path
If we do they'll be able to achieve their dreams and have a happy life
Dreams huh
Hey diet
What are your dreams
A soccer ball
I want a soccer ball
I see
Thank you for dinner I was hoping we could continue our conversation another time of course I am sorry
Sorry we couldn't finish it up tonight Mr 10
I'll be back
Perhaps I can come by tomorrow
Well did
Hello I'm sorry
Hey I still make a purchase
Mr Hartman
It's me tema
Mr Hartman Mr Hartman what's wrong please open up
Mr Hartman
Mr Denmark
Teacher what happened to him he was playing he was standing on a chair
My dear data
I would really hurts
Where did her where does it hurt
It hurts everywhere
It's your heart man call an ambulance quick all right
Detail let me take a look
My God
What are all these bruises
Does this hurt
What about here
So if your ribs are fractured
And also
Your shoulder is dislocated how did you get this injury from falling off a chair
The ambulance is on the way and should be here soon so everything's going to be all right good
But where these bruises come from I said everything's all right
You can leave now Mr tinma but your hands just now it was like you're examining him
It's as if you are a doctor well Ten Mile I thought I heard that
Somewhere before you are a doctor aren't you the one wanted for murder
These bruises just how did he get these bruises all over
You shouldn't worry about the boy you've got your own problems don't you the police
Ambulance Mr hot mom what really happened to Peter how did he get all
Well these injuries
What's it matter to you
I mean you're the one who's wanted for murder doctor
You're very short tempered just like a fugitive
You did this to him didn't you did what what do you mean you're the one who's been abusing
Why I'd never do such a thing to an innocent child
Right Dieter
What are you doing I'm taking teacher to the hospital first murder and now kidnapping
Don't move the police will catch you eventually
It's okay to
We'll be at the hospital soon I'm scared I'm scared of the hospital there's nothing to be afraid
The doctors will take good care of you but Mr Harmon is always the one who took care of me every time
Time I got hurt before
What are you telling me
You're completely covered in scars and bruises and you've never been to a hospital
I'm scared
The world is full of bad things that's why I have to become stronger
If I'm going to fight all the bad things I have to be
Stronger
Is that what heart mom told you
The world is dark
The futures
And that isn't true
The world's not a dark place that's a lie
Really
Yes really
Oh I almost forgot
This soccer ball is for you
Tomorrow will be a good day
I promise
I'm sorry for coming so late thank you nurse
But the ER is pretty busy at the moment
It might end up being a while before we can treat him
I can't you move him up at all
There is a very big accident I'm sorry
So we need to ask the truck driver about the circumstances of the accident
You broke both his legs but he can still talk any
We have to treat him first
You can question him after we're done
All right then we'll wait right here until he's ready I see
I'll be back in 2 hours please just do what you can to take care of the boy
And whatever you do please be sure not to let anyone else take him away I will be coming back to get him
I owe you one is the accident site cleaned up yet
Traffic still backed up okay what should I do now
First what to do with Dieter even if I call the police I can't go with him
I don't know much about the girl except that she was left at an
In a different District
A different orphanage wait that's it
There's a child that you want me to take in
Well are you the child's parent
What are you doing coming here at this hour I'm sorry I know it's a strange request but this child needs you
Look I understand that the child is being abused
But if I don't know who you are then how can I
I just I can't take in a child from a suspicious person who won't even identify himself
Wait
Did Anna Liebert live here with you with this orphanage by any chance
Hold on a second
Are you saying that you know Anna Liebert
That's right
So you do remember Anna
Yes of course I do
How is Anna is she doing well for herself
Yes
She's currently taking classes at Heidelberg University
Really then I guess she's doing very well
Anna was such a nice girl
I heard she was adopted by Mr Liebert of the Commerce Ministry
Along with her twin brother
What was his name again Johan
That was it his name was Johan they were truly very close I felt so sorry for them when they had to be separated but they
They had to be placed in different orphanages
Before the two of them arrived here they only had each other they were truly alone in this world
They were found walking hand in hand near the border of Czechoslovakia
Just the two of them
Shivering all alone in the cold at first Mr Liebert was only going to adopt
No hunts but Johan wouldn't go anywhere without his sister there was no separating them
Thankfully Anna was able to live a happy life because of her brother
I heard that the conditions in the orphanages in East Germany were pretty terrible not all orphanages were like
511 kinderheim
Inga deer the bathroom is the other way
Down the hall okay
It's all right it's
Right there's nothing to be afraid of now you can go to the bathroom by yourself can't you
These poor children have never really felt the love of a parent in order to develop as a person
The only thing you need is love
The orphanages of the East Side were truly horrible places for the children to grow up in everything was so
Doing personal even this place was only known by the number 47
You'd better believe we did everything we could do within our power so that we wouldn't be controlled by the
Pregnant we weren't going to be another 511 kinderheim it was a
Orphanage controlled by the ministry of welfare and the ministry of the Interior do you know what that means
No
The reality was it was a Ministry of the Interiors Pet Project East Germany was using
That place for experimentation on the children