How many times do you plan on coming here you can ask me until you're blue in the face I'm always going to tell you the same thing
Councilman boltzman didn't have sex with that woman that prostitute
This had better be your last visit
I would hate to have to take action against you take action
Are you going to sue for defamation
No
You wouldn't dare
You're a secretary
You wouldn't want councilman boltzman's name to come up in a case like this
Inspector are you threatening me
No of course not
I simply want to know the truth of the matter that's all
I know he works for a hot shot politician but man that guy's not going to give an inch
No
Who come around boltzman's got a pretty good thing going here why risk it all on some random prostit
The victim was no ordinary prostitute the names of countless politicians and business
Were traced back to her well yeah but there's only one person who claims to have seen them both
It's at the same Hotel
Just cuz they stayed at the same Hotel doesn't make him a John if you decoded her client list for me
Actually we're still working on cracking that code it's a lot tougher than we thought
I'll do it myself
Just give me the disc
Great but don't you already have a bunch of other cases on your plate it doesn't matter give it to me
There's something I've been meaning to ask you for a while
What is it well how do you find the time to sleep what does that have to do with the case
Huh
It's an irrelevant question Detective
Well have you gotten the chance to talk to him it doesn't really matter when we tell him he doesn't
Listen he stopped listening to me a long time ago I know but the sooner you tell him the better keep it down
You're being too loud
He's here you know working in his office yeah I wonder why
Damn it are you still trying to connect councilman boltzmann to the murder of
That prostitute is there a problem with that Chief yes
From the ministry of the interior
You're just going to have to smooth things out like you usually do no I can't unburn any more bridges for you
It's too big do whatever you can chief
Give me a break here Loom gay you're good but you're only human sometimes you're going to be wrong
Are you going to risk your entire career on a dead hooker
Come on do you need another feather in your cap
God don't tell me you're doing this for the principle of the thing
Justice
I'm not interested in either
All I know is a woman was murdered in Cold Blood
I'm just interested in finding the killer nothing else matters to me
Excuse me inspector you have a visitor
Got it
I managed to figure out the encryption that she was using
Use this formula to get all the names on our Client List oh
From that woman is here again sir
You know the one
Hey you can't just come back here we've been over this before
When will 10 be arrested you have all you need
It seems like you've been drinking quite a bit this morning just so you know
I've already figured out the case regarding Dr Tenma
He insists that everything is the work of a man called Johan but this Johann is just another personality
Within 10 was mind
If you think about it with this hypothesis what seemed illogical now makes sense
Well we have to do at this point is just wait for the police to capture him
So that means it's not your problem once you got an arrest warrant is that what you're saying there are a lot of things I would like to
Ask him when we finally meet
Doctor Tenma
What an interesting individual he is
However I have so many other cases piling up on my desk as we speak
If you'll excuse me
Don't you people ever let up
I told you councilman boltzman has an alibi for that night
Of course he did
The murder was a professional
I'm sorry
Are you honestly suggesting that my employer hired a hit man to kill that girl ridiculous I've cracked the
Code on the list of clients of the woman who was killed
Councilman boltzman's name was on that list
You know even if that were the case it still doesn't prove that he had her killed
Right
Come to think of it that's as far as we've gotten
I'm sure you'll be in touch now leave
We're dead in the water without a Smoking Gun wouldn't you say
Are you familiar with the Publishing House called shellhorn
They're not a major company but they stay in business by publishing tell all books on famous people
Like politicians
They're known to play very dirty
They hire unscrupulous women to build relationships with famous men
In order to create scandals to write about
If I were you
I'd watch out for people like that
Check and mate you should have seen it it was great boltzman's guy just stared at him like what
Blunga is unbelievable nearest I can tell all he does is work
He's a robot I'm telling you
Man I hear you the guy barely seems human to me
All right speaking of Checkmate there it is what the hell hey don't put into our game buddy
You shouldn't waste your time with my numbing games
It seems after a simple little threat the president of the Publishing Company chose to confess write a report
Here
What do you think you're looking at
It's at call girls notebook
It records the date and time and other details of encounters with a certain client
I can't really tell you the man's name
He's only referred to here by the initial b
Not to mention shellhorn publishing also made arrangements with the woman to release her autobiography
Interesting
Don't you think
Oh by the way
Have you ever been in contact with a man named yanker you may be aware that he is a professional Hitman
I want you to leave
You get the hell out of here now
We're moving out both of us right now level with me you never even
Even noticed I was pregnant not even now did you are you going to the man or father to your child what do you
There I bet you didn't even notice that I was having an affair with another man did you
Please understood I
I have to go we can talk about this later
Inspector what just happened here
Councilman Boltzmann's an innocent man
Not much of a suicide note but that's all we got
Looney
I'm handing this one over to inspector Kaminski
I'm giving him the reichner park in gallon murder cases too given what happened I think it's for the best
So then
What am I supposed to do now
Get your head together
Then we'll talk about work
Well doctor Tenma it seems there's nothing left to distract me
Sorry inspector you have a visitor
It's a behind a man
I could tell her to come back another day if you know
No children
I had a great time Eva
How long until next time
Not sure babe
Maybe when I return from my next business trip
Oh I don't want to give you back to your wife come on stay all right
I'll give you a call
No you won't be coming back not after getting in trouble for that perfumed handkerchief that I carefully placed in
Suitcase you stupid bastard
You were eavesdropping again weren't you
You must see all the different men I'm with isn't that right
Well what then you want to join in the fun is that it no of course not you pervert
You're wrong and I mean I just I forget how nice it is
It's beautiful
I really love this Garden
Looking at all this Greenery helps me forget about the distasteful things out there
I'm so glad that you like it I'm going to plant some mimosas here
Bent over there I'm planning to put up an arch for your roses when summer gets here it's going to be beautiful
If maybe someone like you could be up to the task so what do you think
Do you think you can make me happy
Hey Dad are you listening to me
Dad
Oh how is my cooking today am I getting any better
You haven't heard a single word I said have you Dad
How come you're always daydreaming
I bet you that's why Mom ran off with another man
I'm sorry
It's fine
Really
Actually
Coletta
Yeah
If Daddy
Found
Someone he really liked
No forget it it's nothing
My cooking is pretty awful right
Come on tell the truth it's not so bad
I see
Not bad huh
Sorry for the trouble
You're a gardener but I'm asking you to do all these odd jobs no problem my handyman kept asking for time off and
Quit
Well I'll do everything I can to help
So how about dinner tonight
Oh well
Okay
Why are you nervous
Well I'm not used to expensive restaurants like this
You must be confident wherever you go
Just pretend you're working in my garden right now
Yes that's right I do feel pretty confident when I'm out there working on something new in the yard
I Feel So Satisfied when a garden turns out the way I envisioned it
I just love being out there you know
People who like Gardens can't be all that bad
And you did say you like that Garden the other day
Are you trying to say that I'm a good person yeah of course
Well go on
You
You know
Kind of lonely
I'm not the only one
I'm guessing that you're lonely too
I'm sorry
My daughter's probably worried about me so I should get going
It's almost Christmas Coletta he doesn't have to come this year
Hey come on sweetie don't say things like that Dad celebrating Christmas Just the Two of Us sounds lonely
Let's not do anything okay yeah well it might not just be the two of us celebrating this year you know
The man you're looking at in those photographs ruined my life
Sorry I was just cleaning up
His name is Kenzo Tenma
He's my ex fian
You're drinking again at this time of day well of course I've been drinking
I just went to see inspector loon gave the bka
Can you believe that useless incompetent inspector sent me away
All I want to know is when they're going to arrest them
The pka
The rest he killed my father and then ran away oh he says he's innocent but he's
Not fooling anybody
My future should have been gilded and gold as the daughter of the director of a large hospital and my three divorces
Everything is his fault and he blames the murders on your home
This is Johan with my father do you think that this child could kill anyone
Is that really what timma told you
It's either nons
Have you ever shown this Photograph to the police course not
I don't know it could be important evidence Maybe
Lego says he has a split personality dammit
Then tell me
Why do you still keep framed pictures of them like this around the house years later
I figured deep down
You think Tema is innocent
You still have
Feelings for him
You watch too many soap oper
Out of all the men I've ever met Kenzo satisfied the most of my requirements
His position suited me he was an elite neurosurgeon who many considered a genius besides he spoiled me
And best of all he never contradicted me
He just listened to my every single request yes yes yes he was the man who always said yes to me
That man could have made me the happiest person in the world do you understand what I'm saying
I think I would ever be able to fill his shoes
I'd be willing to tend your Gardens for the rest of my life
If that would help to ease your pain any
Knock knock yourself just because I slept with you once you were just something to pass the time I was bored
That's all I was playing with you and you fell for it you fool who Do You Think You Are
Truly a sad and lonely person
So are you
On Christmas Day I'm having a party at my house with my daughter you're welcome to join us
Well Dad everything looks delicious
Did you really make this all by yourself
Yep
I can't guarantee it'll be good
Do you think so
Mom's coming home for Christmas
Charlotte
Mommy
I'm so sorry to hear
I'm sorry
Who cares about Mim
Or about Frozen or beautiful gardens or this whole damn estate
Thought of it means anything to me now just let it burn
Welcome back
So inspector loon gay you finally decided to listen to me
I had some time open up that's all
This man was my only hope I must see to it that his life is ruined
Or I can never be happy again