She has a baby back
They're in the new Nazis are planning to burn the town
Dead up on the third floor
We're approaching the meeting place where Johan will be expecting you I'm not sure what will happen there
You do know how to use that gun right now
My plans have changed why the sudden change of heart what about killing Johan I'll deal with him later now
As I say General wolf will be disappointed to hear this news he personally requested that you kill Johan he
I don't take requests from anyone I'm going to kill
All ignition points are ready to go sir
Awaiting your orders to proceed
Well done
Time to celebrate our superiority with a little Firepower
Now
What are we going to do with them
These two are an insult to our race
Unfortunately these types do exist Among Us
What is a
And the brat was trying to save the Turks
They're both filthy scum purify them it's time to teach him a lesson
This place is going to burn anyway leave them for the flames
Oh come on little one don't cry
Your mom is coming back
Real soon
I can't believe you're still alive
How do you find me
It's all thanks to Dieter he told me that you lived in this building
So
Where is Teeter
Didn't he come by
Then where do you go
Hey have you seen Aisha
He needs her he misses his mom a lot
It can't
It's not possible I don't believe it
What about this poor little child he's too young to be without a mother what am I going to do what do I do
She's the last
There mustn't be any more victims
I need to see the leaders of the Turkish quarter now
So what does everyone think
Set the town on fire huh
Not
We are rumors about the right wing extremists all the time
We can't overreact every time they threaten us
What's even more suspicious to me is this Japanese guy Waltzing in here though he says his life is in
What's the matter with all of you I say it's dead don't you get it
She was killed because she tried to warn all of us about this Danger
I wonder about that
She was a prostitute like you right
You women go off with Germans all the time and end up missing
There's nothing new
You may call us Turks look bad
How do we really know whose kid that is anyway
You all know how hard it is to make a living you should know better than to act like this
If you want to live
You've got to listen to me
Forget it do what you want you can burn and go to hell for all I care
No wait just one second
Are you suggesting Patrol groups
Maybe we should do is this Japanese man says we have nothing to lose Mr Denny's
Are you really going to listen to some Asian we don't know
He might be suspicious but there are certainly plenty of trustworthy Japanese
People in the world
I don't know
Word
General
Who's
You mean you don't know about him
General knowgee was a brave Japanese man who saved the Turkish navy when they were lost in the Pacific years
Years ago
Go ahead and gather all our men IMM
It looks so delicious
Let's dig in shall we
No need to be in such a hurry ladies
Take your
We wouldn't want to finish eating before the
Entertain
I planned it so by the time the main course comes around the show will be reaching its climax
In the meantime let's enjoy the 76 Chateau Le Tour I saved especially for this night
The first dish we will indulge in is my favorite
Raw Flounder with caviar
And does the feast begin
Voila the first fire
What a wonderful
But like I told you that's still just an appetizer
Where is the main course
Remember what I said don't be impatient
If you Savor your dinner my show will be something you'll truly enjoy
Tell me where the main course is if that's an appetizer
Then what are you going to burn for the main course
Cuz I thought
The plane started up wind this whole place could go up three groups save the women and children oh my goodness
What a lovely surprise and do what do we owe this honor
Don't even try it
Or kiss your boss goodbye dangerous thing away
Why don't we enjoy this meal together
Unfortunately it seems your appetizer is fizzling out
Don't worry that was just the beginning
This is your favorite right
Sorry about that
Don't be so contrary my dear
You see after all this is a great celebration in honor of Johan
Listen to me Johan doesn't want any of this
And tell me how can you be so certain
I saw it with my own eyes
I followed his messages I know what he wants
Johan doesn't care about your plans
What exactly did you see
He doesn't want any of this don't you understand
Relax
Calm down just take it easy because of you
I won't let anybody else die tonight
So where's the main course what part of town are you going to sit on fire
Take
Have you had any luck finding Dieter someone
Told me they saw a kid who looked like him near the park around noon
No
Let's just continue with my dinner is planned that girl sure is something I suppose
Just running the family the look she had in her eyes she
Kill me it's a good thing she didn't realize how close I was to giving her the actual
Location of the main course well shall we bring out the next dish sir no eat me some under
First
A scary girl isn't she
You're going to be just fine
Everything's okay all right now
Up here anyway
You want to know what happened lady
This bread almost got me killed
Forget this
I'm getting the hell out of here
If that was the smallest fire those skinheads said I wouldn't be a bit surprised
I grew up in this neighborhood I know the place like the back of my hand
If I wanted to burn down the town this wouldn't be the spot believe you me
This town ain't out of the woods just yet
There were three other fires up wind that were all so put out
We can't thank you enough for your help
Right everyone
Our next step is to take care of the injured
No I won't have any more victims not one more
Wait
What are you talking about
Well the wind's going to change direction
It always happens every night around this time the wind just stops and it starts blowing towards town from where the
The wind
And now
Time for the main course to be served
Did you see them running away
I love me
That should take care of it
Thanks for patching me up doctor
Let me buy you a drink
What are you talking about you have to take it easy for a while
Oh come on loosen up Dr right
That's right it's thanks to you we were able to put out those fires and save the neighborhood
I bet those Neo Nazis are scratching their heads right now wondering what the hell happened
No doubt they are that'll teach him never underestimate that Turks what are they tendon
All the other injured people
Hey Dr 10ma take a break and relax come on why don't you have a drink with us
Not until everyone's taken care of
If all of the fires up until now we're just diversions
Where do you think they're going to light the real fire how the hell would I know who cares about this stupid town anyway
Besides there's something much more important on my mind that I got to take care of wait I need you to tell me and
I need you to tell me now
Where would you start the real fire get your hands off of me
Like I already told you the wind's going to come from the river
The abandoned Factory down there would be a perfect place for a fire
If I'm not mistaken there should still be a bunch of chemicals in the warehouse
Long
Something I can sink my teeth into yes this is going to be Del
We're right on schedule the celebration of the master
Price is about to begin
It's
Why did you follow me because I have to put out the fire I made a promise to Tenma
This is it
It's the warehouse
Thank goodness looks like they haven't found this place yet these are all filled with chemicals
If all of this were to go up it'd be hopeless there'd be nothing left of the town I'll protect
This place no matter what I'm not going to let those horrible people burn it down
Okay I slipped
What the heck is this
Smells like gas
What's there
It's all right I'm fine
Hey you can walk on my own
Let's get you to a shelter so I can have a closer look at it
Hey twisted my an
It probably happened when I was trying to get away from the fire
Now that I finally got this rug who gives a damn about this stinking town
I bet I can probably get $800,000 marks for this baby no a million
What happened to Dieter couldn't say he's probably where is he where did he go what happened to him
Last I saw he was going to the abandoned warehouse by the river
Why there
The wind's going to blow in from the river soon
So if the chemicals in that warehouse are set on fire it's all over for this town
This is what I was talking about tell
You evacuate from the Riverside shelters right away you're going to take me there
Who is
Who's back there
Please don't move
Can it be true
Are you really Johan's sister
Once I sent this trail of gasoline on fire
This Warehouse is going to go up
An inst
I'm going to shoot you in the head before that happens
I can fire quicker than you can flick that lighter and I'm not afraid to do it and what if you miss I haven't skipped a day of
Training in 6 months straight
So I know
I can hit you from here
You don't
Don't you know this is a celebration of the master race
This is our big welcome for Johan
But Johan doesn't want any of the things you want
Yes it's true that he was recently seen here in Frankfurt
The only reason he came was to kill one of your leaders and all of his subordin
He left a message behind you know
What
Listen to me Johan is not the person you think he is
The truth
Is much more complex than that what are you trying to say
It's
It must be terrifying for him
He's suff
He's an anguish and teetering on the edge of despair
You know I'm not so sure it's such a good idea to be making enemies of these guys
Which way to the warehouse I didn't sign on for all of this
I'm going to call it a day see you where the hell do you think you're going to let me
You told me about your friend you said that his name is right
Would you believe that I know a man whose name is Tema also for real
Is your timer Really Brave too
Yes but he must never fire a gun not if I can do it for him
I don't want him to kill anyone he's a good man killing people is always wrong you understand
Even if they're the bad guys
Don't ever do what I'm about to do
Close your eyes don't look don't don't shoot
Quick I can put up the fire and use the
1 million marks
Nina
Damn it all the cops are coming
Get out go I'll take care of things here
There's a boat over by the river
Please tell me you have to leave now
My main
Thank you for all your cooperation young lady
Wait one second okay I'll be right back
Mina you have to promise me something Nina swear to me you will kill anyone
Years ago the night I shot my brother I finally know what he meant when he told me to shoot him in
Now I understand he's not alone
There are two of them inside
That's why
It wasn't your fault you didn't do anything wrong
I must
I have no other
I have to shoot you hun again
Hey wait up what the hell are we doing here anyway
Come on let's get out of here
Can I give up
There's no use for this guy
I guess I'll be starving and broke forever
If only I still had that
The hell's that supposed to be
A message
The monster inside me about to explode
What is this supposed to mean
He has a split personality