My wife and I divorced about 3 years ago
No that's a
She divorced
3 years ago
She said that I stopped listening to her and I suppose she was right about that
This was the only thing I did really listen to by that point
My wife said I was broken
She said it was a Voyer peeking through the window and people's innermost thoughts
Crazy
Doctor
You're abnormal
Maybe you're right about that
I became transfixed obsessively gazing into the abyss of the human heart
I suppose it's possible the Hibiscus is back into me the depths of the human mind are filled with treacherous landscapes
Your fourth victim was an 18 year old girl in Munich I believe
I'm curious
Did you experience any form of sexual arousal when you cut her up
I don't want to talk about her today doctor I want to talk about my 12th
Fair enough then
That would be Mrs Hunter Kemp from Krupp house
52 years old
At that time
I was in
I'm not prepared to talk about her
I promise we will eventually get to Mrs Kemp but for the moment I would really like to focus on victim number 11
Is that all right
No then
Peak of your arousal
Does that come before or after you commit a murder
The victims were all girls with long hair
Ages 16 to 18
Clear these murders should all be categorized as acts of sexual homicide
But then he
Confesses to the murder of his 12th victim
This is Kem
Mrs Kemp was 52
And showed no signs of sexual ass
He claims to have killed Mrs Camp as a favor for a friend
And obvious in Desperate last ditch attempt to disrupt the investigation
Who is it
Who is it I know that you're in there
It's me Rudy
This is a surprise
Yeah I know
I'm sorry for barging in on you like this Rudy
You've heard about my situation
That's putting it mildly
Well
Do you think I'm a serial killer
I don't know
But from what I've heard
Both the newspapers and our old classmates think you're as guilty as
So the question is
What are you doing here
Why come to me
We were never exactly what you'd call close
I know for a fact you despise me
I could tell from the way you looked at me
I saw the contempt burning behind your eyes
Haha that's what this is all about
You've come to collect what you think I owe you
Is that it it's not like that at all
You've become a noted specialist in criminal psychology
I have something
I'd like you to take a look at it
My dear Dr temma
Look at me
The monster inside me is getting bigger
Help
The Munster inside me is about to explode
What on Earth is this
Quite a story
So 10 years ago you saved the boys life who went on to kill the hospital directors some staff and his foster parents
Then he's gone
Leaving no Trace other than a series of cryptic messages addressed to you
Which is why it's so urgent that I find out where he is now
Because you think by finding him you'll also find something that might prove your innocence
20 years ago
There was a young man attending a prestigious medical school
He was driven to be top of his class one day a Japanese transfer student came and changed
Everything
This new student was Charming quickly gaining the respect of peers and teachers alike he had a brilliant mind as well
No claiming his position as the top of his class within his first semester much to the men's dismay by
By the next semester he had become obsessed with regaining his title he had managed to earn full marks and all his classes so
How far however
His last test was in his weakest subject medical law
If he failed this test then all of his efforts would go to waste
So he resorted to Desperate Measures measures
God would put them back on top but he was caught
The Japanese student never
Told anyone about what he had seen
As a result
The man regained his throne
So is there anything you can tell me about this man based on the contents of these letters
You think it may be multiple personality disorder
And you've come to the conclusion that one of the personalities is committing these murders while the other personality is trying to get
Yes instances of serial killers leaving these sorts of notes or not unheard of
Just as often these notes are fabricated as legal proof
Of their insan
Separating The Pretender from the genuine article is the art of the criminal psychologist
I believe you me this is no easy task the introverted shifty-eyed serial killer is more or less a Hollywood fabrication
Many killers are highly intelligent intuitive and extremely Charming they are
Adoptive and skillful Liars
So that's it
Think he might be toying with me well let's not add to the mounting pile of conjecture just yet
Why don't you tell me a little bit more about this Johan
My wife and I got divorced about 3 years ago
What I mean to say is my wife divorced Me 3 years ago
Thank you Rudy
I need to do some research give me a call next week all right
Do you have an opinion about this person
Seems like my kind of guy
Can you elaborate on that
The monster
I get all that
That's interesting
You get the monster
Makes sense of course there's a monster inside both of you
To be fair there's even a monster inside of me
Shut your mouth
That's nothing but textbook garbage
What I'm telling you doctor is that a real monster does exist
What do you think you're doing just stop looking at me like that
Don't you dare look at me
What are you doing
I'm telling the guards
Are you scared
Because there are things out there that would turn your blood to ice
I'm going to tell you a secret
Operation
You really still convinced that Tim was going to try and contact you again
I'm sure
And when he does he'll notify you immediately
However
Well go on
After his arrest I would like to get permission to use him and his case in my research
Doctor Turner would make a compelling subject
He has a complex Criminal Mind
I'm going to tell you a secret go
Sonic Kim's house in group house make your way to the basement you're going to find all of your answers down there
Down there you'll find proof proof the monster
It really does exist
This is Rudy
I've been waiting for your call
Yeah all right
Excell
And I'll see you there
Officer call Tim I just called we've arranged for a meeting tonight
Odell Park tonight at 8:00
By the fountain that's right
Goodbye then
I'm currently retracing Jurgen steps on the day of his 12th confessed murder
According to our interviews he broke into the basement
And stayed hidden there for several hours
Later when Mrs Kemp returned home
He made his way into the upstairs bedroom and murdered her there
There's nothing out of the ordinary
Except
There are framed photos
All over the basement
Their own pictures of Mrs Kem
Just a doll
Almost gave me a heart attack
Evidence of this so-called monster Jurgen sent me to find clearly isn't here
The supports my theory that Jurgens committed the 12th murder to confuse investigators
His first explanation was that he committed the murder as a favor for a friend
One he Associates with a primal monster archetype
When I was a kid
My mother would beat me
What she would do
This big dog
The basement wakes up
Wherever I
What does it mean exact in every detail
Is it possible did Jergens actually recreate the basement from his childhood
The boy next to Mrs Kemp
It can't be there's no evidence connecting young Jergens to Mrs Kemp
Something is not right here
Into the photograph
This one and this one and another
All of these Mrs Kemp never had any children
So who is this boy
Who are you down there you'll find proof proof the monster really
Does exist
I followed all of the instructions and my friend left me in the letter perfectly
Who was he
Just listen the first letter came in a blank envelope without a name or return address
He would just say he understood me sympathize with me crap like that
I was annoyed
Angry at first
But then another one came
And then another the next day
And again and so on
He's a letter
But before I knew it I started to expect the letters
Even enjoy them a bit
Then I thought
Maybe it's possible he might actually be a friend to me
And then one day one of his letters asked me for something
He asked me to go down to the basement of this house
Did the basement belong to Mrs Kemp
I still don't know how he could have known
There's no way he could possibly have known what happened to me down there when I was a kid
Somehow he got everything right down to the smallest detail
How do you do that
I just got so confused
The next thing I knew I was upstairs and Mrs Camp was dead
He's a letter freak as well
What is this another
And this another one
Look at me look at me
Let's try inside me is getting bigger
Help me the monster inside of me is about to explode these are the messages
You said Johan left me
They're the same
Jergens's friend and your hot is
Anything yet
It's way past eight already
Inspector call
Target in sight
Asian male
Long hair
I appreciate you making time for this Rudy
I want you to know I did research what you gave me
But I thought you were making it up
I thought that Johan was just a ruse a scapegoat you created to buy you time once you were caught
You've got to believe me
Rud
I've been conducting research on a serial killer named Jurgens and something he said caught my attention one of his vict
Symptoms is off pattern showing no connection to profile or ritual
It doesn't matter Rudy please just listen to me okay listen up everyone will finish for today
I will see you tomorrow seems like the carnival is wrapping up
Everyone in position
Make sure they're ready to move in on my mark
Yes sir
I want every detail of their conversation
You hated me didn't you
You've hated me ever since you caught me cheating on that exam in college
I could feel your dis
Go ahead and say it
Inspector coal this doesn't look good
Dr Gillian and Tenma are headed toward the west exit
Will lose them and that crowd that's leaving
You'll be well within your right
A man like me doesn't deserve your respect
Rudy this isn't the time to remin listen to me
Now then I looked up the answers and wrote them all down on a cheat sheet
She just like this one
Run we're surrounded by the police
Don't look just walk
Is Dr Tema threatening Gillen I'm not sure sir there's too much background noise for me to hear
Hey is my turn jurgen's recently confessed to me that he had killed Mrs
Camp at the request of a friend
Rudy what is this
Something I found in Mrs Kemp's basement
But Mrs Kemp never had any children
I have found compelling evidence to suggest that jurgens' friend and your Yohan are both one and the same
They've passed through the West exit
Should we move in
Tell everyone to hold their positions he may be armed
I found a letter from Johann and Mrs Kemp's house it was almost identical to the one you brought me
I believe that Johan had been in the care of Mrs Camp at some point in his life that would explain his
Motivation for orchestrating her death you're an innocent man
I'm sorry I can't give you as much detail as perhaps you'd like but here's what I've worked out on
Yo hun so far
I don't know how he does it but Johan can somehow identify other killers
He finds them worms his way in beguiles them then manipulates them
It is worth noting that to the best of our knowledge
He hasn't killed the foster parents who cared for him as a teenager probably because by the time he reached that age
Longer found himself dependent on anyone
Perhaps
But I have another theory
What if Yohan found himself his ideal family
And then became a part of it but why work so hard to erase his past was there an UL
If that is indeed the case did he make his way into the family for a specific purpose
And what would that purpose be
Well
We're at the bus terminal
Yes confirm which bus Tim is getting on
They get a car over to the terminal and have him follow yes sir
At least I can do is buy you a bus ticket
You know
There's still time for you to turn yourself in and prove your innocence I promise I can help you
The truth is I'm not chasing after your hunt just so I can prove my innocence
Thank you for all your help Rudy
Cinema you don't have to become him to end this
That reminds me
I really didn't despise you back in college Rudy
I mean it I thought you were brilliant and it was a shame we never had a chance to talk I'm glad that I can
Finally count you as a friend but I know you caught me cheating on that medical logs and there's no doubt about it
I saw you looking directly at me and my cheat sheet well yeah I cheated on the medical
Be careful tema