At least I can do is buy you a bus ticket
You know
There's still time for you to turn yourself in and prove your innocence I promise I can help you
The truth is I'm not chasing after your hunt just so I can prove my innocence
Thank you for all your help Rudy
You don't have to become him to end this
That reminds me
I really didn't despise you back in college rud
I thought you were brilliant and it was a shame we never had a chance to talk
I'm glad that I can finally count you as a friend
But I know you caught me cheating on that medical logs and Professor hesse's class
Well yeah I cheated on the medical law exam too
Be careful Tima
What did that sign back to say I missed it
I've been trying to figure out this map this way or that way I'm not quite
Sure we're headed in the right direction really where'd you find that map lying in the street
Do you know me better than that you were right beside me when I picked it up at the car rental place
You picking anything up you must have grabbed it when I went off to use the facilities
Nice names with such small print at my age it's almost impossible to read
Yeah both weapon housing and amputs housing and he's got two
That's quite a mouthful then these German names all sound like don't they they
I'm using I wonder if Germans think that about our towns when they read British Maps
Now we need to know when the next Crossroads coming up
There's a pedestrian let's ask him for directions
Let's give him a ride if you ask me we're looking for trouble giving a ride to complete stranger
Maybe so oh wait a minute he's traveling with a small child
I feel sorry for them let's pick them up all right fine
Hey look 10 of those people just stopped for us
Couldn't talk
Sorry we don't speak German
Do you understand me
Oh are you both from England
We're trying to get to freiheim and would really appreciate your help
Could I see that map
So where is this place
The place you're traveling to
Oh well all right
We're around this area now so it's just a bit further south from here
I suppose
Duncan
You're quite an Odd Couple aren't you
I mean I don't believe you're his father you appear to be Asian and the boys
Clearly German Caucasian yes in fact he's my best friend's son and
Some sort of well-educated professional man it's the way
I must apologize for him sorry it's not personal he just enjo
I was observing people now that he's retired from the police force
Nothing she just said that he used to be a cop
Let's get out of here 10 months easy so
I've been thinking I'll bet this is the first real vacation the two of you have taken since your husband retired
Yes you're right my husband was such a workaholic I never truly believe we'd be able to take a big
So I'm sorry we're imposing on this time you plan to spend with your wife
We'd be happy to catch another ride if we're being a nuisance here so far the biggest nuisance has been
Getting lost cuz we can't read directions not to mention the trouble we've been having ordering food it might help
Russian mentally do I have someone like you traveling with us if only doing celebrate the bloody language
Well what should we do now de
There's nothing we can do I'm afraid
Except find a gas station and bring some back
Look here comes the truck
Hey stop hey over here
What's wrong
We're out of gas
That's kind of a problem out here in the middle of No Man's Land huh
Well I've got room for two of you in my cab
Is that okay somebody should take the chap up on his offer
Don't worry about us will be all right we'll work something out
Listen as soon as I see a gas station I'll get them to send somebody out here with a can of gas for you
Thank you that would be most helpful and we really appreciate it
This is great thank goodness right now everything worked out perfectly
How long do you think it will be before we come to a gas station
He's been quite a while now
Indeed it has my dear
With that nice young man let them know that we're stranded out here on the motorway
The petrol station will send someone out won't they
There is another possibility
He might just have left us and forgotten about us
I don't believe it
He's not that kind of person
He struck me as a very caring man
Maybe not
What a beautiful scar
I'm not really in the mood to enjoy a sunset tonight
See one you've seen them all
Oh I'm not talking about the sunset
The sun's already disappeared
But just look at the lovely pastel colors the sun has left behind
It's like a watercolor painting in the sky
I wonder if Roberts watching it now
We be seeing it together
My goodness
I think it is do you better take a look my ass might be deceiving me
Someone's coming this way
It's getting bright and closer
It must be him I just knew it
Couldn't find
Gas station
Can I borrow the gas and a lamp from a farmer
See I told you
Oh that was a delicious meal wasn't it de
Thanks to your excellent translation of the German menu we were actually able to order something we could enjoy tonight
Especially that one
Oh it was forcedur
It's from the palatnet region
Got liver dish was just scrumptious
The liver canoodle
That Cyrus pronounced
It melted in my mouth
If you hadn't been with us we'd have passed all these wonderful places without a clue as to what we were missing
I want to thank you for treating us to dinner
You're almost finished
Would you like some more to take with you
Thanks but if he has any more help burst
Do you think this plug looks like a criminal
For this chapter these are trial for murdering his wife and there's a big picture of him in the paper see for yourself
What's your opinion
Do you think you did
Well who can tell really before I retired from the full so I was a detective with
Watch a long list of criminals that I put behind bars
Oh come on dear we're enjoying the evening it's really not appropriate to brag about all your past exploits
Well
I would look at a person's face and I'd know if he'd done the crime
I possessed an uncanny neck for spotting the guilt that a person tries to hide
I see
Let's talk about something else now dear
I think you've had a little too much wine
However
After years on the job I couldn't tell anymore
Was one person good and another bad
Was he guilty or innoc
I couldn't Spot the Difference that it won't seem so clear
It probably means I wasn't such a hot shot detective after all
Enough said
Maybe I did have a little too much to drink
Tell me once more
What was the name of that wine
It was fosterone
Excellent bouquet
How cute they each
A friend
When this trip is over Dieter and you move to a new place I hope you make lots of friends
Oh
Sure that'd be great
Everyone should have a happy childhood
They should enjoy every minute
It goes by so fast
Yes
Oops
Sorry
Should be somewhere right around here what are you looking for
Is the address dear
Almost there
Sorry but we have to make a stop before continuing that's fine
Oh here we
The police
We won't be very dumb if you don't mind you might as well
Legend the car
What should we do tema
Let's run away
What's wrong someone's parked in one of the officers only spaces again he looks foreign
Guess I should report them
What are we going to do
Mr Jones
We want to get to freiheim and I don't know if you're aware of it but you're heading in the opposite direction
That's right it's just a brief detail I want to stop at Steinbach Castle
Starting by Castle or something I want to see for myself
How are you doing are you all right
Oh thank you
My son wrote us a letter about steinbe
He said the view from this Castle is truly breathtaking
He wanted to bring us here so we could both see it
Oh does your son live in Germany now
We're on our way to see
It's just that we have a few details to make along the way
This is the view he sold on that fightful day
My
I am flashing blood killed a man
We came to this country to visit him because he'll never leave
Well we'll be okay from here
Thank you so much for everything thank you
For your kindness and the pleasure of your company
Chariot
Look after yourself
Such a nice young man
Yes isn't he it's hard to believe that he's wanted is the prime suspect of
Series of murders
You must be mistaken no I'm not it's him he's on The Wanted suspects list
Impossible I'm afraid so and when we were at the station to speak to the detective of Arrested Robert
Those photo was prominently posted on the wall
There's so much good in him
Oh no
I thought so too and yet everyone seems convinced that he's guilty but my instincts keep
You telling me
He's an innocent man
A good in him out why is the bad I'm sure of it
It was unbelievable to think the rubber that committed murder
But he did and the fact that I couldn't sense what was going on with my own son maybe realize it was time for me
Turn in my badge
But you know something dear I just want to be able to trust my instincts again
Robert may have committed to try and true but I know he's a good boy at heart
Come on let's go in and see our son
Oh dear Robert