Hey honey can I trust you in this Moscow mule
My pleasure
And for you A big glass of juice on the rocks
Come on Fred's now be polite and thank your father
Thanks Mr Mueller
Stop it Fritz
Leaving B Barbara Rome wasn't built in a day you know
It's the same deal with my new antique business rough start then smooth sailing
Well for me everything is really happened so quickly
I suddenly get to live in this gorgeous house
And I have a wonderful and caring husband
Who makes me great cocktails
Hey honey
Did you see something just then
There in the window
I get this feeling sometimes
Like we're being watched
What honey that house has been empty for a while yeah I know
It's OD
Actually I talked to Mrs Daughtry from across the street
What about she said
The 20 years ago
A couple was brutally murdered in that house
Anyone who moves in never stays for long they say the place is haunted
Michael dear what's the matter
Wait a minute now don't tell me that you believe in ghosts too do you darling
Of course not what do you take me for
Are you going out sir yeah
I'll get the car
Not this time
I thought it might be a nice change of pace to go out just the three of us
Don't worry no one's going to try anything
I get it
Unless I'm mistaken you're wanting a little father son time with the boy you're a smart body guard you know that
Best of luck to you Daddy
Have a good time
All right off we go
So Detective
Why don't you dig up
Regarding Dr Tenma
Everything checked out exactly as you told me
He's the main suspect in the murder of the Fortuner couple but the police have no idea where he is at the moment
Here's a transcript of 10 statement
He made it back during that first question
He operated on a boy at Eisler Memorial Hospital 10 years ago saved his life
Kid went on to kill the hospital director and two other doctors
The boy's name was joh
He was already a young man the next time 10 men encountered him
Turns out Johann executed a patient in his care
Next up Nina Fortuner
She was the murdered couples foster daughter
No one seen her since the night they were killed either
Messner was a tougher nut to crack
But I did finally track him down in Frankfurt
Well then what did you find
The grave with his name on it
Turns out he was stabbed to death about 2 months ago
The official police version is that he was on the wrong side of a drug deal gone bad
Back when I was a detective on the force Messner was my partner
Sorry for your
They caught Messner with confiscated narcotics and booted him off the force
After that he got some help from a man called the baby
Bring any bells
He's the spokesman for some nationalist group in Frankfort
How is this relevant
You remember hearing those news reports about how it's Turkish quarter almost burned down last
Right
Word on the street is the whole thing was the babies brainchild
And the Turks credit an Asian stranger with having saved their neighborhood
Turns out that stranger's name was Tenma
What are the odds
I'm thinking it was the doctor
And what's more people are saying the baby had those fires set to commemorate the introduction of a new leader into their
Group some Wonder can they were all really excited about he was going to change everything
Who is this guy
I've already told you
What was the name of that boy Dr Tana saved a decade ago
Johan
Well that young man who was supposed to take the reins of the babies organization in Frankfort
He was Yohan too
You should have seen that one coming
Call me crazy Robert
But I feel like one of the ponds on this chess
Waiting for the
Oh goodness
What's going you looking so pensive all of a sudden
Thinking about the past
Everything was going straight to hell for me at the time
But after that phone call it change was like night and day
Back then my partner Messner and I were selling drugs
Whatever we confiscated off of the dealers we busted
The voice in the other end knew everything
He said it would be our little secret
If we did him a favor kill some couple in Heidelberg
The fortuners
And I didn't know him from Adam
But there was another guy there that night a
Paper reporter or something
We killed all three of them no choice
After that somebody wired money to the both of us when I left the police force The Syndicate was
Just waiting with a great offer
They gave me a plum job and the pay was top-notch I had everything I wanted out of life or so I thought
That's when you met your wife and decided to go straight or so I would wager yeah but I still
Can't figure out why they let me just walk away
Who was it
Who called me that day I got to know who transferred all that money over to us who the hell is manip
Letting my life oh damn it
Robert
I want to be sure that you know
I really appreciate your help
Well if that's how you feel
Take back that last move
Sorry my friend no can do
Ouch now you're being harsh
All right honey we're leaving
Okay have fun you guys
At first say goodbye to your father fr
Don't even be honey
He's got toys on the brain
Hi Daddy
Roberto
Were there any calls from the detective
He should have come by now
Roberto
Roberto get up here listen to detective oh God he's
But
Yes I'm the daughter of the foreigners the couple you murdered
You shot him in Cold Blood
I was watching from next door your bodyguards the one who killed him
No he couldn't have
I know Roberto I trust that man with my life
You
You murdered him
You came here for revenge and he got in the way right
Damn you
Roberto
Help me
I'm taking this bag stay here or run for it I don't give a damn
Just don't be surprised if you're the next person who dies here you bastard
Was that you shouting just now Mr Mueller
Is everything all right
Start this car right now move it
You've been watching me all this time from the
House next door will isn't that right so what happens to me now
Give me one good reason not to shoot you but he knew we had to do
Every said if we didn't kill your folks like he asked he was going to tell the cops about the drugs we were
Selling on the side don't you get it we had to do it we
You didn't have any other choice
You didn't have any other choice stop
Stop the car God damn it
My parents were wonderful people
The kindest couple I'll ever know
Mom and dad love me
You love me with all their heart and soul wait
Please don't do this it didn't even matter to them that I wasn't there real daughter
They love me all the same
My mom and dad were Angels they were Angels I'm sorry
Please don't shoot angels and they were murdered by a faster like you
Barbara
Trying for your family about mine
So this is what it feels like
Right before somebody kills you
Fritz he called me Daddy today
For the first time don't take that from me please please let me live
I finally found someone worth living for Barbara
Been friends I met them at half past 8:00 in the morning
Cafe in dusseltorf
I quit the force and joined the syndicate
My boss told me to act like a businessman
Made for a nice cover every morning this woman and her little boy would walk by
They were my daily reminder of the regular honest life I've given up
Hey so how you doing
I'm fine thanks for asking
Tell me something what did you hire that detective for
I was hoping he could find you in 10
And my former partner
I wanted to know what he was up to
Messenger's dead
Whatever it's worth
Stabbed to
When I heard about that I asked the detective to find out more information last night I got a phone call from him
I've been digging around
What do you mean strange
Here it is
The draft of the report
Mrs Keller
Roberto
Look at this
Do you know what this means
Yes hello
Hey
I need that bag
Robert
Your wife and Fritz are already home
What are you saying
If you hurt them I might be hurrying right back
A lot of accidents happen at home
Give me a gun
Look there's something I got to do
Remember
That model is intended for close range work
Only got four shots so make them count don't worry about me
I was an officer Once Upon a Time
Can have me dying before you take me to the police and have me confess to killing your parents
That's right
So don't even think of dying on me
I'll cover you from the empty house next door good luck
Hi Daddy
Just kept on insisting he had to
To go fishing with his daddy
Barbara thank God
Where's Roberto
Oh that reminds me
The gentleman from his security team are here
He said something happened while we were out
Team
There's no need to worry he said everything's fine and no one was hurt
Oh Roberto look Michaels come home
Everything's all right
It was nothing important just a broken window
Probably just a kid from the neighborhood nothing to worry about nothing at all
Where's the body what have you done with him damn it a body what are you talking about
What's going on Roberto who the hell are you fr
It's in the little wife here heading inside don't be stupid hand over the bag
Now there you go
All right gentlemen nothing ever happened here understood just another boring day in paradise
Like yesterday and tomorrow
Nina
She is such a beautiful girl but
What did you do to her don't look at me like that Nina's Fine my employer considers you're a very important
Important cast your employer well that young man he was your home too
Johan Johan Johan everywhere I look Yohan is there who the hell is he who the hell
How are you talk you want to live happily ever after with Barbara and Fritz don't you come back to your
Trust me leave it alone as employers go you weren't too
But this is where we say goodbye
What are you going to do with Nina you going to die you
Care now
Hey Daddy can you and me go fishing sometime soon
Oh yeah
If it's sunny
How about tomorrow
It's over
I don't see ghosts anymore
You have very nice eyes
You're definitely Johan sister
I let you take me in without a fight because you promised I'd get to see him
I did indeed
He's really looking forward to catching up with you right now if you must know he's living Happ
Italian Munich
Ich you know you really have very nice eyes Such a Pity
I just can't bring myself to do it
No what's next
Ah yes Dr Tenma
But why
Why did you come
It's like I told you
For Better or For Worse
I did used to be a cop
Don't worry you're almost home I know
I told Fritz that we'd go fishing tomorrow I promised
Good I hope it's sunny
I'm sure
It will be