You wake up
Leave me alone
Yeah like that's going to happen
Now get up
We can still do this the easy way come on this isn't a hotel
Don't touch me
How dare you
Do you have any idea who I am
All right
Here's all the stuff you came in with
If everything's in order you can sign here
Ms Heineman
I don't ever want to see you tossed in the cooler again
Passing out drunk alone in the dark alley be thankful something horrible didn't happen to you
You got a cigarette
I'm just asking if you've got a cigarette
There's no smoking in the station go outside if you want to smoke
Later
Where is my lighter
My bag
I want to know what you did with my bag
And I already told you it's the only bag you had
You liar I know you're not telling me the truth I had another shoulder bag where is it
Probably with whoever stole it from you when you passed out drunk in the all
What are you going to do about it I have valuables important things in there
I tell you what
You can fill out a theft report if you like
But I really wouldn't get your hopes up
How the hell did you lose your key
My bag was still in last night just hurry up and open the room for me
What what happened here
Damn
Somebody really want to town
Oh man this is awful
I got to change the lock now
Which reminds me miss heinemann you still owe me back rent
I don't want to have to ask you again the deposit you put down is already run out I'm going to need the rest of what you
These people even broke into my damn suitcase are you listening
You have to pay for a new lock and all that back rent
Well I don't have any money
What
Fine I'll get out don't worry
Such a tragic story still I don't know what you expect me to do about
Any of it you know I seem to remember you being the one who stormed out on me oh come on that's
Ancient history now so I know buy me a drink
It's just a stolen purse for God's sake you must have had some extra cash checked away somewhere
Honestly have yet to meet another woman who could burn through money the way you do and here you are finally coming to me for
This is it welcome to Rock Bottom baby
I'll sleep with you you know
I'm asking you how much you'd be willing to pay honey as
General rule most men won't pay to have sex with women they've already had a bunch of times
You can at least buy me a drink you'll find yourself a street corner to work who
She might get lucky and meet some Sad Sack is not too picky desperate and middle-aged and drunk must be someone's type
Yeah I'm positive you didn't leave any
Papers here last night maybe you left it wherever you went next
How to remember anything after I left this ball
If it's worth any money you might as well Kiss It Goodbye
No it's not it's not worth anything at all
Not any money that is
Hey
I've been looking for you
I asked for you at the pub back there
And they told me you just headed in this direction
Yeah and who are you
Are you serious
We had such a good time drinking last night
I was drinking with you
Your bag
That's why I was looking for you
I guess this means I have to make
Awkward introductions again
I'm Roberto
So should we grab a little something to eat
Your hotel room
Really
That's terrible I'm so sorry I mean it's not like you did it
Well no obviously not
I didn't even dare look in your back
Oh look my hotel keys are still in here
A little late for those
I don't need them anymore
I'm sorry it's all my fault
If I'd return your bag sooner you wouldn't have been kicked out of your room in the first place
Besides I'm very grateful that you gave me back my back
Honestly I'm kind of grateful that you lost it
Well last night as I watched you leave the pub I sat there thinking to myself
You shouldn't let this person slip away
And now thanks to your bag
Here you are and here I am
You have something very important in there don't you
I do
This is all that I have left in the world
A photo album
May I take a look
That's my father
He looks just like I imagine
He was a hospital director right
Yeah did I talk about him last night
You did you spoke very highly of
You mentioned that he died 10 years ago
I could tell that you still miss him
Let's see
The ex-fiance
Please don't tell me I told you about him
I believe his name was Tem
Quite a guy
This Tenma
I really want to know what I said last night
Well I wouldn't make a habit of it
It might end up making other men jealous
On this page is empty
Is that so
The photos that were on this page looks like somebody tore them out
Well I guess I didn't need those pictures anymore
So I see
Hey
Let's get a drink
Sounds good
So you were running a security company
I'm impressed yeah
In the south of France
Then we had a bad day and one of our better clients was killed on my watch
So that was the end of that
We're both going through tough times forget it let's drink to the hearing now enjoy yourself
You know
It's good stuff huh
So you like this song too
Of course
Let's Dance
Come on
I don't really know how to dance around me
God
I know a man who love this song he wasn't a very good dancer either
So you'd end up dancing like this
That's right
How fun
How about another drink
Just one more
Thanks but I'm good
Lightweight
Time for bed
Sounds good to me babe
There's just one more thing
What's that
Pictures
Where are they
What pictures
Stop playing stuff
Those photographs you took out of the album
Where'd you hide them tell me see I'm
Your little secret you're looking for Tenma aren't you
I know you get those photos from burning and I'm sure you have them with you somewhere
Know where 10 - yeah
Photographs that you're talking about
May the ones with father in that boy am I right
Wasn't it
Him you know blonde Charming handsome he's grown up well I
A year ago and Dusseldorf
Enzo let's start over you
Do you need me
Enzo
You Belong To Me
I will get you back because you're mine
So
What are you up to these days
I've heard all sorts of rumors
The rumors are probably true
I've been married and divorced three times now
Between my father's inheritance and my alimony I'm living pretty comfortably
But enough about me how is life been treating you Dr Becker
Huh
I don't know
Nothing's changed with me
I still have no chance of moving up in the world
Speaking of which technima's now chief of surgery where it is he's on his way to becoming Hospital director love to be
In his shoes let me tell you
But please who am I kidding it ain't so bad I still managed to have a good time
There's more to life than promotions I never want to be like 10 men have no time for women or fun what's the point
Is Kenzo
Do you know by any chance if Dr Tenma ever did settle down
No not yet
And a be completely honest I've introduced him to quite a few very nice women but you know him no interest at all his work
Comes first
As a matter of fact I'm about to set him up with a new girl God only knows if it's going to work out she's the daughter of
Picture of a state senator and she is absolutely beautiful
If she can't keep his attention that I give up
But anyway you called me about something
How can I be of service Ava
You know back when you were the daughter of the hospital director you never even gave me the time of day
Who would have thought that you'd even think to call
I understand you're well off
But really
I think you're getting lonely aren't you
I mean it when I say it Eva I'm more than happy to listen anytime
Look I don't want you to let them meet up
Dr tenman the state senators daughter
Don't let him meet her
Man I should have known
You're still in love with him
Don't let him
Do me a favor don't screw it up this time I went out of my way to set this one up for you then
Well we'll see about that
This is it this is the clock that Mr Yonkers was talking about at the hospital
Excuse me about the clock what's going on
What are you doing
That's a very beautiful watch
Why thank you I mean I wear a watch but mine is nothing a trinket
Honestly I don't even check the time anymore
I wonder why
Time seems to be moving faster and faster
Excuse me but who are you
I'm sorry I don't mean to be rude but are you Senator Burgers daughter Angelica
Goodness
You're a pretty little thing well aren't you
I thank you
I think and you're convinced that the entire world revolves around you
Am I right
Going through life thinking that there's nothing you can't have it must be very pleasant
I'm sorry what are you trying to say I'm confused who are you exactly
I have this tiny little birthmark on my inner thigh
He used to kiss it
How he used to love kissing me there
After 10 minutes
You know him
Oh no
See see she left because you were late and it's all because you had to stop in that store
Oh too bad I'm sorry about that
Can you do me a favor and apologize for me
Oh wait
Hey turn off
Maybe if you give her a call right now she might come back who
I want to stop by the hospital for a quick minute what at this hour
I've had it with you fine leave
Kenz
You're mine
You're all mine
Mr Yonk
Please wait
Mr Yonkers
Kenzo
What's going on
Wait cancel I have to talk to you
Mr Yonkers
Cancel
Oh great I broke my heel
I saw him you know oh yes a year ago
So in Dusseldorf I saw him it was Johann I'm sure of it
You saw your arm huh
I have to kill you