I saw you on
Disown have to kill you
Yes I've seen something that I wasn't supposed to see
I'm thinking it was that sweet looking blonde boy I saw in Dusseldorf a year ago
Because I've seen Johann this is how it ends up
That's how it works with you
It was dark and raining when I heard those three gunshots
I was there alone and got scared so I ran away
At the time I was pretty certain it was tedma who'd been shot dead
But the next day there was this big article in the newspaper saying that a man named Yonkers had been found dead in the same location
And that he'd been shot three times
So then that boy did it didn't he
Might want to rethink holding that trigger
If you kill me you'll never forget what you really want
That photograph you've been looking for the one of Johann as a young boy
Let me tell you what will happen if you do decide to kill me
If I die I've arranged for that photo you want so much to be delivered directly to the bka
If you want to see that photograph you need to tell me exactly where tenema can be found
Just what is so funny your whole body is quivering you
Talk tough but your legs are shaking so hard you can barely stand
You really do amuse me
Tell you where he is so what is now oh he's still working as a doctor
But our friend is going on the ground
How's this older guy in Hanover who was the number two men in a certain organized crime family well
You guys boss kind of freaked out and put out a hit on him but the job got botched the guy got all shut up
But he didn't die so Tim was at this remote Alpine estate patching him up it's up on a
Near foosen
Excuse me but why did you just stand there like that
Hey mister it's almost time for lunch
Why in the world are we eating outside
I just thought
The weather looks so nice this afternoon
Why not mix up our routine and eat outside
Why have our lunch out here
Dieter
Go ahead and bring the plates out here
Okay
Oh your wounds are healing nicely
And this fresh air will do you good
I have to say doctor
If you hadn't been there I doubt I would have made it
That country Clinic was pathetic but the masterful skills you possess allowed you to save my life
Maybe the one bullet just grazed your head and the other one went into your leg and passed through cleanly
Just be thankful it didn't catch your femoral art
To be honest you are quite lucky
Lucky huh
Alrighty guys lunches
Wow that smells good heckle
Surprising isn't it it tastes Del
Delicious Heckle may look more like a pickpocket but he's actually quite the chef don't you agree and what in the hell did you mean
Mean by that
This my friends is chicken Marengo the key to the dish is the sauce you have to get it just right
It's based on a recipe from a three-star French restaurant called La Petite
Look like you just can't appreciate the subtleties of fine cuisine you know this would take Stephen better with a dash of soy sauce
Soy sauce not that again you put soy sauce on everything thank you this is dining
When you sit down to eat this is how it should be
What a Wast
All my life everything I did was to make money
But while I was earning all those Millions I lost things much more valuable
Both of my parents
And my only brother disowned me even my wife and son were murdered
I always wanted to leave peacefully
Dying like we're doing right now
Money can really change the way people
Allow me to share a good example with you
5 years ago a covert banking organization was formed to facilitate the underground funds flowing throughout Germany
But these guys pulled off was absolutely amazing
Within days of the Dirty Money flowing in through Shady companies it would come out the other side perfectly clean
A money laundering operation exactly
On top of that this organization functioned in many ways like a real Bank
Making loans and investing in speculative transactions
And a girl unbelievably fast in five short years they made a fortune
Hot damn
But that all changed this year because the man who'd been running the show suddenly vanished he hasn't been seen in months and
Windows where he
Guess what happened then
All of it fell apart
The entire operation
Uploaded
The associates that remains started fighting over who would get what was left and who would be in charge
Most of them ended up killing each other
The entire operation disappeared
If only they've been sensible and talk things out while sharing a fine dinner
You think that guy got murdered or did he just run off
Keep up doc I mean the head honcho guy who disappeared
So kidnapped murdered what do you think
Oh no
I'm quite sure he's still alive
In fact he might even be posing as a student somewhere
A student
That's right I forgot to tell you
I left out something important
According to my sources the guy who created that money laundering organization 5 years ago was just a kid
15 years old
15 years old you sources must be nuts no way it could pull off something like
Like that but it's true this kid did it
Senses if he was conducting his own experiment to see how adults deal with money
As though he were a child
Playing around with a line of ants
Where was all this
Do you know where this covert banking operation was based
The organization was headquartered in Dusseldorf but the kid at the top was constantly on the move
He controlled the entire operation from wherever he was you know
And did anybody figure out the last place that he was seen before he disappeared
I saw the details I know but I heard right after their young boss went missing all of his money hungry underlings went Rush
Into mun
Communicate
Hey Doc why the long face huh what's going on
I know
Let's invite that man down the hell up here for lunch sure why not
That's a good idea
Sorry doctor but that means my body God he needs to stay down there
But haven't you been officially declared dead already
You still think there are people out there who want to do you harm
Are you planning to live the rest of your life and fear hiding behind a bodyguard
How much has been with me for a very long time indeed
Go ahead son
Go and get helmet so that's his name he wouldn't be at all I bet
Go and tell him that his duties is My Bodyguard her over
Is the only one left is like family to me
Ask him to join us
Have him come here so we can discuss our future at this table
Mr Helmut lunch time they want you to come up and join us
Time is right up there in the mountain Villa
You do want to kill him don't you
Something to matter that was a security breach signal from helmet
Unfortunately I think he's already dead
Wait someone's coming after you
There's no telling but I'd say someone's heading up here even as we speak
Mr helmet song
Go tell him
You have to tell him to run away
Hurry go until 10 minutes now
Tell him damn it
I said go tell him
But your leg you've been shot don't worry about me go
Hang on
Who's shooting at us
Did you get him
I'm not sure
But now's your chance to run for it get going
But I can't go you're out here in the open I can help you I can handle this just
No no you can't I'm going home quick
Well well
Looks like I was wrong
She didn't want to kill him after all
You going to be all right man
I'll be fine
But I think
He's already heading up the hill on his way to the villa
Not a chance I would have seen him from here there's really only one path to get all the way up to that house
What are you talking about
I've explored this whole mountain and this path is the only way up there all the other pass lead to Cliffs no one can climb
So then if we guard this Trail there's no other way Roberto will be able to get far enough of the mountain to get to the villa
You mean you know this guy
I know him too well
Roberto's after 10 money he wants to kill him
You know Tenma so who are you ma'am are you a friend of his
What you laughing about ma'am don't make me sound so old stop calling me man
Now get out of here kid you get up there until 10
Tell him to run away quick
But but man I mean lady you're bleeding
I'll be all right
You just get up there and warn him but your leg looks like it's bleeding a lot
10 my mustard those gunshots I bet he's headed down here to take care of that guy
It's not good
Roberta wants 10 minutes come down here and try to save us so we can kill him
Don't you see it's a trap and where the bait to bring him here
But what can we do man if we try to make a run for it with your leg you might bleed to death stop calling me ma'am what did I
Tell you
So just what are you to tend anyway I miss friend
What about you
I mean lady
Aren't you a friend of tennis too you must because even though you're hurt really bad you're still trying to save him
I'm not trying to be nosy but
You like 10 but don't you
Are you a girlfriend you just keep watching that side
Do you like 10
Yeah I like him a whole lot what exactly do you like about him
Lots of things
What do you like about
I know you're there crawl around all you want for you
Pretty stupid to shoot me again I already told you if I die that picture of Johann is a child that
You want so badly will automatically be sent straight to the bka I mean it this is your last warning if
So that photo you've got is something you really want it's a lie and it might not
Don't work he's too smart to fall for such a trick lady are you feeling all right
Need to fade I've lost a lot of blood
Now go we'll get out of here save yourself
I can't just leave you 10 minutes on his way he would have been here by now he's got to be headed here
I mean it look there's no way he would ever come to save me
Nothing but a waste of time
Peter where are you
Over here just stay there
I'm coming to get you Peter
Don't move
If you try to come get us there's a man here that's going to shoot you
That's why he's come here 10
To kill you
I know that voice but it can't be
10 months this lady is a friend of yours she's been shot and she's bleeding a lot
You can't die no not what I'm so close I'm handing you over to the police
I want every waking moment to hurt for dumping me stop shouting you're straining yourself
Hey Jesus just tell
Tell me if you can hear me okay can you tell where the shooter is
No I don't know
I've got no clue where he is or even if he still here
Stop yelling to him I need 10 more alive
Hang in there he's getting close
He's not coming to hear you're wrong
He would never come to my rescue
It's all over for me don't die please
Why would she ever
Rescue Me
What's all this why did you bring me out here
It's time for lunch
Your leg has been healing up nicely
And I thought you'd enjoy eating lunch outside in this beautiful sunshine
You're a lucky woman you know
What do you mean
Just
A guy who shot you was a real Pro you know what he was doing
He understood how difficult it would be for him to infiltrate this mountain Villa
There's only one path to get up here
And there are security cameras everywhere
He also knew this Villa would be guided by experienced men so it would be like he was attacking an Alpine Fortress
That was the reason he used you
Hold on what do you mean he used me
It's simple
He must have figured that a pretty woman making an unexpected visit would have a much better chance of getting all the way up here than he
But when you betrayed him his old plan was sunk
He had no plan B there were no other options for him
So he got out of here quick and cut his losses
So then he got away
That's right
We search the whole Mountain
This is a special dish
It's called chicken Marengo
I tried to recreate the recipe but I can't guarantee it'll be any good
You know there's another way you were very lucky
You were lucky to have a great doctor like Dr tender treating you
So is Tim still here
He already left
Where to thank you said something about going to mun
Munich a
All right
Let's see if you and I can enjoy this chicken I got a feeling you're like me and I
Long time since you sat down and enjoyed a meal in peace