Old Karina why are your letters
Ever ever so short
As with you police The Scholar of the Stars
And his
Astrology that you drive my heart mad and such the gold
Ideas it's colors faded while the work of the artist
Well what are you waiting for put the book on the shelf and go if I did something
Your friend me you're offending me right now
I'm not sure what I did to upset you sir but I'm sorry nonetheless if you can't wrap your tongue
No your brain around Latin you're of no use to me is a reader understood I'm sorry sir
I'll be more careful I told you to get out
He really tore into you back at the Mansion didn't he
Don't move Carl
Business major should have thicker skin than that
I'm sorry but
Do I know you
I'm loved to Frank a cultural anthropology major I'm guessing you work for him too are you another one of his
Part-time student readers whatever needs doing
He only lets boys do the reading
As I'm sure you already know
Anyway he's got a different reader each day of the week
Your Tuesdays of course
Hey so what do you think of our boss anyway the ever mysterious Hans gay York shuval recl
Tycoon
Nah beats me
I was looking for work in the money was good honestly that's all I needed to know
Are you saying you've never heard the rumors about him
He works the stock market like a marionette
One phone call from him leaves Banks across Germany quaking in their boots they call him the Howard Hughes
Bavaria
He has no family no close friends it's just him and his money his fortune keeps growing and growing every year
On Earth is he spend it on anyway
Who knows
I didn't even get to the weird part yet
Other nickname is the vampire of Bavaria
How come just as the clock strikes 2 a.m.
Like a hearse and whisk him off into the night
I've seen it myself something out of a horror movie
Maybe he's getting some air
I'll find out soon enough what else you've all up to
What do you mean you're going to find out
It's for my research paper silly
Mental activities of medieval and present-day Financial figures of Bavaria
I lucked out she was all the gold mine
So you look me up cuz he yelled at me is that it
Just your name and your major I'm not a snoop
Anyway I wouldn't lose any sleep over him chewing you out
He yells at all the guys who read to him
Yeah
Well I guess it's a good thing I'm used to getting yelled at
What do you mean
It's just I spent a lot of time in foster homes some of them weren't so nice
So that's why there's no record of you at any of the local high schools
You looked up more than my major in name
It's got to be rough
Growing up without your real parents like that
The truth is
I came to Munich for school because I thought maybe I could find my mother
That's great
Have you seen her yet
No
It wasn't meant to be
What do you mean
You just throw in the towel
Hey you don't happen to know your mom's name
Well go ahead
It wasn't meant to be okay
Come on tell me
If you don't we both know I'm going to look her up anyway
Margo
Her name is Margo Langer
Silly you have her full name and you were ready to give up like that find her
What are you waiting for
No
It's too late for reunions
Here we go Margo Langer what do we
Oh no
Like a chestnut mare at full stride
Passion Electric
Barking great wife
Only beautiful things are deserving of my love
We are reading pains
Why didn't you explain Carl
If only I had known
Now I understand why you gave up looking
I'm so sorry for your loss I already said that it doesn't matter didn't I
Well listen
Carl if there's anything I can do just ask me
That's sweet of you but I'm fine
Hey Lott
You said you wanted to figure out where shoe Vault goes at night
You're going to follow him right
Would you mind if I came along for the ride
No not at all
Sure does beat sneaking through the darkness by myself
I'm telling you it's true
Are supernatural phenomena research group is finally hit pay
There is no way
In any case
Listen up Bishop gropius one of the founders of our school wrote this poem in the year 1502 that much
Already know for sure
Now consider the following vers
On the second to the last big year
The boy of Thursday will arrive upon the land
And the book shall go up in flames
The entire world will be shrouded in sorrow crazy huh
So it's spooky what's your point again
Don't you get it guys
Look it says right here the second to the last big year
What year is it 1996 right
So that means this is the year
How do you figure
Listen
The Big Year means leap year
And the only leap years left in this Century are this year and the year 2000 he will arrive upon the
And the book shall go up in flames
The part about the books in this land means that this University will go up in flames
Okay then who's this boy Thursday huh
Thursday
Well let's
Don't understand comes from the word donor
Yeah and donor means Thunder the god of thunder
You lost your damn mind hey this is going to be the front page story of our next newsletter it's no laughing
Better run the article if it'll make you happy but come on nobody's going to buy this a God of destruction coming to
Our University
Vampire at Bavaria he is
And this is what we find out
There he goes
Well that was stupid I'm out of here
Okay be careful I want to see what he was up to
What do you think he was up to
Hey
Maybe this isn't such a good idea
You're probably right this is no place for a girl you should go home only beautiful things are deserving
Of my love
I need to know
I need to know how miserable of a man he really is
Yeah it's open
If you're looking for some fun you came knocking on the wrong door
I got out of the business a long time ago kid
Who are you
Nice manners kid you want my name shouldn't we start with yours
Margo Langer Pleasures all mine
I bet your students from the University aren't you
Right
And both of us have part-time jobs working for hanshuvalt congratulations what do you want
Tell me why
Why does he come here to see you in the middle of the night like he does
It's simple kid I make him feel better
But not in the way you're thinking just cuz he's up at this hour doesn't mean he's up at this hour if you catch my
He brings me money scads of it
And why shouldn't he
When I finally went to shoe volt and told him who I was he broke down crying and apologized on the spot
I had his son and he threw me out on the street like I was a piece of trash
Wait so
Carl is she saying that you're hunchew about son
How would you know you liar
How dare you
How dare you pretend to be Margo Langer
The real one was all over the papers a year ago
Prostitute
Former prostitute Margo Langer murdered police say killer still at Large
The woman you call yourself is already dead how could any human being stoop so low
You're using my dead mother's name to kill all that of his money and he's falling for it
Shoe ball knows the score
Well he knows I'm not the real thing but he still gives me money hand over fist
All the money in the world can't buy him forgiveness from the real Margo Langer that ship is sailed
I understand is the next best thing money money
That's all the bastards been living for
And the only way he knows how to say sorry
Don't look so teary-eyed kid you know Saint yourself
You and I both know shoe balls on his way out
Take a good look at him if you're going to play the long lost Sun card better do it while we can change his will
Are you implying you're giving me grief for being an imposter
But you didn't exactly Walt's in here with a positive paternity test
Just watch out for the competition boy
You're not the only one who says he shoveled son
Yeah he came to see me a little while back told me the same sob story you did
No way it can't be
Excuse me if I don't take your word for it
For the record I think you're both full of it so this other guy who is he another student
A bunch of you take turns reading books to shoe ball the different boy every day of the week ain't that right
You've got that in common Carl yes sir I think he's the Thursday
Day boy
You could have insisted a little harder that you're his real son
What's the point
I was passed along from foster home to foster home from most of my life
Usually sending me from bad to worse
But I finally ended up with a couple who loved me as though I were there very own
They're everything I ever could have wanted
But they're being so wonderful made me want to meet my biological father even more
I thought that if I could see what a sad little man he was with my own eyes
I could finally return my foster parents love
That's all
I was trying to do
Hey Lotte tell me something have you ever seen this Thursday boy
That's one day of the week I always have off from work
But this one Thursday I went in to grab something I'd forgotten
And he was there reading right
Tell me what he looked like
Let me think
I want to say he had blonde hair in a very beautiful face
Who is he
Someone in this University
Is pretending to be me
Carl are you listening to me this is important take this money
What about you Mom
Honey I already told you I can't go with you
But how come are you in trouble I don't want to go alone mom you have
No choice if you stay with me they'll call you off to some orphanage around here people will mock you was the son of a w****
Now go on what about my dad can't my dad make it better somehow his name
My name is hanske York Schubert isn't it
Who told you that old Mrs Bella from across the street my dad's riches and he
He said he abandoned us how come you would do something like that
He didn't abandon us Carl
No just go where he is and you can find us there no you can't so when can I see him
Oh Carl when you're all grown up you can meet your father if you want
You hate him if he turns you away please
Why shouldn't I because
Mommy doesn't hate him even now
Keep this with you always
It was a gift from your father on the day you were born
Carl I know who he is
Earth to Carl I know who the Thursday boy is what
His name is Edmund for
He's a philosophy major
I'm sure he's the guy we're looking for he reads books to shuvall that the Mansion every Thursday
Edwin Farrah
Get ready
You should be coming out of that lecture hall any second
Hey
You wouldn't happen to know Edmund foreign would you
Oh
Hey guys is Edmund here
Who had been foreign
I think he was a no-show today
There you go
Oh
Okay so he dodged the bullet today
But seriously
It's only a matter of time before we give that fraud what's coming to him
No imposter's going to cheat you out of shoe balls inheritance
It's not about the money
I couldn't care less if I see any part of his fortune no if they want to Rob shuvall
Fine they can go right ahead
Who cares
Then why
Because
Because I can't stand the thought of this bastard far and pretending to be my mother's son there's no forgiving something like that
With the pedals of your silk flowers swaying in the breeze
The Cry of the Mockingbird rang through my heart
You haven't told me to stop reading yet
Why is that sir I berate you all the time why do you insist
I'm coming back
Here's the money that good that isn't why
With all due respect sir it's nothing like that
Is money the only incentive to do something in your world
In my world or any other
What are they
Your parents
Actually I was raised by a series of foster families
Forgive me for praying
Would you meet your real parents if you could
Well sir
Actually
I'm yes this young man who reads to me just may be the one I've wait
It for
It doesn't seem to be after my money
Who is he
Never mind I'm talking to myself
It's time we called it a day Norman
Oh one more thing
Regarding your Latin boy
It is much improved
Well thank you very much sir
Looks like Edmund fahren's playing hooky today too
Pictures laid up in bed with a bad cold or something like that
Tomorrow's Thursday he'll be there
He'll be at the mansion in so will I
Oh I get it you're going to bust him as the faker he is right in front of you right
That's awesome
Let's go get him already
He was supposed to be here an hour ago
If you were sick and stuck in bed at least then we would know where to find him
Hey
I want to barge into his room and confront him there
Hold on
Don't tell me you looked up Florence address
204 jackpot
Here we go
It's been so Grim around here
The whole school's talking about what happened to Edmund foreign
The school paper actually printed a suicide note didn't they
I can no longer continue to deceive
So that's what it was about
I guess so
Spending all that time with you all to acting like his son maybe the guilt just blindsided him
I've been known he was going to grow a conscience he'd have been better off not trying in the first place
Lot
Yesterday must have been tough
Hey
Don't you know it
Since we're the ones who discovered the body the police held us for questioning all day
Well I didn't end up reading today after all
Mr schewald is taking the news very hard
Hey I'm being rude this is Carl he's the Friday reader
A pleasure to meet you
The same here
I'm call Norman from the economics Department
I'm you hun Liebert I study in the School of Law