That's good enough
When you say that just what exactly do you mean Mr shoevald
I've decided that I've learned enough I am calling off the investigation
But sir we had a breakthrough and I'm close to another I checked out Carl Norman and one thing certain that boys
Real son I'm quite grateful to you for all you've done
Now hold on there's still more to be done there's still the Edmund foreign they should have figured out Edmund pretended to be your
He didn't really commit suicide if that's really the case someone else
Just pulling the strings and may have killed foreign
It has been solved to my satisfaction
Father I made some tea would you care for some yes I would
Good afternoon Detective
Would you care to join us no thank you I'll be going
Once again good work just send me your bill
Good day
It sure looks nice outside oh and Johan's come as well
What a surprise so johann's decided to visit
Shoe volt it always been known as a distrustful man with a sour disposition
Who would have thought that he turned into such a good-natured soul when he found his son
Well that smile of his
Who'd have guessed that people still call him the vampire of Bavaria
What a surprise so your heart's decided to visit
How cute
So you're trying to track down this puppy
What a job
My client told me her ex-husband basically dognapped a little fell
I guess disputes over pets can be just as bad as one's over kids
You're right about that
I think I left some wine if that's quite all right with you
Are you go ahead
I'll be sticking with a sparkling water
I'm glad to hear you say that I know it works scarce at the moment but it's a good choice on your part not to Cloud your life with
Alcohol
I'm doing okay
Least of that account
What do you mean
Are you saying there's something else in your life that's bothering you
Well I find that with all the free time I have now I end up rehashing things a lot
Such as
I spend hours and hours pouring over this personal notebook I have of unsolved crimes cases I never solved as
Detective
How interesting
So tell me when you look at it how do you feel
I feel frustrated
There were so many murder cases I wasn't able to solve
It haunts me to think of those vicious Killers still out there walking around in our world
They're free because of my incompetence
Even now I can't seem to catch them
You're being too hard on yourself
You could have caught them you had the skills to solve those cases but yourself critical nature was impeding you Richard
You got frustrated that you couldn't read these murderer's minds and that caused you pain
So I turned to alcohol
Sure of course you did gentleman
Dinner is served
Oh good it's time to eat
Actually I think it would be in your best interest for you to keep trying
I would encourage you to keep looking at your old police notebook
But why
I'll just become angry again
Stop thinking that way
You have to analyze what you did in the past in a new light
Your mind is clearer now that should help
Let's be frank with each other we both know that you shot a young serial killer when you were drunk
And I must say you are facing the reality of what happened that night admirably
But now Richard you face a far greater challenge
Facing your thoughts when you pulled that trigger
You're still haunted by that boy
You see him in your mind everyday don't you
When you brought everything to light
All those things festering under the surface
That boys ghost will finally move on
I see
When I've brought everything to light huh
The Homer murder case is a good place to start
The victim you I came home or had a long and steady career as an accountant
He was never involved in anything shady
They had no enemies
And when he was murdered
There were no signs of a robbery
Then there were those two voice of God cases
The victims were a former housekeeper and a chauffeur
What connected those two killings was that the words I have heard the voice of God were left
Scroll on a wall at both crime scenes
The door knock company president case
Go to Gall cuz one of the wealthiest businessmen in Bavaria and his body was discovered in the heart told Forest
And then there's the spirit a couple case
Both were forcibly drowned at their bodies washed up along the east our River later on
This one's still being investigated is one of a string of murders involving middle-aged couples
A material witness in that case disappeared Japanese Doctor Who's still on the Run
Oh man
The more unsolved cases I had the more booze I drank
Then it felt good
Different now this is tough
It feels just like the doctor said so I'm sober my mind is clear and I'm feeling calm
Hold on a second
Come on think
Playing card Richard
So
You tried doing it again and what was the result
I did
I looked at all my notes
And I thought of something new but
But then I
You saw that boy's ghost again and once that happened you lost your train of thought right
There's no need to worry
When you have an important thought like that sooner or later it will come back to you
What was it that I realized
An idea flash through my mind it felt like it was a key to solving one of those cases
Just My Imagination
Who's there
Show Yourself whoever you are I'll catch you
Just like that time way back I was
Sorry for coming here so late at night doc
Nons
If you think you've figured things out and you're ready to share them go ahead then tell me everything
Back then I felt myself looking deep within that killer
That's when I knew it existed in this world
Later was true evil
And once I saw it standing right there in front of me I shot and killed him
That's good thank you for sharing Richard by telling me this you're well in the road to recover
There's still more doctor
It just came to me that idea that it flashed through my mind before all
All those unsalt cases I have been working to solve separately I realized
They are actually one single case huh
Greetings my dear Dr Gillen
I'm writing to thank you for sending me a copy of your recently published book
Transcendental criminal psychology
I found your book informative and a very interesting read and it pleases me to see that a student of mine from Duss
University
Has now become a leading Authority in the field of criminal psychology
Now I have a question for you regarding another matter
You told me in a phone conversation that you conducted the lengthy interview with the serial murderer Peter J
After you spoke with him you told me that Jergens claim that a friend of is it encouraged him to murder the victims
Sadly my memory isn't what it used to be so could you please tell me again
What was the name of jurgen's friend who he said told him to kill
I'd appreciate that information as it may Aiden associate of mine
P
As I mentioned earlier you were quite a student in college and excelled in my class
And you had a fellow colleague who was equally bright
You often competed with him for the best marks
He graduated and became a neurosur
At any rate it seems that he's become a suspect in a Multiple homicide case
With your expertise I'm hoping you could help me get a better picture of who he is
Please tell me everything you might know about him
What kind of person is he
Where do you think he might be right now
This doctor Tenma
I remember you you're a detective
It will I used to be
And now I'm a private investigator
I'm sorry to show up unannounced here at your
And I hate to bring up a subject I know must be painful
I'd appreciate it if I could ask you some questions again
Of course you can it's been 4 years since I last spoke to the police and it seems like they're done with their investigation
Mr
Yes I believe your mother was actually employed
Wasn't she once the head housekeeper at his mansion
Well at that time she became very ill
And after her sickness she only worked close to home in the neighborhood
Was that it or could it be she had some problem with Mr Chev
No not at all
They were actually quite good friends she told me that she used to read poetry to Mr schubald when he was still able to see
My mother just loved reading poems to him
Come along
I want to show you something
Look how generous he was to her
I've kept all of them because they remind me of my dear Mother
Every one of those books are collections of poetry that were given to my mother as a thank you from Mr schub
How are things change
The head detective and the door knock company president cases now just a private eye
Do you worked as Mr gox Chief business liaison and personal secretary
I asked you once again did anyone hold a grudge against him
You mean did anyone hate him
There aren't enough hours in the day to count all the people who despise him
In business Mr God was such a fierce adversary that he personally forced some of our competition to go bankrupt
But there was another powerful and well-known businessman in Bavaria wasn't there
How did Mr gauch feel about him
I take it you mean Mr schewald
Well they were lifelong rivals in business but of course you knew that right
They knew each other very well
When Mystic golf was still alive she was company went bankrupt two
That second bankruptcy happened when Mr gauch undercut two volts prices for the purpose of ruining him
So what you're saying is the Mr gauch was consciously trying to crush him
Mr schewald made certain we suffered serious losses too
So then they both hated each other
Of course
A few times they happen to be at the same party and it looks could kill they both would have been dead
Oh it was very tense they had expl
Fight
Like to Vipers
But those snakes understood each other's every move
Only those two tycoons could talk to each other on the same level
I never felt like they were enemies
This may sound weird but they were really more like friends
Hey careful up there
Careful up there
Oh yeah
I knew Hans real well
Poor Hans was one of those two people that ended up being victims in that awful voice of God murder case that Hans was
A good guy he deserves better
Just what is it that makes you say Hans was such a good guy
He was nice always treated me to a drink or two
Generous huh
I heard that Hans used to work for Mr shoe ball as his driver
He told me that but he worked at Shoe volts driver almost 30 years ago
Did Hans say why he stopped driving for Mr chevald well that was around the time old shoe volts company went bankrupt
So Hans never said that he and his boss didn't get along listen to me what I'm about to say is to honor the memory of Hans
If ever there was a guy who could get along with anybody and everybody it was Hans he was a prince even
Rich bastards like that vampire of Bavaria shoe vault
He treated us poor folks like kings and Hans always said he was the one who taught you about bird watching
A time about bird watching a vampire when he took
Welcome to the forest
It's hard to believe that was 2 years ago
But whenever I think of my dear husband
I just can't understand why such a kind and wonderful man ended up being murdered
It's unfair
He tied so horrib
You have my sympathies
Pardon my ask
But I believe your husband grew up as
Yes he lived in an orphanage till he was six then with different Foster families until he was 18
After that he became an accountant
Is it true Mr scheuvo the business tycoon asked your husband to be his corporate accountant
He did many times
But my husband always turned him down
My husband was quite busy with work at the time but that wasn't why
He said Mr scheuvald had a different set of financial principles
When it came to money my husband was very honest
Again thank you so much I appreciate the help
My husband's killer
Will he ever be caught
I'll try my best
If I can do it
I swear I'll catch him
Well then
One more thing
Yes
I forgot to ask you if you knew how your husband and Mr schuevault first met each other
Oh that
It seems they met in the forest
The forest
Yes they met in the forest back when Mr shoe ball could still see it was a total coincidence
What were they doing in a place like that
They were both their bird watching
After they meant they went to the forest together all the time
Bird watching
More like a happy kid
Red poetry to Mr shoe vald
Friends
Hey buddy you okay
Yeah I'm fine thanks that guy was driving like an idiot
From what I saw look more like he was trying to run you over
Man what a creep
Dr recvine
I've re-examined all the evidence
And what I found out supports what I told you before
Some of the key murder cases that I wasn't able to solve
I'll point to one killer having just one Mot
There's the voice of God
Murder case
And the door knock company president
The accountant murder case
Look at the three of them
They're all extremely different
The methods in which they were committed for example
And the victims were related to each other
None of them even knew each other
However
I have discovered that all of them shared one common Bond
There was a man who connected all the victims
And because they knew him they were all murdered
Every one of them was killed to further isolate Mr shoeval
There's also another Connection in these cases that's rather curious in the door knock company president case
His secretary said there was a certain young man who was supposed to meet with Mr gauch right before he was murdered
And in the voice of God cases under I have heard the voice of God this name was scrawled there by the murderer
And then there's the spirit a couple murder case
Since both of them drowned that case seem to be unrelated to the others
But the name of the killer given by the Japanese Doctor Who was the only witness in that case was the same
It was the same name in every case
Yohan
I've been in touch with the former student of mine who's now a renowned criminal psychologist he interviewed a murderer who claim
And he committed his crimes on his friends orders
In here he wrote that friend's name
And the name that's in this letter is Johan
Johann is a common name but based on what you found it's also possible that all these cases could
Would be related
If by chance you're findings are true this Johan has been systematically murdering people for the past 4 years
I can't help but wonder why this man known as Johann is trying to force you've all into complete isolation
Oddly enough Margo Langer the woman who bore you both suck conveniently died as well
And there was that young student who was pretending to be shoe Ball's son he conveniently killed himself
As soon as he made his claim if Yohan really does exist I wonder where he is right now
No perhaps he's close
An the weather
He's right next to shoe volt