Rainbow Ranger J
Hey that's not fair you're supposed to fall when I kick you
My evil empire is going to take over the world you're puny little kick isn't enough to stop me
The bad guys always losing the TV show don't you know anything hahaha well well
How's the global domination coming along
The big secret to breaking the rules is to make it look as though you're following them
So what sort of plans do you have for the Earth
Who knows why should I care I'm just going to destroy everything anyway
A lot more fun than being a stupid hero yeah forget being a rainbow refilling
Well guys shall we start making our way back
Okay come on so did you have fun today
Time to go home
Finally starting to warm up a bit
That's good
I guess
Has Rosemary
You know
Not a one
Too busy romping around with her friends to get sick
That's good she used to get those fevers like clockwork
Hey remember that one time years ago rushing her to the doctor and the dead of night
Those old pictures
You always keep them on you
Of course I do I bet she's a lot bigger now they grow up so fast these photos of mine
The ancient history
But still
No matter how grown up she gets I'll always know it's her the moment I'll rise mate She'll always be my
Oh almost forgot whenever she's ready please give Rosemary what's in the sandal up
The newspaper clippings mostly and the official Internal Affairs report
From when I shot that young man who killed all those people
I'm not asking you to defend me
Done that enough
I shouldn't have shot him
And I'll be the first to say it
I just want our daughter to know to know the truth about her old man even if it's terrible
I understand
She said either way
I'll ask her again if she wants to see you
If she's okay with it then so am I really oh thank you
Just give me a call at the latest time usually home by 9:00
To see the old you again
That look in your eyes they Shone like that when you first made detective remember that fire
Are you heading your belly when you and I first met
We both had
So what do you think
If you enroll today we can get you in at a lower premium
The thing of it is we already have insurance
We don't really need another policy
Let me just show you our rates Mr Liebert that's all I ask
The coverage we have right now is more than enough
I couldn't afford a whole new policy at the moment anyway
We've had our current one for 4 years ever since we moved into this neighborhood 4 years huh where were you
Anything before
Well over near Manheim in Boone
Bruton how about that it's a nice area so are you folks from their originally yeah we are
Nice is an understatement
So do you folks have any kids
He's attending the University of Munich here as it turns out we're offering a new plan
Perfect for young adults hear me out this won't take a minute
Oh your son I presume
Well he sure was a handsome baby
What's his name
His name is Johan would you like some tea
Yeah don't go to any trouble on my account
They must keep him pretty busy at school
Seems like he hasn't called us in a long time boys get like that when they leave the nest sounds like you speak from exper
Experience
Hello Dr rifine
I'm back
Yeah I went to Johan's folks house
That's the
Thing
They were normal as could be
Totally average
So what do you make
Richard
Hello back in my detective days I probably would have said there's nothing fishy or than normalcy
Or something to that effect
Now I just don't know
At any rain I'm going to keep checking out the people around you hun
Where's the flaw
Nobody's that perfect
You won't enjoyed a great reputation during his prep school days is grades were Top Notch and is evaluations
Game is a model student
But still no matter how grown up she gets I'll always know it's
You're the moment I'll rise mate She'll always be my little girl
The baby's face in the photo there's no way he grew up to look like you're on
Here you go sir the birth certificate you asked about
Thank you
Johann Wilhelm Liebert
Date of birth
9th of February 1976
So it was definitely born in this town
Everything here reads pretty legit
Mr Hertz how many times do I have to tell you you cannot
Not light up in here just give me an ashtray I promise I'll smoke it real quick no way and risk another fire like
4 years ago I am not replacing all those damn files again mister
You had to recreate your files from scratch we
We got all our ducks in a row again eventually
Hey
Thank you so much for coming Dr Gillen
Good to see you again
It's been too long Dr reichv
So I'm to understand that when Dr tenmark came to see you he was looking for a young man he called Johan
That's right but there was no evidence with which to corroborate his story
However if the young man in this photo is the friend who manipulated my current research subject
When Peter Jurgens a serial killer into committing another murder
Then Clues must exist that tie these three events together
I'm counting on you Dr Gill
Right
I'll get clearance to interview Jurgens as soon as possible
I'll let him see this Photograph and monitor any reactions if it might help prove 10 minutes innocence it's worth
Try
So he's dead
That's right
The real Johan Liebert who was born in Boone town
Died when he was 2 years old
Hold on
You're saying the liebert's replaced their dead sun with someone else and after that fire destroyed the original records
I use that chance to plug the other boy into that identity I'm afraid so if they did
Then who's this young man masquerading is Johan Liebert alive and well
Beneath the
Who the hell is he
At any rate
I did pass along Johan's photograph to Dr Gillen when he stopped in to see me
Hopefully he'll get to interview that killer of his again sometime soon
Now then
How about dinner
Sorry but it's getting late
Another time what's this
You run around all day and now you're working through the night as well hardly
I'm expecting a very important phone call
Cross your fingers
There's a chance I may get to see Rosemary
Really
Don't worry I'm okay
You're always telling me to focus on the road ahead aren't you
Of course
This is an important step in your recovery
Yes hello
Hi
It's
Hi Rosemary
Yeah Daddy's fine
Of course
I'd love to see you
You say when
And I'll be there
Mr Brown
It's Johan
Tell me you're against this young man
Do you recognize him
Maybe you've met him somewhere before
I don't know him
Best friend of yours
Johan right
You only know him through his letters you've never actually met him isn't that correct
But Johan certainly seem to know a lot about you
Could I borrow your PIN for a moment
What's that
I'm sorry you know the rules here prohibit me from giving you anything
Give me your PIN
The park
That's where I was
Killed someone the day before
I remember thinking I'm going to stop killing people
I've had enough of office
That's what I told myself
He was there
With a bunch of kids
Wait hold on a second I should be recording this just start over again please
Come with us come with us
Come with us come with us comma
What are you doing here
We met at Mr schewald's estate remember
Johan Liebert sir
I've been trying to get in touch with you but to no avail so
I figured I'd drop by
Yes
Oh Dr Gillen it's you good
So did anything interesting happen when you showed Jurgens that photograph of Johan
Wait he's dead
Correct
I'm at the hospital right now
The police still aren't done questioning me
So I'm stuck
Listen we lost a vital witness tonight because I was careless and handed a psychopath of ballpoint pen
But I do know one thing for sure
Jergens committed suicide
Because he saw that photograph of Johan
I'll be over there as soon as I finished up
Police all right
All right
I'll give Richard a call and let him know
He'd better be home
A report for class huh
That's right
On the recent un convention on the rights of the child
And if the treatment of juvenile offenders holds up
Oh how rude of me care for something to drink no thanks I'm fine
That's right you do abstain from alcohol
Yeah
Probably for the best
You did have quite a drinking problem
I mean you were drunk when you shot that boy isn't that right
So I've heard
Yes I was
Not that it matters
What I did is unforgivable drunk or not I have a few questions about what happened if you don't mind
Tell me about the victim
Stefanios age 17
Of what crimes did the child been accused
Don't be so naive son
Yours was a monster
He was old enough to rape and murder nine women and almost killed two more
So you executed
No I didn't
Pardon me
Speaking of
Article 40 of the UN convention
States every child is presumed to be innocent until proven guilty according to the law
Were you familiar with that
Yes of course I was I used to work in juvenile detention and article 37
The one that goes you cannot impose capital punishment or life imprisonment without possibility of release on any person
Symbol of the age of 18 you know that one
The convention Agreements are considered basic human rights for adults and children alike
What kind of a fool do you take me for you really think I planned it all out in advance my shooting him was a drunken mistake
Look I know that what I have done can never be undone all right
And I accept the consequences of my actions
I'm not trying to antagonize you I just want to cover my topic from every angle
I'm very sorry sir I really should have used more tact
Shall we walk the night air might do us some good
I'd like to purchase the bottle please
Just something to take the edge off of the night air
Oh Dr Gillen
I keep calling him but there's no answer
You know Richard did say he might be getting to see Rosemary soon
But this hardly seems the hour for a father-daughter reunion
Well when you finally do get a hold of him let him know how dangerous that young man can be
And tell him that I'm in route to his apartment
Did you ever look into Stephanie's background
Of course he grew up in an East German orphanage or something like that there's more to it than you
His crimes were to be expected
If you knew his past
To a child like Stefan
That orphanage was hell on Earth
He was a good boy
But that didn't save him from the horror that might have even made it worse
That orphanage devoured his mind
And then picked its teeth with his soul
The convention on the rights of children article 6 the right to life survival and development
Article 8 preservation of identity Article 19 protection from abuse to Stefan the
So many fairy tales Eva
There's no more fitting word for a place like that I can barely speak its name aloud
511 kinderheim steel sends a chill down my spine
So when will you be seeing your daughter
What did you say
How do you know about her
Before you answer the door you were on the phone with her
Isn't that so
When do you see her
Tomorrow maybe
Enough talk
What are you up to
I'm just doing research for my report
That's all no damn it
I'm on to you kid you're going to tell me what you've got planned for shoe Vogue
So who are you
Who are you
Tell me
You got drunk and shot that boy to death that's
Plenty of people did see you drinking in a bar that day
But that was after you'd already killed Stephen
It's kind of odd Mr Brown
I've researched this case exhaustively and try as I might I can't find a single person who saw you drinking before
You murdered that young man not a one Mr Brown this charade has gone on long enough
Will you really drunk when you pulled the trigger
You are quite sober
And you are calm you executed stephanieos and you knew exactly
Did I get it right
I'll wake the mind when it wants to forget
Maybe you didn't forget maybe you're lying is it a lie you tell everyone around you
To lie you tell yourself were you absolutely certain he committed those crimes certain
To put him down like a rabbit dog you're guilty of murder do you think
Bad Boy's blood is on your hands how are you going to look Rosemary in the eye tomorrow
Isn't her daddy a coward and a murderer hiding behind an empty bottle
Well Richard
How about a drink
Huh
Dr Gillen is that you
We're the police
We've come here regarding your patient Richard Brown
He's dead