Our brother has answered his call and gone home to the heavens
What lies here in this casket
Is nothing more than the physical shell
Richard Brown
We know his soul has been set free
It will go on and live forever
Let us Embrace his memory
Remembering that wherever his family will be
This loving father and hard-working husband
Will always be wearing Spirit too
After he had risen from the dead
The Lord said it doesn't make any sense
I just left so much unfinished
I'm shocked that no one from the police force is here
Richard was an excellent Det
Stupid not one of them came to pay their respects
It's ironic about
Drinking on duty cost him his career
And in the end the drunken fall is what custom is life
At least that's what the police report said
His voice was so alive when he
He was very excited about seeing his daughter but he never quite made
Spirit has planted in each of us
Immort
I ask myself for me did I really do everything I could to help poor Richard why of course you did Doctor
I just sat there listening to him Spilled Out his life to me and I told him he was well on his way to making a full recovery
I was wrong I feel like I never did enough to help him
10 min is the key if we could question
We might get the answers to help us solve all of this I do believe you're right
I think there's something we both know doctor
This wasn't an accident or a suicide as you said a few hours before his death Richard was on the
Phone happily talking to his daughter he wanted to see her
Doctor you did all that you could and you would help them Richard and quit drinking and was on the
Road to recovery
Whatever happened
It wasn't your fault
Listen to this
You weren't going to believe it
I'm serious
I found out my husband's having an affair
So I can fronted him and now he won't even speak to me he just washes the car cleans the garage and gives me
Silent treatment
I know he's avoiding me it's so obvious
I wait up for him to come to bed but he falls asleep in his chair besides being blonde and beautiful what she got that I
Doctor are you listening to me of course please
Continue
Now here's the part you were just not going to believe
I decided to confront this other woman so I go over to her place and what do you think she said for me
Homicide
No not a chance doc it was an unlucky accident Richard Brown was alone that evening when he went up
To the roof of building number 12 at Munich University
He polished off a bottle of whiskey and he got so drunk he fell off the roof end of story
The bottle
Did you ever thoroughly examined
Yes
Of course we did and we found Richard's prints on
If you don't mind
Could I see that bottle
Why yeah sure I suppose
But it's all in pieces
Oh Richard
I think there's something we both know doctor as you said a few hours before his death Richard was on the phone
Happily talking to his daughter he wanted to see her
Yeah
The guy in this picture was definitely in here that night
Was he alone
I'm not sure I really don't remember
So you remember that he was here but you don't recall if he was here with someone or alone
It was him he had a cup of coffee
Coffee yeah that's the reason I remember
Most folks ordered drinks with alcohol when they come here
So tell me
Is there a chance this young man was with him that night
I really couldn't tell
You're not even trying look I told you I don't know we got tons of customers who come into this place Mister but like I told
The cops I think the coffee guy did buy a bottle of
I got a receipt
Are you sure it was Richard who bought that bottle I told you I don't remember
All I know for sure is on that receipt there's a cheap bottle of whiskey
Wait
What did you just say
Like this one a fifth of blended whiskey
I can't believe it
Why didn't it hit me when I saw that bottle at the police station
Have you been drinking again
Well
Just a little
So what do you drink
Scotch
I only drink Scotch
So you're stinking up my entire office with the smell of cheap booze cheap booze
You kidding me
I've never drink cheap rocket if I'm going to drink it's real scotch
Or nothing else
Richard didn't buy that bottle of whiskey
Yohan it must have been
I'm sorry I ever get up period so I
I don't get off Facebook Spotify
What do you want why did you just try to push me under the tracks
What the I don't know what you talking about
Hey there old man you got a problem with my friend bad idea
Who told you to push me
You need to shut up
It's your age old man you should be at home playing with your grandkids
I still want an answer
Speak up why did you try to push me earlier
I don't know
Don't you die trying to pull it over on me somebody asked me to do it
It was some big guy
What do you mean a big guy
A guy I met in the subway paid me to push you off the platform and onto the tracks
He gave me money to do it
I bought you Scotch single malt
The really good stuff you liked
You deserve it my friend
It's okay
You can have a drink now
You Can Count On Me Richard as God is my witness
I identify the guy who did this
I swear it
Island cover your hands true identity
So listen to this doctor I finally told my husband what I think
I said that his cheating on me is a disease that's festering inside him
Then I told that ape that he's the one who should be sitting here and counseling not me
Did you hear what I said
Why yes
I did
Go ahead
Well then tell me
Is my husband keeps this up I feel like my depression is only going to get worse isn't it
Well no
I don't believe you really clinically depressed at all
Honestly I'm more concerned about your husband's actions than I am with your mental state we must find out why he's giving you
Silent treatment doesn't know which end is up
Please doctor I beg of you
Please make some time to see my husband of course I will
I have a slot open the day after tomorrow at 5:00 in the afternoon
All right thank you I'll tell him tonight
Make sure you give that cheating jerk a good talking to you Doctor don't hold back you got that
That was the last of your appointment for today
Good thank you very much mer
See you tomorrow then
All right then good night
Oh and there's one more thing yesterday you forgot to lock the stairwell door to our office again
Wait I did it again I'm sorry I almost forgot today too I can't believe it have a nice evening
Hello
Dr Gillen
It's Dr Reich
I saw today's paper
Why yes I saw your newspaper at in there
Let's talk about our memories of cheating
Rudy
So you really think of Dr 10 Masis this message in the paper that he will try to get in touch with us
Contact me
I ordered it so it would be something that only he and I
I see
Now
Please don't make any moves until we hear from
Understood
But there's still one related matter that I need to investigate
What's that
This prostitute who pretended to be Margo Langer just might have answers
I'm following up on something Richard said that prostitute told me that went far and the boy who killed himself
Went to see her he had a young man accompanying him
He was a young beautiful guy with blonde hair
Whatever
Please be careful
Oh I will
If I want to get to the bottom of this I'll have to be very cautious
But Richard's memory deserves no less
Well
I'll call you later
Oh no
So a mer
Today you forget to shut the window
Magalangor hunt never heard of her
Well I understand she goes by the name of Sophie or something like that
Oh yeah so you want that fat old hat
Is that what floats your boat cramps no wait it's not like that
Fine make a ride to blocks down the brick building second floor thank you young lady but I know she's
He's not there right now I haven't seen her around in about a week
She probably went to some place that's nicer
And where might that be who the hell knows what makes that fat old hat so popular with all you guys
My guess is she's with this really rich guy he used to be a regular customer
Hey what do you say you give me a child man you must have money and I'm sure I'm more fun than her
Do you know where she went
How would I know
Maybe she went off somewhere with that new customer of
So she has a new client hey
She should know better at her age than to fall for a guy like him he was a large one
So he was a big man
Oh yeah and I heard he was pretty big downstairs too
Doctor excuse me do you remember me asking you if it would be all right for me to leave early today
Yes I remember that
You said you needed to leave at 5
That'll be fine
The only appointment I have left today is Mrs hess's husband
Are you going on a date tomorrow
Please make sure you lock all the doors
I need to find that prostitute called Sophie who was pretending to be Margo Langer
And show her this photo
If I can get her to confirm that this Johan was actually with foreign I'll have someone who can testify to that fact
Which would bring me closer to getting to the bottom of this mess
Yes
Yeah my wife booked a session for me
I buzzed the door please come in
I might have better luck tonight if I go down there and look for Sophia again it's worth a shot
Good evening Dr Reich
Mr Hess welcome
What's
Nice to meet you
Please sit down
Hi
This is my first time in counseling so well there's nothing to be nervous about
All you need to do is relax we're here to talk about whatever you want
You can rest assured that our conversation will be completely confidential what we talk about stays right here
You won't tell my wife
Of course not
How have you been feeling lately
And what is it you worry about
My worries
Yes yours
Well my wife
She found out about my affair
And your feeling
I feel like I'm a stranger in my own home
I just washed the car and clean up the garage
That's all I do
Everyday
Does doing things around the house make you feel better
Not really
And it seems like I hardly ever talk to my wife
If any more
Do you want to talk to her but can't find a way to
Well
I don't know about that
Well what about the mistress
You know the woman you had an affair with have you two
I guess so I killed her
I mean I had a dream where I killed
So how often would you say you have those kinds of dreams
Oh not
Just
I really don't have many dreams
Guess I did it cuz I was lonely
Is that the reason you chose to have an affair
No
It happened after I met him
Met who
I'm at this really beautiful young man
With blonde hair
Before he showed up I felt like I was living
Underwater no matter how many people I killed even after the wall fell it was as if I was in
Dream after that everything was a lot
More real I didn't feel like I was all alone anymore
Would you like some
Hot tea perhaps
No thank
I'm fine
Well I could use some I'm feeling a bit thirsty
You can just wait here
My secretary is already gone for the day
She has a date
She already knows how to brew tea
It's too bad she's not here to make it for us
Hey do
What is it
I figure your job's going to be pretty tough
I mean there's a lot of pressure
People telling you all about their dreams and secrets incl
Floating ones that you probably don't want to know about you know ones that could get you into trouble
Like mine I mean now you have to walk around knowing I'm a hitman
So anyhow
If you want to make amends towards your wife
You you need to start talking with her
I hope you forgot to lock that damn door Meredith
Wait wait aren't you get out of here
Doctor camera I've been watching over you talk to right fine you're still in
Danger you need to get out of here now run