Hey
Oh hi lot
Do you have a minute
Not really I'm running late
But what's up
Maybe we could go and have a cup of coffee
I thought you might want to talk about how things are going with you and your father I mean you were so worried before
Not now I'm fine everything's good
Yeah but I'm off sorry little but I've got to get home my father has a business meeting and I have to take him to
To it see you later
I was thinking maybe we could go
Please finish up the library will be closing shortly
We're closing now
She's come back here again
I've been a beautiful girl like that doesn't have to worry about getting someone to take her to a dance
Man it's so unfair
What is it about her
Come on I'm closing up now
Yes ma'am
I've seen her
Can't remember where
A dance
Yeah
I guess that's what it's called
Normally I wouldn't be interested in that type of thing
But a friend insisted that I buy some tickets
I'm afraid I'm not going to be able to make it sorry
I have to go with my father to an official state banquet
It's kind of an important political event
I'm sure you won't have a problem finding someone to take it to the dance
See you later though
No big deal I didn't really want to go anyway
You seem familiar
Hey wait
It looks like you're doing research on Margo Langer
Okay I'm doing research on her too I mean we could sure notes
Please don't erase anything
I'm putting together data for a paper
I'm not too Frank I'm a cultural anthropology major
And what about you
Well you've collected a mountain of information Nina
This page is about the accountant murder
I also have a newspaper article on the voice of God case
You've done amazing research
I was thinking mine was impressive but you have me beat for sure
Well I've been researching all the unsolved murders in Bavaria over the last 4 years but at the moment I need more
More information on the former prostitute Margo Langer
Do you think you could help fill in the blanks gee I've told you pretty much all I know
The child born to Margo Langer in the very wealthy hanshuval spent years in foster care but was just recently
Recognize by his father and accepted as his rightful heir
Maybe he's the one responsible for the awful events surrounding Mr schumalt
It's not possible
I'm 100% sure of it
You really obsessed with this I mean considering that the research is just for a paper that you have to write for
For your class
You really think so this isn't about some paper is it
To be perfectly honest with you I'm looking for someone
Hey can I ask you something
In your whole life if you ever had to worry about anything
I've been wondering
Do beautiful girls like you always get everything they want without lifting a finger does it fall in your lap
What are you trying to imply
You can probably get any guy you want and never have to spend a minute worrying about it
It's fine okay I'm sure you don't have worries like me just forget it all right
Oh man
Life just seems to be so unfair
Listen
Come with me to the dance tonight it'll be a lot of fun
Normally I wouldn't come to these type of things you know come on let's give it a chance
These guys will talk to me as long as they say I'm with you everyone's looking at
Hey Google
I'm Constantine the president of the
Supernatural phenomenon Club
How you doing out give me a break who do you think you are trying to hit on
Nina how about the two of us hang out
How to get it tonight you know who me he's made a mistake no be happy about it
Well I better be going now
I'm in a little bit stay with me Nina please
God dang it
What kind of depressing I don't think we're fitting in
Really oh yeah really
All those guys were talking to you but one by one you push them away
Come on you're way too picky Nina I wasn't consciously trying to be rude
I guess it's just that
I'm out of practice huh these guys all hang out together they used to joking around
And having fun
But for me it's been a long time
Nina
It sounds like
And you're pretty old fashioned despite the way you look
Despite the way I look and what exactly is that supposed to mean lota
Hey guess who's back
Want to dance with me
Come on babe what do you say leave me alone don't be like
Like that just one little bit yeah
Hey you
No it's not like I'm asking because I dig you or anything
You're a fine one to talk buddy you're just playing rude come on one stupid little dance let's get it over
If you don't dance with me then I won't get paid
Paid to dance with me yeah but I'm not supposed to say anything
It's just between calling me he must have thought you wouldn't be able to find anyone who would want to dance with you
Carl did this
But whatever I'll dance with you so what do you say let's hit the dance floor it Brown is not to step on your toes
Let me go come on sweetie
I'm really sorry I won't ask anymore I promise
Let me go come on please
We're done
I must be crazy
I really liked Carl
I even helped him get reunited with his father
I liked him so much
Thought he liked me
Whatever since Mr shuvald acknowledged him as his true son
He has no time for me he's busy with his father
I feel a lot that it hurts so much
I never thought that getting rejected whatever feel like this
Right now the world is full of pain
But everything will be all right
I know it
A bad things can't keep happening forever
We have to do our part to stop them
I have to be on
On my way now so wait tell me where I can reach you Nina
Oh sorry Lota but I'm still trying to get my living arrangements figured out
Promise me you'll give me a call you know when you get settled in
Sure
I enjoyed spending the day with you I really hope you find the person you've been looking for
I know what it is
About Nina
Why I thought I'd seen her somewhere before she looks just like Johan
If This Were a regular gun you get high marks for skill
But in this case it's the Precision of the rifle rather than your ability doctor
This weapon might not have tested well enough to be designated the official sniper rifle of the German Army but it
And hit the center of a 5 cm Target from 300 M away
Even if you're an amateur
I don't know what you're planning to shoot but I'm going to give you a couple of pointers
First the closer you get to your target obviously the better accuracy you'll have
And of course you'll need to find a place where you can get off a clear shot
It comes with 4.338 Lotto magnum bullets
But you won't have time to re-aim and fire off all four of
Really one shots the most you're going to get
You come here every week
Are you an avid bird watcher
Oh yeah
I don't know why but Thursday seems to be the most popular day of the week for visitors like that
Man with his two young companions over there
And
I suspect you like the Solitude of this Forest
I'm enjoying it
And yourself it's complicated
Well actually
I'm making amends with this place
And I've been doing so for over 60 years
I haven't seen him before
From the looks of it
He didn't even take one bite of my special dish that is such a shame
Are you ready for a fabulous fries it's
We've been dreaming about going camping and look for years
You'll be able to take them camping every weekend and stop
Now get ready for your first question
Are you planning to sit here and stare at your food again you came in and did that about a week ago
I make it my business to remember my customers
If you don't have any appetite at least try some soup before you leave
It's on the house
Come on you better eat thank you for your concern
I'll
Clear shot here I've got to take him out in this Forest
Thank goodness
I never thought I'd dripping full I know every inch of this Forest I've walked here for so many years
Well I must be getting old
You may not have an actual fracture
I've wrapped it up as a precaution
But you should get an x-ray at the hospital too
I didn't Peg you as a doctor
When I first saw you I thought you were a bird watcher or maybe a hunter but that doesn't seem to be the case
That's really amazing
What are you talking about
All the birds huh
They're Gathering Together overhead
A long time ago
Oh the wild birds would flock together when a young boy appeared
He would extend his arm like this
And the birds would come to him
As a young boy growing up he'd spend his free time in the forest with the
But then things changed and Hitler's era came along
The boy was now a young man enjoying the police force
He was convinced at the National Socialist German Workers Party would turn his bankrupt country into
Ideal place
Then out of the blue this young man was given an order
A vicious criminal had escaped into this very same Forest
And because he knew these words so well he was commanded to go out and find him
Shoot the violent Criminal on site they told him the Young
Face the criminal through the forest that he knew like the back of his hand he kept on and on until finally
He was he had him cornered with his hands up then he realized that the vicious criminal was actually
Just an ordinary man a foreigner it didn't matter the young man felt he
Had no choice but to obey without question so he carried out his order
Since that day the birds never came to rest on his arm again
For 60 long years now with this man of the forest has been trying to make amend
I'm sorry I'm so sorry
Apologize though he may the birds refuse to ever come near him
That's amazing
It'll be okay now little bird it's your home we respect it
Never again will blood be shed in this Forest is
Right