Domo you're cooperation is greatly appreci
Thank you
It's a pleasure doing business with you
Perhaps the next time we meet it should be over a round of golf what do you say to that all right but only if you promise to go
No easy honest of course I'm looking forward to
Oh Domo
Dom
Double this double that
It's a fairly comprehensible culture
Domo domo apologies for the wait
My meeting ran a little longer than expected
The name is he why of the carterfuku corporation Munich branch
Inspector lunge of the bka
Pleased to meet you
Domo
A demo and a bow
That was unexpected
Coffee
Oh and a refill for him too
My apologies I know you were expecting to meet with Yamamoto today
There was an emergency in the Czech Republic but he's expected back in town sometime tomorrow
You seem rather busy
Oh yes I mean you've heard
Mr schewald's corporate Dynasty ever since he came out of seclusion and resumed his financial activities
All of his affiliate companies and related businesses throughout Germany have been very active
The whole Japanese business Community is desperately vying for his attention
Why is he laughing
So Mr Yamamoto will not be able to meet with you today
But I can say that I knew Kenzo 10 my just as well as he did
So feel free to ask anything
But of course
I have to say inspector I'm shocked
He's still under investigation
Well
I'll just say that we haven't come to any conclusions
I was floored to hear 10 my name does a suspect in your investigation I couldn't have imagined such a thing you just
Said you felt shocked was it really that unexpected absolutely
Kenzo tenmark killer
Come on it's just crazy not in a million years what I have paid 10 months of killer
We had drinks a couple of times
I guess about 3 years ago
You really didn't seem like a bad guy
So he really didn't seem like a bad guy
You're saying you thought he was a good guy then a good guy
Let's see
I think reserved would be the word I'd used to describe tema
What you're saying then is that not being open is what makes him a good man
You're being social that's what I meant by not a bad guy
Japanese people don't normally wear these sorts of clothes
Japanese people are skillful with chopsticks
So now I will be Japanese
Domo
I'm Japanese
I am a Japanese man
I am 10
Hello
Yes
Fine
I called because I heard you were in
I had my baby
I thought you'd want to know
I see
That's good
I know a lot of things have been said between us
I want you to see your grandchild
Will you see
Of course I will
Would tomorrow be okay
Yes
As long as it's after 6:00
Where would you like to meet
Near Marion plots
Okay
All right
See you then
Dom
Hey
You're pretty good with those Chopsticks you know that
Is that so
Sure these days I see a lot of foreigners using Chopsticks better than native Japanese
So Dr Takahashi
As a former colleague of temas what would you say was your impression of him let's see
As I remember he wasn't a hard guy to like
Though he was occasionally more than a bit indecisive still
Go on
With a scalpel in his hand he was a whole other person
People called him a genius brain surgeon and I can say that was no exaggeration
What about his parents
He never really talked about his parents much
But he said his father and older brother were doctors also
So I guess they put them on the physician's path whether he liked it or not
In fact
I think I remember him saying he hadn't been back to Japan since coming to Germany for medical school
Matter of fact his parents didn't come to Germany at all to support him when the Scandal broke
I don't think they made any public appeal for their son's innocence either I guess he and his family weren't all that
You know what I mean
Thanks for waiting
Sorry it's taking so long but we've just gotten word from Yamamoto
He's left Prague and he's back in Munich
But unfortunately he has a client who needs must be tended to immediately
He seems to be a busy man
If it's any consolation he did say he was going to join all of us at a bar after work a bar
That's right
Care to join us for a drink inspector
The fates of delivered you this opportunity
After all it's always good to make a few new contacts
No
Tonight I have to I guess he and his family weren't all that tight-knit you
You know what I mean
I am
Sounds great
I would be happy to join you tonight
Yeah tomorrow well done
Inspector Lungi how about a song yeah
No this next song is mine let's sing
All right
I am 10ma
I am 10 I don't fit into Japanese Society
I do not ask others for help I don't fit in anywhere
I have no home to return to I am
Alone
Domo domo I'm sorry I'm late guys
There you are Yamamoto
Inspector Lungi you know the one I told you about on the phone I'm Yamamoto of the Munich
Ranch of the kind of fuku
Domo so how did it go with Mr coached in the check Republic
He's a tough nut
Oh yeah that thing I was supposed to get
Done what thing you know that one thing that you vaults right hand man was asking us to get the blonde
Guy that
That's great news right now kissing up to him is the best way to close a deal with shoe volt so we got to get on that man's
Good side and stay there
I went poking through all the second hand book stores in Prague and I was finally able to find a copy
Wow so that's the picture book you wanted unfortunately it's kind of worn out and the cover is coming off a little
Restoration and it'll be beautiful
Excuse me
I think we can use a couple of beers over here hey Google
It's written in check
All right it's my turn again all right that's great
Hope you guys been practicing
So inspector what are you looking up in the dictionary
Translating check
Check huh
So does it have something to do with that investigation you've got going no
It's a personal project
I'm kind of surprised to see you're doing anything that's not related to your case it's from a picture book
I like the illustration
I just wanted to know what the passage said
Inspectors reading a picture book
That's something you don't see everyday
Look at me
The monster inside me has gotten this
I see
So Johan is pulling the strings on that billionaire
Dr Gillen you've been telling me all about this Johan person for a while now
You painted him as quite the monster haven't you
Monster
Yeah
I mean I've killed some people sure
But he's transformed himself into the sort of creature I could only dream of becoming
This Johann has become my idol
My hero
Really
Well there is one more question that I would like to ask of you if you don't mind knock yourself out if you were
What would be the next move that you made
Well that's
Obvious
The parents you know the lieberts
I think it would be time for them to die
Mr Liebert
Mr Hebert
What brought you to that conclusion
Because
I've gotten bored
Yes hello
You're a psychologist I'm sorry we don't understand
What can we do for you Dr reichvine I won't waste your time with a long winded explanation I just want to ask some
Questions about your adopted son Johan
Johan adopted
You must be mistaken
That boy is our child I gave birth to him that's enough Mrs Liebert I know for a fact that your real child
Child is buried in brunthal
There was a fire that burned down the town hall along with all the birth records the fire allowed you to apply for a new birth
Certificate as if your original child were still alive
What's this all about
Look I didn't come here to make threats I promise you
All I want to do is help if you let me
Please read this
It's a report about Johan
About Johan
Yes a friend compiled that information
I've met him
He came to the house selling insurance policies
That man was former detective Richard Brown
He's a detective
He was
He's dead now
Just read
The story actually starts a few years ago
When an East German government official escaped and sought Refuge here in West Germany in 1986
What's it about is he after money money
No Johan couldn't care less about money
Then why go after a billionaire like shoe hold in the first place
You know that thing you did as a kid what thing
When I was a kid I would find a line of ants
Yeah I'm not playing with them
Mess with her formation
My God I refuse to believe this it's all simply Dreadful
This story is ridiculous look I understand that you don't want to believe it the two
You lost your only son at a very early age I know your life moves on and you wait to be blessed with a new child
Until one day a boy nearly the same age as yours appears and to sweeten the pot the boy arrives with money
He provides you with the wonderful house to live in in a nice neighborhood with a beautiful garden
And he provides you with love I understand that both of you
If you want to believe in him however everything that's written in these documents is true so
Who is Johan really I need you to tell me about Johan
You hun
A good boy
Yes he's just a very nice boy
And he's very smart a clever boy
You see
Johann is our reason for being
And is that all
You've been acting as his parents for years
And that's all you have to say about him
It's obvious neither of you knows the first thing about him
I've come here because I need your help
My friend Richard has already died at his hands
Right now
As we speak a man named Tenma is
He's moving towards something drastic that can't be undone
Please you have to help me
No
More importantly
You'll end up
Like all the other couples mentioned in this report
They were all previous foster parents of johann's just like you
Murdered every one of them
You have to leave now
If you stay you'll die
Oh the apple tree
Such small fruit but I think next year's apples will be much healthier
That will be delightful yes so very delightful
He's going to be killed by a Japanese guy soon
Is that what Johann is telling those kids
Correct what do you think
What's it mean
Well he's not thinking about suicide that's for sure
Okay
But what does it mean
Man who really knows what goes on in a brilliant mind like that
Although
I can at least say this much
If nuclear war broke out in the world burned to Ash
He'd still be standing
He's basically telling us that there's nothing we can do
And he's right everything we've done so far is let us absolutely nowhere
My God we weren't even able to save poor Richard
Look we can't just throw in the towel but we still haven't been able to track down Dr Tenma
Face it we couldn't stop him from trying to kill Yohan even if we wanted to it's been in vain Dr
Find please we need to try and remain calm here
Yeah you're right
He talked about breaking up the line of ants
Even ant
Possessed soul
Doctor where are you going at this point we've got nothing to lose
Do we it's time to tell the old man our story
I'm going to have a little talk with shuvault what
Additional 50 chairs so many people this list just keeps growing and growing you mean all of this is
Just for Mr schewald's book donation ceremony yeah a lot of VIPs have been added it's turning into a pretty big
Thing I guess everything shootout does is bound to turn into an event
The library will be closing shortly again the library
Excuse me
I'm sorry
Could you get that book down for me
That check dictionary up on the top I can't reach it
Oh okay
Is this
Yes
I'm sorry
Thanks a lot
Actually I'm borrowing a check picture book
I'm trying to translate it
I see
Would you believe it
My friend collapsed right here out of nowhere while looking at this book
I thought that
Maybe there was something in the book that could have triggered that response
So your friend
He's all right now he's fine
Thanks again
Sure
Once upon a time in a land far away
They're left a nameless monster
He was dying to have a name so the monster
So the monster made up his mind to set out on a journey to look for one
We're close enough hun
I will be closed tomorrow for the ceremony