I'm supposed to shoot shoebox
So how come there's a fire
Amazing
Amazing Johan amazing
Come and watch the it's pretty
Everyone is running and falling over each
Without a thought for anyone but themselves
Can you sense it in your the fear
Whether or not he is successful in his first kill
That's what it all comes down to
Remember
Either he's got what it takes or he doesn't
So have you ever trained with a gun before
No
I guess that means that you're self taught
Actually
I've never shot a gun before
What you mean not even once
Right
Remember two shots
Whenever you fire your gun you always pull the trigger twice
Better is your chances of taking out your objective if you can do that then you're as good as dead
It's all over
I have to shoot
You won't be able to do it
I have to shoot you
I'm sure you can't
I have to kill you you're a doctor of Medicine
And you've dedicated your career to saving life
Taking life is my job
And I do it well
Give it up you can't do it
Remember two shots
I can do this
More shaking Yohan
Tim the
No I have got to get him now
Not getting away I won't let do it
Listen do not panic
The security guard so that we can it's no good sir
All the doors have been locked from the outside that can't be whatever
Can you tell me just where you plan on taking Mr shoovald in this Sea of Fire
The book stop running
So many of them alight the Flames quickly consuming everything they touch
Describe all of this with such damn calmness flames of Chaos
You're getting quite a thrill out of sharing this hellish scene with me aren't you it's
Now you always sounded when you read to me and now you're going to take my place
Giving up on something that's even more compelling is popped into my head
You're Not Afraid even now Mr Cheval answer
This where did you come from who are you or what
Can you see
I know you can barely see anything but when I'm this close to you
What can you see what
See you when you look into my eyes
I was born in a town that was straight out of a fair
Many people died there
And when I walked away
I have hands with my other self
To me it seemed like we were the only two people in the world
Neither one of us possessed a real name
Hey lady
Wait it's you
Peter
Do you know this young lady have you seen her somewhere before
Burning
I forgot some papers I need you to go retrieve them for me
Go to the mansion and get
They're on the desk in the study
These
It's my mom
It's like detective services
Investigative report
About Margo Langer
Her death
Margo
Whose real name was helenka novakova
Was born in Prague to czechoslovak
On August 12th
In the spring of 197
When she was
15 years old
She somehow illegally gained entrance into former West Germany
4 years after entering Germany
Margo became a high-class call girl in mun
Clientele consisting mainly of politicians and influential
Businessman
Even though her name was Secret in high SOC
He became famous
Our client in this investigation
Hanske York
Was one of her more generous and steady
Her father
Even after it all you were still trying to find out more about mother
At age 22 she bore Mr shoeval to son
That male child was given the name
Of Carl
Carl
Are you listening to me
This is important
Take this money and ride the train on track number five
What about you Mom
Honey I already told you I can't go with you
I don't want to go alone mom you have no choice if you stay with me they'll cut you off to some orphanage
Around here people will mock you with the son of a w****
Now go on
What about my dad
Why doesn't he help us doesn't he love me
Why do you abandon us
Don't hate him if he turns you away
Because Mommy doesn't hate him even now
Her son Carl was moved around to many different sets of foster parents
The young man went through a lot
But eventually ended up in a loving family
He felt as if he was always
Always alone in the world
Of course it wouldn't say that in the report
Margo Langer remained a top high class prostitute
But retired in 1992
Furthermore
There are rumors that Langer was involved in an affair with
The president of an underground Bank just
Before her retirement
This information has not been confirmed
In investigating Margo's alleged affair
A lot of information was learned about this underground Banks operation
This Bank laundered money for Germany's Black Market companies for 5 years starting in 1991
Money laundering is the term used for an organization in the business of taking illegal funds and turning them into legal
Currency
After her retirement from prostitution
Margo Langer left mun
Nick and lived in Offenbach
This is
Picture of the apartment building that she lived in at that time
She shared her third floor apartment with a young man about age 18
The nature of their relationship is unknown
Margo Langer lived in offen
For nearly 4 years until on November 2
1996 she was found dead on high
According to police files
Her death was the work of a phantom kill
The culprit was never found
Mother
Margo Langer sent a letter to a close friend 3 months before her untimely death
You're able to obtain the letter and have attached a copy to this report
Oh my God
I have finally retired from working
And living a very peaceful life
In this
I'm filled with thoughts of my lost son
I also think about my best friend from Prague
We try to escape from Czechoslovakia together
But she was captured at the border and taken back to Prague
Later
I heard she gave birth
The twins
And was very happy
Recently
I met a young man who was about the same age as my son
He looks exactly like my friend in PR
When I'm with him
I feel like I'm talking to my
Own son
I'm sure my boy has become a fine young man
Just like
He must have grown up to live a happy life
That's what I hope for
I'm all right now Mom
I know that I'll never feel alone again
I know dad sent me here because he wanted me to read this
Now I get it finally I understand what she meant
I understand completely
It's all right
Stand
Damn it every one of these doors has been locked tight Peter did you find a phone to call the fire department yet
Yes sir I called them how could this have happened what the hell's going on in there
Out of the way
Everyone move
So stupid question mark
Two shots left
Crazy
How
Hold on what are you doing
Nina Jones
Don't do it
Don't