We've just confirmed at least five are dead and 34 injured due to a fire that broke out here
At the University of Munich's Friedrich Emanuel Campus Library
Earlier we had a chance to talk to some of the survivors let's take a look
Suddenly found myself surrounded by fire everywhere the smoke was so thick in the air I can hard
I thought I would die
Then somebody rushed in and saved us yeah he was this young Asian man
Is it all right
I saw him shoot the hinges off the door to get it open but
After that
If it went for him
So many of us would have died
The police have confirmed that the fire was started with a mixed kerosene gasoline accelerant
The police have also promised to bring the arsonist to justice as swiftly as possible
It's completely destroyed
So much for this so-called Legacy of human wisdom ashes to ashes I guess
Were there any fingerprints on the sniper rifle we found I don't think we're going to be able to pull any reasonable
Prince on the other hand the weapon is a Mauser sr-93 just like the one purchased by that Japanese
Man who we believe to be Dr tema
I'm telling you it's going to be difficult to find any trace of the perpetrator a fire this hot really cleans the crime scene there's no
No such thing as a clean crime scene here's a cufflink
Send it to the lab someone was here and nobody can do anything without
Some sort of trace of themselves if there were such a person he could hardly be
Considered human but let's suppose someone was here and that we still couldn't find any trace of them who does that
That only a demon however since no such thing exist
Exist there must be someone real to arrest
Engine meeting with shoe volt for me but he still held up in the Intensive Care Unit admittedly his Burns aren't really
Really that severe but because of his Advanced stage the doctors are refusing to allow him any visitors let's go
You're being unreasonable sir he's not ready for visitors yet he's conscious isn't he
I only need a few minutes of his time he needs
Absolute quiet
Who's the young man
Oh him that's Mr Shoe Volt's son
I'm sorry such a terrible thing happened to your father
My name is Lungi I'm with a bka
I know I've already talked to the police about this but there's someone I really need to find
Wait who is he the person in that photograph is the man who tried to assassinate your father
Are you sure you don't recognize him I've never seen him before
But maybe Johan would have
Johan that's what I've been trying to tell everybody his name is Johan Liebert and I need you to find him
Johan Libra today
The last time I saw Johan he was going to attend the ceremony at the library with my father
But I've searched everywhere and I can't find him
Yes I understand
I'll call for a search immediately
This is the room Johan Liebert was renting
Like I said before he moved out of here two weeks ago
We checked at the
High school at Friedrich Emanuel but his name didn't show up at the registrar is he really wasn't a student didn't you say his parents live
Lifting off in Bach what about them yeah that parent-angle turned out to be another dead end it seems they never really
They talk to any of their neighbors I guess there's nothing left to do except dust for Prince huh we're probably not
Going to find anything I have no data to in
Never before I've never
Never seen a room so devoid of any human presence yeah I am
I am Johann Liebert who am I
I was here but I don't exist
Am I a demon
I'm just glad your injuries weren't that bad Nina
I'm sorry to make you worry loud
Thank you
Well of course I was going to worry about you
I mean they kept pulling survivors out of the library and you were still nowhere to be found
I didn't know what had happened to you
Still it's a miracle you made it out of the library all on your own with those injuries
Even the firefighters were shocked
That's because someone saved me
Somebody saved you
Nina you were the last person that made it out of the building
A Japanese man
Huh
Do you know if there was a Japanese doctor among any of the survivors
There were some Japanese people
But all of them were just businessmen
That is impossible
Inside the Library I was trapped under a curtain when he found me
Nina
Nina Nina
I'm sure that he was real
I know he was
According to Witnesses
Just before the fire started
You told everyone attending the ceremony to evacuate
What would cause you to do something like that
You knew something was about to happen
Was that it
Mr schewald
Why don't we call it a day do you know the man in this photograph
Can you see the man in the photograph clearly sir
This is the man who we believe tried to assassinate you
We have witnesses placing him at the library
But here's what doesn't make sense to me
All of our Witnesses claim to have seen this man rescuing people from the fire
Look that's enough
Please just let him rest
Don't forget to contact me if you should remember anything else
Just one more thing
Do you know where your secretary Johan Liebert has disappeared to
Please
Just leave already
Looks like he's gone completely senile well I guess it can't be helped I mean
When you see something that terrifying at his age you know so ends the reign of the vampire of Bavaria
Once great emperor of the business world no he understood every word I
Oh let's question the other Witnesses shall we do you have the list of victims
Oh yeah but what's this all about we have testimon
People from the fire maybe it's just like that multiple
Personality theory
Nina Fortner
What about Nina Fortner
If you're looking for Nina Fortner she checked out of the hospital this morning
And unfortunately the address we have for in the police register is fictitious how about the hospitals
Yes sir
I'll look it up right now
Nina Fortner
There was a Nina Fortner whose parents were killed in Heidelberg
Her current whereabouts are unknown
Thank you for sharing such a painful story with me
You know Nina
It matches up perfectly with another story from 10 years ago told to me by Dr Tenma
Yes
And that story started him down to path that led him here
And from here he set off on his journey
To kill Johan
Nina
That day
I went to the library because I thought the timer was going to carry out his assassination attempt
But then with that fire
I don't even know for sure if Timo was there
Let alone Johan
Please Nina
Let go of any thoughts of chasing down Johann
He's not someone you can handle yourself
Look I know the police don't seem very helpful
But we have to try and lay low and take our time to fight this I promise the truth will be revealed in time
It's okay
We're all here for you
You must be tired
Please feel free to stay here as long as you like
He was there
I mean
I saw him that day
Tema was there in the library
You've got to eat something
I know dear
Thank you it's called a kaiser roll
It has roasted ham and gouda cheese on it
10 more really likes them
That's very kind of you
Really nothing picks me up like something delicious
10 more always used to say that too
I want to see him
I want to see Tema again yeah
The weather is finally starting to look nice again
Father when you're feeling better why don't we take a vacation together
Maybe the two of us could tour Asia
I think A Change of Atmosphere would be nice
Why don't you just rest a bit longer
I know you've been through more than enough recently
Bridge
There
Father what is it
Are you trying to tell me something
The three frogs
Three frogs
In his eyes
I saw hell
Right there in his eyes
Hell
In the eyes of a living human being
Yes
I need you to deliver a message to a certain man I yes
There's a man
A man waiting interesting
Interesting what do you want me to say when I find him I want you to tell him that I
Yes
And the man in Dresden he'll know what you're talking about right so should I leave
Leave now father
I understand
I'll leave immediately
I know
I know that your mother hated me in the ad
You're wrong I promise she never hated you
When you return from Dres
Can you promise that you will come back and stay with me
Yes
I'm afraid
I see
Afraid of what
I don't know
But I'm afraid try and stay calm
We need you to remember
Just go slow
Like a town from a fairy tale
A fairy tale Village
Where was it
The feelings that you had when you were looking at this picture book
Just
Tell me whatever pops into your head
Dr Gillen careful just a little bit more
There were three
Two or three frogs
There were three frogs three frogs
What are you talking about
What
Is there a picture of three frogs in the children's book that made Johann faint
I've never seen a single frog anywhere then where did you see them
It's all right
Why don't we stop here for now
Okay
I'm going on record saying it was a mistake to trust that inspect
Longe from the bka
Yes I think it's time for us to rethink our strategies
The next time we take anything to the authorities will talk to his superiors
And that's only after we've taken our time together irrefutable evidence to support our claim agreed
You think we should take our time
How much time as of now the profile we built for Johan is vague and unimpressive at best
Johan with you about secretary
It's reasonable to think she was might have some information
But he's not taking visitors at the moment
How about his son Carl he's been gone for the past couple of days now and I can't get a hold of him
It's nothing concrete
But I've heard some of the witnesses say
That an anonymous Asian man was seen rescuing people from the library fire
But if they find him his fingerprints on the sniper rifle then all those witness reports won't mean anything they'll just assume
He's guilty why wouldn't they it all will have been for not how long do we have to wait
We don't have any time by the time the truth is revealed in the police finally make a move by that time
Nina
I'm so sorry
Nina I understand how you feel about this I told you before I lost one of my closest and Dearest
It's Richard to this case
He had such a bright future ahead of him
But Johan got his future short
I am not giving up on this I never will
No let's eat
Three frogs
Like a town from a fairy tale
With
I remember
Cheater I
I'm going to
What are you saying dear you can't come with me
You need to stay right here all right and please tell doctor right fine that I said thank you for everything he's done for me
Take care
I want
I want to see Tim
The third day was a bus too waiting the Town Square he says he's got to be kidding this
Place is just too big
Sorry Father it doesn't seem like I'll be meeting up with the
Can you talked about after all
Your car right wait it's you
The man who was attempting to assassinate your father
Is that what the police told you yeah well at least it doesn't look like they have anybody
Telling you
For 3 days I've been watching you from that building
All right you can give me the message now
Try and hold on we're almost out of here just run
You have to go the police are on their way but I can't just interested
The Public Square By The Station my son Carl will bring you a message
Give me the message
Here it is
Should talk bridge and the three frogs my father said something else also
If the monster that you're chasing
Happens to have a twin
The mother of those same twins
Is still alive and Brock