Just run you have to go the police are on
The Public Square by the station
There
Give me the message
Here it is
Bridge
And the three frogs my father said something else also
If the monster that you're chasing
Happens to have a twin
The mother of those same twins
Is still alive and Brock
So Mr Grimmer have any luck
Did you find some of the information you were looking for
What's your after won't be easy to locate
Record keeping changed when the East and West United
Data from before then it's hard to find
My thank you for this opportunity principal
Frankly I'm surprised you have even this much left
Most
Far less
And of course you're quite correct
When the Berlin Wall fell
Almost all of the data involving East Germany's unsavory practices disappeared forever
You know
I feel quite sure that the children in the orphanages of the oldies Germany were victims of physical and mental abuse
But of course the real challenge here is actually finding any written records to prove my thoughts are true
You're thinking sounds right
You know most of East Germany's orphanages were being managed under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
But a much bigger problem was created when the authorities classified a child's parents as criminal offenders political prisoners
There's spies or even illegal immigrants
In the midst of all of the orphanages that took care of these children there was one special orphanage run by the notorious internal
Affairs Ministry
Apparently there were many instances of abuse and these inhumane personality Corrections took place
At one particular orphanage
Anyhow that's what I want to find out
And as much detail as possible
I want to know every last little thing that happened there
I'm leaving no stone unturned
My that's a tedious task huh
I'd like to help but there's not much information to share
Most of those involved have passed away kept silent or their leading new lives
I'm sure you're right
Even Mr schner who's now an instructor here won't speak with me wait did you say Mr schner
Yes he was a teacher at East Germany's 62 kinderheim under the old regime
I requested interview I'm about his past but
You refused my request
Listen
There's a real possibility Mr terrorized children while he worked in East Germany so I'd be a little more cautious around him
If I were you
Oh would it be all right if I photocopied some of the information in these books sure that would be just fine
Mr Grimmer if I may you are a newspaper journalist from West Germany isn't that correct
No I'm from this side
Well I work as a reporter for a newspaper in leip
Well
I never expected a human rights Advocate like you to be from the Eastern BL
It's true
During that time I used to travel all over the world as a special overseas news correspond
Yeah I went everywhere on missions for the government
Do you understand
I used to be a spy
Here we go
Goodness you're back looks awfully heavy
Well it's packed with all the data I've collected traveling around East Germany
I can't wait to read up on your findings
So where are you heading to Next oh to the Czech Republic
On to PR
Thank you for all your help principal
I heard you getting treated pretty badly by those boys
And they ended up taking your shoes away didn't they
You know crying won't help
Hey you know what it's been proven that people can live without shoes
After all every last one of us was born barefoot
But I must say
Anyone who bullies other people by stealing their shoes
They're the worst
Anyhow now you have shoes again so there's no need to cry anymore
Take care
I'm guessing they're a little big for you am I right
Excuse me sir
Do you have a second sir of course what is it
I'm kind of in a fix
You see I have a big problem
My briefcase that had my passport and it was stolen just a while ago
Your passport was stolen not really is a big problem
I turned around and it was gone I'm on my way to see my younger sister who lives in Vienna
Only yesterday I got a phone call saying that she suddenly collapsed
She collapsed
You need to find a way to get there as soon as possible
Where are the police maybe they can help you I already talked to them
The bigger problem is my poor sister doesn't have any money for a doctor
Oh no that's got to be the worst news yet
And the top things off my stolen briefcase had my wallet in it too
No
I know I can't go but if I could at least find a way to water some money to my sister she could get some medical attention but now
Now it's looking like I can't even do that so just how much do you need oh no no no you don't need to help out
Honestly I don't need that much money really
All I need is to pull together a small amount of cash just enough so she can see a doctor
Here I'm just sorry I don't have more to give you
Oh thank you sir don't question I swear that I'll pay you back very soon
Just write down the address where you want me to send the check
That's all right no need to repay me
Just see that your sister gets the help she needs okay
God bless you sir
Thank you so much I wish you and your sister all the best
Come on Daddy how could you hand over your money to that Hustler
He was lying and story was just a scam
A scam
That guy works as train station all the time looking for suckers like you I can't believe you got fooled
Play that Hustler
I really got fooled
Attention the express training frog will be departing
3:15 p.m.
Damn it
I didn't think it was going to make it for a sec
Thanks for your help you're welcome
Hey thanks again for earlier do you mind if I sit here no go ahead
So where are you headed
Oh man I'm headed for Prague
I'm guessing you're Japanese am I right
Konichiwa oh dumb you know I visited Japan a couple of times
Oh how long has it been since I was there last well it's been a couple of years I can tell you
That much the last time I was over there was a business trip but I went to Akihabara to purchase some wiretap equipment
Another high-tech gadgets oh yeah that reminds me this song it was really popular I'm sure you know
Oh talk about dorino
No no that's not right you keep tunnel soccer
Oh that's right that's how it goes tunnel
My son would have loved it if I
Brought back a plastic model toy for him so where's your son now oh he's gone
My son died
Departure passport check if you would present your pass
Oh sure I love course
Danke Schoen
Look there's the Elder River how's the trout fishing
Been on the Elba River this year anyway it hasn't been very good sir
Huh is that so cuz last year I caught a trout this big on that river that wouldn't happen this
This year Duncan sir
He's on to the fact that was a fake passport you just showed him
You need to get moving right now Dr Tema how is it that you know who I am that's not
What does matter here is that the Border Police have realized your passports are fake and I'm sure they're on their way
So you need to get out of here right now doctor Tenma
Move it you come on we need to get past you sorry about this guys
My duffel bag so big and overstuffed I guess I'm kind of stuck here I can't seem to move get out of the way right now
Believe me sir I am trying to get out of the way what's in that bag anyway some very valuable
Good I finally got loose
Do you know where that other man went to me there was an Asian man who was sitting with you in this comp
Yeah you're right well maybe he got hungry and went to the dining car movement
Passenger car too we have an Asian man using a fake passport who's running loose on his
What's wrong
You did very well back there
They're not chasing us
They're searching the other way
Since the train was stopped I figured I should get off
Oh I guess I forgot to introduce myself doctor
My name is Grimmer
I thought you might need some guidance doctor 10 minutes so if you'd like I could show you the way to the Border
I'm very well acquainted with this area
Actually I fished around here quite a few times it's mountainous terrain so the hike ain't easy but the view
Grimmer
Why did you help me anyway
Well you see I worked for a newspaper company in East Germany
But now I'm doing my own
Freelance journalist
I've read every article about you I could find and I have to admit I find you very interesting
Being falsely accused of crimes was a part of everyday life in East Germany
Political prisoners charged without Merit
Accused murderers who weren't really guilty
Seeing that happen all the time
You got to have a pretty good eye for spotting who was guilty and who was innocent
And I'd say you're innocent
Does that sound about right doctor ten
Listen do me a favor and stop calling me doctor
Huh
But doctor Tenma you're one of the world's most brilliant neurosurgeons aren't you proud of that
I am no longer a doctor
So
What do you think
The Magnificent view isn't it
And from here we can see anyone coming up the mountain after us
That said I think we've earned a well-deserved break for lunch
Would you care to join me for a sandwich
I also brought a rather nice red wine
Oh and some delicious cheese
Thank you for your offer
But I really need to keep on moving
It's hours until sunset
It'll be easier and safer trying to cross the border after Dark
Eating outside like this
It's just the best
It's such a treat to do this once in awhile isn't it Dr tema
Enjoying delicious food while taking in a wonderful View
It's moments like this that help me truly feel the pleasures of living
I must admit I have a profound respect for you doctors journalists like myself served entertain people
Hopefully my readers feel happier to be alive after reading my articles
But what you do
That's powerful you literally give people life
But I
Shot a man
I did it on purpose
It happened last month in mun
It's the first time I shot someone
I think he probably died
My hands were trembling so much I couldn't name
I think I'd really be able to do it
But after I shot him
My hand stopped Tre
And now
I know that I have to shoot another man
I have to stop a man that's pure evil
One thing is for certain
I'm not doctor
When I see the Elbow River I think of how I'd give anything to change the past
Yeah I would have made a difference so I could have shared the joy of fishing here with my son
What was he like your little boy
You can catch a trout this big in that River
My poor son died without me ever sharing the pleasures of the outdoors with him
What makes me the saddest is feeling that his life could have been saved
If a doctor like you had been there for him
I swear you can catch trout this big I'm not kidding around here
The other side of that mountain is the check border
Follow the force path pass there and you'll hit a road where you might be able to get a ride
As for me I'm heading back to the train station now
Thank you Mr Grimmer I never would have made it this far without you helping me
I truly wish you the best of luck
Dr
Say if we meet again let's plan for another great picnic all right
Hey doctor Tenma
Everyone in this world carries around their own sins
And they never go away
But that doesn't change the fact that we do what we must
How wonderful
I'd always heard this was a beautiful city this may be my first night in Prague but I'm already Enchanted it's like a village
Message from a fairy tale
Excuse me do you mind if I sit here
Search yourself I must say I'm completely
Captivated by this city
You're Mr pedrov Right you bought your Russian citizenship and now here you are
Living in Prague
I'd like to ask you some things about your past sir would you be willing to help me with some answers Mr
Pedro
Oh my mistake your real name is reinhard-beerman isn't it
There was this very special orphanage located in East Berlin right
It was more of a laboratory really we're experiments were conducted on children's personalities
It was called 511 kinderh
And you were the director there Mr bierma
You should know all about the abuse that went on there
After all sir you were the one running the place
Just what were you trying to achieve in those experiments
Back in East Berlin
511 kinderheim care to explain it to me