So Mr pedrov
Oh my mistake your real name is reinhard-beerman isn't it
There was this very special orphanage located in East Berlin right
It was an experimental lab where the staff did personality Corrections on the children that were house there
It was called 511 kinderheim
And you were the director there Mr bear
You should know all about the abuse that went on there
Just what were you trying to achieve in those experiments
Back in East Berlin
511 kinderheim
Care to explain it to me
Hey please wait a minute don't rush off Mr pedrov
You're unique
You're both a psychologist and a psychiatrist
You used to work for the Internal Affairs Ministry focusing on personality programming
The form of brainwashing
You see that's what got me thinking
Why would someone with your skills and behavioral modification have been appointed director of Amir orphanage
I mean certainly there were people more qualified in the field of child welfare
Right
Leave me alone
I don't know what you're talking about
Just go away
So where did you hide the records
You know the results of your experiments at 511 kinderheim
Now I've heard all the usual rumors that when the Berlin Wall was destroyed
A countless number of secret documents disappeared
And there's a theory that they were sent to the Soviet Union by train via Romania
While on Route there was a revolution in Romania that Chao sheshko government fell
And supposedly the German documents were lost
But I have a feeling that the data concerning 511 kinderheim was not among those lost papers
Do you know why I think that
Because you sir are a true academic
You're devoted to research
Data and statistics are far more important to use scholarly types than life itself
You wouldn't let go of something that important would you
I'd sure like to see that data
Must be interesting
There's nothing
What were you hoping to accomplish there
At your lab at 511 kinderheim
Go away your experiments with a really successful
It must have given you so much pleasure to use children as human guinea pigs
Your experiment
Failed didn't it
In 1985
511 kinderheim burned to the ground
And according to the rumors surrounding that tragedy
Children of the orphanage killed each other
At the time
I was no longer director of that facility
The incident does not involve me at all
I see
Lucky you you were able to escape death
Now the director right after you wasn't so lucky he was the first one killed in the Rampage
That catastrophe never would have occurred if I had still been there
I assure you my experiment was a success
Boho so now it seems you're admitting to it
You're telling me the experiment went well so I shouldn't need proof
Right
Huh
You know what I think
Even if many of the records went up and smoke during that fire in 1985 not everything did
The experimental data from your time is director of 511 kinderheim is still intact somewhere
Careful you're treading on dangerous territory right now
Who knows what could happen
That almost sounds like a threat
You should know I'm not afraid of taking risks get lost
Sorry
I'm going to follow you everywhere until I get the information I'm after
Back off
I'm warning you not to ever come near me again just disappear
People we found you
We've been looking for you you were gone a long time
Hey who's that guy with you
Forget about him he's nobody
Come along let's go home
Walk away leave this alone
Living out the remainder of his life peacefully surrounded by his grandkids
To think back then
He did such horrible things to children
Who is it
Do you have a delivery from Mr pedrov Sir
Mr pedrov
Sure give me a minute
Corner rooms with a bad view are convenient especially in moments like these
Wow
It's been a hell of a morning I almost didn't make it out here
Yeah a couple of strange men showed up at my hotel room
Here we
Watching your grandchildren play
This is wonderful
Life is good
You know when I was working for a newspaper an oldies Germany I couldn't even dream of A Moment Like This thankfully times have
No I'm a freelance journalist writing whatever I want gosh
That was unimaginable just a few years ago back in our socialist society
Being free is nice
I've been watching you ever since I left the hotel did you know that
Great home
I saw you when you came out the front door and thought to myself he has a lot of space
I'll bet you have nice big rooms
I'll keep must be difficult
And rents expensive isn't it
Spending the whole day at a cafe
Taking walks and playing with your grandchildren
All the while maintaining is leisurely lifestyle without working
So I wondered
Where do you get the money to afford this
You must have sold something
Maybe the data to your failed experiment
Did you get a good price
I told you it was a success
That's all the more reason for it to get a good price
Just leave me alone
I have nothing to say to you
Now go
There they are again earlier he was at the movies with those two
Now they're all eating parfait
Each time they look different one two three three
Sex
This is Mr pedrov's home right
May I come inside
Hey there
This is horrible
I know what he's up to he's doing it again
Right here he's trying to replicate the very same EXP
Unconscionable
How could that man do this
She's trying to replicate
The very same experiment
511 kinter
There's a red light district at the German border
These boys were born there but we're never nurtured
And some were just abandoned by their impoverished mothers
Their business fell off when the Berlin Wall came down
So you just went there and gathered up all these children
For the purpose of continuing your 511 kinderheim experiment here
Oh Mr pedrov I didn't realize you had a guest
Don't worry about him
He's going home now I was planning to prepare dinner
Will Connecticut be all right for tonight
Yes
Everyone loves your Kennedy leaky so much that would be just perfect
You're convinced I'm continuing with 511 kinderheim
I will tell you again
I have no need to continue that experiment
That project was a huge success
Oh yeah
Based on what
The educational program I created for the experiment
It's shaped personality so they were eager to absorb all kinds of knowledge
Educational
There was nothing educational about it
Human experimentation Dam
Calm down and think about it for a moment
What is the purpose of Education
Isn't it supposed to help people acquire Knowledge and Skills to become useful members of society
The instructor is main task is to create conditions to stimulate learning
All education is an experiment
At 511 tenderheim everyone was challenged to learn
I highly Advanced educational system was established
You did such a horrible things
And now you want to justify them
Horrible things yes think about what your Advanced protocols did to their minds you're a
Freelance writer you don't possess the scientific background to critique my procedures
What's with that look
What about the incident where the children killed each other
You deny your experiment was the cause of that I told you that happened after
I was removed from my position as director
The emergence of an unexpected anomaly through the entire program out of control
Unexpected anomaly
Like what
Like Darkness
Hatred apathy destructive urges
Unfortunately people easily succumb to these negative forces once they get in they're hard to stop
Stop and soon they possessed all of 511 kinderh
Yes one boy arrived and all that began I suppose next you're going to tell me that
Didn't have anything to do with you as I keep telling you the experiment was very successful that's
Lie and you know it
All those children at 511 kinderheim shared a common character flaw
There was one thing they could not do
They were incapable of loving
I'm interesting comment
Now then our little chat is over and I would like you to leave
Don't even think of telling anyone about this place sorry
You're breaking one of this country's loss I have to report this to the police I think you're forgetting you're not
In Germany anymore
The Czech Republic is a democracy they frown upon things like an unauthorized orphanage with an unlic
Director you want to make a deal that's what this is
About your offering to not report me if I cooperate
And I give you all the data from my experiment
All right
Let's go
What are you planning to do
You guys want to play some soccer well what are we waiting
Waiting for where do you think you're going with the boys oh didn't you hear we're going out to
Can you play some soccer
Listen up everyone
Mr Petrov and I are sort of working out a deal
And I want you guys to help me make the right decision in this matter because it concerns all of
If I reported him to the proper authorities
Then you'd all be free to go
I mean you'd like to leave wouldn't you
But you have more freedom out of there don't you
Care
Happy face
Okay
So genuinely happy
Possible
Where you going
What a beautiful lady yeah
Can you hear me
Mr Petrov tell me who shot you
Walmart
Woman
Mr petroff please tell me
Did you alter the program this time
The
The card
And the secret code number
You'll find them
Hidden behind the third drawer of my desk
Therefore my safety deposit box
With the experiment data and tape can be found
What
Of an interview
With a certain boy
Recalling his past
Under the use of chemically
Induced hypnotism
That boy is the malevolent monster
His darkness and evil influence
Let 511 kinderheim
To destruction
So now
What do you think
Are these children
Lacking anything in the development
Mr pedrov I don't know but it appears you educated them differently than
511 kinderheim
Apath
Hat
Destructive urges
Dark Forces I wanted them to repel but how could I do that
What would make them resistant that was love
Yes it was that's the new discovery I factored in Mr Petrov
Love isn't any new discovery parents give it to their children all the time
An experiment