From here on we've got to keep a tighter lid on all of this once it's gone things
Will be as smooth as silk my head I sure could go for a nice drink right about now how about
About a whiskey Bonbon instead
Hey there better than nothing besides these were a gift from a real Beauty
What's wrong you look depressed
I feel like I can't believe in anything anymore
I'll help you if you want me to
I believed in him I never would have thought that inspector zaiman could do such a thing
What happened I believed in hell
Right now the only person who I really believe in
Is you
A terribly shocking Discovery was made early this morning at the Prague police station
Three men
Two big questions remain
There have been rampant rumors of the Prague police force having ties to the former Czechoslovakian secret police but these
Have never been substantiated
However
With the murder of these three prominent detective do you know who the murderer is
Sir can you confirm that the drug used to commit these murders with a muscle relaxant we've heard rumors that hit cheap Hamrick was somehow
I'll link with the check secret place any truth to that
Well I is there any connection between these murders and last week's killing of inspector zaimon
Well
We are an investigating that
I mean we're not rolling out that possibility in saying that do you mean the department strongly believes that these two incidents are linked
No I
Right now the department is pursuing all possible leads in this investigation sorry but this detectives not assigned to this case and we have no
So you need a button that lip of yours and get out of here
Yes sir
So exactly when are you going to make an official statement we will have a news conference when we feel we've gathered enough information
Not a moment before drug treatment
Why are you here
Have you come back to interrogate them again I'm very sorry ma'am
Look I've been given orders to investigate this case starting again at Square One
This is my last stop I've already spoken with all the boys who got placed in other orphanages
Think of what bringing this up again does to them
Mr pedrov raised all those boys like they were his own children now they have to live the rest of their lives with the image of
Raymond is made lying they're dead
Even now some of them still cry themselves to sleep
I want to help them forget this as soon as possible
And yes
That's not something they can just forget about knowing that someone they truly loved has been taken away
Forever
15 minutes
And don't go asking them questions that are too graphic am I clear
Sure
It was lots of fun living with Mr Pedro
Yeah he and Mrs Anna were really nice to us all the time
I see
No I'd like to talk to you about the day you found them if that's okay
That day you had Mr Grimmer come to visit have you met him before
No
Not before then
Do you know why he came to visit
As they talked did Mr Grimmer act friendly towards Mr Patrick
Come to think of it they didn't talk or act like friends but
But I didn't understand
They were talking in German
But you know a few words in German don't you
Whether some words you did know
He was saying that this
Was unauthorized and
Police should be
So Mr Grimmer said that
Yeah
He also said experiment and the word education
Experiment
Anything else
What else
You don't have to tell us if you don't want to hunza
He said 511 kinderheim
Tenderheim huh okay
So hunza is that a place that you've heard of
No never
Do you know it
There's no such place in the Czech Republic
I see
So tell me about Mr Grimmer
What kind of person is he
Oh he's a really nice guy
So you like him too is he
People in soccer with us
It wasn't really any good at it
Put Mr Grimmer look like he was having a lot of fun delay he has a soccer ball is just awful
He went up for one and fell flat on his butt he's probably even worse than hunza really
The other boys told me you were the leader at Mr petrov's orphanage is that right Antonin
I wouldn't say I was really the leader it's just well you see I'm just older than the other
Now I'd like to talk to you about that day is it about Mr Grimmer
One of the guys already told me that you were asking honza and Izzy about him
Oh
I see
What do you think
I think he's a nice person
I got a question for you do you think Mr grimmer's a suspect no
But we're still investigating
Mr pedrov and Mrs Anna had already been murdered by the time we got back home from playing soccer with Mr Grimmer
I told the police already but I think I saw did it as we got back home I saw this beautiful woman with long
Blonde hair and she was coming out of her house
Are you trying to catch him catch who Mr Grimmer no but he sure
There's someone I'd like to have a chat with
I'm actually going to meet him later on
I promised him and we already set where we're going to meet
And would you tell me where that is you're sure that's all right because I might be forced to arrest him
Well you don't have to cuz there's no way he murdered anyone
Hey
Hi
It's been a little while
I'm so are you guys all holding up okay
Things are a lot better
You haven't been crying yourself to sleep right
Easy with his bed twice
Well it was the truth be known I went in my bed until I was a lot older than he is now really
Hey Anton
Did you bring that one thing I gave you earlier
Thank you
I'm glad you held on to it for me
See this is something very important Mr pedrov left behind
I'm glad you're all okay
I wish I had more time to share
But I've got to go
Can't you stay and play soccer with us
I'm sorry boys I really should be moving on
But we're ready to play those are a new friend
Yeah
I can play for a while
All right
Come on I'm open on the right guys pass it to me
Oh I got it Grimmer going in for the steel
It's easier said than done
You're Mr Grimmer aren't you
Did you come to arrest me
Don't start waving your gun around
Come on their kids here
Then I order you to hand over your pistol this instant
Sorry
I don't have one to hand over
So you tossed it
I never had one in the first place
Tell me did you kill inspectors Amon
I don't know
I can't remember
I was half dead from being tortured at the time
Your nails done
I know it wasn't me who fired the gun
But I might be responsible for killing the other two
I passed out before it
Mr grandma
What are you up there resting
Your team stop playing a man down cuz you went and took a break
Sorry about that guys
Hey I'm old cut me some slack
Okay you
Antonin told me that you were planning to meet them to play soccer that's how I found you
You're a person of interest Mr Grimmer
So what's the verdict am I the murderer you seek
I don't know
Over the past few days some of the people I deeply trusted betrayed me
My faith in them was so totally shattered I don't know what to believe in anymore
The only person you can truly believe in is yourself
You can try to trust other folks but sometimes they let you down
So we going to the station
No just promise you won't leave town okay
So
Where are you staying for the time being
At the Pablo hotel room 302
Whenever you decide I am the murderer feel free to come and get me
You be sure to hold on to that key I think it's the
The real cause of all these murders you're investigating it's to a safety deposit box
That sign up there
Well it's actually an old Relic
It's a sign for a pub that was established here 200 years ago
But the three frogs Pub has been closed down for AG
Even though it's old and Faded it's considered a landmark
And it seem a lot
It's been through World Wars the fall of Communism and disasters too
It's amazing that whole thing is survived
About a decade ago it even made it through a fire
Really
Yeah
This woman with a young kid lived up there on the second floor right above it
She sure was a beautiful woman
What kind of antisocial hardly ever went out
And for a good reason
Seems while she was living there
She was using it alias
One day this big official looking black car came and it took her and the kid away for good
It was a big deal we all heard rumors that the woman was arrested for having participated in anti-government activities
That sort of thing happened to all too often in those days we lived in fear because the government terrorized everyone it
It was really quite awful during those final years before the fall of Communism people disappeared all the
That woman who got taken away did she have one child with her did she have twins no
She only had one child with her what a pretty face that kid had what's that woman's child a boy or a girl
Let me think for a second now which one was it sometimes it's really
Hard to tell whether they're a boy or a girl with Children of that little man I can't remember all I can think about is how they
They took away that poor innocent kid with them when they took the mother away that was a sad thing to see right after they left
Left the fire started I ran up there even though I didn't think anyone was around then I got a huge surprise
Her child was in there
The child must have been released that's all I can figure but I imagine the fire got started when he got hungry and decided to
Use the stove to try to cook something so where'd he go
I hate to admit it but after that fire happened I don't know where that young kid went I've always wondered what
That kid
What if that child was one of the ladies twins what if the police took away one child and
The other one up in that room well if what you just said is right that might make sense
But I don't get why you're so sure about the fact that she had twins
So after questioning the boys I was able to meet with Grimmer and check him out for myself
I really don't think he's the murder
Well I'm just an amateur at crime solving Maybe I'm Wrong about him Mr
He's not evil that much I do know
Just from us talking
He was able to help me figure out what's really going on
It first went inspectors Amon was found murdered
I thought it was my duty to avenge his death at any cost
But then I open my eyes
I discovered that inspector zaymond
A man I looked up to
Was a corrupt cop
I have been willing to risk everything for him
That's all changed
And then after that
The chief and to senior officers I always reported to wound up poison
When I heard that those men might have been corrupt
As well it shook me to
I mean it's beyond belief
How far has this terrible Darkness spread in the world
Darkness
Yes the dark Specter of the check secret police hangs over all of this
The check secret police work directly under the former Internal Affairs office
They were a brutal force that served as an essential tool of the Soviet Union
But when democracy came 10 years ago they were disband
Their leaders were put on trial but some escaped and went underground
Even now they're still planning to regain their former power
That's as much as I know about
In their quest for power many innocent victims have wound up dead
Are the secret police the only ones Behind These murders
That's the question I'm faced with
Is there any way we can really know just
How closely the darkness is encroached upon the world we live in
I don't think I believe in anyone anymore
Mr Grimmer even worn me
Only believe in yourself
He said when you trust other people it doesn't always work out
And as he said that he entrusted me with something very important
Sorry
I can't stop talking about this
It's kind of tough on me not even knowing your name
Hey listen it's all right you don't have to tell me
I always thought when people spend time getting to know one another
Told each other their names
About their pasts
Just talking to you makes me happy
Both of my parents are still alive
Their school teachers
But my father used to participate in Democratic activities in the police always watched him
So my mom ended up divorcing him to protect me from any potential trouble
When I finally told my mom I wanted to be a detective
She got angry and told me not to do it
And why did you want to become a detective I believe my friends at the bar told you the reason why I remember
Wasn't it because you grew up liking cops on TV
Yeah I like playing cops and robbers ever since I was a kid
Of course I always got to be the cop
You don't have to laugh that much
What were you interested with
Earlier you were saying the Grimmer and trusted you was something important
It's a key to a safety deposit box
The safety deposit box
Apparently whatever stored in there is super important
This old German man named pedrov who was running in legal orphanage was murdered last week and
Well inside that deposit box of pedrobs
The data from some kind of
Human experiments he supposedly conducted
According to Grimmer the material that's in that box is the real cause of all these murders
Don't say that again
Don't tell anyone what you just told me not even the police
Nobody
But
This thing isn't something I can handle all by myself
She loves you a lot
When you told her you wanted to be a cop you know why she got mad
It's because she was worried
Put something awful might happen to you
I got a bad feeling about what you just told me
The best thing to do is not to tell anyone
I don't want you to get hurt
I care about you too
I'm sorry
My name
I want you to know my name now Young
It's Anna
My name is Anna Li
Anna
What a beautiful name
So your last name must mean that you're German
See you later
Anna
Good evening Mr Toluca
Oh Anna it's a nice night isn't it
Good evening Anna good night Mrs yoga
A safety deposit box key