This is the most scandalous case that has ever occurred in the history of the Czech police force
Much to our dismay we discovered that the three officers who were murdered were connected to the former Czechoslovakian secret police
In light of these incidents I would like to believe that all the dark connections which have stained our reputation have been purged from the
Rock station
Remember you are proud officers of this Force I expect conscientious behavior from all of you
And let me say this
That's your new Chief I intend to carry out a very thorough reform here and my first order of business is to regain our
Citizens Trust
I will now introduce you to the five members special investigative task force which was sent over here from the government
It goes without saying that I expect you to cooperate with them so we may close the book on this atrocious case as soon as possible
Possible
Your detective so
Correct
Yes
As your new Chief I would like to say thanks
For the fine investigative work that you've done on this case to help bring it to light
You're very welcome sir
Oh and by the way detective what case are you currently working on
The one inspector zemon was on which involves the murder of pedrov
A man who was operating an illegal orphanage
Very well then
Please continue to devote all your efforts to solving it Detective
Yes sir
I'll be on my way then
One more thing
That tall man who emerged as a suspect and inspector zaymon's murder
Do you have any pertinent details on him that you can give me before you get back to work
No sir
I don't have any solid information on him as of yet
I see you may go now thank you good
Sir
Young souk
He's been assigned to this division for a year now same on took him under his wing early on and they became
Soup uncovered detective patella and Janet checks hidden past he also met
Chief Hamrick right before he died I want you to keep an eye on that kid
Yes sir
Hey
You know when I called up that hotel where you told me to be staying and I was kind of surprised to hear you you answered the phone
Not that I'm complaining
Well it sounds as though you thought you were going to be deceived again
Maybe
Orange juice please
Mr Grimmer I know you wanted to meet me some place where there were large crowds
But is the spot really okay what do you mean by okay
I spoke to the new chief he hasn't taken you off the suspect list for zaymon's murder yet
Besides you're being pursued by former members of the Czechoslovakian secret police
Come to think of it you might be right about the crowd maybe it makes you safer
There's no such thing as a safe place
If they're fixing to do it they can get me any place anytime for example
They can take me out from that window with the red drapes
Look Mr Grimmer I want you to level with me okay who are you really
Just a struggling freelance journalist but if that's true then why put yourself through all this guess
I'm just nosy seems to come with a territory how can you make light of it
At every moment your life isn't danger don't worry about me
It was my decision to get involved I knew it was risky
Suk is currently in a cafe in Republic Square
And he's not alone
He's meeting with the suspect now
It's all rather lanky fellow
There's no doubt in my mind that it's Grimmer
Yes
Should we continue to observe them for a bit longer sir
All of the started when you went to see Petrov
This was a man who conducted brainwashing experiments on orphaned children in East Germany back before the unification right
Right and then before he died I drive gave you the key to his bank safety deposit box where he kept a record of those
Same experiments is that right yeah
And he also mentioned something about the monster's past
I wonder what he could have meant by that it seems that there are many people who for whatever reason want to get their hands on that
Data
You mean the former secret police and also that lovely blonde lady
The children at pedrov's orphanage also mentioned her called her the pretty blonde lady and I said they saw her leaving
Leaving the house right after pedrock was mortally wounded
Do you have any ideas who that woman might be
I don't have a clue she's a mystery to me
Is it all right you're being here like this I mean we haven't told your superiors about this meeting
We're here acting on your own aren't you
That's not exactly what I'd call being an honest team player look I'm not planning to hide any of this from them
The moment I'm exercising my own discretion I'll report to my superiors after I've gathered out evidence in this case
And if I do a thorough investigation I can prove to them without a doubt that you're innocent
It is something the matter
Looks slowly to your 9:00
That's suspicious looking fellow sitting under the umbrella reading a newspaper
What do you think
Couldn't say
Now then
Shall we go all right but where do we go
You brought it with you didn't you you know the key to the safety deposit box that I gave you
Yeah
Don't you want to find out
The identity of this so-called monster
Yes
In that case we better get going though knowing who it is might be hazardous
Your health
You're looking a little pale soup
Did I just see that pretty blonde lady
Hey what's wrong
Nothing
Must have imagined it soup is on the Move I'm on them
I spoke with you before on the telephone
Undetective souk Pride police
Just wait here a moment please
Thank you both for your patience
If you follow me
I will take you to the vault
This is where we have our safety deposit boxes
You may use that room to view the contents
Research papers
And a single Cass
Well
I do have a tape recorder with me
If you're ready to hear it
And I'm going to press play now
You know what this place is
I want one gender high but voice it's a boy
What is your name
My name is
Johan
Joh
What is your last name
Let's try that again
My name is
Thomas
Which one is your real name
Once Upon a Time
In a land far away
There left
A nameless monster
The monster
Was dying to have a
Is that a story that you've read before
I was waiting for Ann
Who is Anna
I was reading a picture book while I was waiting for Ann
This boy was drug Suk
They gave him something before this session was put on tape
Who is your father
I don't know
Your mother
I think she's alive
You
You're a very bright child
Is there anything you're afraid of
What is it that you are most afraid of
Let me ask a different question then
Have you ever killed anyone
Many people were dead
It was like
Anna and I were the only two people in the world
Let's go back to that other question again
What is it that you are the most afraid of me
Getting bigger much much Chom Chomp gobble gobble
Much much jump jump
Lunch Chop Chop bubble gum what I'm most afraid of
It's
I'm going to throw up
What happened Mr grim
Hey are you all right
What did we just hear on this tape
I mean was that little boy the voice of the monster
I really don't understand what's going on
Even though we don't know what this tape is about
There are people out there who would do anything
To have in her possession
For one the former Czechoslovakian secret police under them it won't make any difference if we just listen to part of the tape
Are all the way to the end
I'm sorry to tell you but there's no turning back
What are you going to do now do you
Time to return the tape and the research papers to the safety deposit box
No under normal circumstances they should be stored here as evidence but all things considered
You're planning to hang on to them then I think we should leave separately
Let me serve as your Decor after all it's me they're watching
Oh yeah better give me your telephone number and street address if we're both able to make it home safely
We'll have a way of getting in touch with each other in the future
I made it
And I don't think I was followed
I'm starting to get a bad feeling about this I mean I don't have a whole lot of
Confidence in him since he lives on Landover Street
What are you doing in my apartment what's going on
That's the same question we wanted answered
Do you know who we are or do I need to Enlighten you
You're both part of that special task force the government assigned you to the Prague office my partner here is detective third
Novak and I'm detective Xander
Also third grade
Care to tell me why the two of you broke into my place
How long have you been meeting with Grimmer
And don't tell me you don't know what I'm talking about
You two just met at the cafe and Republic Square
And went to the prohaska bank together
You also know the man in this Photograph don't you
Captain Carl lunker
He was an important name in the Czech secret police who are now Underground
What
No I've never seen that man before
Our task force rent a check on your bank account
You recently made a hefty deposit
Weird all that money come from
What are you talking about I don't know anything about a deposit we've heard your mother is currently being hospitalized for a serious I
Illness at the crewmov hospital
I understand that hospital care and private nurses can get quite expensive
Yeah so what are you trying to imply
Well after your mother separated from your father she raised you on her own without any support from him
Which says to me
You must care a lot about her
Just what are you suggesting Detective
We would like to search each room of your flat
Yeah do whatever you want what do I care
You're going to see I'm not hiding money or anything else
Because I've got nothing to hide
Pezonda
Come here for a second
Where'd you find these things they aren't mine they were
Shelf in a cabinet above your bathroom sink detective soak no I don't know what they are they don't belong to me we
Can't say for sure what this drug is until we check it out in the lab at the station
But in the bodies of the three dirty cops who were murdered in your station we found a muscle relaxant mixed in with this type of
Whiskey bon bon candy
You can tell us your side of the story back at headquarters
As You Wish investigate me as thoroughly as you see fit oh we will
Can I ask for a favor
Before we head out can I change into a clean shirt I've been wearing this one all day
Fine but hurry up
Just calm down calm down I haven't done anything
My records perfect
I just need to go in and explain to them that I'm innocent
Wait I smell gunpowder