This news story about the police just keeps getting worse and worse any new info coming in
Yeah that was the police calling to say they're holding a press conference about the case at 3:00 p.m.
No my years I've never seen a case it's crazy is this
No don't tell me you've been here looking through those documents since I left you last night
Yes but it looks like I found that article I was looking for thanks for all your help
Hey you're welcome glad it worked out
Oh one second I've got a question right now
I know
In this article I found there's this Mr X
Mr X huh that's right 3 years ago your paper ran an expose entitled the truth about the former
Czechoslovakian secret police
Oh yeah
That article explained how after the wall fell that instead of pulling back the German right Wingers and the former checklist of Locke
Secret police extended their influence even more by organizing crime syndicates as a matter of fact I'm the guy who wrote it
You wrote this article
Well what would it take for you to introduce me to that check secret police agent you interviewed the man you referred to as Mr X
You said before that you're a special correspondent hear from Japan
So enlighten me why would you want to have an interview with our Mr X anyway
Oh well he's newsworthy
I'm sure the folks back home would be interested in finding out about how abductions imprisonment and other things were done here during the
World War I got to tell you those guys are crazy
I feel like I really risked my life to do that interview back then
They're still very dangerous
And they're still very active based on what just went down
I know you've been in here a while but did you hear the latest update
I mean have you seen the headlines from this morning yet
Well I even if you're not from here if you're trying to do a story on the secret police you should be following this big story
We ran about detective soup here's a copy of today's Final Edition you can read German can't you
This young guy young Suk was working as a rookie detective in the Prague Police Department
After shooting two detectives from a special investigative team who are assigned to keep an eye
Suits run off somewhere
Flown the coop
This inspector named zaymon was murdered and it turned out he was a corrupt cop who worked for both the former check Secret
Police and the current Prague police force silk discovers that fact and goes to the chief to report it
Not knowing that he has ties to the secret police as well but someone poisons the chief and his two
Tony's in all three of them die
Duke's hail is a hero for helping to clean up the department but then he goes and kills two cops were assigned to watch over him
Soup was a promising and skill Detective
It was a young man on his way up
Just what is it that you're mumbling about exactly
Three superiors poison to death
I whiskey bonbons
With a muscle relaxant in them
That's your
Excuse me
Could you please tell me if fiance mother is here
I know
She's staying in room 409 thank you
Us
Keep your visit short she may not want to talk
Pardon me man but are you
Six mother
Oh y
My young
At last you finally come
Ma'am I'm not young
I'm so glad you made it here my son
Won't you come closer and let me see your face darling
You should relax now go ahead and lie down
Ma'am have you received any phone calls or letters from your son young lately
That Katarina the girl next to me is so cruel she took my toy and won't give it back to me
You know it's not precious little stuffed animal that I'm very gave me
I want to be sure you know something
Your son is an honest cop
And he's innoc
Well I'll be going now
All done
Tell the truth
I have a hunt you've been playing there again weren't you young
You always like playing cops and robbers at that same place
What place are you talking about
You may like to think of it as your own little Hideout son but I know all about it
The abandoned building on Bruno Street
You found out about it
That's right
I certainly did
Take care
Now don't go getting hurt son be sure to come home in time for dinner
Once Upon a Time
In a land far away
There lived
A nameless monster
The monster
Was dying to have a name
Once Upon a Time
Inland far away
The nameless monster
I figured I'd bring you some food
And the latest newspaper
You're getting to be quite a celebrity you know that
Tell me
Are you concerned someone will find that tape and research papers from the safety deposit box that I sent to my mother
Well one thing's for certain
They're a lot safer with your mom than if we had them here with us
After reading all about what happened
I have to say it's amazing to me how much your situation reminds me of that other incident it's uncann
What incident
I'm referring to something that happened in Dusseldorf about 10 years ago
This one Hospital's director and two other doctors died after ingesting poisoned candy
The main suspect of the time was a promising young neurosurgeon
What ended up happening to him
Four guys been on the run ever since he's still trying to prove he's innocent
You're still in good shape you
After all you have me as a witness
You mean you actually saw her she was coming down the stairs of my apartment
That I did
Our Infamous blonde Beauty
But even if that woman really is the murderer if we can't find her we have nothing come down suke no
Have you seen it from now on we're stuck being on the Run why did all this happen to me
What the hell did I ever do to deserve this crap
Take it easy
Are you saying it from this moment on you expect me to just disappear off the face of the Earth cool it come on
Put together
I've told you how to handle this haven't I
Remember when I told you the only one you can believe in is yourself
Good
That's much better
No let's eat
He
When I was little I used to come here and play cops and robbers
And that's very room
That
What was the police inspector's desk
It's hard to believe that it's still here
Just as it was
I would sit behind this desk and give out orders to everyone
Just like on TV
Gentleman
This case is a real tough one
But all of us must do our very best
In the name of Justice we must Prevail today
We can't let evil run rampant
Feels like old times
Soak
Stay still
We're surrounded
Don't worry Sue I got you it's got you away from the window and behind this desk
That's fine you're probably in shock
Question is who shot at us
Where are they shooting at us from
That shot didn't hit any vital organs you're going to be fine
I need to borrow your gun
The tape
Raw soup
Purpose missing his heart now on purpose
Give us the tape God they're going to shut both of
Tell me grandma okay I'm going to work my way over
I'm coming for you right now
It hurts it hurts all over
Just breathe try to stay calm all over quite
Listen save your strength
If you can get out of here want you to go don't worry about me I won't leave you
They're right there above
Talking about it's a problem
No it's your favorite
They're speaking in check but what the hell are they saying
427 yesterday
I'm out of school
You can help me set up tonight can I still send them yet
We're actually photography
Remember please I don't want to die here Dom
Location message
Microphone
Can you speak German
Yes
I need
Who are you aiming at over there
Wait
Who in the hell are you answer my question
What are you doing okay
We took care of them
Two of our guys charge that building
The detective and tall guy
I've already been wiped out
I'm too damn late
It's quiet up there
I know you a man from the Train
Look what he did
The Magnificent Steiner right
It's the Magnificent Steiner folks
He's done it once again
What happened
Hello Dr Tenma
I'm glad that you showed up when you did
Could you save his life please
Who cares a fine young policeman
So please do whatever you can to help him pull through
He's not the only one who needs a doctor
Who did this
Do you know
Guess it was probably me
Or my other half rather
The one that's deep down inside of me
See doctor
I was one of those special children at 511 kinderheim
I was glued to that TV whenever I had the chance to watch the magn
Jefferson Steiner in action the main character on the show was a frail young man
The bad guys would always Corner him at the worst possible moment but before you knew it
The Magnificent Steiner would appear and flatten all the villains
I didn't realize it at first but the Magnificent Steiner start
Showing up in my life for real whenever I was in real danger it appear in Rescue Me
Feed all the bad guys
The only vivid memory that I still have from being a child was watching The Magnificent Steiner on TV
That's it all of my other memories were taken away
Every last one of them lives clean out of my mind
At 511 kinderheim
Listen to me babbling away like this
I mean you don't want to hear about my past that has nothing to do with you all right I've treated him as best I can
Thank you doctor
So do you think you'll pull through
All of the bullets that hit him pass through cleanly but the wound that runs from the auxiliary artery to the brachial art
Serious
That's something I tied on him should keep enough pressure on it to stop the bleeding
That's all I can do for now but he's in shock
We have to get him to a hospital as soon as possible
Mr Grimmer
You just said that your past doesn't involve me but it does more than you can know
Especially 511 kinderhan
Now let's get an ambulance for soup
Where's the guy that's hurt there are three men in there we're going to need another ambulance call dispatch
How bad off are they pretty bad we need to move them but but what well what's wrong these guys have already received
First day and proper first aid at that wait you're saying somebody already took care of them
Grandma look at me the news
Oh yeah what are they saying
They're speaking check so I can't follow it
But I found out the name of the hospital where they're being kept
It's yakubazemi Memorial
Once the ID suit the police are probably going to arrest him
It's a sad State of Affairs
He is
I wonder if I should go and testify
So then doctor Tenma
How on Earth did you know we talk about what you were saying earlier please
There's something I need to know more about Grimmer
511 kinderheim
Actually I don't really remember being there
I don't remember that period I can only remember the fragments
Dark hallways
A stain on the ceiling sound of
Squeaking smell of my multi bed
The memories came back to me at least a little bit
After I was finally freed from that orphanage
I can almost hear someone saying I was 14 years old
Now that I think back to them when I was first enrolled in that strange School
They went and gave me a brand new name
It's only then that I became Wolfgang Grimmer
The place where they chose to raise me was this totally artificial neighborhood
That little bubble was our whole world and we weren't allowed out there was some man playing the father figure
And a woman to play the mother too they taught me languages there
English Spanish French I could speak read or write them all
You were trained to be a spy I must admit the schooling they gave me did serve me pretty well
The toughest thing to master
Was just learning how to smile now then we have to go
Go to the hospital where they're keeping soup
Mr Grimmer they had your picture in the paper they want you as a witness in this case you know that
I know
But I'm the only one who can prove suk's innocence