Are you okay Mina
He was taking and drag down these very steps they took him away who was
My big brother
Yes he was called the man of red rose Mansion I believe
What was his real name
It was Franz Bonaparte I see Bonaparte however I'm not
Not certain if that was his actual name bonaparta was also known to have a pseudonym why would he
Well you see he was also the author of a children's book
I was reading a picture book in here
Someone came back home
Children's book that's right it was a strange picture book
It was called the nameless monster
This summer is real I've been
Before I was reading a picture book sitting here by myself the one who
Open the door and came back it's me
How could that be
It was greeting myself
Welcome home
You're looking for young souk's mother
Well then mrsook is right down the hall in room 409
I'm sorry to say the poor deers memory comes and goes in spurts
You'll have to be patient with her
Is that you dear
No
Oh my what a beautiful girl are you one of y'all's Little Friends
That's right
You've brought such pretty flowers
I'll put them right here how about that
I have to be very careful so my Aunt Olga doesn't take them
She's always coming around poking into my things and taking what she wants
She was in here yesterday and when I turned my back she took my favorite doll
Well she sounds perfectly horrid
But I think she passed away over 10 years ago now don't you remember that
That's right
I'm surprised at how much you know
I've heard a lot from young man
I see
Where is he is it a school day
Of course
He's already finished with that
He's a detective
Everything's fine your Yawn is all right there's nothing to worry about
I like talking to you
You have a sweet face and very kind eyes
You can tell me about anything you want
Whatever you can remember
Well let me think
And knows what the latest fashion trend will be even before
This is so much fun it's been a while since I've had such a good time
I'm glad to hear
I must think of a way to thank you for your visit
You don't need to do that actually though I was really hoping that you would show me that thing that John recently and
Yes like I said tape of course I remember there it is
It never would have occurred to me that you would have sent them to soak's mother
It shouldn't take very long I'll wait here while you go in and collect the tape and the documents
Make sure you don't forget about our arrangement
Remember we did make a deal
Come on
Let's get going Dr Tem
I'm sorry that I said before this had nothing to do with you doctor
No words can describe how I felt when you told me everything that you've been through
The last 10 years must have been horrible for you
But this cassette tape maybe the key to unlocking the whole story and you'll be able to prove your innocent
When that happens your entire life will change for the better
But Mr Grimmer
What about your life
Well well it is true that I've been on a mission to investigate 511 kinderheim and what it did to the children
The truth is
Even if it all becomes clear
It won't lead to any big changes in my life
So your friends of Mr Sook and came to check up on his mother
At the moment she seems to be doing quite well
Good
You know I think the conversation she had with her other visitor today really helped to lift her spirits
Father visitor
What was their name
I don't know all I remember is she was a beautiful long-haired blonde
You actually did come
I was told to expect you shortly and here you are
The tape where is it
Let me see
I want to know how Young's doing
At the moment
He's
Take me to the hospital where I can see you on
My Yawn is in big trouble isn't he
My mind is alert and has been very clear since that pretty girls visit
Talking to her reawaken my memories
But it might only last through the day
Please let me see Yon
I will take you
To the hospital
Where you can see your son
Just took trimmer
Turns out the secret police are willing to make a deal with us
Mother you're here
Oh
Why didn't you call me so I could have come sooner
I'm really all right
Nothing
Nothing at all
You're making light of it to try to keep me for Mooring aren't you dear just like you did the last time
The last time
I was so worried but you kept pretending nothing was wrong and walked around claiming you felt just fine
But you had badly sprained your ankle
Dear God please don't ever take him from my mind
Everyday my mind slips a bit more
So many things are fading away Lord let me remember my son is the best
Child and mother ever had
What is it that you are the most afraid of
A monster
Getting
Gob
That's enough
I don't want to hear anymore
Regardless you should listen to this
The nephew that you ended up sending to 511 kinderheim went through the same experience as this boy who was drugged
And interrogated on tape
You should know what that experience entailed you need to hear this
I only listen to this far into it the other day
We need to hear more to get the full picture of what happened
Let's continue on
But I'm most afraid of
For getting on
Strange lessons we have every day
Making my
Please
Don't make me forget Ann
It's only Anna and
Give me that
So I can allow you to hear
I don't understand who's this young man talking on the tape what did he do did he erase the rest of the old record
I finally figured it out he didn't erase
Did the person who visited souk's mother before record this
Whose voice is it I know this
That's what you want sounds like today where I must go
I finally figured it out Dr denma
He's on vacation
That workaholic
I can't believe
It's his first vacation since he started working here
Well
It's not like we're especially busy right now
Even for an elite officer of the bka
He pushed himself too hard
He just doesn't know his limits
His wife and daughter left him because of that
So where's the inspector spending is vacation anyway
He said something about Prague in the Czech Republic but I wonder if he even knows how to relax
What would you like to drink sir
Just coffee very well wait a minute I'm forgetting that I'm on vacation
Make it a beer
What kind of beer is this waiter
You actually believe this investigative report will satisfy the public
We don't know where detective soup is and we can't prove that the checkoslovakian secret police are involved
If we release these Half Baked results the media will eat Us Alive
There's a problem all the people who would have been able to help us with this are dead now
Blaming the dead doesn't let us off the hook it's not that simple the public demands that we do a complete investig
Yes sir if you understand then go uncover something
And while you're at it find detective suit
Immediately
Yes sir whoops excuse me
Oh there's someone here who would like to meet with you chief
You know I don't see anybody without an appointment
Besides now it's just not the right
But I will
Inspector
Well hell this certainly is a surprise inspector Lungi
We met each other at the Interpol conf
I remember we had a very interesting conversation and I was extremely impressed with the lecture that you gave
I'm sorry to be interrupting you with such a busy time
Don't worry about it it was nice you drop by on your vacation
I am a bit envious though
Due to the present situation here I doubt I'll even get away on a break
Congratulations new chief nepala
You must be very busy you said
If you don't mind I'd like to ask your advice
The case we're currently working on has grown into
Big Tang
Mess
It involves a connection between the Prague station and the former Czechoslovakian secret police
It all began when an inspector named Simon was found murdered along with Renegade members of the secret police
We thought had been disbanded years ago
At the time inspector zaiman had been conducting a murder investigation the victim had been running an un
Registered orphanage
We found out afterwards both Zaman and the orphanage director had ties to the secret police
This all happened before I took charge of this division
Do you have any leads on the murderer
A man named Grimmer who discovered the orphanage director's body has surfaced as the leading suspect but the children
Someone else leaving the crime scene immediately after the incident happened
Who's the other person
A pretty blonde woman
That was just the beginning this case has expanded
Here's what we do know
The former station Chief and two of his veteran detectives were found murder
Killed with poison candies
As it turns out those three dead officers were involved with the Czechoslovakian secret police as well do you know who gave
Then the poison candies
We suspect a young detective named young souk who reported directly to Z
Do you have any proof
No I'm afraid we have nothing conclusive
But two detectives recently assigned to this division by a special investigative task
Force were found shot to death and detective suits
Very interesting
So where's detective soup now
Right now is whereabouts are unknown
The circumstantial evidence all points directly to so
But you're wondering if he has a sufficient motive
Yes that's true
And he's not the kind of man who would normally commit such a crime
Yes but
How do you know what kind of man is
Let's just say that I know of a very similar case
I'm impressed even while on vacation your hand tells me you're focused on work
You know how to objectively a mass data I remember when listening to your lecture I was impressed when you said you can
Perform a completely subjective investigation and at the same time that you somehow get into the head of the killer in
Can we try it
If you were sick what would you be thinking and where would you be right now inspector knowing that law enforcement is looking for you
I'm sorry but I just can't
I'm on vacation I need time off for myself
Oh please forgive me I should be apologizing to you
So are you enjoying our beautiful city I've been visiting second-hand book shops
Something in particular
Yes and I searched 13 stores for it
But I finally came across one that had it
Actually I came here today to ask if you could translate this check into German when you had some free time but it appears as though
Too busy
Oh I see it's a picture book
I'm surprised I never would have imagined you were into such things
Leave it with me I'll have one of my officers translated by tomorrow
Who is it for
Your child or maybe a grandchild
Well yes I suppose it would be something like that
Hey Suk is an honest guy
As his friend I believe without a doubt that he is completely innocent
Look the police already asked me a whole bunch of questions but I know he's not guilty no matter what they're trying to imply
If you're in law enforcement you've got to help him make them listen to you if it will do you any good we'll give you as much information as we can
Unfortunately I'm only here on a vacation
So my influence is rather Limited
Were there any other people he was particularly close to
He was working on getting his girl to go out with him
Yeah but so far he'd only gotten her to give him her name hey do you remember what it was Anna
Yeah that's right her name was Anna Liebert she had blonde hair and she was dropped dead gorgeous
He was really happy he thought things between them were going pretty well
Anna Liebert one of the twins that survive on the East German Diplomat and his family
They were murdered 10 years ago
I don't think there's anything left now
I remember that Amy will share base the nameless monster was one of the books we published years ago but
If it was published during the old regime that would have been before I became president of this Publishing House
Is it possible that a meal share Bay was a pen name
You're right matter of fact I believe it was
Come to think of it he had other pen names as well
It was something bonaparta
Jacob farrobeck and
I think Klaus Pope
Klaus Pope's Box is right here
Oh you found something that's a surprise may I open it
Sure go right ahead
I'm sure it's all just a mountain of old sketches anyway
A pregnant woman
And she gave birth
To a girl
They were twins
I see
You were able to get a translated for me
Thank you Chief NE
I do appreciate
Oh there's something I've been wondering about
If you don't mind could you do me one more favor and read the last paragraph of the book to me now
At last he had found a
But there was no longer anyone around to call him by
Such a
Joh
I never thought to ask but how long is your vacation you there cancel the beer and
Make that a coffee instead
I think it's going to be a long vacation