Bad boy you're such a troublemaker how many times are you going to pretend to run away from here
You do that again and you'll get no dinner understand milosh
All right
You get your hands out of your pockets when you talk to me
Okay
You're really mean
Yeah was that blonde lady
So you said you saw her walking on Dominican street that right it could be that she lives on that street yeah so why didn't you follow her
We're all the way home and find out
I was so hungry my stomach was growling like a tiger here's the deal guys it's up to us to go find out where
One lady lives and turn her into the police yeah Mr Grimmer didn't kill Mr pedrov we've got to prove his innocence
True is innocence if we can do that would see Mr Grimmer sure we're figuring out how to do that right now come
Milos hurry up and eat your food
The first incident occurred right up there
Pedrov's illegal
It was in this building
Someone went up there and shot down the former 511 kinderheim director In Cold Blood
The children who lived there said that a blonde woman walked past them right after it happened
Pedrov was continuing his experiment here
But he did the complete opposite of what was done at 511 kinderheim
Instead of mental abuse The Children Here were raised with love
So tell me
You want to go in and take a look
The police have probably already carted away everything in terms of evidence wait
What are those on the door
Mr officers Mr Grimmer is innocent
Mr detectives the blonde woman is the murderer
It's those orphans
The children who used to live here must have come back and posted these notes on the door
For Mr Grimmer
Milan boche
It's a famous soccer players trading card
To those boys that card is priceless
How should I react to this
I mean what kind of expression should I make in this situation
All of my emotions were taken for me at 511 kinderheim
After that I had to attend another school where I was taught what were appropriate emotional responses
Situations like this
Very difficult
What's the correct way to react to this gift
Perhaps you should go and pay those children to visit
So you're Mr Grimmer
It seems like I'm always hearing the boys say such nice things about you
The children are out playing in the neighborhood they haven't yet
They really should be back by now
Oh here look at this
It contains the children's journal entries or rather a lot of letters that they've written to you
Mr Grimmer Let's Play Soccer again
Mr Grimmer I'll teach you how to play soccer since you're not very good at it
Mr Grimmer I can't wait for us to play together again
Right now
I'm still smiling aren't I
You know
I had to learn how to do this
I actually had to learn how to put a convincing smile on my face
I really only spent an afternoon with those boys
They have fun memories of that time I shared with them
Why do they seem to care about me
That's because they admire you
They probably like you
They like me
You know doctor
I've never understood these things not really
I didn't even know how to react when my own child was dying
I was asking so many questions of myself
Should I cry in this situation
How much should I Cry
Should I wear out loud or mash my teeth
Even now I still don't know how to react to it
I wish I did
Mr Grammer we need to talk to you dancing what's going on
Well what is it what's wrong
We just heard something from the kids that just you orphanage it's terrible
Just calm down take a deep breath and tell me what happened
They found that one lady we saw that one day yesterday we all decided to go out and try and find
And then poor meatloaf well he's gone Milo she's disappeared
I see
How interesting
So then let's review all the people who have come to visit you here
A certain middle-aged gentleman
A long haired Japanese man
And a tall German man
That's right
There's one more thing
I think you may have forgotten another person who came to see you
According to the desk nurse
A long haired blonde woman came to visit you recently as well
A woman
No there weren't any women who came to
Well
The nurse said she was certain there was
She said she was a beautiful blonde
She was very beautiful
But
Was definitely a man
I see
So tell me
What's your name
I'm your
I wonder
Have we met somewhere before
What were you doing when I saw you
Nothing
I know your face
You walk around this neighborhood a lot don't you
What is it you're looking for
Look for
My mom
Why don't you have a seat and make yourself comfortable
Here have some juice
Are you about to move out
Why do you ask
Because you have that big
And there's no stuff in this room
So your mother she's somewhere around here
Your mother
You told me you were looking for her isn't that right
But I don't really know if she lives around here
Then how will you find her
Do you have
How come
Too bad
You don't even know her
Oh no my mom when I see your face
No one at the orphanage believes me either
It'll keep telling me it's not going to happen
But when I see her I'm going to know her face for sure
Count on it
Really
Yeah and my mom will know it's me when she sees me
Even if you did find your mother what if she acts like she doesn't know you
Thank you were born because you were wanted
I mean why were you abandoned
Could it be that your mother left you because she hated you
No way
There's nothing special about being born
Not a thing
Most of the universe is just death nothing more in this univers
The birth of a new life on some corner of our planet is nothing but a tiny insignificant
Flash death is a normal thing
So why then
You think you will want it
Who wanted you
So what is your reason for living tell me
You're asking about a beautiful long hair blonde
Oh that would be Anna
So that young woman Anna would you happen to know if she lives in this neighborhood
Yeah I think Anna lives in a three-story apartment building go down this alley it should be about two blocks down
She's a very friendly nice young lady she always says hi to me when she sees me
Ann
She's such a nice girl she always has a warm hello and a smile for me what's her apartment number in
Florida she live on
Up there
That's her apartment Window on the top floor
So if what the boys told us earlier is true
And it turns out the woman who lives here actually did kidnap me Lush
And she happens to be a young blonde lady named Anna and she just might be the one
You're right and if this young blonde woman is the person I think she is and I swear this
Will end here now
Looks like for too
There's no sign of milosh anywhere
She took him
Didn't she
He was out actively looking for that blonde woman to try and prove my innocence
What should I do now
If you know tell me
How is a person supposed to react to a situation this terrible
Those boys got involved in all this because they were trying to prove my innocence
You can't blame yourself for everything
The boys told you that Milo usually walks around the streets of Prague he's always out there searching for his mother
He must care for his mother an awful lot
I don't have feelings like that
When my son died
Didn't feel anything
Many years ago while I was working for a newspaper
A female coworker suddenly came up to me one day
Told me that she loved me I ended up marrying her
I've been told that I'd be less likely to be suspected of being a spy if I were married it'd be a good cover
Soon she got pregnant she gave birth to a healthy baby boy one day my wife went
Shopping and left me alone with the baby my son was in his room taking a nap and when I went in to check on him he was
Stone had stopped breathing
I began giving him CPR right away and I called the doctor at the same time
I did everything I should have done to help him
I did it perfectly but my son died anyway
At my son's funeral my wife was so angry with me
She said
How can you stay so calm when our son is dead
Why aren't you crying didn't you love him you've always been cold like that
You've never shared your feelings with me not once look at you you're a heartless machine you can love anyone
You have nothing in your heart and you have no love for me and then my wife left me
I have to find milosh you told me that Milo she's the child of
Prostitute worked in a big red light district near the check border didn't you
I did if that blonde woman were looking for is the person I suspected is I don't think
Think she's going to let me Lush live what's worse if she won't just kill him quickly
If this turns out to be who I think it is
They'll confront me Lush with the coolest thing possible before finishing him off
Follow this road
It will take you to Germany
Will I see my mom
Your chances are good
There's a lively Town up ahead
You think that my mom's up there
I'm going to wait right here for you
You go ahead on your own
You know who your mother is when you see her
And your mother will know just who you are when she sees you
But listen
If it should happen that nobody calls out to you
And that means you aren't wanted by anyone in the world
What will you do with yourself then
What will you do
We'll go on then
I'm coming mom
The cruelest thing God
Thank you ladies thank you
What is it kid what do you want I'm looking for someone
Well spit it out who you looking for
My mom
Your mom that's a good one
Nothing no actually I know your mom personally
YouTube show me where she is no that's hard to do there's so many places she could hide she could
Be anyone anyone of 50 women
Oh my God it's you my boy it's you
Who are you lady
It's all right now
We don't looking for my mom because so good just let me hold you like this what
What do you think you're doing with that brat
You're acting like he's your kid so is he
Of course not
You know I don't make mistakes that big sure I guess you got the clap on purpose shut up
What do you pay
Wait hold on
No not here I paid you didn't I
I'm the customer you do as your customer says
Let's go get a room yeah
Come on stop there's a kid over there
Oh
Hang on
Don't run away yet
Stay here and watch
I'm a school teacher
In Germany
At school I have a spotless reputation I'm a gentleman as well as a respected teacher
Everyone thinks I'm a wonderful teacher
I am a wonderful teacher
Here this is for you
Thank you were born because you were wanted
Hey kid
Got cash
Are you sick lady yeah
I'm going to die soon well why don't you go inside I guess
Because I'm dying I have no money
Give me some money please
All I have is this
Most of the universe is just death nothing more
You think you will wanted
Thank you were born because you were wanted
I got it now
I get it now
This is it
The red light district ends here
I know
They said they saw milosh wondering around
Should we go ahead and turn back I mean he might still be in town right
Milos
Hey Michelle
It's all right everything is fine
Why don't you come back over here huh
Did your best
Tried to clear my name didn't you
I'm so lucky to have a friend like you there's
Nothing to worry about
We go
Things all right
This good doctor tema
Am I doing it right
It's been better if I've been crying
They never bothered to teach me
Such a difficult emotion
Why did you do that
Milos what's wrong what did you see
What happened to Milos what did you witness
Why did you find out tonight
Milosh
Listen to me
I know that you have no mother
But son
Listen
We're definitely born for a reason I want you to know that Milo she were brought into this world because somebody
He wanted you to be here
Definitely
We definitely wanted you here I mean it
Telling the truth
Not wrong am I
No you're not
What expression do I have
On my face right now
You're cry