Why are you crying
It's just my friend's letter
My very best friend
When I was 15
The two of us decided to cross the check border together
But my friend was captured
And she was taken back to Prague
She says she's doing fine
She's been such a good friend
She knows me better than my parents do
Or even my siblings
With the government's tough inspections and censorship
Who knows what she went through to get this to me
She
Please visit me if you have the chance
I miss you so much my friend
Near cheddock Bridge
Inside the three frogs
I want to go back
Oh my
Just for tonight
I want you to call me by my real name
I am
Helenka Novak
For tonight I'm no longer Margo Langer
I sold my stock Holdings and Razer Burger Pharmaceuticals at the right time and then when I bought some
Talking neuter Laboratories
But I really hit the jackpot
Well I wanted to celebrate so I did
So you had a drink
Sure just a little
That wasn't too smart
All I had was wondering what an alcoholic like yourself that was a foolish choice you made
In your case it doesn't matter if you drink a little or a lot
Another thing that concerns me is it seems you stopped going to your group meetings as well
So
By the way
You can keep a secret right
I've got this special woman I want you to meet
Have you gone and found yourself another mistress
Not really look this one's got a serious issue with alcohol
She's waiting just outside could you see her for a minute
I don't do counseling that way
Have her make an appointment to see me
Come on just see her for a few minutes
I'm making a house call next
For a very important client
I took a few days and went to Prague in the Czech Republic
I found it a very nice city to visit
I saw Prague Castle
Oh and the wonderful Gothic cathedrals
It's such a beautiful place when the Old Town Plaza is all lit up
It's just like a land out of a fairy tale
What about sheddock Bridge
Did you go and visit the chetak bridge I did
Exactly as you told me to do
Here it is
See I took a picture of the sign with the three frogs
And the woman was she there
No sir in fact no one was living there
Unfortunately I didn't find any useful information for you by going there
It was so frustrating
I didn't find Tenma
Or any good leads on Dieter and Nina
Here
Take this
It's a rabbit's foot
It's for good luck
Now listen
Please give it to our child after it's born
Margo
No
Helen
You must know
I thank you
Excuse me ma'am
I've come from Germany and I'm searching for a missing woman who might have lived around here a while ago
Do you know young woman by the name of Margo Langer
Wait sorry her real name was helenka novakova
Helenka
Anyway Mr schewald
Your son Carl recently gave me a call
He expressed some concerns to me about the fact that you haven't been eating properly
I classify that experience you had at the library fire as traumatic
A near-death experience can change one's life you know
I sense that paralyzing fear still hasn't left you
But you're very blessed to have Carl here with you
He's a wonderful thoughtful and loving son
You really have nothing more to worry about
Please do try to eat regularly won't you
The monster
As long as that monster exists
It's so difficult
How did he know so much about Margo
Where could he have obtained all that information
He knew much more than Carla I did
Years ago Margo told me of this girlfriend she had who knew her even better than her own siblings
Your parents
I remember that conversation
This was the woman who Margo exchanged letters with now in the 1980s you began to search for Margo
At that time had gone missing
You went to Prague and actually met that woman didn't you
I did
Considering she was supposed to be Margo's best friend I assume that woman might have heard something from her
I was wrong
She said she didn't know where Margo was
But for a while we did talk quite a bit about Margo as we stood in the door
And that's when
They were listening
Listening in on every word
Who do you mean that quietly listen to what we said they stood behind the woman
Absorbing it all those twins
Yes
Come in
Welcome have a seat
You're the young lady Mr thalbach wanted me to see aren't you and you're a compulsive drinker
Please just relax today all we're going to do here is have ourselves a nice friendly chat
What is it Meredith can't you see I'm right in the middle of a session
Excuse me for a second repeating or breaking news story check police have Ann
He's a witness and possible suspect in the poisoning of three doctors at dusseldorf's Isler Memorial Hospital
He may also be connected with the murders of the journalist Maurer and the Fortner couple in Heidelberg and the Phantom killing at
Heidelberg Castle
For now these are all the details we had him the police
I'm here
Miss heinemann
Cancel
I'm sorry for being late everyone
Why Mr Hess you look 10 years younger
Playing with my grandchildren is keeping me young
Huber how you been
Fine
I'm actually finishing up my final Academic Year
I hear you're pretty busy too Mr Kiefer
I was bragging about you saying how I'm friends with a screenwriter who's going to
I just happened to catch the eye of a producer who has a big imagination
My first story idea is in development in my mind's brimming with new plot lines
You're on your way no that's surgery saved my life
If my surgery hadn't been a success I wouldn't be here to hear you laughter
Thanks to him
And I never would have walked in the park with my grandchildren
Think of that
Right there
He always sat over there by himself drinking his tea
Other doctors went to nicer cafes but he came here
Because it was closest to Eisler Memorial Hospital
And when we patience would come in here
He would look at us as he sat there
And smile at us
He was the kindest doctor
Yes
A great doctor like him
He would never do this no
And that's the reason why I've gathered all of us here today
The others who aren't here said they feel the same as we do
After all they were doctor 10 most patients too
Bad news Dr Schumann Mr Merkel just collapsed sir
I'll be right over but I'm busy at the moment you better go and wait for me there all right
Really
Dr Tim I wouldn't do those things calm down and listen to me Mom
Please dear go to him quickly
Picture I can't just
Don't you give me any butts Dr Tema has been charged with a crime he didn't commit
If he hadn't been around you know I wouldn't be alive right now
My dear Dr Schumann are you so heartless that you don't want to help the man who saved your wife's life
Then what will happen here
You know darn well I'm the only doctor in this Village
What will happen to everyone that lives around here if I go and leave town
You want to go don't you quit your blabbering and get going right now Dr Tim I need your help
I took an oath and if there's a patient who needs me I can't just leave him
That's the way Dr Tema would have behaved
Please doctor would you see us now
Be patient I need a little more time
Don't want to hurry up
Stop your whining the doctor is taking a big risk by practicing without a license while she's going to school
When you're in the darkness you only sink deeper into it
Keep the lights shiny
You've got a real gift for this you'll make a fine doctor
All right I'm ready to start now whoever's first come in
Lawyer right
But father wait
We still have no way of knowing exactly where in Germany Tema will be sent then we'll have to retain a lawyer that
Like to defend him in any of the German states get us the best criminal attorney
Yes sir we must have 10 I have the feeling that he is the only
One who can do it he's the only one who can get rid of the monster
We need strength in numbers
Well let's try calling in more of doctor tennis former patients
As individuals what we say may not matter much
But as a group we might just that's right
Let's ask Isley Memorial Hospital for helping getting organized and we could ask them for funding too forget it
That's impossible
Isler Memorial Hospital is not about to help you with something like that
Hey
I've been listening to all of you and it's quite a touching story
Really
But come on folks
Be realistic about the situation
How's the doctor Tema fan club going to prove his innocence
Dr Becker it's you you know Tim I had no alibi and unfortunately he did have a motive
The police even came out and said they found physical evidence at the scene of the crime
Even if you hire a brilliant lawyer to defend him
And you gather a ton of people to make a lot of noise it's not going to help
No matter what you folks do on Doctor 10 most behalf
It's impossible to prove that he's innoc
I do ask you
Anyway
It's a real shame about his career
Yeah
It's a real shame I'm going to ask you again Ava
What's your relationship to Tenma
Look Miss heinemann I don't know who you are in all of this but I'm on this train because
Cuz I mean to save doctor Tenma so I don't want you coming along if you're here just to do some sightseeing
Ava Heineman
Heinemann Miss Heineman
Could it be that you are are you the daughter
Dr heinemann the murder director of that hospital in Dusseldorf
Dr tema
He had quite an effect on me you see he destroyed my life
And yet
I'm the only one
Hooking really save him now
I saw so what
Dr Kenzo t
Prime suspect in the serial murders in Dusseldorf and Heidelberg is still in custody in Prague
However
Officials have said he will be extradited to Germany as soon as possible
He will most likely
Is it possible
This is Dr Tenma
He's the one who saved your life sick you're alive right now because of his first aid treatment
It turns out Dr 10 was also been framed for a crime he never committed
I guess you two are in the same situation huh
Save my life
He's going to the same ordeal as me
You're a detective aren't you act like it
You have to calmly dissect and scrutinize everything there is really only one way to prevent yourself
From being betrayed all you have to do is doubt the person you believe in the most
I've got to go
I've got to get to the Prague police station and talk to 10:00 no matter what it takes
There you are sick
Well then
Detective project
Please listen to me you don't have to run away anymore
My God you must have gone through a lot
You've been exonerated Sook
The letter was sent to the station
This is a copy of
A letter
It's a handwritten confession
It has details of the events that only the killer would know
So you've been cleared of all suspicion
Who sent that letter
A journalist who goes by the name of Grimmer
Did you say grandma
Yeah Grandma's been put on our most wanted list he's now our chief suspect
Wait just hold on a second relax you're in the clear
Inspector zamons murder the head Chiefs poisoning and the shooting of the two special team members that had tailed you back
Back to your apartment
All those crimes are now solved
Well chief
Was doing some sightseeing
Give me a break
Stupid
What are you talking about
Quit the ACT
Oh
Are you talking about Dr tema's arrest
You know it didn't
10 mobile will be arriving at Dusseldorf tomorrow at 2:00 p.m.
Since you're in charge of this case you'll need to meet the check police to take him into custody
Dispatch someone else to take care of it
Prague is a very nice place
Please understand sir right now
I'm still on vacation
Now let me see Dr Tenma
As I've been telling you sir you cannot see him
And why not I thought this country is supposed to be a democracy doctor Tenma is already in the process
Stop being extradited to Germany I just need to see him for a minute
We came on that way for nothing all that time and effort what a stupid waste let me see him
I'm begging you
On your feet
Come with us
When we interrogate people what type of person do you think
The hardest time
People who remain expressionless no matter what we say to them
People who don't say anything at all
That's the hardest kind
A love letter from the monster to the beauty
This appears to be a draft for a novel
I've been watching you
I wanted to devour you whole
But instead
Everything about you consume me when I was falling apart how
How did I look to you
When I was falling apart the object you gave me
You left me a beautiful Jewel
Those twins who look as if they are blessed with eternal life
The most sinful deed is to take away a person's name let's get your name back
I'll give you your name back your name is Anna
Right now I'm sad sad sad
Sad
It exists
There are many people that met their end in that room
And then a horrific monster was born