My Consciousness awoke inside a coin Locker
In complete darkness
Blue
The blue skies the blue sea
And the blue window frame
I want to go to Tunisia
Gunter Mills arrested in 1988
For attacking a bearish on this Bank cash transport vehicle placed in buddenberg prison to serve time
I'm in 1991 devised a means of Escape it's been 6 months filing through the iron bars of a cell with a large
Nail sharpen into a file he was caught three days later and sent a Criner prison in 19
93 Escape through a drainage pipe prison issued garments soaked in sewage were found on a nearby River
Soon arrested again for the attempted robbery of a Maximilian and company payroll delivery truck
In 97 broke out of ingeborg prison through a hole in a shower stall spent a year digging and Escape Route with a
The toilets in this place stink pretty bad
Escape through a sewer once so you better believe I know what I'm talking about
Talk about looking down and out eyes forward
Yeah if I'm not mistaken that's Dr 10 keep walking pal
I never imagined that fella would be looking so hopeless and pathetic
I'll ask you one more time
The poisoning of Dr Heineman director of Isler Memorial Hospital Dr oppenheim chief of
And Dr Boyer in 1986
Confirm or deny it which is it going to be
From the beginning of this interrogation you haven't uttered a single word
Cut the crap 10 Ma
What is this going to accomplish
The prosecution will go forward whether you keep silent or not
And you don't stand a chance in court
Why not talk to us
Come on why don't you make things easier for yourself
What's going on what's Happening down there looks
Pretty bad no she's got severe stomach pains hey
Dr Dueler
Has anybody seen Dr Dueler he's in the examination room
Apparently Peter drank some kind of cleaning fluid I'm heading over there now
This is bad it sounds to me like you might be choking on something what
I can't bre
Oh man
Guess we have no choice but to ask him
Tenma the doctor
Think you can take a look at them talk
Does this hurt
And what about here I'm going to need plenty of hot water towels and fresh sheets
Get out of the room this could be contagious
Why don't you pretend to be sick
Come on show me a little Mercy
I must be losing my touch you're the first doctor to see through my ex so fast
I had it all figured out
If I got sent to the hospital I'd have a better chance to escape do you know what I do when I want to rob an armored truck
I jump out in front of the vehicle and pretend to be very sick
When the guards run out of the truck in a panic then my friend pops up with an automatic weapon and threatens to shoot him
I've never really killed anybody myself
That's where you and me kind of differ
So how about it
What do you say we escaped together
You've already got the look of a man who's never getting out of here
But if you stay in this dump it'll suck the life right out of you
I despise cramped spaces like this crappy little Rat Hole
My Consciousness awoke inside a coin Locker
And that total darkness my mom and pop would put me there while they went off to work
I waited in that Darkness for them to come and take me home each night
Let's go to Tunisia someday that's what they'd always talk about
If I would say if today goes well we're going to Tunisia
But three days went by
And they didn't return
Mom and pop just left me
They probably went to Tunisia by themselves
That's the place to live
As soon as I blow this joint and I'm out of these I'm going to Tunisia
You're a real mess you know that you look like a guy who's got nothing left
I live for
Unlike me I got plenty of goals
What will you do if they catch you again
I'll just escape again keep on doing it
No matter how long it takes
Now then
I suppose this is going to be just Another Day of Silence
The truth of the matter
It's even as we speak right now terrible things are happening
So I have to tell the truth
You won't believe it
You won't believe a word I say
But that won't stop me I have to keep fighting
And I'll keep on doing it no matter how long it takes
Over and over again
I'll tell you nothing but the truth
This court hereby sentence is the defendant to 20 years in prison
My path in life was chosen on that fateful day when my father was found guilty
After the war my father moved from Sudan land Czechoslovakia to Germany starting a small radio station
In there in 1949 but in the 60s during the Cold war between East and West Germany he was arrested
Did for being a spy and for the murder of a federal politician's secretary this news shocked the West
My father proclaimed his innocence but was convicted to 20 years in prison my
My mother believed in my father's innocence until her death in 1971 my father filled with sorrow
When regret died in prison a year later in 1972
In 1973
While I was in the gymnasium my father's innocence was proven
After graduating from Dusseldorf University I joined the large firm of Hoffman law
In my first case I defied expectations and prove the innocence of a falsely accused defendant
One after another
My victories in the courtroom continue to grow
Fritz verdeman wants the son of a spy and now a hero in the legal world
Over the Rainbow
Everyday the broadcast of my father's radio station would begin and end with that song
I see
Both you and my father lived in the east
So this song must have symbolized the Free World to you
Yes
My father died before he was able to prove his innocence
To honor his memory
I want to be involved in as many cases as possible where the person standing trial may be falsely accused
I want you to tell me everything you know
About Dr Timmy's case
Elsa
How did your prenatal exam go what did they say
Everything's fine the doctor said to expect the baby any day now
Did you pass a man in the lobby on your way up
Yes
Is he the one you mentioned earlier
He
A man by the name of Alfred ball
He asked me if I wanted to team up with him on the doctor Tim the murder case
Well if I remember correctly you already refused to take Doctor Thomas case
But at the time I was being solicited by Hans gay org shuval
And it wasn't made clear to me then why I was being asked by that business tycoon to be the doctor's legal counsel
However the reasons Mr ball had were all perfectly clear
What were they
Every one of Mr Ball's clients was a former patient of Dr Tenma
And he'd save the lives of all of them before he went on the Run
And now I'm certain about one thing
Dr timma was a well-respected and highly skilled surgeon
So are you taking the case
Yes but if I had made that decision when the billionaire was footing the bill we could have made quite a nice profit
I doubt these patients will be able to pay nearly as much
Then you'd have a much larger firm by now
How about that
It's playing your song Honey
Please turn it off
Just turn it off please
How about we go out and get ourselves some dinner
Carrying around another life must make you pretty hungry we better make sure you order enough food for two
The baby always kicks when it gets to be dinner time
So dear what restaurant would you like to go to tonight
How about that place we saw last week
And then he just
Disappeared into the blazing fire
And that was the very last time
I ever saw Johan
Do you want me to start my story from the beginning one more time
Because I'm going to keep on telling the truth
Over and over as long as it takes
You're the fourth one you know
The other three wanted to represent me all had the same suggestion that I should confess to some of the charges
Admit to part of the crimes to lighten my sentence
That's all they wanted to talk about
I'd assumed as much
It seems to me you don't really care too deeply about proving your innocence
You apparently would rather spend your time proving the existence of a certain young man named Johann
Yes that's right
Legal expertise won't help with that
Dr Tenma
When did these events all start happening like I've been saying when a boy with a gunshot wound to the head was brought into the
No but something must have happened before that so what was it
A Turkish woman was yelling at me
But human lives are created equal
Was what I did back then
Really the right thing to have done I just don't know
There's no way of telling if a patient is good
More evil
My only crime is that I went ahead and saved the life of a little boy
I don't know
But
The doctor's even have the right to choose who they treat based on the quality of a patient's soul
People's lives aren't created equal they are always cool I can explain it
But I know that it's the truth it's the same way with lawyers
We can't tell what kind of a person the accused is
Here's a list of names of the people who asked me to represent you in these legal proceedings doctor
Mr McHale hotter Mr Stephen Crump
Also Mr Franz Kiefer
And Mr Rudolph Huber
Mr key for Mr hub
Glad to know they're fun Mr Horst henschel Mr Harmon Hess Mr Hess as well
It's good to hear
I hope he's enjoying his grandkids there is whole world
Time's up thank goodness for that they're all okay
Dr tinla I will accept your case I'll represent you
You know lawyers can't tell what's inside a client's heart either
There's only one thing we can do when we represent someone
Try to have faith in him
One more
Didn't you hear me I said one more man you've had enough
Since one of those bars are refusing a service Bus customer
Hey you just laughed at me didn't you
No
Not at all yes you did you looked over me with a big laugh
Hey hey I know you
You are always there
Coming to our house with your head in your hand groveling you're the vice branch manager at nordrine West
Don't give me that look
I can drink here if I damn well wanna
Whether you like it or not Eva Heineman has returned home to Dusseldorf
You've certainly brought me a wealth of important information
Thank you Dr Wright
Listen I've been trying to reach you ever since I heard the doctor Tenma had retained you to represent him
I'm sorry you had so much trouble
I've been out investigating everywhere
Investigating
That's right
I've been meeting with the former patients of Dr Tenma who hired me on in this case
Did you learn anything
Well just that they think he's wonderful and that they owe their lives to him
Yes but did you get any evidence that would be useful
Not really
I'm hoping to find a witness or someone who can provide Dr Ten though with an alibi
In my opinion to establish tenema's innocence we need to prove to the world that Johan actually exists
Listen Dr Reich
What
Regarding that part about Dr Tenma planning to shoot that young man named Johann
When you're called to testify please omit that
But wait a minute my testimony about his plan is all we have to prove there is a Johann whether or not Johan exist
Best doctor Tenma is innocent
Please hear me out Dr Wright Vine
The country wants this case closed so any scapegoat will do right now
My child will be born soon
I want him to live in a world where True Justice exists
Judges and prosecutors want to bring matters to a close quickly
In order to do so they carelessly rush to condemn innocent people
As guilty
It's high time this country repented for its lack of True Justice
And that's what's most important
Well Dr reichvine yes
That's right
Anyhow I'm looking for a particular witness at the moment
She might know something which could prove vital to Dr tennis defense
At least I hope so
Who is she
None other than my client's former fiance
Miss Ava Heineman
Is something wrong Dr reichfind you look surprised
She's here in town
She came here with me I guess she's decided to move back
But that woman
They were laughing
Every last one of them was laughing
They just give me one look and start in
Ava
Are you listening to me quit bugging me you're so annoying
Just meet with the lawyer won't you do at least that for 10 more
Please
Your memory is kind of shot grams
I told you before I tried to shoot him once but I couldn't pull it off
I remember that quite well but I was surprised to hear it
But you didn't go through with shooting him
That's right I didn't shoot him
Do you know why
It's because I can't have him die on me yet
That man ruined my life a fast death would be too easy I want him to rotten jail for eternity to make
Make him regret it I'm going to lock him up for the rest of his life he'll be sorry he left me when I'm through with him
Yeah maybe then he'll regret that he dumped me
Passed out again
You were asleep you must have had a bad dream
Shots from the gun
I didn't say
I didn't
Didn't see it
Blonde haired man
Who did you see did you see Johanna that night
Over the Rainbow
The song that symbolizes a great free world for all
Your wife's gone into labor
She's been taking to the hospital Mr Vermont
What
I've got to be there Mr Cleaner contact Mr ball immediately
Ask him if he'll be able to meet with Dr Tenma in my place because I'm having a baby
Nice to meet you
I'm Alfred ball
Mr verdeman asked me if I could come meet with you today
How are you doing
Getting enough sleep in this place
I guess
Well that's good
I used to be right-handed actually
I'm still having a little trouble adjusting to holding a pen in my left right
You see
My right hand doesn't work too well anymore
Perhaps you remember me now
I know
Lost quite a bit of weight
Yep I got to admit I even impressed myself
To think that I was able to escape that sea of smoking fire
You call me by surprise when you actually shot me
No it's kind of funny I can't seem to hold pens worth a damn but
And I'm able to handle a gun just fine to tell you the truth I'm thinking of killing
I'm thinking of killing your former fiance the lovely Ava he