Tell Elaine and Gustav that I'm counting on them to tape detective Forester the crime drama on television right now
It's my favorite show I'm addicted the reruns are on at 10:00 on Tuesday morning
Tune in you might learn something
Come on Miss will you get serious
You shouldn't be kidding around right now
The boss isn't happy with
You're sloppy work
Do you have any idea how much
Trouble you caused by screwing up and getting yourself caught
Despite the fact that you are a complete idiot the boss still sent me here to be your legal coun
So how about showing him a bit of grat
Come on who do you think you're kidding you're here to keep an eye on me so I don't spill the beans right
I won't deny it
Listen up news
I presume you are aware of what would happen if you were to
Well aren't you
What are you so worried about I never read on any of my buddies
That's very smart
I need you to stick to the scenario that I laid out for you and confess all right
So is my next job been decided
I kind of like to prepare for it
What do you mean next job
Given your present situation you won't be getting out of prison anytime soon
Yeah how can you be so sure
Think about it did you forget who I am I'm going to Mills king of prison escapes
I'm getting way behind
So just stop the nonsense
If you follow the blueprint I'm drawing up and confess
You'll get out in about 5 years
I told you to tell Elaine and Gustav to tape detective Forster while I'm in lockup
Yeah but they're not very reliable are they
I may have to try it one more time
I'm still at this station jail house
Try what
Are you sure he's not just faking it again I don't know he's hard to figure but I did see blood in his
Vomit and you can feel his body is really cold hey don't throw up in the hallway
Oh you came just in time I'm glad you're here keep an eye on this place for a bit they just brought in a few Young
Punctuate berserk on the third floor some people were injured so I need to get up there right away
Looks like he's going to die at any moment
You back again just put him on a bed over there I'll take a look at him later
You better get me to hospital right away before I die
You'll be fine I won't be gone long
Damn all of a sudden it's getting busy in here today
Give me a break you can't put me next to a serial killer I know my rights I demand another bed why is he even
Stop complaining milch that man's refused his meals and collapsed from starvation
He's hooked up to an IV I'm feeling a lot worse just being next to him see
Just lie there and be quiet doctor you said some people were injured do you have any idea how many
That's what I'll find out as soon as I get there wait till I get my hands on them those punks are going to do hard time when
I've been thinking about what you said the other day
Need you to help me
I have to get out of here
I'm thinking of killing
I'm thinking of killing your former fiance
The lovely Eva Heine
So what do you think personally I like the
The idea very much you know she's dangerous
She knows a little more than she should
That Rainy Night at the building the one under construction
She heard three distinct gun
And she saw someone as well
It was
No we don't need people like her complicating things
We really don't don't you agree oh yeah
You can't
It's not an option
She'll only Testify the things that will hurt me do you understand so so
That's why you need to take a little more time to consider my idea she'll be out of the way once and for all
And you may not have to go to prison if she's not on the witness stand
This could be very good for both of us
Elimination is the winning choice no matter how you look at
I mean what other options do you have
If you go to the police they won't believe you and accused murder
What are you going to do tell Mr verdeman
I wouldn't
I mean think about it he could be one of us who really knows
We'll make sure you're found innocent after all that's what we brilliant defense
And once you're free and moved out of this place you should have yourself a drink to celebrate
Just by that time that miserable stuck up loudmouth b**** will be long gone from this world never
Ever to be seen again
I want to
I'm allergic I can't sleep with this serial murder
Pregnant milk
Hey knock it off
They'll be moving me out of this holding station in 5 days because I'm going to confess then it's goodbye forever
Cereal murders like you what's all the rocket for huh pretty fast recovery yeah
Just another one of your fake out
I'm going to be rid of you in 5 days I'm done looking at your miserable face you're a real
So work milch I'm not already
Just five more days to go
So on that particular Rainy Night
From inside of building under construction you heard three gunshots
And soon afterwards saw a young blonde man come hurrying down the stairs
Is that correct Ms Heineman
That's right
Now what's the plan
Are you still proceeding with the case and denying Johan's existence
I don't know
Listen Miss Heine
If I called upon you would you be willing to testify to this in open court
No I would not
What did Dr Tima possibly want this late at night would you kindly tell us what
What this is all about well I don't exactly know
He just asked to see you right away
So what did you want to talk to us about Dr Tenma
It dusseldorf's Isler Memorial Hospital there was
The director Dr heinemann
The chief of surgery Dr oppenheim and then Dr Boyer as well
Along with one Adolph Younkers
What's a patient of mine at the time
It was me I confess
I killed every one of them
Hard
The bottle fell over
Sandwiches were covered in dirt that's when he
Smiled so sadly
According to this announcement made by the police
Murder suspect Kensington conf
Shortly before Dawn
Up until now he had relentlessly kept silent about all the charges against
Now in regard to the killing of the director of Isler Memorial Hospital in Dusseldorf and two other doctors
As well as the murder of Adolf Jun
He has admitted
He committed these
But that can't be
This is breaking news
Shortly
Kensington who had previously maintained total Silence about the charges
Surprised authorities with his unexpected confession to the string of serial kill
I want the truth
Hey what the hell did you idiots do to 10
What method of torture did you subject him to in order to obtain that false confession huh
Please take your hand off me and calm down
I'll talk to him myself and find out what kind of treatment to receive during his questioning useless Dr Wright fine
I've already tried he won't even see me his own lawyer
It would appear that his confession was completely voluntary without any coercion
But that's impossible
I did a little research it turns out that his interrogators are men I know personally
And these are men who would never condone the use of torture
Tim must summon them both when he made his declaration
Then he proceeded to willingly admit his guilt
Wait Mr verdeman
You're actually suggesting his confession to the murders is genuine
How can I even begin to tell what he intended when he won't meet with me
Mr verdeman
You've Got to Believe
Dr Tema didn't commit murder
I still believe he's innocent
Hello this is verdeman
Oh
Mr ball
That's all right
How did it go
No
He refused to have anything to do with me what can I say I'm stunned
Here we are in the middle of an effort to prove is complete innocence
Working hard to get them to drop all the charges they have against him
Then he breaks down on fully confesses
No matter how unbearable he's interrogation God
He never once capitulated
Your father held steadfast was innocence
So then
Any idea of what we should do now to help out Tim
Person who can prove Dr temma's innocence
What did you say her name was
Ava Heineman
Where is she
She's staying at a local hotel
I'd certainly like to meet her and hear what she has to say
Well
She can be a pretty difficult lady
I think for now I'll try meeting with her again myself
Where you admirable father
Miss heinemann it's Fritz verdemon
Could you open the door I'd like to speak to you for a moment
Look you might as well let me in I know perfectly well you're in there drinking because the maid's been trying to get in all day to tidy up the
Place
Miss Heineman
I fully understand that you have reasons to despise Dr T
Your father's death was a big loss for you to Bear but if your relationship with tinma had continued it would have helped
Heal the pain of
Event and major life easier
When he broke off your relationship you felt very alone
Your life was thrown into turmoil
And you blamed Tenma for that
I'll tell you about my father
They sentenced him to 20 years for Espionage and murder for a very long time I was
It's called son of a spy fingers were pointed at me and I was shunned
My father's actions through my life into turmoil
But all that stuff didn't really bother me
Would you like to know why
Would you like to know how I was able to endure and keep on fighting it was because I believe
I truly believed
My father is innocent
She was innocent
He was innocent
For me to represent someone I must first believe they are truly innocent I'm going to prove
I'm leaving you phone numbers for my partner and myself
When you're ready to testify please give us a call
What are you saying he's being transported to the Detention Center tomorrow he's only been here a few days why is he being rushed
That is standard police procedure after someone willing
Well can't we do something to delay at Mr verdeman
No she went out for all I know she's probably gone off to get drunk at some bar again
Tissotor
I remember all these places nothing has changed
I despise this town
Oh did you just get here
I've been sitting here staring at you for the last 5 minutes oh sorry but I've never seen anything more interesting than this book
I just had to write some of it down
Do you want to go somewhere else to get a bite to eat
Maybe you'd like some kind of foreign cuisine
Italian might be good
How about French where would you like to go you name it don't let me tear you away from your book
Why don't you just keep on reading I didn't mean to AV
This sandwich
Is the best thing you brought your appetite
Pretty good huh
What are you doing
Holding it down
I'm putting a rock on the edge of the blanket so it won't blow away in the Wind
That wasn't what I meant I'm wondering why you're putting down a blanket at all
It's fun having lunch out here every once in awhile
And the weather is nice too
And who would be having this lunch
The two of us of course I made my favorite sandwiches I hope you like them
There are bugs everywhere
It'll be all right
I've all got dirt on them now
I'm afraid they're ruin
You look hungry do you want this
Franz don't bother the lady
Here thank you
Hasty huh
Start walking
End of the truck
Oh hello
This is Eva Heineman
I'm having trouble reaching Mr Vermont no one's answering his phone
That's why I'm calling you
Please feel free to discuss
You like with me
Well there is a matter I'd like to discuss
And what is that may I ask appearing in court to testify to tema's innocence
Oh I
Well we're very grateful to hear that
Where are you staying at the moment
Yeah I've written down the address
I should be over to your hotel in a couple of minutes