Oh that Mansion go right up the street you should be able to find it
I appreciate it
Thank you
You're welcome
Roses just like the
Sleeping Beauty
It's Anna my name is Anna Liebert
You go get him Mr Detective
It's because she was worried that something awful might happen to you I don't want you to get hurt
I care about you too
Were you dreaming just now
Detective
Hold on
Who are you
Inspector lung
I work out of the German bka office
What do you want with me calm down
You don't have to get up relax
Nobody sent me to arrest you
I haven't even met with anyone in your division
You've been assigned a very nice room
I went to several hospitals that had connections to the former Czechoslovakian secret police before finding this one
And judging by your excellent care
You must be a pretty important person
To the Czechoslovakian secret police am I right
Please believe me I know everything you've been up to since you joined the Prague division
Inspector Zaman who at close ties of the secret police was beaten to death
The Prague station Chief into detectives were killed with poison whiskey bonbons
To investigators from a special task force who were tailing you
Were found shot
And at the moment
You're being pursued as the most likely suspect in all of these cases
If you were to be judged on circumstantial evidence alone
Then you'd be the murderer no I'm not
I'm completely innocent
Then what about that thin lanky fellow named Grimmer who inspectors aimon brought in for questioning the day before his murder
Mr Grimmer didn't kill anybody either he's not that kind of person so then who is the killer
Don't you know him
Don't you know who the murderer is
What is this
What are you talking about
If I knew who it was this wouldn't be happening to me
My God
So many people have stabbed me in the back
Now I find myself being framed for murder
And all the police want to do is lock me up
I've had enough of this damn it I'm so tired of being betrayed
You're a detective aren't you
Act like it you have to calmly dissect and scrutinize everything
Dig up the truth is rationally as you can
Even if you have to sacrifice your own happiness in the process
There is really only one way to prevent yourself from being betrayed
All you have to do is doubt the person you believe in the most
Who the hell said you had permission to be here
I want a meeting with your boss tell him I want to talk to him about
The red rose Mansion it's safe to say you'll want to meet with me right away
Inspector Lungi of the bka
I ran a background check
Dug up some of your past
I heard about your past too when the old regime was in power captain lanke
And now you are for all intents and purposes leader of the Czechoslovakian secret police
That's quite a position
Seems to be some trouble attached to you at the moment
Why thank you for your concern
I'm envious of people in your position who can take such long vacations
2 years ago wasn't it
You're Relentless ways drove the Secretary of Mr boltzmann a candidate to lead the German Democratic Party
Suicide
You have to be a lot smarter than that to move up in the world
You and your people were quite foolish
During the democratization if you had taken a softer approach and managed your secrecy you could have been the ones
Trolling the president's actions behind the scenes
However
Now the fear that people feel towards you and your men is merely an illusion with no basis in fact
So I see
You are quite clever
You asked to see me
So what does a clever man like you want
An answer
As you already know I'm on a long vacation but it's not entirely just a pleasure trip
I'm here looking for something
I'm looking for an embodiment of true fear
I want to find out if a real demon was born in that illusion that you created during the
The reign of the old regime you're referring to the Rose Mansion aren't you
I found it but before I got there I wandered around quite a bit
The man who wrote this picture book years ago use many pen names
The name he used when he wrote the nameless monster
Was a meal share Bay
His address was a room and an old building in Prague
At the moment
Someone else is renting that room
As Klaus Pope he lived on a farm deep in the countryside
But that place is already been torn down
The yakup far back name only led me to a rented office
But you didn't stop there did you
You finally arrived
Franz bought a partis
Strange place to live
The rose mansion
Franz Bonaparte
I wanted to know who he was
No matter how hard I searched I wasn't able to turn up anything on him that could only mean one thing that Bon
Florida was one of you that he's a former member of the Czechoslovakian secret police tell me what it is
That's simple
I want to know everything you know
I know nothing however however
There is something
I've consciously been trying to forget
And that is the fact that the rose mansion ever existed at all
I've avoided thinking about it that's why it still stands there empty and untouched all of
The political prisoners who were taken there as well as the entire research staff just disappeared one night
I swear that's all I know
What's the reason for the plastered wall
What wall I went in yesterday there was no sign of anyone setting foot in there the
The Mansion was completely unoccupied and looked to have been abandoned for some time but the north wall
All in the second floor it looks like it was coated with plaster as though someone was trying to conceal something
With your permission
I'd like to tear that wall down
Captain Lincoln
What are you afraid of I'm afraid you might die
If you get any closer you and I may end up facing an unimaginable experience
A true fear
Friends Bonaparte
Goodness haven't heard that name in a while
Would you like milk and sugar in your coffee
Black is just fine thank you
What's the matter
Well
To tell you the truth I'm surprised that a friend's born apart a fan has just suddenly shown up
I got your name from the Moravia Publishing Company
It is my understanding that you were Mr bonaparte's editor for several years
Is that right Mr zob
It is
I guided him and helped him as his edit
But that was only when he was writing under the pen name Klaus pop
I wonder if you can tell me more about him
Like what kind of person he was
He would come here to my home
We would discuss his work and sometimes rewrite sections of it
Oh yes it's sitting that chair in the same position you're in now
Often he would take a break and play in the garden with my daughter
I didn't think anything of it at the time
But my daughter said something
She said Papa that man is
Of course she was very young and now she's a full grown adult
I'm sure she's forgotten all about it
At that time could he have possibly been working for a government agency
Well
Probably
I did assume that but it was never discussed
However there was something about him
I guess it was his manners the way he spoke the clothes he wore
And the kindness that seemed out of place from the officials of the old regime
Bonaparta was a practicing psychiatrist
And also a medical doctor
He specialized in neurosurgery
I see
I'm trying to remember his last visit
It was a summer of 81 or 82 I believe
I recall that he just showed up here one day without any warning
He wanted to talk about a new book
Oh my goodness
How happy he appeared to be at the time
The new book
What was it about
Well it was about a monster Falling in Love
It was strange it was almost like a combination of Beauty and the Beast and Sleeping Beauty
Of course I vetoed it on the spot
Then at the door as he was preparing to say goodbye he just stopped and
Said maybe you like this better then he turned to look me in the eye
It's a story about a door that must not be opened under any circumstances
I asked him if Paradise was on the other side
If a monster would come through the door and he said no
You can't open the door
So I guess there's no story he left when he said that and then he was gone
And that was the last time I ever saw him
So doctor Tenma were you able to find out anything interesting or helpful about bonaparta
A little but not as much as I hoped
Mr Grimmer what are you doing here have you been following me around perhaps
I'm just sitting here enjoying the sunny weather
It's nice
You can say that again
I knew it was him
Is this the police department
My name is Joe Buck I live on schweig court in a private residence a suspicious man just left my home
Well I'm pretty certain he's the primary suspect in the serial murders that occurred in Germany
Yes he's Japanese
He looks like that neurosurgeon Dr temma
Ethanol
The smell of disinfectant
Nick dick
Death
How many people died here
I guess
A lot more
I've seen that woman before
She's the one from the Sketchbook could she be the mother of
Twins
Hurry up or the older boys will take over the field first
Come on Milo hurry up I am hurrying
Fall back no one's defending the girl we're going to score
Oh man are
All right
A really nice day below you defended the Google good job evolution
He seems to be happy
He's all right now isn't
Well Dr Tenma
What do you think
He's fine
Mr Grimmer wait up
Don't you want to spend some time with me lotion the other children
I suddenly realized why I'm not really all that good at soccer
I guess it has to do with playing as a team
I'm just thinking about what lies ahead for detective so
He's the prime suspect in a murder which means his career is over and his future is pretty much washed up as well
Sad
Even if you were to turn himself in how's he going to be able to prove that he's innocent
And how is he going to find any evidence to verify that the blonde lady I saw leaving his place even exists
Souks in a similar situation to the one you're in
Except for him there's one big difference
What
Time for us to say goodbye doctor Tenma
Only one person knows it all
Everything concerning the events incriminating detective Sook
You're looking at him
Here give it a read
I think the police will be very interested when they get it
What is this
Just a letter written by the perpetrator of the recent series of killings
I even mentioned details the police haven't released I think it'll make a very compelling case for my being the real murderer
What if you send something like this to the police will be arrested
Oh but before that can happen Grimmer will suddenly disappear
The police will be Swift
The Grimmer will have already made His Brilliant escape to Germany say
After all
He used to be a pretty good spy you could slip his way out of tight spots think about it
You'll have no life you'll be forced to live on the run I'll be fine
The truth of the matter is Grimmer never really existed in the first place it's not who I am it's just
What's the name I was arbitrarily assigned one day so even if Grimmer is a suspect for the rest of his life
The real me is unaffected well anyway what do you think of my letter
Do you think the police will buy it never mind I guess now you
You'll be heading off to that Rose Mansion am I right
That's right
You're almost at the Finish Line your search might be coming to an end any minute I don't know I can't be sure
Even if I tell you not to do anything rash I suppose you won't listen just
Be careful
Mr Grimmer remember what you said when
When we parted at the check border let's have a picnic when we meet again we'll fish
For rainbow trout on a beautiful day
And have a good wine and cheese
I'm holding you to that
For the rest of my natural life that sound is going to haunt me at every turn
I hurt my knee it's bleeding alive
Don't be scared let me just see if you can move it
It's only a scrape but I'll put some antiseptic on it so it doesn't get infected
Tough it out you're a big boy you can handle it
That's better
You're very brave
Your Kensington is that correct
Prague police we have orders to take you to the station