And you've been wearing that same shirt for half a week
You promised you'd shower every other day
Quit nagging me will you
You have a visitor in the reception area
All right I'm going home
Listen you're going to have to make your own coffee okay
He hasn't had a bath either you'll like him he smells almost as bad as you do
Give it a rest
Yeah well whatever
Whose fault is it that I haven't been able to take a bath anyway
She's completely oblivious to the fact that it's cuz of me that we all still have work
Even though this paper has no future
No hard is that to figure out
Sorry to keep you waiting
Hello my name is Tim masser
And I've come here to ask you for your help
She was right
He certainly looks filthy
I see
So you're a doctor huh
Well you don't look like one
Let me get this straight
I just want to make sure that we're on the same page here
So what you're saying is that the infamous serial killer who's been executing middle-aged couples throughout Germany has his next Target
Heidelberg
This particular couple haven't adopted daughter and you're saying that when that girl turns 20 the killer will come
Take her away
And when he does show up the foster parents are going to be killed
And you have no idea who that girl or her parents are but you want to save
If that's not delusional I don't know what is I'm not joking about this you have to believe me
What a load of hooey
Not even a third rate tabloid would buy that story look I didn't come here to sell you a story after the
Twins Escape they disappeared
It was at least 6 months that went by before the brother was seen in Munich so what's your point huh
I believe that after leaving the hospital those children must have come here
To Heidelberg together you know this is just your the
And then the two of them were raised by the twin sisters current foster parents but the brother ran away from home after
Short period leaving the sister behind
Why don't you write a novel
Probably won't sell though wait maybe the couple reported a missing child with the police
Or there might be a newspaper article about it from 9 years ago
All I'm asking is to look through your archives from the past 9 years I'm begging you
Wait please
There must be any more victims The Killing has to stop
Listen to me
The boss is allergic to technology
Reduced versions as well as the original archives from 9 years ago and the rest of these
So the articles that never did make it to print
Thank you very much
So is that some sort of Japanese bow well domo arigato
Let me say this this doesn't mean that I believe you I just don't have time to listen show
Yourself out when you're done looking you got that
Why do I always have to deal with the weirdos
Please please let me find it
Good morning Nina
Good morning
You're looking much better I'm so glad
I was really scared when you faded like that you know I guess you really didn't like the boy we hooked you up with huh
No that's not it at all I just felt sick all of a sudden
I need to apologize to him I'll never mind you don't have to worry about him trust me
But turns out when I talk to Auto I found out he wasn't your prince charming on a white horse after all
Yeah we asked and he said he didn't know anything at all about those email messages
Really
So you're saying that you fainted right after you saw this particular boy at your campus huh
Well what did this fellow look like
I only saw him for a second so I'm not
Really sure
And do you remember exactly what you felt at the moment when you saw him
I remember I
Logic
Maybe not
I don't know
How to explain it
Go on
Just take it easy Don't force yourself
AB
EV
I don't know how to put it
It felt just like when I used to have that nightmare
Absolute evil eh
It sounds more like it has to do with your religious belie
I don't think so I'm not really want to go to church regularly
I think if I see this young man again it might help to clarify things for me
You're thinking this might help you recover your memory is that it
I suppose that's one way to go about it
But I don't think you should allow this to disturb the peace you now have
It's important you continue to focus on your future and the road ahead
Don't worry
Just work up a sweat doing your Aikido and your anxiety should disappear
Hey mower
So did you pull another all nighter
Yeah by the way
I'm just wondering
Were you the one who told that person he could use the file room
That weird guy
Yeah
I asked him what he was doing there and he said you would give him permission to look through the archives
Why you mean he's still in there
Hey you time to hit the road
Hey
Are you all right
Come on heat up
Thank you
Good isn't it
I always come here for breakfast
So don't you ever eat at home then
What about your family
Haven't got one
My wife walked out on me a while ago
I was always too busy with the work
Before I knew it my wife left with our daughter and moved back with her parents
Do you ever think about trying to patch things up with her
Why would I do that she's the one who walked out on me why should I have to be the one to go after her
Well it just seems like you regretted spending so much time at work
That's complete nonsense
Work is priority number one you hear any woman who can't understand such a simple fact is welcome to leave whenever she wants
Sorry about that I didn't mean to pry
That's right
None of your business
Oh another thing please do forgive me
But you smoke too much as a doctor I recommend you cut back I told you already it's none of your business you're
Beginning to sound just like that wife of mine
Well what's so bad about that
It means she cares about your health
Just mind your own damn business
Is that Nina's birthday present
Yes I was finally able to finish it
Goodness I remember when her sweaters used to be this tin
Honey do we really have to tell her
Does she have to know that she's not a real daughter
Why
Just leave it alone
You're right
There's no point in telling her that now
Nina's our daughter
That's all there is to it
I'm home
Welcome back
I am so hungry
All I have to do is focus on my future
Yeah maybe Dr guidel is right after all
See you tomorrow
7:00 p.m.
Heidelberg Castle for your birthday
Tomorrow
Heidelberg Castle
I'm a very busy man
I've been staring at newspaper clippings with you for 2 days
I admire your gumption but
Don't you think it's about time you gave up
Hey Doc
If
And I say if
I were to
Ask my wife to come home again
Do you really think she would give it another go
If you kick the habit one day
What is it
Found it
11 year old boy goes missing
There's a possibility the child has been abducted but there have been no Ransom demands made as of yet
Address 16 Decker Street someone named Fortner filed a missing person report that day
There should be some more information in here somewhere
Oh here it is
Oh man what is it what did you find
Duck you said that killer would come to take his sister away the day she turned 20 isn't that right
If the boy in this article is her twin brother well see for yourself his birthday is printed on it
Those twins are turning 20 today
Hi Dad
It's me
I just finished up at work
I'm going to be meeting up with a friend and then I'll be coming home
Yeah and Heidelberg Castle
Really
Your mom is making a birthday cake so don't stay out too late
Was that Nina de
Yeah
She's meeting a friend before coming home
I'm wondering who this friend is
Nina's a big girl now
Maybe this will help me
To remember things
I want to know
Well I really am
So dark
What are you going to do if this girl is at the fortuner's residence whatever's going on one thing's for sure they're in danger
So I'll call the police and see if they can send over a car
Show up relax nothing's happened yet doctor but if we wait till then it'll be too late look nothing's going to happen
Come on is this all in your head hey duck listen up I know what I'm
Talking about I actually went to the crime scene of the fourth middle-aged couple murdered in cone
There was something unusual about those crimes no motive no Vengeance no
Nothing yeah it just seemed like whoever did this wanted to kill for killing sake
I've been a reporter for a long time something tells me you're way off base this time around talk
Honestly do you really think a 20-year-old kid could be such a cold blooded killer there's no way a kid
Do something like that it's something a whole lot worse
Hell that's just it I have a hard time finding the words to describe that case
Whenever I tried to describe it the whole
Nothing just sounds so corny but the truth is how was the devil's work
Things for certain doc if I had half a chance I'd snuff that guy in a heartbeat
16 Necker Street this is it
Good evening sorry to bother you so late
Yes
I'm sorry to bother you sir my name is Mara I'm from the Heidelberg post
So you're a newspaper reporter
Yeah
I'd like to ask you a few questions
What about
Well
The missing persons report that you filed for your son in 1986
I've got nothing to tell you
I'm sorry sir but you need to talk to us please listen
We know that you have a girl living with you
The twin sister of the boy who disappeared 9 years ago
This is important please answer me
I have a
I saw a cake
I just saw the mother in there she was holding a birthday cake
9 years ago you took in a set of twins and the sister is still living with you both
Please leave
Nina's our daughter we are a family it's that simple please don't cause us any unnecessary trouble
Just leave us alone please
You took in a pair of twins 9 years ago the little boy had surgical scars on his head the girl
Play Amnesia and the boy disappeared isn't that right Mr
Fortuner listen to me you got to call the police now
All your lives are in danger your daughters and your own
Mr motor
What what are you talking about
What do you mean look it's very important we talk to your daughter well she isn't home with the moment she's out
Where did she go she's gone to Heidelberg Castle she said she was going to meet a friend there
Please let me borrow your car no way we got to call the police station first we don't have time to waste explaining things
Things to the police give me the keys quickly all right you go
And I'll call them myself thank you hey Doc listen
Be careful like I told you before this guy's the devil don't die on me you got that
Mr Miller right you better come back alive do you hear me I promise
All your advice and I'll finally quit smoking so get back here quick your wife will be glad to hear that
Oh boy how am I supposed to explain this to the police what's going on is our daughter all right
What is it what's happened
Don't worry she'll be fine but I need to use your phone what has happened to our daughter
Just tell us already calm down lady
What the hell is this
It's dead
The phone lines been cut
Please Anna just hang in there hold on it's
Getting pretty late he's probably not coming well I guess that message must have been a prank after all
I'm going home you can't do that
You can't go you
I have to wait here
Who are you
He told me I'm supposed to make sure you
Right here I just told you to wait don't you
Understand what I'm saying
I'm supposed to keep you right here Lady it's my job to keep you here
I guess
They're calling you Nina now
Do you remember me
I'm Dr tema
Thank God you're okay
Anna
Dr Tan
Let's go
Back to your house
Are you
My prince char
Who the hell are you
Don't interfere you can't interfere in this
She needs to stay here that's all there is to it
If she doesn't I won't
I
F****** pain you bastard
No one else was supposed to show up
Hey are you all right
Yeah but how on Earth did you
I need something to tie him up with quick
Tell me who put you up to this
I don't know okay well when is he coming back here what did he say look I don't know
All he said was he would be back as soon as he was done with something very important he had to take care of
Oh God
He's at your house
Come on we have to get back to your house right away why I'll explain it all later we have
To Ariana
Let's go
You have to untime me
Please tell me who on Earth are you Dr tema
You got it wrong my name is not Anna I'm Nina no but that wasn't your name back when you were brought into
My Hospital you were honor and your brother your brother's name
My brother