The
The key
And the secret code number
Therefore my
Deposit box
With the experiment data and tape can be found
What
Oven interview
With a certain boy
That boy is the malevolent monster
That led 511 Kinder
To destruction
Well here's his office
Inspector Simon I brought the witness
Inspector
Sure
This man was the first to arrive at the pedrov murder scene yesterday
Mr Grimmer sorry about having to keep you here at the station overnight
I slipped and dropped my nail clipper under my desk
Yeah when you're a guy my size seems like you're bump into everything
Hey you're a pretty tall guy yourself yeah
My find eye bump into a lot of things as well
Anyway I'm in charge of this murder case my name is Damon
Hi I'm Grimmer
All right please have a
I was just in the middle of clipping my nails so I hope you don't mind me finishing them
Go right ahead
My wife's always nagging me about it
If my nails start to grow out
Nah she really doesn't like that at all
She can't stand seeing the white part
So thanks to her sometimes I wind up cutting them too short
Oh nice
Well that must have been a terrible scene yesterday
Yeah
I mean I would have thought something like that would happen
I understand you're a freelance newspaper journalist
That right
I imagine you might have known about the murder victims past
Michael Ivanovic Pedro
That's him
His real name was Reinhardt beer
He was in East German
After Germany's reunification he was accused of various illegal activities
Including suppression of Human Rights
Illegal Detention of minors
And several charges of extreme child abuse
He escaped here to the Czech Republic right after the wall fell
The German government maintained the charges against them
We chose not to extradite him allow them to be free and kept him under surveillance
Is that
Indeed
We kept an eye on him and found he was associating with some former secret police types
Why the check secret police
You know how brutal their tactics were when it came to restricting free speech and thought during the Cold War don't you
Well they also gave their support to the terrorist activities of some extreme leftist organizations be that
To me though
With the peaceful separation
Subsequent democratization of the Czech Republic and Slovakia they went underground without being noticed
Without causing any trouble
That's who pedroth was in contact with before he died
We think he was probably selling them information he had
What we have yet to ascertain
Look at that
Cut it too short again
Oh yeah
Did you happen to see a woman leaving the crime scene
Excuse me
It appears as a fairly good chance that pedross murderer was a woman
And allegedly
She's quite beautiful
Right as we got to pedrov's the boys said they saw a woman leaving
Not the time
I guess I didn't notice
That's too bad
What about the children
What's going to happen now to all those orphan boys that Mr pedrov adopted I'm curious
Child Services told us to keep all of them overnight right here at the station but as of today
Most of them are going to be sent out to different local orphanages
Huh
I see
It must be terrible for you getting dragged right into the middle of this huge mess
It's fine
Come to think of it
What exactly was your purpose in trying to contact pedrov
I wanted to ask him questions about his past you know the kind of stuff you were mentioning earlier
Well how did things go did he tell you anything
No
Before we could talk
They look great my wife can't get mad at me now
You can go now Mr Grimmer and again I apologize for keeping you here so long
No problem
I almost forgot
Free died Mr pedrov happened to say anything to you by any chance
Anything at all
No
All right your meal
So where's Thomas yeah I'm here good all of you are here
Now let's get in the van everyone
Come on enough of that let's get going
News 3 you're going
With no bloody orphanage
Hansa Antonin Izzy this must be sad for
I mean you boys got along so well and now you're being pulled apart
But even when you're apart you're all still under the same sky
And someday you'll all play soccer together again just stay positive you three
Antonym
You're the group's leader aren't you
Keep everyone in touch by writing letters to them if you do that it'll keep all of you feeling good
Had a boy Antonin
Come to the play
What oh the hotel Kafka no wait before that let's stop at prohaska bank
Bunker prohaska Rochester Hotel
I don't understand check very well could you speak to me in English or German if you please
Yes yes Kevin G
Why are you stopping here we're not even
Majestic Obama for such
The best in the prime minister of Arizona
Hey mister
You could have at least warned me you were going to pick up other fares
Giver television of the
Hello
What's the name is
Oh wait what's going on you're driving us way outside of town
Look I just want to go back to my hotel in the city
The key the key
What what are you talking about
Food stamp of thirsty
Well
Are you all right
You know I had a hunch it might be in danger so I decided I better follow you you heard much you look
Pretty rough
Those two were probably Hooligans from the former Czech secret police
Do you have any idea what they might have wanted from you
No not really
Well I can't imagine them doing something like this without having a good reason
They had no reason to do this
Are you sure
You're not trying to hide something here
No
I find that rather hard to believe
You got to know why they did
No I'm telling you I don't
Sorry you've already taken it from the safety deposit box at the bank
The tape
The audio tape
My friends
We are looking for his roots
Who's Roots what do you mean we're searching for the monsters
Roots they're going to sell for quite a lot monster will know a lot more when we get to
Tape we'll know precisely we're in the Czech Republic the monster's mother is living now right
Oh hello
This is inspector's am
That man who got caught robbing the supermark
Did he say he was partner
Well that's great
Good work detective suit
Mommy
I still have something I have to attend to
Yeah
I'll be back at the station in about an hour
I'll see you
Guys I think that's probably enough or you won't be able to talk
So grammar
Now do you feel like talking
Where's the key huh
Look I don't know what this key is that you keep talking about
Wait let me reason with him
Mr Crim
It's really pointless of you to try to hide it from
That safety deposit box keep heads off
Where
Like I said
Before I can't tell you what I don't know
I got you you want money don't you
Well then let's make a deal here
How much are we talking about
Nothing I may be a hack journalist but at least I make enough at it to keep myself fed
Mr Grimmer
What a mess
This is just not right
You know my wife would say your nails are in desperate need of a trim
I told you how she likes them didn't I
Why'd you do that you should have moved
Now let's try again
So where is it
Where's the key
I asked where
Even if you did visit that bank and you're able to open the sleeping deposit box with the key and you got
Tape and the data it wouldn't be of use to me
Who possesses that tape is of a claim importance to the organization they're trying to do something
They're going to restore the Eastern block to its former glory
The exact identity of the monster is recorded on that tape of pedross
And they need to know everything about that monster
That monster is like a king that monster can unite them all
All of those orphans from 511 kinderheim
Yes those children were selected to be
I mean this is the highest order the 511 kinderheim group was the most elite group that East Germany had
And the monster can summon all of them to do his bidding it's been said that he was able to control all of the
Working as a 511 kinderheim and that he was the one who had it destroyed in the end
He's a real monster and the only person who could unite that Elite group
All right now where's the key
I think they're an elite group
Why the hell are you laughing
What do you want is it money you're after I get I'm a capitalist hey I love having lots
The money
I'm not taking sides I just want to sell them pedross tape so they give me a load of cash what's your angle on this
Is this all for social justice
There's no reason for you to go this far for that just who are you really
You say you're a journalist from the Old Eastern block but most of those folks were agents
Government intelligence in fact the very best of those agents were spies who was it that
What you think you're a super spy
Sure
You're going to die if you don't talk
Okay this is your last chance where's the key
You ever hear
Of a magnificent Steiner
The cartoon
On TV in West Germany in the 1960s
The signal is so strong
You could even watch in East Berlin
I mean character
And select weakling
But when you get into a really dangerous fix
The secret friend is would come and save him
And beat his enemies to appalled however the main
He always blacked out before he arrived
One day he realized his special friend
Awesome self and whenever he got into a situation that was truly
You would somehow transform into the terrifying magnificent Steiner
Came to he'd find all the evil doers bleeding At His Feet his transformation made him Unstoppable
Well you better trans
Gone transform right now
Pour some water on them
He'll tell us about it soon
It's only a matter of time
And who are you
What
A woman came in
A woman
Amen then I heard a single gunshot
And one of those men was shot in the head but on the other
Another two bodies there weren't any bullet holes
The Magnificent Ste
I did it again