Petra open up
Petra
You're going in for a checkup and that's vital
Yeah well if you open the damn door right now it wouldn't be a waste of my time
Look who's talking you quack
I've never been to a doctor in my entire life and I'm a healthy woman
I'm very healthy Woman as a matter of fact
Now leave me alone
We got a problem
Dr Schumann
Yes what is it it's a drunk thing he got hit by a car out on the highway
When you left it was he still awake I'm not sure but some guy was treating him
When I left somebody who just happened to be passing by I guess
So mind telling me what happened here oh he insist
I'm so sorry I tried to stop him but he said he needed to take emergency measures because the patient
A joke to
Well who did he say he was
I don't know
He never did tell me his name
Oh he did write something on the chart though
The patient kept pleading with me not to bring him to this Clinic because he said he had no money to pay for a doctor
Please take this to cover any medical expenses
Bastard
Who does he think he is
Doctor where you going this fellow what did he look like
He was an Asian man and he had a little boy with him
Doctor what about Mr Fink
There's nothing more I can do for him only took emergency measures to prevent him yeah
Emergency measures my eyes
That's stranger patched him up perfectly
Listen dear
You can't keep following me around like this it isn't going to work
I can never stay in just one place and you can't go to school like this
You won't make any friends
And who is that
It's you
That isn't what I meant
Was it you
What were you the one showing me up in my own Clinic
Keep your damn money
Maybe I'm just a country doctor but I take care of my own
I would never stoop so low as to charge that poor drunkard for treatment
Sir I just you're probably some big city doctor out on vacation I bet you're
Please dispatch you got to go show us Yokel some charity
Hey
How's it going come on Peter let's go
I'm not finished with you yet I'm terribly sorry
We're in a hurry we have to get going now
Faint got injured in a hit and run
Oh you mean that guy who drinks too much
We're looking for any Witnesses
Good luck with that one
Oh hey there Dr Schumann
So how's things doing
Looks like he's going to pull through
I'm more worried about the bottle doing them
And you are
Who am I
Dr Chan
We're alumni from the same medical school
He figured he dropped by The Village while he's on vacation
Dr Chan huh
Have you and I met somewhere before
He took care of Fink actually since I was out making house calls
Good thing he was here yes sir
Speaking of house calls guess where I went again today
Where Hines isn't it obvious I'm talking about your mother Petra my mother
You need to tell her to come down to the clinic right away
There's no telling what may be wrong with her without a checkup
There's no way
She's too stubborn come on you know that woman won't listen to anybody she's your mother stop acting so flip
Don't worry doc
Trust me mom's not going to die that easily
What besides
She raised me so what's left to do
When it's time she won't have any regrets what did you say
Fight your Tong
Petra has plenty of living to do do you hear me
Why did you lie to him
Because I never would have made it to think in
No he'd be dead right now if you hadn't stepped in like you did
Thank you very much sir
You turned white as a sheet when you saw Hines how come
Never mind
Least now I know you're not some hot shot doctor from the city
I'm in your debt sir I really do mean it
I don't know how I can ever pay you back
Is that so
Pop in the car I've got an idea
Your splint is misaligned I'll straighten it
This may hurt a bit but just hang in there
There you go I should do the trick
Don't let me catch you not wearing that in the next two weeks hey Doc I made some smooth
Apple wine how about we drink to my new cat I think that's an awful idea but I'll have a drink with you
You in the cast comes off you should be fine 5 days and you can go
Go back to the fields
Good news hi Mr Shawna why don't you take some potatoes we had a good crop this year
With a truck
Thanks for the help
My specialties internal medicine but I have to be a jack of all trades out here I'm all the doctoring these
Yeah and there's only one of me
It's wonderful yeah Tranquility is the one thing this place has in Spain no I didn't
In the land
I mean how much you love all the people in this Village and at the same time how much they all seem to
I love you back
Love huh
That ship sailed a long time ago
This is my job and that's why I do it
Well one last stop and you're a free man
I saved the best for last
Yeah just don't quit do you
Quit
I don't even know the meaning of the word
Like I'm talking to a mule
Patrick's the mother of that officer who had you spook
She collapsed 3 days ago working in the field
I talked her into coming down to the clinic but she changed her mind on the way over
She's been holed up in there ever since
Not his worrisome
Not to but in but do you mind if I try talking to her
It's not going to make a lick a difference
Doctor please you have to come down she'll never come out if you keep yelling at her like that
Wake up and that's final I'm not going to stand the possibility of losing you
What I mean is I wouldn't have anyone to fight with anymore
Also I wouldn't be able to eat that goulash of hers if that stubborn old thing passed on
Hey mister how come your face is red
What did you say you little br
Please miss Petra open the door
Another doctor are you kidding me
What did I say it's a waste of time
So tell me why do you hate doctors
Why do I hate doctors
I'll tell you why
You play God with people's lives
That's why
So I wish
Sometimes I think it would be great if we were
And try our best but we make mistakes too
Wouldn't it be great
If doctors could be perfect like God and just heal people
When I see my patients it's always the same
On the inside I'm trembling like a Le
Please miss Petra let me at least see you
What is it I'm smelling
You're cooking up some goulash in here aren't you why you asking you like goulash or something I do
But it seems that Dr Schumann is a particularly big fan of it at least that's what he told me anyway well that's news to me
I always make it for him and he eats it but he never says a word
He's very shy
This looks really delicious
My goodness
My shoulders are so stiff and I still have a lot of food to prepare for tonight's dinner
Miss Petra
Can you touch your chin down to your chest
Of course I can't easy enough to do watch let me just check something man
Four fingers wide
So what was that all about
Oh nothing
How is she
It isn't good
A subarachnoid hemorrhage
Hey
The fax came in for a murder suspect make some copies
Is your mom okay I heard that she had a fading spell three days ago she's all right
Yeah that tough old lady is going to outlive all of us
The first stroke occurred less than three days ago
We can still make it but we need to operate immediately can we get a helicopter here in time
Can you do it please if you can perform this
Me the woman I love
For a second time
Are you sure that it's Kensington
Positive
All right he probably hasn't gone far set up checkpoints along the highway
If we catch this guy it'll be big Hines yes sir
Prepare for emergency deployment
This is great if things go well I'll get promoted
Hey Hines you have a call
This is sign speaking
The nurse from the clinic
Are you kidding me my mother collapsed again
God why didn't I drag her into town
If they had checked her at the state hospital I wouldn't have come to this
You're the only one who can save her
Just as I suspected
It's an aneurysm of the middle cerebral artery
We don't even have a surgical microscope or a cranial here
I can still do it as long as I have an aneurysm clip
No it's too difficult even for someone of your caliber
We've got no other option here
If the aneurysm ruptures I'm afraid she's not going to survive the night
It's my fault this is happening again
What are you talking about Dr Schumann
Those aren't the words of a man who single-handedly taken care of this entire town
I don't know what happened in the past but
You have to do the best job you can do right now
That's all we as doctors can do
Yeah
Hey kid
Dr schumann's inside isn't he operating why are they doing it here
Convert this Clinic instead of taking her to the hospital in town hey don't worry
How's her blood pressure and pulse
Blood pressure holding study at 1:26/84
Propulses 88
Amazing
He's so fast and efficient even without the benefit of a craniotone
What the hell are you doing
We're operating on your mother isn't that obvious what are you doing with that gun put your hands up
Do it
If he stops now she'll die is that what you want he's the one trying to kill her
Is wanted for murder he's a suspect in several killings
He killed a man and Heidelberg
And he's the prime suspect in the serial murders of those couples
Who would have thought that I'd find you here
Leave it to good old mom always looking for new ways to help out our boy now put your hands up
If you don't I'll shoot like hell you will
This is a sterile operating room or it was until you came barging in do you want your mother to die of meningitis
Cuz it's very likely to happen if you keep standing there
There's a subarachnoid hemorrhage in your mother's brain
And she's had it for three entire days
If we don't save her now
She dies
Now get out of here Heinz no way I'm on to you you're just planning on using my mom as a host
So you can run away from here all right now
Aneurysm clip in forceps now
That's my mother on that table I won't let anyone hurt her yes Petra is your
You're her son
But what kind of sun have you been to her these past 5 years
I know you didn't visit her once since you left for the city
She's sacrificed a lot for you
And what have you done for her in return
Anything
Listen son the folks we love can be gone in an instant
Do you remember what your mother's goulash taste like
Even now years later Petra sets out a dish for you
I should know I'm the one who eats it
Remember
How delicious it is
He's giving it everything he's got
So if you ever want to taste that goulash again you'll get out of here now
Tim was there so it's okay
Blood pressure 140 over 86 pulse
Good
Her Vital Signs have stabilized
Why don't you get some rest Misty
Doctor you've been up all day
God like you haven't I'll be just fine
Yes sir you did well today
Doctor timer you should get some rest too
Don't worry about me I'm fine
You're fine that was a grueling operation you must be dead on your feet
I want to stay and make sure she pulls through that way when Miss Petra has recovered enough you can go ahead and finally
Propose to her
What do you mean for pose
Hey I thought you were supposed to be asleep
I'm not sleeping
Not until I take him down to the station
What's he talking about anyway
You're not thinking about marrying my mom are you
Of course not
Don't be stupid
Even if I did
I'm not the kind of man who's worthy of proposing to anyone
I used to work at the University Hospital
Didn't give a damn about any of my patients
All I cared about was moving up the ladder faster than the next guy
I got in good with the director and ended up writing all his research papers for him would you believe it even
Sorry the boss's daughter what a clich
Well I moved up that damn ladder all right
And ignored her like the wrong she was
If only
I had been a real doctor or showing her the least bit of attention
I'd have known in a moment
My wife came down with a simple cold at least that's what I wrote it off as
If only I had looked at her I would have seen it
An intern would have seen it
Severe liver failure
Before she died
She said
I finally have
You're undefined attention
I don't deserve to love anybody after what I did to that poor woman
That's not true
You have been paying attention doctor you've been watching over the people of this Village Petra is going to survive
Five this because you were watching
Do you still plan on taking this man to jail
What kind of murderer would do that
This is Hines
Get me the chief
Chief
I made a mistake
I'm sorry
We should cancel this search
The man I saw before was not 10
He was another doctor by the name of Chan
I thought it was him because he was Asian
Yes that's right
Yes yes sir I'm very sorry
The doctor from the state hospital sure did
I'm surprised
Well of course he did he probably never expected to see such amazing results from a little clinic in the boonies
Dr Schumann are you really going to let that young doctor leave I was making him something
But he packed his bags
I'm left with the kid
Don't go
This town is safe for you there's no need to run away
Dr Schumann what are you
This is a nice Village isn't it you're right
This Village may be a very good place for a boy like Peter here yes but not only for him you could stop running you
You'll be off the radar if you stay
The folks in this Village need more than I can give them on my own together there's no end to the good we could do
I can't
I'm sorry but I really have to be moving on but why
Take care of Peter
He's better off here
Can we wait I'm going with you wait please
What's more important than that
Save countless lives
Before I do that
As a man whose life I have to end what what are you
You can't mean that no damage you're a good man
You fought like hell to save Petra's life why you're not a killer
Tim was going to go no matter what you say to him
Go take care of him Peter
If you stay with 10 amount maybe you can keep him from going down the wrong path go with him and look after him