Excuse me sir just a couple of questions please
Stay there stay right there
Please tell us what the police are thinking what are your views on this situation
Mr and Mrs yopay were quite wealthy and have no children right no matter how you look at it it's obvious this
It is exactly like the other cases of murdered middle-aged couples across Germany
No comment at this time
I've heard that the bka is sending an agent to look into this is that true
Does that mean there's a connection to the serial murders oh man
I think I'd have better luck talking to a bka suit directly than trying to get this guy to give me anything
Just trust me all right
I promise you will be the first ones with the story
Just make sure you leave plenty of space on the front page
Just dude I got to go
Excuse me sir
My name is Kipper
I'm with the Hamburg tog
You've been sent here by the bka to investigate this murder correct me if I'm wrong
I was wondering
Is this case somehow connected to the others here real murders well Kipper of the Hamburg tog
You're right on both counts
Get your pen ready
Because here's my statement
A middle-aged couple was murdered and it appears to be another serial slaying
I knew it
And it's a suspect that Japanese doctor
Yes I just saw the report
It's his Mo the murders were carried out the same way
Thank you for the scoop
Got to run oh one more thing
I'm aware the Hamburg tog is the leading local newspaper
But I expect you to make sure your story gets published in every major newspaper in the country as well
Hey consider it done
Thanks again for all your help friend
I have become the Killer
I think to myself as I approach
What's the best way to
Need to get into their house
Should I knock
I don't want to startle the Yoke pays by walking in on them
Such a friend
They greet me
And show me to the living room
These folks aren't the least bit suspicious as they Lead Me In
The husband's chair naturally I sit on the sofa facing him
A few minutes later the husband will die on the floor over there
But I haven't made that movie yet
So I have to decide when to eliminate him
I'll do it when the wife leaves a room where did she go
To the kitchen to make us some tea she is stabbed in the back before she even has a chance to serve it
Obviously that I need to make my move on the husband while she's occupied in the kitchen
I reach in pull out the knife the husband sees this Panic tries to stand up by stab him
But I miss and end up slashing him the husband runs off with blood dripping from his wounded left hand
So I try to get him again I swing the night this time I only puncture his right shoulder I'm such a clumsy
Amateur desperately the husband yells his wife's name only she can't hear him from out in the kitchen
Recently she's developed a hearing problem yes turns out I knew about that didn't I
Shout all you want I can take my time to kill you and then your wife you're trapped
There's your left hand print on the wall you can't get away from me I've got you pinned against this table
You're finished
But then something prevents me from completing the task
5 m from this point where the husband dies
How come why not just eliminate them here and be done with it
My weight
Do you suspect he's the one who broke in and murdered my neighbors
For the moment I can only say he's a person of interest but I'm asking everybody in the neighborhood for their cooperation in this
If you see this man just act normal I don't want him to become suspicious
Then get in touch with me as soon as you possibly can
That would be all I need for you to do
I personally assure you you won't be in any danger
Hard to imagine such a tragic event like this happening here it's such a pleasant
Quiet neighborhood
It really is
Any old pays for such nice people just the best
When I call out to her from my doorstep Mrs yopay would always greet me cheerfully
That's very interesting
I've been told Mrs yopay lost her hearing about a year ago and refused to hearing aid
Huh are you sure
It was in her medical record
If I had to guess
She really couldn't hear any of your greetings
Well knowing the type of person she was she probably sensed my presence and wanted to make me feel good
So then in your opinion nobody else in the neighborhood knew about her hearing loss either
No I wouldn't think so
It certainly appears that your business is booming
You made rapid progress at an early age
It's not easy for a young man to achieve such quick success Mr
You're right
The contracts I made with the car manufacturers just happened to work out
Before we begin I'd like to extend my deepest condolences for the recent loss of your aunt and uncle
Thank you
They're passing was a great loss they were the only relatives I had left in the world
It appears they never had any children of Their Own
So they must have taken good care of you since you were there only nephew
Yes
They treated me as if I were their son
Sir tell me you'll be able to catch the murderer
I will
I'm pretty sure I know who's behind it me too I bet it was that Japanese doctor wasn't it
Sounds like you're very well informed
Well of course I am
As a matter of fact I've heard he's been linked to other murders similar to this
I'm curious
Just how much do you stand to inherit
You see I found out that Mr yope was quite a wealthy man
So what
His wealth has nothing to do with the serial murder case
Sir I presume you are the sole heir to their considerable estate
Seeing as how you are they're only nephew
It's inappropriate to be discussing my inheritance in these circumstances
A company can appear to be booming on the surface but underneath may have serious cash flow problems that have gotten out of
It's a common occurrence in the business world
Just a minute you're implying I murdered them when there's a serial killer on the loose how dare you
What are you so worried about you have a perfect Alibi for the time in question
And you have plenty of witnesses you bought your secretary and some others a nice dinner after a long meeting
What exactly are you getting at
That it appears that you could not be the murderer
I'm sure you agree
Inspectorlingay well
What do you want Kipper what the hell is going on
Going on with what
Don't play dumb inspector
I've been out digging up stuff on that nephew for the last couple days
His company looks profitable at first glance but turns out to be holding a lot of bad stocks and bonds
Cash Wise it's in the world of hurt
And now
I found out you've been investigating the same company
I want the truth who killed those folks Looney
In light of what you've uncovered
Do you still think this case is related to the other middle-aged murders
All of the newspapers have printed A variation of my story
If the cases aren't related then it's just Sensational journalism my reputation could be damaged
Your instincts are correct
It's the work of a copycat it was set up to look like the serial killer
That's just great
I've got to publish retraction right away no it's fine as it is you'll continue
Follow-up stories as if this case were another one of the middle-aged couple murders what it's not ethical no way
I won't do it I tell you oh but you will I'm I'm an honest journalist who believes in reporting the whole truth and
You're not going to tell me what I can write well let me give you the truth Goode right love
You have a pleasant home with a devoted wife and a doting daughter who both
Adore you but it was impossible for you to resist the charms of that attractive Other Woman wasn't it
Continuous before
No beef it up a little
Write a special report about the serial murders if you do as I've asked
He'll most certainly come I'm counting on you
Yes who is it
Excuse me ma'am may I ask you some questions
Well
Sounds like the your pace we're really a wonderful couple
They were
I see
And you're absolutely certain they didn't have any adopted children
Oh yes
Did any children children that you never seen before live with them even for a short time
No never
But they took very good care of their nephew he was the apple of their eye
Would you like more tea it won't take a minute I'm fine
A little more tea won't hurt you
There's no mistaking
Right now
Nothing to worry about
Thanks for your cooperation
Inspect a long day someone's here to see you
Well who is it
He says he's the nephew of the lope
That couple that was killed
Inspector you believe I'm the one who murdered them I'm your suspect right
You think I killed my aunt and uncle for their money
That's what you hinted at the other day
Let's
We both know that I have many debts right now
And the inheritance money they ended up leaving me will more than likely get me out of this whole mess
However that's not the kind of person I am
Is that really all you came here to tell me
All I came
Wait a minute how dare you speak to me in such a condescending way
Well if you'll excuse me there's somewhere I have to be right at the moment
Don't you walk away I demand an apology for your disrespectful Behavior
Perhaps you weren't aware that the police had been following you
Well now that order has been canceled
Your local law enforcement thinks that you're innocent
Isn't that good enough for you Mr geebel
You want to know if I think you are guilty
That really doesn't matter to me at the moment
My chief concern is to catch the man I've been after
The blood stain over there can only mean one thing
He must have missed then am I to assume that you're convinced the Japanese doctor is responsible
Never assume anything I've concluded it was a copycat murder
Look like the middle-aged couples homicides but how can you be so certain about that
Because there's one element this case has it makes a different from all the others
The killer Corner the victim here but he doesn't
Finish him off he waits till his victim gets over there before delivering the final blow
Why why does the murderer hesitate
It's not him
That element
Is emotion
Emotion
Yes you see the man I'm after always take small valuables
He tries to make his crimes look like robberies
He murders quickly without hesitation or emotion
At least that's his go
But this crime scene is full of emotions
The killer panicked when he saw his face and the victim's face together in the mirror
You needn't worry
From what I've observed the police in this town are totally incompetent
This crime was definitely not committed by Johann
But somebody wants the police to pin it on him
How much longer is this all going to continue
When will it end
Hello it's been a while
So we finally meet again
Dr tinma
I've been looking all over for you
For a very long time
I've been hoping to have a quiet
Chat with you
There's no use in
Away anymore stop trying to escape and talk to me period the fact is
There's no place you can hide Dr tena
Yes you're all mine
Why couldn't you just leave it alone
Your confession means nothing to me just stay out of my way
He's been seriously wounded
I've got to do something now or he's going to bleed to death
Who could have
I'll drop him off in front of the hospital and get away
Where are
I need the keys to the handcuffs tell me where you put them inspector
Don't bother reaching for your gun
I took it off you while you were unconscious
Don't be so stubborn just give me the keys I'm a doctor but I can't help you like this
How you examined your wound the best I could
It appears that only your muscles sustain the damage
But you're losing an awful lot of blood if we don't stop the bleeding you're going to die
Come on confess
Do it
Best to what
That you murdered the director of Isler Memorial Hospital along with three others
And that you've been on a 3-year Killing Spree targeting middle-aged couples
It's time to
Come clean
Admit
Done
If you keep this up you'll be a Deadman
Come
Don't try to
You're only fooling yourself by running around chasing this elusive Johan
Yohan doesn't exist
Admit it you made him up
Your Yohan
Entertain
Own up to it
Inspector right now you require emergency treatment I have everything I need to do the procedure
Except for my hands and I can't save your life when I'm chained together yes
When you're the
Dr Tema those are the hands of a highly skilled surgeon
I will save many lives
But how many people have you killed with those hands
You've got it wrong I'm not a killer
No but you change into Johan
It's a good
Turn into the
Monster
I already told you he mistaken
They tell you
I never make
Mistakes
Your blood pressure is falling you're going to lose Consciousness soon
Your CR
Always
No more talking it'll weaken you
Your crime scenes are always lacking in something
An emotional
Factor
Save your strength
Dealing with
Day forces
Emot
Right
You develop a cold EXT
Yes I always find it's your crime
Calm emot
Taking of life
I am not that kind of man
Every time I operate a thousand emotions go through my head
Hey affect my every decision
Is my diagnosis accurate
Will there be any unforeseen complications
Well my patient even survive
How can I become when I hold a person's life in my hand
His hand
How in the hell can I become
Closer
Stop I can save you
I will
Shoot I need my hands to stop the bleeding are the keys in your pants pocket tell me
You really had us worried for a while
But you're looking quite well
Lots better than when you're running around investigating crimes
I guess this means you're not rid of me yet
Yeah you'll be back on your feet in no time
That emergency procedure you received before you got here was done perfectly
Your doctor said you wouldn't be alive without it
I'm assuming that
And used them to save my life
Yeah well he got away but we got G
He confessed a murdering the you'll pick
He stabbed you because you were on to him
You did good lung
Thank you
Well
What do you think
About what
It's quite clear that Tim must save lunga's life
So I'm worried looking might have a problem pursuing him now
I'm wondering if I should remove
The
I'm sorry did he call for you again inspector loon get can be very demanding
Oh he really isn't that difficult at all
In fact I find him to be very pleasant
I keep telling him not to rush through the recovery process but he's quite determined
He's already working on strengthening his grip and he's taking long walks down the hall
He seems to be having a really fun time recovering
He's having fun
Yes he's always telling me that nothing has been more enjoyable for him than what was the suspect's
Name again oh yes it was 10 ma that chasing after a criminal like is the most
Funny could ever have