After 10 mom
I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore
You did what you had to do as a doctor it wasn't your fault
Please eat the sandwiches
And get some rest too
Please live on
And continue to save as many people as you are able to
Nina Fortner
Nina are you planning to do are you going to kill
Brother second time I did it I brought him back to
Life that monster it was me
I brought him back to life
There are a lot of blood vessels in this arterial venous malformation
Cutting all arteries
And now the veins
Extraction of the night is complete
That went very well yes as usual
He's remarkably quick with the clipping
An amazing operation
How is it possible that even after a long break the work of a genius like you only gets better and better
It's over
Never mind it is an important
Isn't that wonderful Kenzo
Wasn't even about me it was all about your father
You did such a wonderful job last night working as part of Father's team I'm sure he appreciates all your hard work
The hospital's reputation no I'm the one who should be grateful
I mean after all it is thanks to your father that I'm actually able to work here in Germany
Hang in there Kenzo if you stick with Father your futures guaranteed
It won't be long before father becomes chairman of the board soon after that you'll become chief of surgery
And then Chief director which means I'll be the director's wife
You better make me happy Kenzo cuz hardship doesn't suit me still want to go out on that date
I said we just
Please sir Madam is resting at the moment
I won't need much of her
This shouldn't take long
You really need to make an appointment with Madam
What's all the racket
I'm terribly sorry to bother you madam but there's a police officer here
The police
Miss Ava Heineman
It's been a while hasn't it
And how are you supposed to be
I worked on your father's case exactly 9 years ago
I'm inspector lung
Of the bka
Loon gay
Oh I see
You may leave us holes
Yes madam
I do remember you
All too well
You were that good for nothing detective you couldn't even close my father's case so tell me what on Earth do you want from me now
I'm quite impressed
You've been able to maintain this residence exactly the same even after your father's death
Actually it appears that the decor might have gotten even more extravagant than before
So then if you come to see how much money I've made from The Inheritance my father left me and all my divorce settlements
As you can see detective I live in Absolute Comfort if you see anything you like
Please feel free to take it with you
As long as I have my liquor by my side I'm fine
I've come today because there is something I'd like to show you
Here take a look at this necktie
A necktie does it look familiar
Perhaps you don't remember
It's a design from 9 years ago
It has a very simple print
But if you look at it carefully
It's a Wonderful piece
With an extremely elaborate weave
So what what about it
Tracing it back was quite a task after all it was purchased 9 years ago
But luckily this was a limited edition offering especially made for a particular stores higher-end
Clients
And your name was on that list Miss Ava Heineman
So what exactly is your point you see
I was wondering if you might have purchased this and given it to someone as a gift
This necktie is a key piece of evidence and another murder case
A murder
Who knows
I've given gifts to so many men I couldn't possibly keep track of them all now could I
They're not interested in me anyway the only thing thereafter is my money
Please try to remember
I told you I don't remember these men are all after my money there isn't a single person
Truly loves me for who I am
That's why I always stick it to them when it's time for the divorce settlement I did not tell all three of them
Damn bastards
Do you want something too you want something just tell me
Michelle pay a high price for it
I'll be back ma'am
If you remember anything please give me a call
Next time you stop by detective be sure to bring me something to drink
Excuse me
Ava please you have to
Talk to your father for me make him see I haven't done anything wrong all I did was operate on an emergency patient who
I was brought in first nothing else
Why is that the ring that I
Spare me Kenzo you're such a fool
Dr Norton you're looking very handsome this evening thank you you're looking especially beautiful tonight
House have my car ready
Well Mr Hess you're certainly looking better today
At this rate I'm guessing you should be able to go home sometime later this week all right
Thank you very much Dr Timmy you did a great job
By the way my daughter is getting married next month do you think I'll be able to attend her wedding yes that should be fine
You just have to promise me that you won't get too wild at the reception
Thanks doctor
I had resigned myself to not going but thanks to you
Hey come on it's because you toughed it out
With you looking after me I feel as though I'll even live to see my grandchildren get married
You truly are a wonderful doctor
I really hope they keep you with this Hospital forever
Excuse me Dr tema
You have a visitor
Oh I'm doing my rounds right now tell them I'm too busy at the moment would you please
Ava
It's been a while hasn't it Kenzo
That ass
Both of us
Have gone through so much
Hello father are you sleeping already
I'm coming in
Ava I know it's difficult but please
Try to hold yourself
Google listen
Cancel cancel
You look worn out you're much thinner
I guess
I hear that you took some vacation time
Well I think that's great you should take a break every once in awhile you always were such a workaholic
Seems like you've lost a little waitress
I've had a rough couple of years
I'm sure you've heard all the rumors
I've heard a few
Spring
You remember
Almost 10 years ago how the two of us would often go out for a drive
We were so young
It was this time of the year when you tried to swim in that River
I panicked and tried to stop you
But you insisted and you just
Luck Eva I can't deal with this now
Cancel I
I want to start over
After three failed marriages I finally realized
That the only one who ever truly loved me
Was you
It was you Kenzo
That was a long time ago
Please cancel
I want you to know that I'm very flattered Ava but there's no going back
Goodbye
Hi it seems to me that next time of yours has gotten you in some kind of
I'm absolutely positive that's the one I gave you as a gift when we were together if you do as I say I'll
Keep quiet about it I promise you there's something very important that only
I can accomplish
I'll tell the police about your time I'll
Oh I see let's bring Dr
My infern interrogation right away
Now we're in the forteners that's not what I'm referring to I'm talking about the killing at Heidelberg Castle
Thank you very much for your cooperation this could prove to
A very helpful in solving several of our open cases
Resignation
But what is the meaning of this doctor ten
I'm very sorry director but I've already made up my mind about this
There have been various odd rumors going around about you recently but I want to be clear I don't believe
Leave any of
Please think this over you
Hey wait Dr tema
Yeah speaking
Excuse me the police
Close up all the exits don't forget the back doors
Where is Dr Tenma
Why are you just
What is it
Get out of the way you people are interfering with the police like hell doctor would never be capable of killing anyone
Anything wrong you're the one though put in jail he would never do anything like that
Who is this
Wow I wonder what's going on in the front
Does police cars over there Dr temma man ain't that a site is that right well I wonder what's going on
Anyway can you drop me off at the station no problem hey doctor are you always this busy
I have
Surgery to perform in the other room
Hang in there kid how save you no matter what
I am not wrong he is he tells me there's a flaw in my character but what about him
Greedy bastard bastard bastard
They're gone sir we can't find them anyway
What's going on what the
It's been a long time doctor it's me
Have you forgotten already doctor twins
I was supposed to die
Night
You're the one who resurrected me doctor
It looks like another scorcher today hey
Why are you all bundled up on a hot summer day like this aren't you broiling huh you're reading an old paper
That one's at least 3 days old yeah a couple inverted got themselves murdered they say
Doctor did it if you can believe that hey buddy you said you were headed for burden wasn't that right
What you know somebody over there yeah I do I'm not even sure if he'll still be there now
I have to try and find them