Hello
The wind's getting cold isn't it
That's strange she always smiles at me and says hello
Oh Ann
Are you headed home for the evening
Hey Nina
Looks like all the restaurants in this neighborhood are already closed
Let's go back to the hotel Nina
What's wrong huh
For some reason people on the street
Talk to me like you know me but they called me
Instead of Nina
Interesting so what's wrong with this
This picture
I'd say a lot Sook is the main suspect in a Multiple homicide case I don't see any police
Security anywhere yeah I'm going to go in there and take a look around
Sure well I think I'd better tag along I could use some answers myself
It's quite as a tomb and there's not
Excuse me there's an injured man being Hospital
Nice to your soup is his last name Young souk he's a police detective
All these men were injured at this vacant building on Bruno Street
Unemployed men who knows what story they're report
On the news but what you're saying is probably the real deal so could you please tell us what rooms they're staying
After their serious injuries were treated they were all moved to another hospital
Where I don't know it says a large ambulance came and loaded up all six of the patients
Those goons attacked us there were six of them what about soup detective Yonce where's he he's the one that was
According to our records there weren't any patients brought in with any gunshot wounds wait is there
For any record of a patient with the name yansuk even being brought in here no not at all
You have researched data in an audio tape from 511 kinderheim
I do
The former director of 511 kinder
A man named pedrov gave them to me before he died
He was running this illegal orphanage in Prague
Those things you have how exactly would be interested in them
I don't know for sure but I've got a hunch
I'd say the check secret police have a keen interest in obtaining any material from 511 kinderheim
That said where are you keeping this data in the tape
Well they're not on me
I've stored them in a secure location
Suk was shot because you possessed something they want
Probably led to him being kidnapped from here what's just as bad as we can only imagine what they'll do to soak to force
That data on tape from my hands
God what a mess
The contents of the tape in the data
What are we talking about here
The research data was a list of technical terms
It also contained a list of names
I didn't have the time to examine it closely
I only listen to part of the tape
So what was this tape recording of
A child talking
A child
This young boy was probably drugged
And the interviewer asked him questions
And when this boy was asked his name his answer was Johann
Doctor Tenma is something the matter
511 kinderheim
Search data Johanna
Where is that tape right now
It might be best if you come with me
Tell us where soup is
We can discuss that after our business
Where is suke
With the both of you come with me please
Doctor Tenma you really should have stayed behind there's no point you
You getting involved in this any further no I also have a couple questions that the check secret police
Might be able to answer for me so you're saying you have your own agenda
Well the first question that needs answering here is whether we can negotiate with these people
People at all
Hold on
You didn't drive us all this way to treat us to dinner did you
Welcome gentlemen
Come have a seat
I know that face
He looks familiar
He must be a high-ranking member of the Czech secret police you're right
He's Captain Carl lunker
I did research on him at the newspaper
Now we're getting somewhere
First I want to express you my sincerest apology for what
The men I assigned to this have taken actions that were far too heavy-handed
This was an error within our chain of command we've been awfully misunderstood
Are you and the world
We are viewed as a road gang of Ruthless killers
So where's Suk
Suke is not in any danger
He's resting comfortably at one of our hospitals
This isn't just a misunderstanding
I don't want you thinking of us as thugs after all it's not like we've killed anyone what about the woman
What woman wasn't that blonde woman who killed pedrov acting on direct orders from you
I've heard about This Woman's murderous activities but she isn't working for us in fact she's been quite disruptive
To our plans we are not in the business of killing people
A German associate of ours informed us that he wanted the tape and the data
And we were delicately negotiating securing them from pedroth in the middle of all this he was murdered
Well there must have been a lot of money involved
Yes but that negotiation failed
We are here to discuss business of a more pressing nature
I want that tape and data in trade for the safe return of Sook sounds fair but I don't have those things
I was supposed to say you do have what we want
I can't allow it
I won't
Who knows what could happen if that information got out into the world for a second time
We must never allow something like that to happen again
There's no point in talking about things like that now
After all it doesn't really relate to our present discussion
That's where you're wrong
You see I'm from there
I was there
As a child I was sent to live at 511 kinderheim
I see
How old are you
Well when did you leave that place
I was 14 years old as near as I can tell
And I was 30 years ago
When were you there
Who knows
Guess I got there when I was about 8:00 so that must have been around 1963
I guess
Did you know this boy
He's my nephew in the early 1960s I was officially stationed as an intelligence off
Chinese Berlin
Where I worked as a spy for the Czechoslovakian Embassy I had a beautiful younger sister she married
This is German after being married a few years my younger sister and her husband plotted to defect and
Across the Berlin Wall
During their attempt to cross over they were shot dead
My nephew was all that was left of their family I heard it was a wonderful place so I signed him up to
Live there
It was touted as an ideal environment to prepare and educate children with dubious past so they would qualify
Fine to become the Communist Elite of the future
I gave it my all I used all the influence I had to be sure that he would get into 511
Kinderheim I don't know him
I have no memories none from that time
Or even before then
I don't remember what happened there I was brainwashed I can't even tell you my real name
I see you're trying to make a profit off of something that was reprehensible
You want to sell information that includes experimental data that was collected from your own nephew
We've strayed off topic
You're attacking instead of discussing things
In a calm business like man
Very well then
You may go
We're done discussing things for today
I await your acceptance of my offer
Take these gentlemen where they wish
I can't believe he sent us a way
What do we do
Saving soup is what's important
If we give him what he wants I think he'd release suit to us right away
Are you okay
Hot
I remember
Once a week we got Coco he always look forward to drinking it
Your nephew was so kind to me when I got a fever and slept in the infirmary he brought me his
He gave me his
I know he liked it so much
Delicious
Never had cocoa that delicious in my entire life and I wanted to thank him in some way for what he'd done for me
And that's what he said to me
That's when he looked into my eyes and said Remember Me
Back then while we were there we all did stuff like that
We talked about ourselves to the friends we made
I don't really know why
But our memories about ourselves would fade day by day after those strange lessons they would put us through we could
That's why
That's why we had our friends remember who we really were the boy who helped me
Hot cocoa drawing pictures and bugs fascinated him but he didn't like bug collections because he didn't like having to kill the
Box the most funny ever had was spending a day in the forest with his parents he caught a lot of butterflies there
And when he went back home he said the butterflies free his life long dream was to be coming into demologist his name was
His name was
His name was Adolf Reinhardt
That boy
Was my nephew
Keeping secrets from him is definitely a no no
People can become whatever they want to be
But toast
Hey welcome home hey welcome home hey welcome home
Hey Nina what's wrong
Somehow I I know this place
The Brick Road leading up to here
The scenery is familiar and even
This old sign
I know all these things
You lived here
I don't know
But what
I'm afraid
So do you know this store
Not sure
Could I Hold On
I'm so afraid
I also recognize these stairs
I couldn't sleep not after what you said
I thought about it all night
What doctor
That research data and tape really shouldn't concern you actually they do looks like we're not going to have time to talk
I guess they're ready to do some more negotiating
Are checked secret police have dropped by for a morning chat
I guess they won't answer
So have you had a chance to think everything through
I have
And I don't plan on giving you the research data or the tape
So you're saying that you don't care what happens to detective Sook if something happens to Sook
That precious data and tape disappear from this world forever I guarantee
Your attitude keeps us from making progress
Hold on
I am willing to offer you a chance to listen to the
The only condition I have is that you forget this whole business about getting your hands on it and selling it to that German friend of yours
I'm fine with meeting you somewhere and letting you hear the tape in private
If you want to listen to it by yourself
I think
But you should want to listen to it
I think you should hear it for your nephew who lived in 511 kinderheim
You should listen closely to what exactly that boy Johan said on your precious tape
So that's the deal you're willing to make
I didn't say anything about making a deal that's enough
We don't have time to be going on and on like this
As we sit here discussing the finer points of some deal and innocent person could be killed because of that tape
Tell me how many people that were somehow involved with the Czechoslovakian secret police have been killed because of that connection
And just who do you think killed them
Any idea
I know exactly who this Relentless killer is
It's a person who wants to take more than anyone
It's Johan
What are you trying to say
I haven't the faintest idea what you're talking about don't you play dumb with me
Your German friend who wants you to track it down should have told you what kind of tape it is
So what is he hoping you're going to find
The monsters identity
That was all
I didn't want to get you involved
But now I'll tell you everything
Before anyone else is murdered over this
I see
So this killer Johan has come to Prague searching for his Origins to uncover his past
Could be
Yohan could be here trying to erase this past completely
You created this mess what the hell did you do 15 years ago
Back then a mother and her daughter lived in Makowski near cheddock bridge and then one day both of them were taken away by
Secret police when your thugs took Johann from the building with a sign that has three frogs what did you do to him
He stairs
Are you okay Nina
He was taking and drive down these very steps
You took him away who was my big brother
During that time I was indeed in a position where I could get any of the information I wanted
But the three frogs building
Grabbing a mother and a child
I don't recall any of that
Don't give me that
As high ranking as I was there was some things even I didn't know about like the things that man did
We didn't even know which branch of the secret police he belonged to
Why we couldn't even figure out whose chain of command he was supposedly following
He was given free reign entertained as many people as he cared to for no real reason and never had to report it
We all Wonder to ourselves how can you do that
He was only the rank of Captain but unbelievably his office was somehow headquartered in a luxurious man
Yes
He was called the man of red rose Mansion I believe
Are you saying that this Captain was involved
He was a very elegant quiet man who kept to himself
He never wore a uniform and he loved having tea and cake
What was his real name it was Franz bonaparta
I see
Bonaparta however I'm not certain if that was his actual name
Bonaparta was also known to have a pseudonym
Why would he need one well you see he was also the author of a children's book
Are you afraid of the store
I was reading a picture book in here
In the door opened someone came back home
Children's
F*** that's right it was a strange picture book it was called the nameless monster
There's nothing in here Nina
This memory is real I've been here before I was
A picture book sitting here by myself the one who opened the door and came back
What's me
How could that be
I was greeting myself
Welcome home