Has there been any change in his condition
Well up no but doctor and his pulse and blood pressure
Dr Tim
What about mayor Rodgers operation
Let's begin the surgery
Right
Wait
What's our patient's name
I want to know the boy's name
Well
We don't even know his name
It's all right
Hang in there
I'll save you
We have a problem those kids TW
Did you search the entire hospital I already checked
But they're both gone maybe they're off playing hide and seek or something like that
They're off playing hide and seek
Something like that
Scaredy kitchen
Where you hiding at this time get out here you big baby
Keep it up and you're going to pee your pants again just like last time
It's getting
Play kids time for everybody to head on home okay
All right later okay
Wait I'm still here
Hold on guys I was right here all this time
I want someone find me already please I'm right
Come find me
Scaredy
That man who stopped by earlier this evening he's still standing in front of the main gate sir
How should I proceed who is he
He said he was Richard Brown psychologist
Brown being that private detective you hired
I'll just go at check them from the premises sir my son I need you to tell me what
Say when you look at this man right he's short and older
What about his character look deeper I think he's a good person I couldn't tell you
Tell you why
And now I'm staring into his eyes and a desperate man is staring back at me
I understand
Thank you for agreeing to see me Mr chevald
I know it's late
Well thanks a wasted on me doctor
My patients run short
Speak your peace and be on your way I agree let's cut right to the chase
You'll be happy to know the length of this conversation depends entirely on you
I'm assuming you came here to talk about the boy
About joh
Yeah silence speaks volumes doctor
I knew this day would come eventually that sooner or later someone like you would knock on my door
And maybe shed some light on the grand mystery mystery how
A person could ever be that perfect I
Imagine having one site just confuses the matter but I can always sense it yes the
So something so unerringly precise like Johan I feel as though he's not of this world
Not at all I do oh he's very much of this world I assure you and he's left a paper trail
Just like the rest of us and here it is
I'll read these now with your permission trust me is imperfections Run Deep
It all started back in 1986 when a nearly dead young boy was rushed to the emergency room
Social dwarf with a gunshot wound to the Head
And that's when he started up as one of your student readers
My murdered friend Richard had a theory
He theorized that Johan was the one who put the foreign boy up to pretending to be your son in the first place
It worked
Damn well but then you're real son entered the picture and Johan changed plans
He quickly latched on to Carl
And foreign was a loose end
He put far enough to one last thing
Suicide
Sir how did you come to be reunited with your long lost
It's Quite a feat after all this time
I want you to think very carefully about how many people close to you have died over the last few years
The driver who had worked for you so unfailingly
The maid who read books to you
The accounted with whom you'd go bird watching
Dead
Every last one of them
Yo Yohan murdered them all don't you see that
To create an empty space in your heart and then fill it himself we have to drag that boy's evil into the light of day but
But I can't do it without your help Mr shuvald
If we don't do something to stop Johan right now
Dr Tenma will
Didn't you say Johan toys with people is always playing with a line of ants taking Delight in
To him where nothing but insects
You must know what people call me
That Infamous nickname of my
Oh yes
The much feared vampire of Bavaria
I'll be straight with you that nickname please me very much
I'd push myself harder and harder never relenting and oh how it did grow
I would swell the monster inside me
But to whatever
They speak my name with such reverence but now I'm a withered husk
I too long to toy with people as though they were nothing more than a line of ants
Just like this
I see that boy fast becoming the person I tried so hard to be
They worship the Dragon for he had given his authority to the Beast and they worship the Beast
Saying who is like the Beast and who can fight against it
The revelation of St John the Divine
Is it not
The only thing that can defeat the Beast
Would be a monster more fearsome than the first
Father
What was that about you talked all night
Tell me Carl where's your heart
Oh he said he's heading straight to the ceremony after he wraps things up at Esther hoven's office
But father
You're looking pretty worn out if you want me to cancel your appearance I will
No let's get ready to go to the ceremony
You're not to blame
You did your job as a doctor and you did your best you are not to blame
Please live on and continue to save as many people as you are able to
That's a real
So you're going to call it quits huh
And just when you were really starting to get the hang of it
Thanks again for the job sir
Well be sure to visit if you ever down this way
Sure
Well
Goodbye
She was such a pleasant little thing too
Hello
May I speak to load of Frank please
Oh I'm sorry
I
In that case
Could you let her know I'm leaving Munich on the 3:00 train
Yes of course
Oh and what was your name again de
It's Nina
Nina Fortner
The vampire is bavar
Out in the sun know this
He'll hear you
You have seen the guest list right of course that's a real Who's Who and not just a Bavaria
Business figures from all over Europe and Japan even ambassadors and government officials this is hardly a simple book
Donation ceremony wouldn't you agree yeah they say every move shoe called mix sends ripples throughout Europe
He plays the continency economy like a marionette this is his first public appearance and I don't know how long
They all turned out to see the legend in person Charities fine but donating his personal Library like this
Doesn't it seem a bit well final hey don't say that he's the Keystone of the EU
We can't have him calling it a day just yet
Yes
I forgot some papers I need you to go retrieve them for me
Oh sure what kind of papers are they
Just go to the mansion and get them
They're on the desk in the study
But father you
Yohan will be here soon enough
Leave everything to him
Okay
What's going on with the investigation inspector
Why it's proceeding smoothly
With my information I thought you were ready to exonerate him
But you haven't done a damn thing with it did you even bother to check on true Vault secretary Johan Liebert
Don't you see there's absolutely no doubting he's The Mastermind behind all of these murders are you even listening to me if
You don't hurry if you don't hurry and take action tell him we'll stop Johan the only way he can
Calm yourself doctor
My investigation is going exactly as planned I assure you
If that's all
Yo honey it's real he's right in front of us
Open your eyes loon game
Indeed spoken like a true criminal psychologist
He's right in front of us
I Harbor no doubt regarding johann's existence
Johan does exist
Within 10ma's head that is
So what's the latest have you gathered any new information
Nope this guy keeps singing the same old song
The gun in question turned out to be a Mauser sr-93
Says he sold it to a Japanese man
You want us to tighten the screws
No
That's probably the extent of what he knows
Yeah
A Mauser sr-93 is a sniper rifle unless I'm mistaken
High Precision model
Come on Earth could he be targeting
I am 10
I am Kensington and I've recently come into possession of a
Powerful sniper rifle my name is Tenma
But sometimes my name is Johan Liebert I killed
The hospital directors and now I have this High Precision Gun I killed several
Village couples across Germany and now who am I going to kill next
I am chaos incarnate I embr
You should probably eat something you know
Thank you teacher
I'm okay
I'm just a little tired that's all
I'm not throwing in the towel no sir
I know I'm not much to look at these days Dieter but I served as a medic with the border patrol I'm still plenty tough
I'm going to save your Dr friend no matter what
I promise
Don't underestimate a former police doctor
No
Since you went to the trouble of making me all this
I think I'll dig in
I mean no one should fight on an empty stomach right Peter
Of course
Hey where are you going to ceremony you wait here
Tim is there right don't follow me Peter
I need to speak with Hans gay or chewball Now call his estate yes sir
Unless I've got the date wrong today's is book donation ceremony at the University of Munich Library
We've got an emergency I know 10 minutes next Target and
Shoe V
And so in light of his generous donation
It's only fitting that we honor our benefactor
Please help me welcome Mr Hans Georg suval
Where is your heart is my secretary in the library
He's right over there
You come
I brought him back to life
Mad monster I brought him back
Florida I'm so glad you came
I tried
But the person I'm looking for
I'm not going to find them here after all
And we were just getting to be friends too
I'm sorry your twins right
You got to be you look just like him
You are aren't you well aren't you
What's this picture book
Cuz this is what he was looking at when he started screaming