You're looking very well
And how's your job everything going smoothly
I'm happy you're doing well
Is Rosemary all right
How she adjusting
She's doing fine
She's made a lot of new friends
That's terrific
Sounds like she's fitting in
Yeah that's really good news
She's becoming used to her new school
It's getting to be quite late
But right now before I forget
I brought you some pictures their new ones of Rosemary
I prefer to see her in person
How about 2 days from now we could meet here again
Fact is I'm completely sober my life's back to normal again
Well
Actually this may be the first time my life's been truly normal
It's finally clear to me how much I've screwed up
I'm going to let her decide whether she wants to see you or not
Yeah
I'm really hoping she will
Richard I have to go now or I'll be late
Sia
Yes sir
Just more coffee please
Dr rifine
What's your impression of this man
Tell me something Richard
Precisely why do you think you're here
Well
You're here for counseling I asked a questions remember
And as I've told you before I'm a doctor not a fortune teller
Right you're inside comes from your years of experience with patience
So who's the boy in the photo this time
A person of interest in my case
He made the initial discovery of Edmond Farms body at the alleged suicide scene
Supposedly he's a friend of the deceased that's all I know well here's what I know Richard yeah
You're a dedicated workahol
But you've got to learn to take time for yourself to relax I'm beginning to do just that we'll wonders never
Cheese and doctor I have news
About what
Rosemary
I might be able to see her very soon
Well you must be looking forward to that
Yeah but just remember
If you do get to see her you can't get back the time you've lost you need to be emotionally prepared for
Changes in her
No matter what and listen you must not touch a drop of alcohol am I clear don't worry I
I won't I suppose you're off to work on your case again
Don't leave yet
I think it's time to talk about the event that got you kicked off the police force tell me Richard what do you remember from that day
Well I remember all of it
He was 16 years old
And a suspected murderer
I've been drinking on the job when I spotted him
My shot I'm dead
He died because I was drunk
You faced up to it
But that doesn't erase it it will always be there
And nothing can remove that memory from your head
So do you know what's important now giving myself permission to move on
That's correct
You may step to the Head of the Class do I get an A+ Professor not so fast
I don't give out perfect scores easily I demand results and besides I'm not all that crazy about perfect patience
They're boring frankly
Neumann
A business admin student in the economics department at Munich University apparently he told that prostitute
Opposing is Margo Langer that he too is shoe volts real son
At this point I don't know whether he was telling the truth or not
However I need to investigate that possibility
Yes excuse me I finished all the cleaning so I'll be going now
Yeah
Thanks for all your hard work
Cleaning for you is never hard work
It's pretty rare for a man living by himself to be so neat
It makes my job here extremely Pleasant
Well lately I've been trying to clean up my act on all fronts
I couldn't help but notice
You've got a new picture of your daughter
Yes
I may be able to see her soon
Really that's just wonderful your daughter will be so delighted do you really think so of
What young girl wouldn't be happy to see her father
Yeah it was a tough one
So were you able to turn your paper in on time
Carl Norman I can't figure you out
If you know for sure then why haven't you told shuvall that you're his son
Are you just another con man or are you the real deal
If you're legit
What is stopping you
Don't you realize that any parent would be overjoyed just to see their own child
I'm so sorry
She said she doesn't want to see you
Oh well
That's fine
She's made up her mind I didn't want to force her it's her decision hey that's okay
Don't worry about it
It's
I've got to go
Yeah
Fine
Yes
What can I get for you sir
Here you go
Then I'll just go where he is and you can find us there no you can't oh Carl
When you're all grown up you can meet your father if you want don't hate him if he turns you away promise me
That no matter what because Mommy doesn't hate him keep
This with you always it was a gift from your father on the day you were born
With none to admire them
The daffodils of Loris proudly bloom
With none to mind them
The Trees of Peoria Russell
The bloody tracks of the nameless man
That was wonderful
I must say Norman you come a long way and become an excellent reader
Thanks very much sir
I'm impressed by how much your Latin has improved in the short time you've been reading for me to be perfectly honest
I'm being tutored by someone
Well he certainly is an excellent teacher
Would he be anybody I know
Johan
Johan Liebert is my tutor
Yoh
A proficient young man
Yes
And not only in Latin
He has an extensive knowledge of Law and economics and amazing aptitude in fact for whatever
Studies
He's a boy who's beautifully gifted at everything he's True Perfection
Mr shoe
What would you think if a boy like him
What if Yohan Liebert was actually your real son
Then he smiled
It was the first time I'd ever seen him smile
He made it clear
That you're worthy enough
To be his son Johan
To be honest I was jealous
No matter which way I looked at it you came off better than me
I'm ashamed to admit it but I do envy you
Why don't you just tell him
Come on Carl what have you got to lose go ahead and tell you his real son will you stop it
How many times must I tell you I have no intention of doing that
What would be the point if I did
He would never believe me
And worse than that
Then he'll think of me as just another greedy Predator only interested in getting hold of his fortune
He'll despise me forever
How my mother lived her life until her death
And with everything I've gone through up till now
He knows nothing about me
And I won't stand for him thinking I'm after his fortune when he doesn't know a thing
That's exactly why you should go talk to him
You have to gain his trust make him understand the truth about his son
He'll never believe that I miss son
Well don't you have something from your past that would prove it to him
Anything he might recognize or remember
You know something you both could recall
No there's nothing
Far as I know
Think back
There must be something
I'm drawing a big blank it doesn't matter I don't want to tell him okay
If that's the case can you explain why you spend all that time having me tutor you in Latin
Wasn't it because you wanted to please him
Because you wanted to make him proud of you
I'm thinking that maybe
I should quit my job being his reader
Yeah
It's for the best
Thanks for all your concern I appreciate it
But I guess I'm done
Johan
I feel you're entitled to know
The truth
I do have something that
Can prove who I am
Well what is it
It's dumb I don't know why I'm still holding on to it I'm not going to convince him and I don't need to
My foster parents are coming to visit me next week
I've been fooling myself
I'm not the son he'd want to have
So I see
When your mind's made up it's important not to waver so for the time being Carl I think it would be a good idea
Idea to let me keep an eye on your proof
We're so happy to hear your studies are going well
Isn't that right mother
But I've been worried about you Kyle I want to make sure you're eating right I'm always eating out so I know I have to
Have to be careful not to gain any weight better stay away from your mother's cooking too but it's so delicious
How's your social life son
Are you making a lot of new friends here
I've got some people I hang out with and can talk to you about anything
Terrific
It's always good to have friends yes that's very true and it looks to us like you're doing quite well
I'm extremely grateful to both of you
That I can even be here
Whoa what's this all of a sudden there's no need for thanks
For years I was shuttled from one foster home to another where no one cared about me
But you two have treated me with such kindness that's because you're a wonderful young man we both think so
That's right girl
Thank you for everything you've given me Mr and Mrs Lindner
Isn't it about time you stop calling us Mr and Mrs
We came here hoping that you would finally accept our offer
We know this is been hard for you
But now
With college treating you so well mother and I were wondering if you'd made up your mind
Have you decided to become our adopted son Carl
We believe in you and we want you to succeed
We trust you
Trust us don't you oh absolutely
We understand why you might still be a little hesitant
There's a chance your real parents are still alive
No matter how much effort we make
We can never be your birth parents but maybe there's no maybe about it
Because the both of you
Or is real to me as my birth parents could ever be
Oh my
Let's have a toast
Feel like some expensive champagne son yeah
Waiter bring us to Champagne list we're celebrating today's a special day
Hello
Carl speaking
Hello Carl it's me
Do you know who this is
Mr schuvalt
Now what's this I hear about
You quitting your job
Right
That's very disappointing
I'm sorry for any inconvenience this might cause
I just hate to see you abandon your lat
You put so much hard
Thank you for your concern sir
It really is a shame
I'm going to miss you you know
As a favor to me
If you don't mind
Would you read to me
One last time
Sure
It'll be my pleasure
How about the third chapter of
From EOS to lemnos
A splendid choice
That mysterious sea
Beckons for the death of even the god Phoebus
What other pleasure could there be
Than to wish death
Upon the Sons and Daughters of Cerberus
Now
Move forward softly whisper Zeus
Move forward move on
And dance in the temple that belongs to the dark gods
The gods of Juno who dwell in the sea
The Earth
And the heavens
From the summit of the Parthenon steal the forbidden apple of Campania
And bring forth
The apple and everything
Everything to save my soul
Bring
Everything to see my soul
Mr schufold but your phone call
Magnificent so heartfelt and meaning
The best I've heard in my whole life
Why did you keep this from me is is that mine
This rabbit's foot holds so many memories I gave it to Margo a long time ago
A good luck charm I wanted to pass that luck to you
This is yours Carl
My son
I've put you through so much
Oh Father I found my
Fun
This is all thanks to one person
He told me about everything his help was invaluable so from now on
You'll be working for me as my secretary he is a young man who can be Trust