That's
It'll be okay now little bird it's your home and respect it
Never again will blood be shed in this Forest isn't that right
So you don't remember anything
I need you to take your time and try to think back to the roof
Any detail you can remember about what you were doing up there would be helpful
Martin you have to tell the doctor what happened if you hadn't hit the Eve on the first floor and got caught in the tree you would
Hi do you understand
Please Martin just talk to the doctor if you don't we're never going to put all this foolishness
Please try to stay calm
If you were to die I don't know what
I just don't
It's all right mad
I'm here to see that your son gets the counseling he needs
I know I know it's just look why don't you take this
Conversation outside
No Peter I want you to behave yourself while I'm gone and remember you're not allowed
Inside that room
That boy
I see your grandson
No I'm just taking care of him for a while
Hi there
Hi yourself
My name is Dieter
I'm Martin
Does it hurt
Does what
That stuff
All the cuts under your bandages
When you fell off the roof but that was really scary for you
Hey what are you doing you shouldn't be standing up
My shoes are in that bag down there on the floor
Get them for me
I can't
You've got to lie down
Look just get the shoes
Where do you think you're going you're going to get yelled at
Why should I care if someone yells at me
It's not like I'm afraid to get yelled at
It's just like he told me
If you come back alive step outside
The world will be different
Now the world didn't change
I'm the one who changed
You see I'm one of the special few who've been
I'm so bored
I never realized how boring this world is
Hey look out
Come on hurry up there's really nothing
Nothing to be afraid of
What did you do that for
Check it out look how scared this guy is Martin
No just look at him Peter someone
Please help me I don't want to die yeah
Yes you're lucky cuz I'm going to let you live
I haven't answered that question
You said you thought that falling off the roof was scary for me right
Yeah
I did
Falling wasn't even a bit scary
After all it's just a game
Just a game
So many people have died cuz of it
But it's so much fun
Who cares about those guys
Two people stand facing each other on the edge of the roof of an empty building then you close your eyes
And walk towards each other one step at a time it's like a duel and it doesn't matter whether
Where you fall or not if you survive you win right play a game like that
You do it so that you can bet against fate those who manage to survive are the chosen ones
How can I put this in a way you'll understand the Survivor gets to keep playing over and
Over again yeah but Martin why play the game at all cuz everything else is boring that's
That's why but the game is real fun and the best part is playing it again once Fate has made you a
Don't you get it and I thought for
Sure that you must be one of us fine I'll show you if you don't get it after seeing
Nothing you really are stupid
Hey hey you're not really planning on going
Going up to the roof are you yeah cuz I'm chosen the superior will always survive
Just like him just like who the person who taught us the game you dummy and who
He's a friend a friend to all the children who've been chosen
Now hurry up get over here I don't think I want to stop whining and
Let's go with me but you need to understand
The scars who did that to you that it was your
You still want to be a part of this worth
Even after everything they've done to you come on you have to see
What
Do you think how's the view how does it make you feel
Oh come on there's nothing to be afraid of stand up close your eyes and take a
Stan Dieter
I understand now
I get what you've been saying and I'll make sense to me
I thought the world was filled with darkness that the future would bring nothing but more
I mean like what's your favorite food
I hate this really good sausage the other day but if I die I'll never get to eat it again
You're such a coward
You're so weak
And the secretary Miss Meredith is nice to me if I die I'll never see him again
They're always things to be scared of learning to deal with that is part of growing up
10 minutes told me tomorrow is going to be a good day
If I die I will never get to see denim again
I'm going to fall
Don't Panic just don't stand up yet
It can't be like him
I can't feel like you want I just can't what did you say Johann
It even scarier game than this one he said that he was going to be killed soon
He said that he was going to be shot by a Japanese guy
I was my
And I walked across the edge of the roof
I'm not kidding I really did walk it
I wasn't scared at all you know
You're walking was supposed to be walking across from me but when I opened my eyes he wasn't there anymore
I really saw it
He fell off the building and died right in front of me
People really die
Anyone want tea
Thank you
Honestly I just don't know about my son he doesn't seem to understand what he's done
I'm glad he's still alive but when I think of what poor Yorkie's parents are going through
I just hope you managed to talk some sense into him
At least he seems to listen to you
She gets on my case like that every day
Seriously she doesn't understand anything
She won't let me out of the house or watch TV or even read my comics
Nothing's worse than boredom
I'll bring you something to help pass the time
Really
You may not be allowed to read comics
But a picture book should be okay
Serious
A picture book
That sounds pretty stupid to me
Hey tell me about that freaking new game you said you were playing
You said you were going to be shot and killed like any minute now
Now that is exciting
So come on when is that Japanese guy going to shoot you spell it Yohan
Herman Hesser
The first edition of Steppenwolf and this our first edition of hofmann's night pieces
To complete anthology of Curtis poetry
This is very impressive
Despite being the head librarian of the University of Munich Friedrich Emmanuel Campus Library I'm simply
Dazzled by your collection I managed to make my way through life without a proper College educ
I made up for this by reading every book I could get ahold
Well your decision to donate this collection is a Priceless gift to the university I cannot begin to express
Press my gratitude my eyes are failing and I've lost the key Envision that reading requires
I'd much rather these books be accessible to your students than sitting here in my private Stacks collecting
Of course you have a number of Priceless books here but I would also prefer to make them available to the
Oh that reminds me we've just finished arranging storage for them and would it be possible to arrange a meeting
At the library to discuss holding a ceremony of some sort well how's the security there
There are a few dangerous organizations we've had to keep an eye on ever since Mr scheuval re-entered public life
We just want to make sure you review your guest list thoroughly wouldn't you agree Yohan
Of course
It was Johann and Carl who thought up the idea of donating The Collection they'll make all the necessary arrangement
I'm getting on the head librarian
Pleasure to meet you
The pleasure is all mine
This is where we'll be storing Mr schewald's collection
The general public is not allowed entry
You've never been here have you
Of course will maintain the appropriate temperature and humidity for preserving the books as well as protective measures against
And stuffed on fire
What an amazing collection of books
A Real Testament to mankind isn't it
Oh it's a testament
You're absolutely right
And this is the central Hall where we plan to hold the donation ceremony with your appro
The library Security will be tightened
Just as Mr schewald's assistant requested we want our benefactor to feel safe as possible here
Thank you
I'm sure that my father will be more than happy to attend
Isn't that right Johan
Is there something wrong
No
It's nothing
Would you excuse me please
Are you looking for something
Yes
I was on the hunt for a picture book for a good friend of mine
For a friend you say
Yes
For a friend in need
Let's see
Well I think I would recommend this one
The illustrations are beautiful
Oh yes
But it might be just a tattoo grown up
I'm sorry I assumed your friend was a bit older
If that's the case then how about this one
Oh no
Thank you very much sir
How embarrassing I'm so clumsy this happens all the time
How about this one
It's a beautiful book I highly recommend it
Did that one catch your eye
Oh my
That is beautiful
Who's the author of this
I'm sorry may I
It's a
Sarah
Moravia publishing
It's a check publishing company in Prague
There are quite a few talented writers publishing picture books in Czechoslovakia
I don't think I've ever heard of cheruba before
Perhaps he's just not very well known
Is everything all right
Help somebody please help
Man this summer heat is really starting to get to me
Just awful
Right here
It'll all end here on this spot