Hey wait up
What the hell are we doing here anyway
Come on let's get out of here I don't give up there's no use for this guy
Guess I'll be starving and bro forever
Only I still had that rock
Damn it
The hell's that supposed to be
A message
The monster inside me
About to explode what is this supposed to mean he has a
Personality
Let's see if I got this
So you told us when you arrived at the warehouse
You witnessed the Asian man in the arsonist engaging in a verbal argument
According to your statement on it as soon as the Asian man saw you there he quickly fled
So Ms Liebert is that exactly how you saw it
Yes sir
Well it's good that Firebug ended up turning himself in
You confess that he's a right-wing extremist said he was celebrating his people when he let the fire anyway Ms Libra
Records clean so that's all we need from you today we do appreciate your cooperation
So then you're saying that I can go home now Detective
Yes ma'am
Oh hold on
There's one thing I forgot to ask about the townsfolk refer to the Asian man you mentioned is Dr tin
Ms Lieber
You wouldn't happen to know anything else about this guy would you
No I don't know anything about him
Tell me what are you thinking
I'd say from the way Ms Liebert was dressed she might just be a high-class call girl
That isn't what I meant
I'm talking about Dr tinma
When we first spoke to the church from that District all of them referred to our Asian guys Dr Ten
But as soon as we told them the doctor was under investigation and suspected to be a serial killer
They got real tight left
All of a sudden none of them knew who he was
They told me I'm responsible for you now
Mr Russo
Yeah it's so great to see you I was worried about you when
Now that's more like it
Now you look more like the honor I've always known I like you better in casual clothes
Come on sit down and eat I ordered what you like enjoy
So aren't you going to eat
No thanks dear I've already eaten I'll just have me some coffee
Go on dig in thank you I am pretty hungry
What's so funny
Well that's what tastes best I say coffee isn't any good at all if it isn't sweet
It's good to see you can smile
I know you're in the middle of a big job interview and up to now you've looked quite serious
Put your smiled when you saw me put all that sugar in my coffee
Your names on
My name is Anna Liebert
So
Well miss Liebert the job's yours
Don't start today
Having a young lady like you waiting tables in my Cafe might give my business quite a boost
EX
Except
Do me a favor
Show off that smile a little more all right
When you smile it'll make everyone feel good
Thank you so much for the job I'll work very hard really
This is an Italian restaurant in a small town two tables of folks this is busy as it gets
Donna come stand over here
Sure
I'll place all the orders here on the bar and you'll take them from here to the customer's tables
All used plates go on that side of the counter
The wine is right here
And the glassware is back here
You'll find more bottles of wine Above This shelf and you're going to hang the food orders on these little hooks
So more wine is above the shelf and glassware is back there
Morning Russo
So how are you today
Good morning and welcome
I'm starving
Nice to meet you sir
My name is Anna
It's not possible I must still be dreaming no way someone is pretty as you could be a waitress in a place like this
Well you're awake and my place is classier than your thought introducing Anna our new waitress she'll be
Serving here from now on like I said I'm pleased to meet you
You really mean it
Hey Anna how about a nice plate of carbonara hey Anna I think I'll have a Bolognese
Donna dear could you please get me some more water when you have a chance
Order up one Bolognese and one carbonara alright here you go
You're a gem Anna
Any orders up
Okay
Hey Russo come on you got to tell us how you trick this cutie into working here for you I didn't have
If you're free tonight how about you let me take you out to a real restaurant it'll be fun just
Forget about trying to make time with my Anna I'd hate to have to hurt you oh boy listen to The Cry Baby Ross so
Everybody suddenly acting all tough hey where do you get a load of this last week he was at my house watching a TV movie
Calling like a baby
Another order of squid in crisotto
Summertime is playing across the street
That old movie house is screening summertime see you there
What a city Frankfurt has
Many great old movie theaters that movie was on TV just last week that one really brings me
Me to tears
Have you ever seen summertime it's touching
The whole thing takes place in Italy actually in the city of Venice
Folks don't know the history of Venice it was a port city back in medieval days and everyone called it the city of
The entire city of Venice was originally built on a lagoon there are these canals that run
Do the whole thing
I'd really like to go see it with you someday it's just beautiful
It sounds to me like you've been there before
I have
The film soundtrack is great music it's very well composed
I bet you've heard it's theme song
I'd say most folks have heard it it was a popular very well known song
Tell me how does it go
Let's see
Hey I know let's go across the street and see it right now we've missed some but they'll still let us in
My life
Some other time it is kind of late and you're still eating
Sorry
Well I'm back
Great
So how was your break
No thanks I can handle it
I appreciate you letting me take off a few hours from work every afternoon
That's no problem it's always slow around this time of the day
And I don't want to be nosy but
Where do you go everyday
Hey forget I ask
It's your private time it's none of my business where you go
Good morning how to shoot a gun
Oh learning to shoot
You're learning at wrinkles Place huh
He's good people
Tell me Mr Russo have you ever shot a gun before
Me shooting guns no way honestly I get all nervous just looking at them
Here you go sir enjoy thank you very much
How do I do this time take a taste
No you should try it
Tell me what's it taste like
Like there's some garlic olive oil parsley and not much else
We're gone right
That just means you're having learned how to make it proper
This cooking stuff
Anything worth learning takes practice
I'm all done with the bathroom Mr Rosso
I'm heading for bed now so
When I was younger I never realized that movies like this existed
Mr Rosso
Movies have always affected you deeply
That's true
When I was younger I always wanted to watch movies but with work I never had the time to
Back then I ate a lot of fabulous meals but to be really honest I never felt any of them had any taste
Flavor
I didn't even appreciate the taste of sugar then
Really is that the truth
You know my past
Isn't that right Anna
Well after you left I checked up on you
And I know what happened
You really need a Fortuner
You disappeared 2 years ago after your parents were murdered
Exactly what were you looking for me to do what
Looking for me to do a hit or did you want me to teach you to kill
I guess I wanted to learn from you that was it
So how did you find out about me and what I did
From one of my professors at law school he had done research on you and all the cases you were involved in
The restaurant in Nino case
Osaka Milano case
A sub 18 murder case
You were called into court to testify in all three of those murder cases
And in each of those cases
All charges were dropped due to a complete lack of evidence
However my professor came up with a theory about it that made sense
There was only one conclusion
A world class Hitman committed all three of the murders and he said that you
You were that man
I suppose you want to know how many people I
To be honest with you I can't even remember
I was never a good kid
And before I knew what was what I was in way over my head
Robbery blackmail if you can name it then I did it
And eventually I became a hitman
I rewarded Myself by eating very well
I never had any feelings about it it was just my job
I was wondering I was doing
Doing what I always did waiting to kill some faceless guy
It was sunny and he was
I've been doing it so long I was numb I didn't know how many I killed or who was next
I had him as good as Dad
He had ordered a coffee and as I watched he started putting sugar in it
One spoonful two spoonfuls
Three four after the
5th spoonful he stopped black moment started me finally tasting the
Coffee I drink when I saw how he was enjoy
Good coffee I couldn't do it
That was the day I put my gun down for good
That part of my life is done
I know I can't kill people and steal their Simple Pleasures
After all the time we spent together I don't get it
You never asked me to teach you how to kill someone
I decided
I decided that getting you involved wouldn't be right
Do you really have to go Nina
Goodbye
Thank you for everything Mr Rosso
You should know killing is easier than you think
You just have to forget how sweet the sugar is