Where's the crime scene down those stairs how many victim
Three men detective you can start looking for any evidence up here before we start taking any action should
We wait for detective crotchi to arrive I mean I'm taking charge here start looking for Witnesses
Or anyone suspicious but there aren't any people around here I said look for anyone suspicious
But no one's here moving
I'm detective soup
Prague police
Is crime scenes go this one is pretty brutal
Inspector Zema
So bad we can't even make out his facial features face is completely unrecogniz
I guess it's good he had his police ID with him otherwise we wouldn't have been able to figure out who he was
The bodies of two other men are over there we haven't been able to figure out who
They are one took a gunshot to the Head the other was beaten to death like the inspector
Preserve the crime scene detective soup wait
Yeah so I haven't found anyone suspicious yet sir
I'm telling you
Stinks
They make fun of me just because I'm a rookie the other police guys all look at me like I'm crazy when I give them an order
You have to work to earn their respect before the listen to you he's right I'm a detective yeah
Rookie Det
And when you got to the crime scene you took one look and lost your lunch
Just because you grew up liking cop TV shows doesn't mean you can do the job
John you always got carried away even when we were back in college
Yeah what do you know about how I feel
Inspector's name on was murdered
He always treated me like I was his own son
When I started I didn't know anything
But inspectors him on was there for me
Batman taught me what it takes to be a real Detective
I respected him you know for caring enough to help out a guy like me you needed a hand
I will avenge his senseless death if it's the last thing I do
I swear I'll track down his killer and I will make him pay okay well
We have a staff meeting early tomorrow morning John hey what kind of friends are you it's still early
I'm fighting for justice to protect both of you so come on support your local police and let's have another round
Just one more what do you say hey got it out crime fighter
You know we're out there working for justice
Meant to get murdered but so sad
That's a hell of a hole board
Hey young what are you looking at
It hurts that girl from the grocery store huh
I've seen that girl twice when I went to the supermarket
It was after working night Duty
That's her
I really wanted to introduce myself to her then but I didn't
Looks like I've got another chance
Hey John don't even try it she's way too pretty to go for a guy like you seriously
Hello
Hi there
You don't happen to remember me from the supermarket
No I guess you don't
I have wanted to talk to you for a while oh my name is Yan Suk
And I'm not some random butterfly
I may not look it but I'm a policeman
Actually I'm a detective but don't be scared of me
I'm off duty now
I just wanted to meet you
Man I don't think she's even said a word to
Yeah he's striking out we better go give him a hand sorry for butting in
Her friend here is feeling pretty depressed any chance you could talk to him for a bit something terrible happened to the superior
He's all broken up oh yeah he's been pretty depressed come on I haven't acted depressed at all
I never met a person as kind as he was inspector's name on was an inspiration to me
And his murderer took that great man away from us I know I'll find a way to bring him to just
Oh wow
Here I am doing all the Talking sorry
You're passionate about what you believe you've got to try your best to catch his killer
Oh I can't believe this I finally get the chance to talk to you and I haven't even asked you about yourself yet
So I what's your name
I wish I knew my real name
But I don't what well maybe I can help you yeah I'll figure out who you are I think
People is part of my job maybe I can guess your name
After all I am a detective now I'm betting your name is I told you I don't even know my name
So there's no way you can guess it
I'll tell you two things I know about myself
Chaddock Bridge
And three frogs
And that's all I know
Wait a second when can I see what did we tell you
You blow it next time try picking one that's not so pretty
All right we've identified the two men murdered at the same time as Inspector zamon
Victim number one is just mere
This other guy is yakovsuit
Turns out they were both sergeants in the secret police
After the fall of socialism they went underground and started getting up to all sorts of no good
After analyzing blood of the crime scene we found something
Besides them on Murat and sewageek we all need someone else's blood at the murder scene
Someone with blood type A B r h positive
Judging from the amount of blood we found we know they were seriously in
At present we're trying to actively determine that person's identity
Detective soak
Soup wake
Yes sir what on Earth were you just daydreaming about
We have lost a billion officer inspector Simon we're facing a dire situation and your daydreaming here
I'm very sorry sir
Anyhow
According to a witness there was a man seen walking away from the murder scene at a time we feel was immediately after the crime
Is described as a tall thin man in his 40s carrying a large duffel bag looking like a tourist
No I want all of you to get out there and track that guy down
Oh well
That girl
Guess she won't be back
Mr Detective
Did you find your friends killer
Have any luck
Not yet
It takes time
But I did get more information that might help
The inspector
He was
Investigating a murder case just before he died
Tell me more
This Old Man
He was running his own illegal orphanage
Somebody shot both him and his maid
All morning
Zayman was busy questioning the man who discovered that crime scene
Who was he
You know
Who was the man who found the bodies
We seem nice
He was a tall skinny looking guy
He was visiting from out of town
Yeah this big heavy duffel bag
Tough and man
And he was carrying a big duffel bag
Could it be
That man being questioned do you know where he is
Yeah
I think I do know I'll call the station and check
Come on pick up
You go get him Mr Detective come on not again
Yeah I'm here
And three frogs
Wait shut up Bridge
That's over in mikosk
I need to find those three frogs
That they are
If I come here I bet I'll see her again
He checked out
See the Grimmer Mr Grimmer
Ah it says here Mr Grimmer checked out the day before yesterday in the morning
There's no dou
I know exactly who murdered the inspector
It was Grimmer he slept here in this room
Damn
Why couldn't I have figured this whole thing out two days ago
Don't worry inspector
I'll still catch that bastard
I swear
Hey
My word detective soup what are you doing here
Chief detective patella I could ask you the same sir
I see
Ah using your witch you progress this far all by yourself that's impressive
Thank you
Answer
I knew I'd be the first
To make a breakthrough in this case I just knew I would
And I won't stop doing all I can to make sure that cop killer is apprehended
Yeah you really pulled things together here great job thanks Chief now I'm ordering you to do me a favor here
Here and keep this whole thing top secret
Huh
But Grimmer killed them all the clues lead to that conclusion we can't just let him just hold on Detective
This case is a little more complicated than you think it is what
Inspector zaimon had been assigned to a special investigation
It was top secret
Wait the inspector
Was working Undercover
Right he was investigating former Czechoslovakian secret police agents some of them had faked their records and we're working
His officers on the Prague police force
Inspector zaymon was working with members of the check secret police
You know those two corpses we found with zaymon
Both of them were formally checked secret police
And aside from myself and the chief
Almost no one knows about this
Don't stick your nose In Too Deep you could get yourself killed
Not a word to anyone about this
Got it
Buster
What should I be doing regarding this case just slow down Grimmer might come back to this hotel at any moment
So you need to be here keep your eyes peeled yes sir
By the way so
You happen to find yourself a girlfriend yet at the briefing as you sat there you had this smitten look
Who's the lucky girl she's not really my girlfriend sir
She just hangs out at this bar where I usually go
She a pretty girl
Oh yeah she's very pretty well in that case introduce me to her what's the name of that bar now
I wouldn't feel right about doing that sir
But didn't you just tell me she's not your girlfriend well I suppose that's true but
Soup sends his regards honey
Well hey he wasn't kidding you really are a beauty
Who are you
Glad you asked I'm one of six bosses but tell us my name
We were talking and he said that there's a real beauty that he meets here
He couldn't come tonight he's stuck doing a Stakeout
How about I buy you a drink
Hey come on honey don't leave why not just one little drink
Hey there soup oh
Detective piano check it's you good morning sir
Patella and I had a little chat
He met that girl you're going after said she's a real knockout so you went to that bar I talked to
See you about
Oh yeah
But you didn't do anything to her did you sir please say you didn't and come on Suk don't
So excited my boy yeah but
Everyone at the station knows the cheap hotel here really has a way with women
Relax she gave me the cold shoulder pretty quick
That Galley yours must be a pretty tough cookie
Most girls fall for him in a heartbeat it's true she's a nice girl
I I mean she's a good listener and interesting to talk to
It's fun just to be around her she's cool
You're not talking to me are you
Anyways Chief our back wants you to meet him right now and inspector's name on his office oh yes sir
Oh yeah that reminds me
Someone gave me these when a whiskey bonbon
Nope I'm off candy fine hey silk you want to Bon bun no thank you sir I'm okay
Hey hold on a second
Yes sir
Don't say a word to the chief about our tall thin suspect
Right
Poor zemon
What a way to go
Looks like his desk is pretty much been cleaned out
All that's left are these two boxes of his personal stuff see to it that is Widow gets it
Looks like a key for a gym locker
God that smells
Nothing in here but sweaty shirts stinky socks and moldy towels
A notebook
What the heck is this
Stop detailed Personnel files
Of everyone that's on the force oh wow
It's even got my whole record in here
Inspector zaiman had been assigned to a special investigation it was top secret
Right he was investigating former Czechoslovakian secret police agents some of them had faked their records and were working as
Officers on the Prague police force
There's something missing
Two files aren't in here
Chief detective patellas and detective Yeti checks
You're right Detective
This is a suspiciously large amount of cash that's why I brought it here chief
So tell me soak I want to hear some eyes about inspector same on from these things that you found
Closer it appears that inspector zaymon was conducting an internal investigation
And as a result he discovered the detectives patella and janicek worked previously in the
Old regime has agents for the Czechoslovakian secret police I think
And it makes me sad to say this sir the inspector must have taken all that cash is hush money
In return for keeping quiet about the truth
The implications of this evidence are serious I know
I feel sick to saying it detective soak yes sir
I need to keep this matter completely to yourself we'll talk again later
Return to your regular duties yes sir
I never
Thought this would happen yeah things have become complicated
We were playing stupid to do what we did
Why we take a guy like soup so light
And we haven't even settled the matter with this guy glimmer that killed Zam
And now there's an even bigger issue that we have to face
So then do we offer the rookie money like we did with zaymon if that doesn't work the only option is
You know
Whatever it takes
I don't want any trouble for allowing former secret police into the force
From here on we've got to keep a tighter lid on all of this
Want six gone things will be as smooth as silk
My head I sure could go for a nice drink right about now
How about a whiskey Bonbon instead
Hey there better than nothing
Besides these were a gift from a real Beauty here
Chief
What's wrong
You look depressed
I feel like I can't believe in anything anymore why
I'll help you if you want me to
I believed in him I never would have thought that inspector zaiman
What happened I believed in him
Right now the only person who I really believe in
Is