Blood pressure 120 over 80
Pulse 92
I will begin extracting the bullet
Bullet is extract
Removal process is completed
It's a little early to be relieved
We must still reinforce the walls of the damaged blood vessels
Right
80 Proline
His current blood pressure is 128 over 72 and his pulse is 88
It looks like he's still under the effects of the anesthesia
Live on kid
Survive and have a good life
Dr Boyer how did everything go it
Looks like the procedure went smoothly on your side
Yes the surgery went well at least
The mayor wasn't so lucky
Really is that so
That's very unfortunate news
You act as though his dying has nothing to do with you
The truth is doctor that you're the one who abandoned our team
Just before surgery too but wait that child was brought in before what does it matter
Who came in first the problem is you selfishly left us a man short we had to scramble to cover for you at the last minute
Somebody died now wait a minute just listen to me
We're aware that I followed the director's orders and I clearly instructed you to perform that surgery on the mayor
Did I not however you chose to ignore that order but doctor you have to understand that because of
Surgery depends on the trust among the entire staff it's a team effort and yet you decided to act on
Tyrone I've already given my report to the director
You deeply regrets this Inc
This will greatly affect our Hospital's reputation
You have only yourself to blame
So wait please wait
Doctor Tenma things are looking very good at the moment the boys blood pressure is 114 over
82 + 84 overall sir the boys vitals are very stable
Well that's good to hear the operation was amazing
After collapsing on a holiday retreat
Mel rodiger passed away at the hospital
Infar
Caused by severe infractions of the inner carotid artery
We certainly did everything we could for him but the condition caused intense swelling of the brain and it resulted in the
Will be taken to ensure a new mayor is chosen I've got to get some sleep
Which took place late last night
The terrorist
Against the
A full investigation is currently underway
And is still
In critical condition
Now the weather
The whole
Shane I wonder what it'll end up happening to the boy
On the way I'm just like him now
Mrs Reinhardt and ICU is complaining that she's having a hard time sleeping that said do you think we can
Dr Tenma
Are you listening to me
Oh I'm sorry yes in that case give a one house in tablet please that should help her get some sleep
What is with him today he's been spacing out all day long
Hey
Dr Becker it's you Alex like you're going through a bit of a tough time there
Come on fish up have you heard anything from the director yet
I did try to warn you didn't I told you the hospital is ruled by politics
I knew what I was talking about and if you played your cards right I'm sure your future would have been smooth sailing
Oh well I guess what this means is you and I are on the same boat now my young friend
Come on 10 man don't be so depressed
I know you'll get a chance to redeem yourself sooner or later
What do you say we go get some drinks that'll put a smile on your face
Hold on a second nurse excuse me
I still need to get a statement from the girl would I be able to go in and question her now
Good time
That girl has disappeared from her room what did you say
Seems like she's always slipping out of her room and wandering all over the hospital
And so the reason that Eisler Memorial Hospital has proven to be the nation's leading medical facility
He is first and foremost because we're blessed to have excellent Personnel such as yourself and I'd like to take
Take this opportunity to thank every single one of you for that
Unfortunately as you all know just yesterday the mayor passed away in our Hospital
Of course as always we did our utmost to save his life
And because of that this Hospital's reputation remains intact
And I appreciation let's have a round of applause for Dr Boyer and Dr Isen who strive to the very end to
Try and save the mayor's life
I looked over your thesis young man you did an excellent job please keep up the
A good work all right
Excuse me
Oh yeah
I'm so sorry I apologize for what happened sir
Now now don't worry my boy what's done is done
Director
You did what you thought was best you followed your heart
Why don't we just leave it at that
Thank you sir
Ladies and gentlemen may I have your attention please now a word from the head of neurosurgery
Please excuse me it looks like I'm being called up there
No you're not Timber
Allow me to introduce the newly appointed Dr Boyer please make
Your way to the microphone if you wish
You remain at this Hospital you may do so
But you'd better give up any dreams of furthering your status
It's not possible for irresponsible people such as yourself
I recognize your skill as a surgeon but that is it and you can forget about presenting any research papers at future
But but sir please listen to me you decide to transfer to another hospital I have no intention of recommending
Sending you
In other words it's useless for you to Harbor any Ambitions you have successfully tied The Noose around your own
Successful surgery requires teamwork it's only with everyone's help and cooperation
Hey please you have to talk to your father
For me make him see I haven't done anything wrong all I did was operate on an emergency patient who was brought in
There's nothing else
Is that the engagement ring I gave you such a fool
Dr Norton you're looking very handsome this evening thank you
Looking especially beautiful tonight yourself Ava
It's quite ironic really
I came to Germany after I discovered one of director heineman's papers
And as soon as I get here it takes me under his wing
So now it all makes sense that paper I was so impressed with
It was probably written by someone else someone he was grooming just like he'd been doing with me this whole time
I knew that he was really just using me
But I was hoping that when I'd reached a certain status I'd be able to make my own choices
With what I wanted to work on
Our priority is to progress as medical Scholars before we save lives don't you agree
That's not true her doctor's priority is disabled every can after all people's lives
He tells me there's a flaw in my character but what about him he says he's a doctor but he's just a greedy Bast
Bastard
He'd be better off dead
I have to thank you
I have to thank you because you helped me open up my eyes as a doctor
So survive and live a good life after all I did throw away everything in order to save you
That's how far I went to give you your life back and I would do it again
You know your name
Don't you
Your name is Anna Liebert
Isn't that right
I did try to warn you that all this was a bit too soon for her Detective
Isn't there anything we can do doctor
She saw her parents get shot to
She's fine physically and I think her trauma induced Amnesia is natural given the circumstances
Is there any chance you might be able to wait to get a statement from her after she gets better not really this is a very difficult
Okay one of the victims was a former East German diplomat
If we're not able to solve this quickly the bka will be all over our back
Those guys always come here after the fact and try and steal the show from us
I haven't got time to take things easy
Oh what if we do this yeah we let her see her brother and then she'll probably be so relieved to see him that it might help
Regain her memory
I cannot possibly agree to such a risky proposition that's completely out of the question
Besides I'm sure Dr tynma would never permit such a thing and
He's in charge of Johan her twin brother
Sure feels like I'm getting a runaround
Hey Dr Tenma you seem a little bit out of it you all right I mean you are looking awfully tired this morning
I've been so busy with emergency surgeries
Wow it seems like they've been working you to the Bone well ever since you were demoted from Chief
Well I don't mind really it actually makes me feel better
How are you really doing doctor
I'm sorry I've just been paged I need to go
Are you so sure it's a good idea to keep on going like this
Hard work won't get you anywhere
Look at this doctor Heine
Look at all the gifts and letters of encouragement
Yes there are mountains of them at his sister's room as well
The media keeps reporting on the twins heartbreaking soda after losing their parents and how they're now on
Brown and this is what we get
As far as this hospital is concerned with no one alive to pay their medical expenses and nothing but An Inconvenient now
Now so their story is a pitiful one that works for us
It only means this hospital is garnering attention think about it a moment doctor these kids are
Very valuable to us am I right or aren't I
Yes sir
Why don't we do this we'll give the media a photo of the siblings together
They'll probably be thrilled to have something like that yes that's something the media has been requesting for some time now
But the thing is just do it don't be naive it'll be a picture of the orphan sibling struggling Brave
Play the survive under the warm hearted care of our Hospital staff however the boys attending physician
Is it a still too early to allow them to see each other who's on this case
It's Dr Tenma not anymore
What's that
There's no need to leave him in a position that's getting so much attention
Just take doctor 10 Mile off the case
Yes
This is a heartfelt gift from the citizens yeah why don't you have one thank you
You're looking well Mrs hankel
How do you feel I'm feeling quite well doctor
And I owe it all to you thanks will be removing your stitches very soon so it won't be long until you
You mean I'll be able to go home soon
That's right
Just make sure you follow my instructions all you have to do is rest
You still need regular doses of anti-convulsants and anti-hypertensives okay
Anna wake up
What happened to her we brought her in to see her brother and
Then she just she just started screaming and why did you do that
But Dr timma take her back to a room doctor boy
The emotional meeting of
Of the Twins and then release a picture to the media will allowed you to do such a thing I should have been consulted I'm the boys
You've been dismissed as the boys attending physician as of today he's
My patient so I made my own judgment that it would be fine for the twins to see each other
Those children
You can turn them into a media circus we were just following the director's orders and I think it would be best
For you not to fight him I say this voice life it's my duty to protect him until he fully recovers well in
Okay just take a look
As soon as he saw his sister he reached out to her and began to cry you see he's regained Consciousness and
What is reacting normally to stimuli
Which means the surgery was a great success
So good job your work is done here
I'll get back to your post that's in order
So it was the director
Daughter's hot don't make me laugh we'll give us a damn about what the chief says bunch of greedy
They're less for power and money screw them
I'm not wrong no matter what those bastards think of me
Hello father I'm home
Father
Are you in your room
Excuse me Dr Boyer are you still in a meeting at this time of night
Hello father are you sleeping already
I'm coming in
That
Have bastard be better off today