Please tell me the runners are you Dr Tema you got it wrong my name is not
Anna I'm Nina no but that wasn't your name back when you were brought into my Hospital you were
And your brother your brother's name was Yohan
Brother
Mr
Mr motor
Mr motor Mr Fortuner it's me Dr Tema I mean Nina
She's here with me Mr Mara
All right you go on and I'll call them myself
It doesn't look like a police ever came
Oh my God
Please come back you must live
Please
I'm begging you
Tomorrow you don't have to quit smoking anymore all right
Back then
Killed him
But now he's
I know I killed him
I did I killed him I know I'm sure I kill
With me
It's the one who brought your brother back to life
Instead the phone line has been cut we're getting out of here it'll
Coming back for you
You okay in there
Where would the police someone called earlier is there any trouble
If you don't mind sir
We're just going to have a quick look around
Good Lord
This is horrible
You two all right
Are you injured you hurt
Well that's a relief
Backup should arrive very soon
They'll take care of the crime scene and we'll take you over to headquarters for questioning so we can file a report on this
So are you the daughter of the victims
I'm sorry for your loss
I'm assuming neither of you saw the intrud
Do then to think something like that could happen in such a peaceful
Pardon my asking sir but where do you come from are you Chinese and no sir I'm Japanese my name is
Is Kenzo Tema okay you're Japanese yeah well seems to me you're quite a ways from home
Then aren't you you're all right now it's going to be
Okay
Sorry but can you tell me
Tell me where we're headed officer the police station remember but wait I don't understand the Heidelberg police
Station is in town yeah but we're from the station in Manheim the next town over
Why why are they taking us so far yeah we're
Almost there just another 15 minutes or so okay
He said they got a call they
They got a call but who could have called phone
There were no Sirens when they first came and
They took us away before making sure the backup arrived at the scene but
Dispatches those badges did look real
It can't be
With these men have
Excuse me
Police checkpoint
Thank goodness
We're searching for a hit-and-run suspect so please be alert excuse me it's you
Well if it isn't detective messenger and detective Mueller good evening to you gentlemen
Are you two on your way back to the station
Wow you got a new car really nice
I'm sure we'll get it banged up soon enough
Yeah we really give our rides a workout
Excuse me Detective
She's not feeling so well back here can she get some fresh air for a minute
Oh
Sure you go ahead
Are these two in some kind of trouble
Trouble not at all it's nothing don't worry
What's going on here
What about that blood
Who could have called them
There's Sirens weren't even on
What should we do
Hey what's wrong Dr Tina are you two okay
How do you know who I am
I gave you my name but I never told you not once that I was a doctor tell me how did you know that
I found a grocery store nearby
I also got you some dry clothes
There's bread sausage and cheese
And I felt this thermos up with hot coffee too
You probably don't have much of an appetite but you really should eat
You're shivering
You should change out of those wet clothes
A
People were dead
My brother and I
We're walking
It was like
We are all alone in the world
Where were you when all of this happened can you remember anything else
We crossed the border
Uncle and auntie helped
They were so kind to
And my brother said
I have a good plan
Soon after that
My uncle and my dear auntie were both
Anyone who is ever good to us died
Without fail
All of them
But then one day
One day I discovered the reason why
Rainy day
You're talking about the incident with Mr and Mrs leebert
My brother did it he shut them
Brother
He murdered
He's the one who did all this my brother murdered them all
So I picked up the gun with both my hands
And then I I aimed it right at my brother
And that's when he said it
He was smiling
After you shoot me make sure that you throw the gun out the window
And he told me to aim for his head
Who shot him like he said
I aim for his head like he told me
Why did you save him
If you hadn't saved your mom and dad would still be alive he wouldn't
Stay here I'm going to the police
If those detectives last night were real
It means that some members of the police force are linked to Gohan if so we can't just
Wait here like this
Nina I need you to listen to me I know that Johan is going to come after you if anyone comes
You're just hide
Why don't you have some food drink some hot coffee and then try to get a couple hours of rest
One step at a time that's how we'll get through all this
You're alive
You must think about the future your future
Were there any clues left by the Killer is there any connection to the serial murders throughout
Germany like I said we're doing everything we can to investigate this case but I can't make
Make any comments or talk about details
Time or is she presumed that as well we're trying to figure out her whereabouts why was that newspaper reporter with them Mister mower
Cheap one question who was that Japanese man who said to have been with it question mark
Who is he he sounds suspicious
Quick question Chief is this murder at all related to the one that took place at Heidelberg Castle around the same time
Heidelberg Castle
So he was killed tomorrow
That's all for now we'll release additional details and due time
Excuse me sir
Of course we appreciate all the support we're getting from Manheim like detectives Messner and Mueller thank you
We both were coming out this afternoon
We're at your disposal to Aid in the investigation anything we can do to help
So how are things coming along sir
Please come inside that way we will be able to speak freely
One more
For real
Those guys were with the police their actual cops
Should I do
Hello Heidelberg post
What I can't hear you we're really busy in here
Just find out Japanese
I'm bringing an important witness to your office at
5:00
But you must not tell the police
If I can't trust the police then the newspaper is my only option
Only they can help Nina now
Mr Maher
I'm sorry but you just can't come in here without permission
He's right
Besides the bka is only working on the serial murders of the middle-aged couples
All that you're going to find in this room is material for the murder of the castle inspector long gay
Please forgive me
I was just a bit curious but the crime you're investigating in this one happened at the same time
Detective
I mean it couldn't have been the same murder
So I see
It appears that this man had been tied up
You didn't happen to find a rope or anything nearby did you
No
Seems the body had already been untied by the time the police arrived on the scene
I see
Yes
There are four possible routes of Escape From The Scene he also had to stay well out of sight
How crowded was the area where he'd come out and how much light was there
Here it is
Nina it's me Tema I'm back Nina you can come out now
It's all right hey Nina
Oh no
Nina
Where are you
He came for you
Disney Nina
I never should have left you here all alone
After 10
I don't blame you for saving my brother's life anymore
You did what you had to do as a doctor
It wasn't your fault
Please eat the sandwiches
Get some rest too
Please live on
And continue to save as many people as you are able to
Nina Fortner
Nina
Are you planning to do
Are you going to kill your brother second time
I did it I brought him back to life that monster
It was me I brought
Back to life