I
Back to
Mad monster
I brought him back
Of course
Hey where are you going ceremony
And 10 minutes there right don't follow me Peter
I need to speak with Hans gay or shoe ball Now call his estate
Yes sir
Wait
Unless I've got the date wrong today is his book donation ceremony at the University of Munich Library
We've got an emergency
I know 10 minutes next Target
Florida I'm so glad you came
I tried
But the person I'm looking for
I'm not going to find them here after all
And we were just getting to be friends too sorry your twins right
You got to be you look just like him
You are aren't you well aren't you
What's this picture book
Cuz this is what he was looking at when he started screaming
Once Upon a Time
In a land far away
A nameless monster
The monster
Was dying
To have a name
So the monster made up his mind
And set out on a journey to look for one
But the world was such a very large place
The monster split in 2
And went on separate Journeys
One went East
The other
Headed west
The one who went East
Came Upon a village
There was a blacksm
He lived at The Villages entrance
Mr blacksmith
Please give me your name set the monster
I can't give you my name reply the blacksmith
If you give me your name
I'll go inside you and make you strong set the monster
Really
Set the blacksmith
If you make me stronger I'll give you my name
The monster
Went into the blacksm
And so
The monster became
Auto the blacksmith
Auto
What's the strongest man in town
But then one day he said
Look at me
The monster inside of me
He's getting bigger
Munch munch
Chomp
Gobble gobble
The hungry monster
Ate a bottle from the inside out
Once again
He was a monster
Without a name
Next he went into Hans the Shoemaker
However
Munch munch
Chomp
Gobble gobble
Once again he went back to being a monster without a name
Then he became Thomas the Hunter
But soon
Munch munch
Chomp
Gobble gobble
Golf
Becky went to being a monster without a name
The monster next went to a castle to look for a nice name
He Came Upon a very sick boy who lived in that castle
If you give me your name I'll make you strong send the monster
The boy replied
If you can make me healthy and strong I will give you my name
So the monster jumped right into the boy
And the boy became full of vigor
The King was overjoyed
He announced
The prince is healthy
Prince is strong the monster became quite fond of the boy's name he was
So
Please with his Royal life in the castle
So he controlled himself no matter how ravenous his appetite became day after day despite
Is growing hunger the monster stayed put inside the boy but finally the hunger just be
I'm too great
Look at me
Look at me said the boy
The monster inside of me has gotten this big
The boy devoured the king
All his servants
Munch munch
Chomp ch
Gobble gobble
The castle was lonely now with everyone gone
So the boy left
On a journey
He walked and walked for days
And then one day the boy came upon the monster who had gone west
I have a name that the boy and it's such a wonderful one at that but
The monster who went West replied who needs a name I'm perfectly happy without one
After all that's what we are nameless monsters
The boy ate up the monster who went West
At last he had found a name but there was no longer anyone to call and buy it
Such a shame because Johan
Was such a wonderful name
You've read this before
Haven't you
So you can recheck
Are you tickles Slovakian
I'm not sure
Wait how come you don't know for sure
I was very young
Three or four
I think somebody read this story to me back then
Who are you really
I mean could it be possible that you aren't actually Nina Fortner at all
And if that's not who you are
Then who in the hell are you
I don't know
What do you mean you don't know we're talking about you
So you're the one who should know right
Tell me what's going on here
I need some answers
Why did I get such a bad feeling when I read this picture book
What does that mean Nina
Student name foreign who claim to be shoe bald son committed suicide
The detective that you both hired fell off a building and died
Margo Langer was shot to death
After reading this book
Why is it now suddenly occurring to me
These three horrible events are somehow linked
And I'm getting a weird feeling that everything is somehow connected with y'all
Sorry I overre
You know that person
The one who collapsed after he saw the book
Does he really look identical to
Is he my mirror IM
I'm talking about your friend you know Johan
You think he looks like my twin is that right
Where is Johan right now
He's at the University Library attending the book donation ceremony
Wait a second hold on
The Grand collection that the shoe bold Financial Group representative
On scale has generously donated
Today to our University's Friedrich Emanuel Campus library is very important
Comprehensive and Val
We are very honored and extremely proud now to have an opposition what you could call one of Germany's most magnific
And we have a duty to preserve and protect this outstanding collection of Humanity's wisdom of AG
We have been interested
To keep this for future gener
Next on our program
Message
Dean of the Friedrich Emanuel campus
Professor Ste
If I pull the trigger everything went
I don't want to die I don't want to die
I have to do it
He is a man who is favored to the bavariance doctor this is how to shoot a gun
Financial
And by donating such an enormous and valuable book collection to our
He is performing a great cultural service for everyone in our beloved state of Bavaria on be
The University of Munich I am proud to introduce
Miss you too I benefactor
At this time ladies and gentlemen I present to you
Now watch how it's done
Pull the
Just pull the trigger
It seems like it's a huge success
A great number of people have gathered here
I guess that Mr schewald is well liked
Must be nice to be him
Golden developing
European Financial
Systems as well and by donating
Enormous and valuable book collection
Into our
Is performing a great cultural service for everyone in our beloved state of bavar
On behalf of the University of Munich I am proud to introduce you to our benefactor
At this time ladies and gentlemen I present to you
Period
Moon
So I am the one you're after is that right
Would you look at all those faces out there
So many people be crowd just to see you
Now I
Stand
How could you even consider this
Now don't spoil the fun
You can watch me
If you're quiet
Everyone please
Listen carefully to what I am about to say
I want you all to stay calm
It is extremely important
That you do not
As you all may know I am blind
So I am unable to tell how many people have gathered together in this room tonight
You need to leave the library this instant
That's right
Just stay down there and be a good boy
It's a real shame you won't be able to watch me do this
Get away from here go
Right now
Single file and don't push
Google Google
So how come there's a fire
I get it
Still running around like ants bumping into each other trying to get out just like that
Amazing you're amazing your heart
Amazing
It's pretty
Everyone is running and falling over each other without
Or anyone but can you sense it in the room
The fear
You won't be able to
To do it I have to shoot you I'm sure you can't but I have to kill you
You're a doctor of medicine and you've dedicated your career to saving life
Taking life is my job and I do it well
Give it up you can't do it