Did you get that dress I made it myself
You're an unfamiliar face get yourself a permit if you're looking to do business here
Last thing I need is an unlicensed hooker
Yeah good luck with that
I just need permission from him don't I
You let me meet him
Sorry I got no idea who you mean
I'll keep coming back until I meet him
Until
I meet the baby
You can't catch the ball with your hands like that you're not the goalkeeper with your whining who died and made you rap
Where the hell did you go to go
Where'd you go
10 my dummy 10 mile
He told me to stay with you for a while cuz he found the man he was looking for that's all
That's all
Who leaves a kid with someone like me
No way in hell thanks a lot of time I have to babysit I hate kids first he drops
The piece of the earth and then he Saddles me with some random brat
Me and him had an agreement doesn't it mean nothing anymore what the hell kind of doctor doesn't want to make some easy money
Son of a
Did I look like I was ready to you hey
Remember what I said you can't use your hands that's a yellow card
I'm throwing this into traffic if you mentioned the rules one more time you keep talking like that you'll get a red card
Shut up
Why the hell are you so late
Hurry up and give me the stuff
Give me the stuff now
Long time no see detective Messner
Dr Tim
That's right that's exactly what you called me back when we first met before I even got around to telling you
What my occupation was
But that was a long time ago
My days and Medicine are over
But I suppose you're no longer Detective
Detective suspended on narcotics charges
This article really came as a shock when I read it 6 months ago
Don't even think about running away
I have a gun trained on you under my jacket
All right what do you want with me
I need answers what happened in Heidelberg almost a year ago
And who was behind it all who ordered you to do such a terrible thing
I don't know anything
You killed the foreigners and Mr Mauer from the post
It wasn't me that did it
I was hired as the lookout that's all my partner Mueller he did it he killed all of them
Detective Mueller also left the force soon after the murders
Yeah he did
I hear that he's very well off turns out he's doing good with his money
You on the other hand ended up wasting all of your money on your drug habit
That sound about right who took on the job and he was the one who committed the murders he ended up getting a
They even tried to get rid of me they tried to kill me to make sure I didn't go to the cops
I'm surprised you're still breathing
It was the organization that helped me
Organization
Enough I already told her too much as it is
Told her her who leave me alone already I can't I
Can't deal with you right now looks like you're going through withdrawal
And with me sitting here no dealer would come within 20 ft of you so I suggest you start talking
I thought I was
I was saved by the baby baby
Go to a pub called candy you can find him there
Wait who's this baby you're talking about
He's all right wing extremist
These also a high official and two of their major political parties
After the wall fell
The baby tried to create a town of only pure blooded Germans
But his plan failed and now he's come back
But why'd he do it
Why do you bother saving you
The darkness
After the Berlin Wall fell
A great Darkness was created
A monster
A monster was born
Now leave me alone I've already said everything to that girl you understand what girl Messner she came
She's the daughter of that older couple we murdered you're saying
I mean Nina Nina Fortner came to see you then
The baby said to me that I
That I was to send that girl to him if I ever saw or if she ever showed up around these parts
He said
That she's important to use as bait
He's using her
As base
You don't give up do you
You're getting to be a regular coming back all the time how about I rent you for an hour or
So the night ain't a total waste
You are the one you said I'd get in trouble if I did business without the babies permission
Yeah not so clever now are you
Is this the girl who keeps asking to see the baby
Yes sir
It seems you're getting your wish
Don't keep him waiting
Please wait right here
Stand on that imot
If you'd be so kind
Directly over the iris please
Yes much better
Now tell me meaning of fortnite doesn't this song resonate with you right down to the
Both of your feet I have to dance
The baby told me the day another hit
Was born to us our country will be saved the girl will be the
How is it that you know my name also
To the name of Anna Liebert but the former is just his false is the latter A Rose by Any Other Name
Does smell is sweet but they call me the baby so I'm biased come on let's cut the rug a bit
Is it true that you know where my brother is right now Yohan right good
Yes you know don't you what are you going to do when you finally have your little family re
Union I'm going to take him
Down you should rip that out willy nilly Miss someone's liable to get hurt Pat
Why I'm sure your heart is searching for you even as we speak
I lived around here when I was your age no this place like the back of my hand
And there's a fellow who buys Antiques and it's on this rug I stumbled across what do you mean don't you
Have any money left Mr Heckle shut your Yap already I'm Hawking this rug so I can get the two of us something to eat
I don't hear you coming up with
Son of a bear goes the
Neighborhood Turks this whole area
It's full of Turks now
You are so called and
It's a fake
What are you talking about
You can't pick this kind of quality
It's synthetic
Tell you what
I'll give you 100 marks for it out of sheer
More like s*** you Cannery the German guy who had this place would it give me 10 grand well you can take it
Leave it
Don't you come crying to me when you realize my rug is the real deal
That one hanging on the wall is the real deal
It's a genuine headache rug
There's your hand woven Sil
Look at the detail there in the patterns
It's perfect
$150,000
You sure got took for a ride if you really can't tell the good stuff from that crap I feel sorry for you
We're out of here Peter
Hey I'm getting kind of hungry
That runs real
It's a hurricane just like he said
Only 150 Grand I could get $800,000 for a rug as fancy is that
Come on let's get something to eat already shut up
If I can get my hands on that rug we'll be able to eat anything we want
How you going to do that
What are you talking about
I'm sure I'll think of something
Don't give me that look
You hungry ain't you whatever Thief what what a sock in it you little
Hold on a second where do you think you're going sorry but I'm not looking to buy
Are you crazy and Asian like you is going to get killed if you walk into a place like that they don't take kindly to foreigners
But you're Turkish aren't you is it all right for you to be doing business around here what are you
Stupid I wouldn't do business in a dump like this
A friend of mine was just abducted by a bunch of guys who are regulars there what it seems like she found out
A secret I don't know what it's all about but I have to find her before something bad happens
A woman I know is in there too I have to get her out she
What is this woman look like does she have long blonde hair don't know I couldn't tell you what she looks like now
Because they just took a young blonde girl away in a car
It was big and red I don't know all right then I've got a track down that red car before it's too late
Wait you have to do something to help my friend too please help her she has a small baby if something
What happens to her please
You're still alive this is my lucky day
This way please
Without your gun
On this point I'm afraid I must insist
Thank you for your cooperation
Go ahead and sit wherever you like
So the baby brought you in here
Eyes forward let me see your face
Goodness
But I should have known you'd be quite a beauty
After all you are a Johan's twin sister
My name is Professor guidlitz
And the man standing next to Johan in the picture is General wolf
We created this organization along with a pair of other like-minded individuals
Where are my manners
Would you care for some fruit
No thank you I want to see Johan
And see him you will
Once he knows that you're here no force on Earth could keep him away
The boys suffers mightily in your absence
You people don't know where Johann is either do you
We need him
His country needs him
We for shall help him fulfill his destiny
Do you have any idea how Hitler became possessed of such power
It's because he saw the three things a person would have to do to gain control of a country
Manipulate the banks feed the War Machine and take command of the military
I'm sure johans working on one of those things right now or
Who really it's a question of if not when
What exactly do you plan to do with Johan think of it
Hitler been a weekend Nation to his will using nothing but raw Charisma all that from a man
Who only made Corporal a man whom Art School wouldn't Dane to let in his
My appeared after he hit his 30s
Not so with your brother Johan he was a leader of men even as a mere boy
Charisma of Messianic proportions but even Jesus Christ
Christ had help consider the three Magi and John the Baptist who heralded the savior's arrival into the world
How they ready the way for his glory likewise the four of us have been keeping track of your hands
Once ever since he was a little boy exciting wouldn't you say what is it that you want with me
Please accept our Hospitality until Johan comes looking for you at the very least
Actually I'm afraid I must insist you know too much for us to let you walk away now
Don't worry about that I came here of my own volition I will wait here for you hun
Then we agree
Now then you should at least try the fruit
Good you're finally awake
Don't look so worried we're not going to hurt you
That's right away at least
So what brings you to my little slice of the world
Doctor Tenma wait how do you already know what my name is
Why don't you leave the questions to me
Now all you have to do is answer
Why exactly were you snooping around
I know you're looking for Johan but I can't figure out why where are you keeping Nina
I told you to leave the questions to me did I not
What are you going to do with her
Nina is our guest whereas you are just a metal some piece of trash to be disposed of
Is she okay
At the moment
But that'll change soon enough
She's determined to kill your heart and we simply can't have that
Always ashamed when a pretty girl dies before her time
You're just using Nina as bait to throw out Johann
What are you planning on doing who the hell are you people
The whole quarter indeed
The night sky tomorrow will be a thing of beauty of fiery cleansing
If I stay here
Then I'll find you on
Please help
Who are you
Where are you right now
It sounds like you're speaking with an accent
Where are you from
Have you been taking prisoner by the people here
Help me please I can't
They're watching me closely I've got to stay in here
Let me escape
I have to warn the other so my baby will die too
Tomorrow night we celebrate in honor of johann's homecoming
Only the members of the pure Master race like us deserve to survive everything
And she'll just burn away