How are you feeling Mr Yonkers everything okay
So
Tell me Mr Yonkers are you able to recognize me
Do you see this finger I'm holding up
How about it
Can you talk to me today
What's that
I'm sorry
What did you say
Coming
Mr Yonkers what's coming
Monsters
The monster
Younkers
I know you're able to speak
You have been identified at the scene of the crime
A four murders
Involving middle-aged couples in the past 2 years
There's no point denying
What do you say will speak up Mr yunkers
All right okay I guess we had better tell you that we already know that you are just a lock pick
Your job is strictly undoing locks
You couldn't have possibly slit their throats in one single slash with such cold blooded Grace Yonkers no
That wasn't your work
Now that means there had to be other accomplices involved
And I'm thinking there would have had to have been at least three of you in order to do both
Open a strong lock
And murder a middle-aged couple
Without resistance
That sound about right
We're almost through compiling a list of suspects who we already know are skillful with knives it's only a matter of time
Time before we're able to narrow it down to one name
Whether you decide to cooperate with us or not
However I must confess that's not really what I wanted to ask you about
What I would really like to know Mr Yonkers is why four couples from across Germany and every one of the couples
Middle aged and without children money and items were stolen but we know the amounts were too small to
Define murdering for a mere third of it
All right
So tell me are you up for some negotiation
If you confess now will dismiss all charges against you
So tell me who is the person who hired you to do this
Mr Yonkers it's all right it's all right
I don't think so we're almost there get out of
Very well but I'll be coming back at a later time and just to make sure he isn't poisoned or that he doesn't
Pier I will assign a guard to watch him closely that shouldn't strike
They're always seems to be so much trouble happening all around you Dr Tenma
We'll keep in touch
Hey hold on where are you going
Just going out for a walk it's not supposed to leave the room without permission
Patients need to get fresh air every so often
We're just going out into the garden
You're welcome to come with us if you like officer
Very
It's nice and warm out here today
You are able to talk aren't you
It's afternoons like this one that make you happy to be alive you know
If it weren't for times like today I don't think I'd be able to go on
Especially when you're here constantly seeing people having to fight for their lives
That's why it's easier for some doctors to think about their money their research or getting prom
I used to be one of those guys myself
I wanted to get promoted and do my own research
I was positive that being successful in surgery was the weight of the top
But have to performing a surgery on a certain little boy
Everything changed for me
He was the older of twin siblings
Been shot in the head
Saving his life reminded me why I had become a doctor in the first place
It reminded me that all human lives should be regarded as equal
And that a doctor's job is to save those lives
Thank you
People start over all the time
It's never too late believe me
You know something
You and I are very close in age
Well you're almost like a father to me
Doctor you saved my life and you've protected me
That's why it almost feels like you're my father
Well it looks like I landed myself one big kid huh
This one time when I was a little boy
I wanted this clock
You
I'm sure you've seen those before
Kind of have a little Nutcracker figuring popping out of it every hour
I would stare at it for a long time pressing my face against that display window at the store every afternoon
So I guess it's no surprise doctor that was the first lock I ever picked in my life
But I was caught in the act
And I never got that clock
However
Ever since that day picking locks sort of became my job
And it all started just because I wanted that stupid clock
All I wanted was that stupid clock
You should just tell them everything
Tell the police everything you know
Just make a fresh start of
Oh my friends
Who did it
Is it this monster
The one that you mentioned before
Do me a favor don't screw it up this time I went out of my way to set this one up for you
You know she's the daughter of a state legislator
She is beautiful and intelligent all in one package in other words Perfection well we'll
Say about that but you know what all kidding aside you're right it is time for me to find someone
Of course I'm right the thing is that someone in your position without a wife just seems like
Hey
I'm sure you've seen those before the kind that have a little Nutcracker figuring pop
But every hour
Excuse me about the clock in the window hey what's going on you're already late for your date what
Doing
People start over all the time
It's never too
I believe
Officer
Excuse me
Officer are you out there
Hello
I'm ready to confess but I prefer if Dr tenmo were present
Where you could have gone
Hey officer I wanted to
Listen I know it's late but can I go see one of my patients
Yes but of course Dr Tem
What is it you have there
I found something special
Hey what's the matter are you all right
Mr Yonkers
Mr young girls
It's the same as last time
McKenzie my patience disappearing just like 9 years ago
Mr y
Mr Yonkers
It's me
Dr Tem
Stay away doctor
Let's go back to the hospital Mister Yonkers
Everything will be all right
Don't come any closer
I'm begging you please don't look at him
At who
He's the one who killed my friends and I'll kill you too
Who are you oh God just run run away
It's been a long time
It's me 9 years ago you
9 years ago
You forgotten already doctor about the twins
That's right
That twin
You remember
Ron don't look at his face he'll kill you
What do you think you're doing here Mr Jones is my patience let him go
What am I doing
And execution
We were hired by him he call us each time will be wired to our accounts after each job
That way it seems like we had taken the money and split it he had it all figured out
The murder of those four middle-aged couples was ordered by it was you
The police started suspecting me and following me so he wanted to get rid of us listen to me the other
Fred said to me just before he died that we had
Oh my God that we have been hired by a monster
He doesn't even blink at killing someone that means nothing to him
Run Doctor he'll kill you where you stand just blood
You talk too much Younkers
Johan
Don't do this
Mr guncas doesn't know your identity but I do
How was your attending physician
You are so hungry but the Elder of fraternal twins
If you were the son of Michael Liebert former advisor of Commerce
Who fled East Germany in 1986
Has a political Refugee to the West
If we know this much about you
You can't possibly Escape
Don't add your crimes Johan
Johan huh
Yes there was a time when I went by that name
But you know something doctor Johan isn't my real name what are you talking about
You must never know about my past not about those four couples
But you're different doctor
You cared for me and you restored me to life so I feel as though you're like a father to
Like a father
The truth is if it weren't for you I wouldn't be standing here right now
A human life is precious don't you see that rescuing you open my eyes I was able to go back
Saving your life made me realize that the weight of each life is equal no one's better
What are you laughing at
I heard you were promoted to chief of surgery soon after that incident
I'm really happy doctor
That you were promoted to that position
What are you trying to tell me
You are where you are today because the director and the others died right
I'm so glad I was able to help
That was a good thing
My God isn't that what you wanted Doctor that's what you said
Right after I regained Consciousness that's what you told me
That you hated them so much you wish they were dead I am not wrong
Bastard bastard
All that I did was grant you your wish
I was supposed to die that night
You're the one who resurrected me doctor
What a miserable downpour
I just spies the wet weather
All it does is wash away the crime scene evidence when you need it the most
Well wouldn't you agree
Dr Tim
All
To summarize what you told me so far
Just to make sure that we piece it all together
Back in 1986
Liebert a high government official escape from East Germany with his wife and two children
Right after they arrive the Liebert family was attacked the couple was killed in the twin brothers suffered a critical gun
Got wound to the Head
You were the surgeon in charge of his operation and subsequently save the boys life
But to everyone surprises fate would have it the boy kills the director the chief of surgery and
Head of neurosurgery with poison candy and then disappears
And last night after 9 long years out of the clear blue the Libra boy reappears and kills a
Police officer with poison candy yet again and right in front of your eyes he shoots Adolf euchre's
Patient
He is none other than the very man that hired you and curse and two others to murder the four middle-aged couples across
Germany
And his name is
Johan
Liebert
I believe that's the entire story isn't it
Yes sir I think we're finished with the doctor he can go
I don't think that someone with Dr tennis credentials or in his position could be responsible for such a crime
He has an alibi for the time the policeman was killed
And we didn't find any gunpowder residue on his hands
So much for key
There go all of our leads to solving those murders of the four middle-aged coup
Inspector Lungi should we get started on this Johan Liebert for the time being