He was released
Yes
Johan Liebert was discharged this morning
Wow that was fast
They said he just collapsed all of a sudden but I guess it could have been anything too serious
Oh you
You come by the library a fair amount
Hey you're a librarian at the University aren't you
So they let him out already
That's a relief he gave me such a scare yesterday
So you were there when you collapsed then
He was trying to track down a book
And I was the one helping him just the luck of the draw
And then it happened
I've never heard a person scream like that before
What's that I'm off
He had this picture book and he flipped it to a certain page
Picture
Nobody think less of you for taking a few days off you know
Your EEG readings were normal they didn't show anything
In fact you're the picture of Health
You know the doctor says it's probably anemia or fatigue
Another possibility is that you experience some sort of shock
Or so the doctor says
By the way he also mentioned something about a scar on your head from a major surgery
I'm just giving you a hard time but seriously you should probably take it easy for a bit
Oh I almost forgot
You got some mail this letter came for you while you were in the hospital
Oh really
It's strange they didn't put their return address
But I didn't hear any ticking so I think you're okay
What's so funny you hun come on share the joke
Just what did they send you anyway
Oh it's merely a letter from the red Hindenburg
Huh
You look pretty wholesome you show your tall enough for this ride what are you lost kid or maybe you're looking
Is it yeah if you want to learn your ABCs I'm the perfect girl for the job come on you don't happen to know
So the red Hindenburg do you the red Hindenburg I'm looking for her she's nearby
Fine they're in the back
Name me fix I'm coming down too hard
Will I find a red
Hindenburg at the top of the stairs
It's open
Oh good you came
Make yourself at home
Yes that face
You such a beautiful face
I saw you on TV kid the evening news right next to shoe volt smooth one aren't you
So now you're calling yourself the red Hindenburg
After calling yourself Margo Langer all that time and before the name was
Sophie call me whatever as long as I get paid
Names don't mean crap right Johan Liebert
If you simply must know it's a pet name for my latest boyfriend
He's waiting back there behind door number one
Thank you honey
Don't go getting any funny ideas sweetie
He's holding a big gun in his hand and he's just itching to give it a go you should see the one he's got in his pants
I'm impressed
Mormon your way and old shoe volt confidence like that you're running one hell of a scheme
I'm not just saying it to be polite
I remember you bringing that far invoice saying he was shoe called son who could have ever guessed the real deal would come
Forward those are some pretty long odds right yes you knew better or little
Redman Farr and
Fool you practically tied the news for him as soon as he'd served his
Well good it took me 2 years
That's how long ago the real Margo Langer died and let me tell you the timing couldn't have been better
After she died her name allowed me to cash in on chevald's guilt
No point letting that money go to
Whatever it's not like the girl was my closest friend or anything
She wasn't even turning tricks anymore she said she went completely clean we just had a couple of drinks nothing
Nothing more
She probably didn't have anyone else to talk to
Let's get her drug shed a few crocodile tears
And suddenly your life was an open book
I heard all about her fling with shoe V
And about sending his bastard to an orphanage
And then the poor thing went got herself killed I used the name Margo Langer to get shoe balls money and I lived
Happily ever after end of story
When Margo was killed the police concluded she was the victim of a random attack Case Closed little did they know
Dead former hooker was just one measly piece and a big gory puzzle
Like Richard Brown
The former police detective I can't help but feel sorry for the guy
If he hadn't gotten so nosy maybe you wouldn't have felt like jumping that faithful night
Goodness me what's the body count again
Enough reminiscing let's get down to why I asked you to come here tonight
Business my dear
And don't even think about squirming your way out of this one
Ain't that right honey
So name a number I'm listening
What are you de
I think it's the ultimate fear I really thought I'd already
What the hell are you mumbling about now but then
I be held a Darkness even great
Wait a minute
You think you can just walk away
I'm leaving this town you see shoe vald no longer amuses me
Try to blow me off kid it's no use how do you shoot a person who doesn't
I'm through messing around
Honey
Honey get out here already
What are you doing Roberto plays
Hello again may I please have a balloon
Here take it and go get your
How much longer is it going to be doctor Connie's waiting for his head
What my kids going in first just wait your turn
Hurt so
Mommy
You said it fellow why no you want there's still only one doctor here am I right
Hey young man what have you got in that bundle of yours huh
Ah this it's nothing
You don't happen to know if this particular doctor is good do you sir
Best of the bunch
If it weren't for this doctor all us Asians around here we'd all be dead
Especially the Vietnamese
Really you don't say
Hold on you're not Vietnamese right
No I'm not
Wait a sec where are you going
Some of these folks are in a bad way son let them go first
Don't worry I didn't come here as a patient for what it's worth
Hey hold up you need to wait your turn he needs to be looked at right now doctor my kid is first
First you got that if you'd excuse me hey what the hell where do you think you're going pal I'm sorry doctor
I just wanted to ask you something really fast how many times do I have to tell you
I don't have time for this
A woman
And she's
Didn't you hear me
Get out of here
How old could she be
I'm in the middle of suturing this wound
If anything goes wrong it's on your head for
Attracting me
Establant in the thigh
It's from a knife
Her stitches are
I think the patient's going to need a drainage tube
I think you need to keep quiet
Otherwise you'd better take this person to a real Hospital they'll take care of it
No it's really not
It's no hospital
Any more than your real doctor
If a real Hospital were an option for these
Don't you think they would have gone
Most of the patients who come here are undocumented IMM
If they took their problems to one of those real hospitals they be sent to jail
And deported
How many people do you think I've had die right here in this room because a real Hospital wasn't a choice
See if your judgment for things you actually know something about
Insert the drainage tube now
The knife he was stabbed with probably wasn't very clean
Unless you insert a drainage tube the wound will get infected and form an abscess look I know what I'm talking about here
Okay now remove a few of the stitches
Insert that tube about 5 cm gently now
That's it you did a good job thank you very much who's the next patient
You're finally awake
You push yourself too hard
Your patience told me you'd been treating them for two days straight without any sort of break
I checked on everyone's post-operative status while you were asleep
You know you're pretty good at this for being Underground
How old are you anyway
I never would have guessed it based on your work
If the skills of a practicing physician
It just happened
The doctor who used to practice out of this building disappeared and left all his equipment behind
My equipment won't get you far without proper training
So where'd you learn your techniques anyway
My father
He was a doctor
Is that so
He had a practice in Vietnam and when he came to East Germany to study he took me along with him
He ended up staying there for keep
Even opened up his own little clinic
And then the Berlin Wall came down
He never had enough time to treat everybody but he tried to help out the Immigrant Community as best he could
Until
The damn man murdered my father
Some neo-Nazi
Just because her skin is a different color
My father's dead
I was just a kid So eventually they sent me to an orphanage
A German family adopted me soon after
Turns out the only reason they took me in was to look like Good Samaritans to the neighborhood
We save this poor little yellow girl aren't we great
So I ran away
Anyway I've been helping my father at his Clinic from the start
I read a lot of the medical books in his library after he was killed
Someone had to carry on his mission and who better to do it than his own daughter
Step aside I can finish up the boys arm
That wasn't so bad go easy on it for a while if you wanted to heal right
Okay
Fine then who's up next
Most of them are treated and gone
You know you could be a top-notch doctor if you went to school
This country is full of opportunities for people who want to learn
Words of wisdom from a real doctor unless I'm wrong
I'm not going to close this Clinic because you say so
Hold on that's not what I'm saying here
I just thought that maybe you could if I leave who's going to take care of all those people who come here for help
No one nobody else here gives a damn listen what I meant was
What happened
My pissed him off he said I had a smart mouth
So he shot me
Mommy mommy your mom walked all the way here after being shot
We
But she's shot I will now go wait out there like
It's a good Brave boy okay
Around here it's the prostitutes who always get shot or knifed or worse
I wish there was something I could do but
I'm out of my league here
We need to get her on the table
Lift up her legs
No way what do you think you're doing this woman needs to go to a real life
Tea Room
There's always a chance as long as the patient is still breathing do you understand
Don't ever give up hope
If the artery in her abdominal cavity had been damaged her blood pressure would have plummeted leading to
But she was able to walk here on her own which means her blood pressure dropped gradually she's in
State of pre-shock which improves our odds judging from the location of the bullet wound there could be some
Damage to the spleen we can perform emergency abdominal surgery on her while transfusing blood simultaneously
All right let's get started pick up the scout
It's amazing he can sleep so soundly
I still can't believe there was no damage to the stomach intestines or any part of the digestive tract
All we had to do was remove the injured portion of the spleen and Stitcher up
You did a great job in there
Only because you were there with me
Mommy
You know Dr Tim
This place could use you
I came here because I had a question to ask and I spotted this article
Blue Sophie also known as the red Hindenburg
Word on the street is you were the first person to arrive at the crime scene
Are the rumors true
Can you tell me anything about what you saw when you got there anything at all
I got a call that somebody heard a shot so I rushed over as fast as I could
I got her in the back of the head Point Blank
She died instantly
I've seen many crime scenes but
This was different
The feeling that I got when I walked into that room
It wasn't a robbery
There wasn't any malice either
Simply a killing
Go on
When you're in the darkness you only sink deeper into it
Keep the lights shining
Enroll in a program somewhere and study hard okay
You've got a real gift for this
You'll make a fine doctor
Please wait the darkness
But you also look like someone sinking deeper into the darkness aren't you Doctor tema
Please tell me that you'll come back someday can you promise me that