Hello sorry to bother you at this hour
We're here on Official Police business
Would you happen to be doctor Tenma
Can I help you pardon my asking
But were you home all last night
What
No
I was out drinking until dawn
Why do you ask well sir Eisler Memorial Hospital
Hospitals director heinemann chief of surgery doctor oppenheim and Dr Boyer
They're All Dead
No one except the police are allowed to enter the scene of the crime
But you're interfering with the operation of this Hospital press is not allowed inside that patience in this kind of Chaos
Can you tell us please
Was it an accident or was it murdered three people died at the same time of course it was murder are you part of the
Hospital staff tell us would you happen to know anything about this internet out of my way let me through hey no one
Pull out in I work here I'm Dr Kenzo Tenma come on step back so did you see
He wants suspicious earlier tonight I'm sorry sir but I don't think this is the time to be
Calm down everyone is the emergency room running smoothly well
Actually we're swamped with the emergency cases right now doctor
Two patients are waiting to be operated on all right then I'll see what I can do can you take care of the car accident victim with the
First I'll go look over the X-rays how about the other case the patient collapsed with a stroke
Doctor
I'd like to ask you a couple of questions I don't have time for this
I understand but this initial investigation is vital
Do you know of anyone who could have possibly held a grudge against the director and the others
A grudge you have successfully tied The Noose around your own neck
Doctor
Did someone come to mind no
Sorry
We have a problem
Those kids
The twins the boy and the girl
They're gone sir we can't find them anywhere
And is the little girl's bed empty is well nurse
What's going on what the hell is going on
In his Mercy
Atlanta hand to many who were ill and suffering we will always remember his great
Accomplishments farewell Dr Heideman may you rest in peace am
Ava I know it's difficult but please
Try to hold your son
This whole funeral business is just too sad Dr tema
Yeah
Up until now she was fed with a silver spoon as the director's daughter but now suddenly she's just another ordinary person
Person that's got to be quite a big shock how can you say that right now sorry about that
Dr Tenma
I am inspector Vise Bob the nordheim westfallen police
Department
Thank you for your efforts this was such a tragedy
Yes let me introduce you
Dr Tan
I am inspector Lungi I'm here from the bka
I've heard about your amazing abilities doctor
No
I still have a long ways to go
Do you have any leads at all to the children's whereabouts no but we have determined the cause of death for the director
The other two doctors
We have discovered traces of nitrate inside all three of their bodies
So there were traces of nitrate
That's a muscle relaxant exactly
I see you're not a
For nothing
How could something like that end up and it was candy
Candy
It turns out the same candy wrapper was found beside each of the bodies the same substance was also found
Found in each of their stomachs
Tell me
Would you have any idea where they might have gotten this candy
Or something else of that sort
I wouldn't know where they got it from and if you don't mind me asking how was the search for the twins going
The bka is taking over jurisdiction on this particular case from the local authorities please don't worry
As it stands after investigating certain events we believe all this could be tied back to the moment the twins parents
Shot to death
First their parents defect from East Germany and are murdered soon after that
Then staff from the hospital where the children were treated are also murdered political terrorism may be a possibility
Those children might hold a major key to this whole mystery
They need protection please do your best to find them inspector we certainly will
Excuse us
Interesting a Japanese doctor demoted by the director and then his engagement at the director's daughter
Broken right before the incident
But the man was in the bar drinking at the time the crime was committed it checks out
Mind if I ask you something what is your hand move like that
Oh this I was just typing
I'm inputting all the information onto the hard drive in my head
And if I access the information
No
I still have a long ways to go
Dr Timo was actually quite modest about it when I commented on his well-recognized talents earlier
The police huh
What are they thinking you're a suspect
There's enough evidence to implicate me
Nothing I can do about it
I don't worry about it
They were persistent when they questioned me too
God I'm so exhausted
Once this whole thing gets settled
I think I'm going to go back to Japan
I came to Germany to do research but
With everything that's happened I see again
Most important thing for a doctor is to save lives
Come on
Don't get all depressed on me now just tired
Tired
Mr Buckner
You're making great progress
Thank you so very much Dr Tim I'm glad to hear it
Do you think I'll be able to work like I used to
Yes of course
Good because if I'm not there I'll have no choice but to close shop
However
You mustn't overdo it
I'll stop by your restaurant for a drink after you released
Now that's just to make sure that you're not over working
See Dr Timmy yes
I heard that you were leaving this
Hospital
Is it true doctor
Don't quit
Please don't quit
Good doctors like you are so hard to find
Please stay please don't say you're quitting
Please
Mr book now
Dr Tim
The chairman is asking for you
Right now he's in a meeting with the board discussing how to fill the open positions
Until now most of these posts were held by Dr heinemann's follow
Seems like they're going to be major changes
For example the rumor is Dr eckner is being transferred
I see
Chapter 10 ma hold on
No matter what the chairman says please don't give up I want you to know we're all behind you
So please don't leave the hospital
Let me say this again
I'm performing Orient
And that's the reason
I'm making you chief of surgery
What a life
I went against the director's orders and lost my position as chief
And my engagement to Ava is broken
And then as soon as I decide to work as a regular doctor without hope of ever being promoted
Will like this is
I'm sorry for calling you out of the blue but I'd heard you'd been appointed chief of surgery
I'm truly happy for you
Thank you EV
Enzo
That day at my father's funeral
I remember you were trying to comfort me weren't you
It made me happy
A lot of things happened between us but I'd like to start over
Cancel
Listen please forgive me I was wrong let's start over
Patient is hospitalized for a spinal cord tumor
Is paralysis has accelerated
I understand I'll do the operation myself excellent doctor I'm glad to hear that
Make the arrangements for the procedure right
I've had it with this damn flood
I thought the world would change when the Berlin Wall came down 6 years ago
And it did
The worst
It's true
They talk about a unified Europe but we just keep getting dumped with the bad
The rate of unsolved crimes is definitely on the rise
Inspector we have arrived sir
Both victims had their throat slit
It isn't pretty
Their identities
Mr and Mrs reichmann from Stitch Drive
They were murdered in their home
We believe they were hidden away in a Clos
But we're washed out to the open because of the rising flood
Another middle-aged couple murdered for GRE
In the past two years there have been four other similar cases across the country
All murder the same way
Probably the same Thief
No
It's too premature to call these simple robberies
Judging from the data
For some reason none of these couples seem to have had any children
Well this couple didn't seem to have any children either
Don't you think there are too many factors in common here to make the Assumption this is just a simple robbery well sir
I'm just going by the fact that money and goods were taken from all the victims homes it was all of it totally in a small amount
Although this would make sense if it were the work of a single perpetrator
Hold on you're suggesting there's more than one two of the homes in question had extremely strong locks and sophisticated
Alarm systems
But the perpetrator bypass them and was able to enter without any trouble
Also none of the couple showed any signs of struggle before they were killed
And the neighbors did not hear a single sound
The time the incident
Took place
Don't you think these were orchestrated all too well for just one suspect
Yeah maybe
Do you know this man
No
Adolf Yonkers 32 years old
He's been arrested twice for larceny
In a robbery he's the one who Gets You Through the front door
In other words a
It turns out
He was spotted near the area and three of those four double murder cases
Then he's got to be the man right
Or not
It's too early
Well
In any case detective your job here is done
The bka will take it from here
Sure
Oh well
It didn't fly after all
Sorry about that I've never flown a guy before in my life it was good you almost did it well doctor do tell
How was your day last night
Oh well she seem like a nice girl
She's the daughter of a director don't tell me you just had dinner and saw her home
Well actually there was an emergency call during dinner so I had to come back to the hospital
Hold on you did what
You'd better rethink that all work or no play doctrine you're going to lose a great catch and regret it someday do you hear me
Hey are you listening to a word I'm saying
Oh okay day good morning doctor how are you
Is this yours Carl
My Grandpa gave it to me
But it won't fly I think it's broken
Maybe the alignment needs to be adjusted
Well doctor do you know how to fly a kite when I was a kid back in Japan I used to do this a lot
Hold it up in the air now all right
You ready
How like this had a boy
Now here
We go
It's flying
All right
Oh man
If I were as smooth as that I'd have at least five lovers hell maybe even 10
Seriously that's so awesome
Get better soon Carl
So that next time you can fly it yourself okay
Today's surgery is a paracellular meningioma extra patient
Will proceed with a right tyrional approach
Yes
Everyone watch closely the chief of surgery himself is heading up this one
Brilliant operation
Just look
Get that he's hardly retracted the brain at all
He is truly a surgical genius
New residents should learn to treat the brain with such care
This is terrible
Ambulance someone calling an ambulance I didn't do it this wasn't my fault this guy ran into
The street all of a sudden out of nowhere
Is this the patient
Yes
How is
Well
We tried
But there isn't much we can do
This man is material witness in a case
It's important that we get his testimony since it may help us solve a string of Serial murders doctor
Can't have him die on us
But inspector this patient isn't very critical condition
Really there's nothing else we can do for him here
However there's a top-notch neurosurgeon at Eisler Memorial Hospital
If he comes here
He might be able to do
Neuros
That would be Dr tinma
Thanks for coming all the way out here Dr Tim
What's his condition right now
He is conscious but a bit delirious
Also one of his pupils is Dil
It's been a while hasn't it Dr Tenma
Sorry but do I know you from somewhere sir it was 9 years ago
The director's funeral remember
Oh yes you were from the bka inspector lunge
Please do be sure to perform a successful operation for the sake of the bka
The thing is Doctor
This patient has to survive he holds the key to solving a very important case
The sake of the police I do it for the sake of the patient
Fair enough doctor now if you'll excuse me I have an operation
I hear you've become the chief of surgery
Well no doctor
You certainly become very successful
Yes and what about it
Nothing
At your age it's quite an accomplishment aren't you next in line to become the
I still have a long way to go
Those murders years ago at Eisler Memorial Hospital due to a lack of evidence that investigation has seen
Very little progress
The only clue we found
Found was the poison candy
This suggest it was a calculated act on the part of the Killer
In that kind of crime
The killer always has something to gain
From the victim's death
What are you getting at inspector
Nothing forgive me
In my line of work
The mind doesn't stop I'm always thinking like this
In any case rest assured
Of all the cases I've ever handled throughout my career not one is gone unsolved
No not a single one
Well I'm glad to hear it
Will perform a craniotomy to remove the hematoma if we don't hurry the brain hernia will worsen
After the Eisler Memorial Hospital murders
No matter which way I looked at it
One person had everything to gain from the incident
And that is you
Dr Tim
Thank you again for going to all this trouble
Driving all this way
No don't worry how is the patient responding well he is still conscious but is right people does remain Dil
He's also got Paralysis on the left side but he has already started rehab hasn't he
The paralysis should go away
He's on the right
Listen I think the police want to interrogate him as soon as possible but that's out of the question
But doctor that detective Loom gay is a very persistent man
Right now the patients recovery is all I'm worrying about
How are you feeling Mr Yonkers everything okay
So
Tell me Mr Yonkers
Are you able to recognize me
Do you see this finger I'm holding up
How about
Can you talk to me today
What's that
I'm sorry
What did you say
Coming
Mr Yonkers what's coming
Monsters coming the monster