Go on young man eat this place is known for its tasty Vice verse
Isn't it wonderful
Your name is Dieter right
Doctor you better eat now or there might not be anything left when dieters done
There's no need to worry Dr Tenma
This place is safe
Only local folks come here
And if a strange face tries to get in
A friend Otto here will show them the door
You know business is really dropped off since I've been doing that
Now who just ordered the spatzler oh that would be me
I pulled together a bed in the ATT
If you can ignore the rats you should sleep pretty good up there
Thanks I owe you one
He's quite a kid here but a decent guy
You can't do much on an empty stomach
Thank you
For getting me a safe place to sleep
I should be the one who's thanking you
By now I'd be dead in the morgue if you hadn't come along and rescued me like you did
He didn't death makes this meal taste even better
Deacon
I already spoke to Dr Gillen
He was very pleased and relieved to hear that we found you
He left an ad in the local newspaper trying to contact you
Did you see it by any chance
Let's talk about our memories of cheating
So you did see it
I did
Well then why didn't you try to contact him
Because
I didn't want anyone else getting involved
But that's what friends are for
Especially during times like these
Earlier you said you were watching over me
That's because of the Richard Brown incident
Please explain
You probably know best what happened to him Brown was drunk when he shot down that young serial killer
That night cost him his career and his family
As I read about the boy Richard had killed due to recognize the photograph theater said that
Boy was in 511 kenderhe
And what's 511 kinderheim it's an orphanage that was in East Germany
Very special one Peter's Foster father was one of the instructors and he kept pictures of the children
That live there
And this orphanage figures into things Johann used to call it home huh so you're saying there's
The connection between Johann and the serial killer that Richard shot I'm not sure Brown died
Before I could get any details from him to tie the soul together
But he led me to you I saw you what is grave I thought you might be able to fill in some of the
Blacks so that's it oh Richard even in death you're still helping us get to the
Bottom of this
I know that until now you've been all alone out there but now we're going to solve this together
We must strive to prove that you're innocent I think I know where we can find Johan
Wait till you get a load of this I thought I had it on me damn I had a photo of Johann before
All the stupid I must have left it in the office when I was attacked if you left that picture there that man
Trying to kill you probably found it if that's the case it's good it's gone
That man said he'd been sending me for counseling by his wife her last name was Hess but there was nobody
I could find with that last name he was a hitman and he certainly tried to live up to that title
Yohan is here and so am I there must be a way to actually meet
Right I will meet you on face to face
Welcome to talbach and shoebald AG
This is their headquarters the epicenter of the shoe volt Financial Group
A year ago Mr shoevold was rarely here but lately he's been around a lot
Every morning Mr shoevold leaves here to tour his Affiliated offices
Richard discovered this pattern when he was still alive
This firm has grown exponentially as of late
His entire financial group has seen huge growth in profits and the reason for all this is quite clear
The turnaround began when a certain youth became true bald right-hand man
And here they come now
Two balls the older man in the wheelchair
Carl's the young man pushing him
Now look closely
Tell me is the blonde
Johan
That was him
There's no doubt
Good
This was the first time I've only seen him at night I've never seen
Johann in the daytime before well I'd say it's right about
This is my only chance that's true we might not have another chance to prove
Innocence but we must be judicious here you better keep lying low in Autos attic for now to prove
Renaissance we must be thorough and methodical
I should have another look at Richard's file
Nah here it is
Good thing I decided to bring this one home
Yes my friend
It'll be just a little longer Richard
I promise you
We will avenge your death soon
We have discovered Johan
And we've got Dr Tenma the key witness there's just one thing left to do
One thing
All that's left is to find someone who saw Richard the night he died
There's got to be someone
Once we find that person we will be able to prove that Johan was with Richard the night that he was killed
Even if that doesn't work out there's that young man foreign who claimed he was shuvall's son and then committed suicide
If we can find that prostitute foreign visited we'll be able to prove that Johan was there with him
We've got to find someone who can put Johanna the scene of the crime
There's even a third way to make our case we can question the couple who claim their johann's parents and then we'll be able to find out
Who this imposter really is
Keep in mind that we've discovered the real Johan liebert's burial plot
We're slowly tightening the Noose around this Johann character's neck
You know Tim looking at your sad eyes I find myself feeling the way I did when I looked at Richard
You look like
Well it says if you're trying to take on the Troubles of the whole planet but don't despair 10 ma you're not alone
There's Dieter and now you've got Dr Gillen and I'm here as well things are
You going to be all right from now on now go get yourself some sleep
Because
I didn't want anyone else getting involved this was the first time
I've only seen him at night I've never seen Johann in the daytime before
This is my only chance
Why aren't you get out of here now now run
This is right Vine speaking
Ah what a coincidence I was about to call you to discuss what our next move should be
I'll stop by later today
By the way
Tell my why he's at the safe house wherever he is I need you to make sure that he stays put
There's an issue that's been bothering me
I don't want to believe it
But that's exactly what I'm worried about
Peter
What are you doing here
He told me
He sent me over here
Then
Where's Tim
Gone
To where
Take care of it
What
Dennis planning to fix it himself
Stop and doctor
Please you got to stop him
Don't let him do it 10 minutes going to become a killer
That's enough for today
We're done
Don't say that now I'm just getting warmed up
Doc this is where it gets real interesting
Not today
We'll pick it up from here next time
How about that
I tell you the third one I killed now that's a great story to hear
She was only 18
My house is great she had no clue
Where's Timber Run off too
Thank Rudy
Greetings Dr Killen
At last we meet
And who are you
My name is inspector Lungi I'm with the bka
Actually I'm well acquainted with your work Detective
You've been responsible for the apprehension of many of the serial killers that I've interviewed
Since I read your book one could say that I know of you as well
Why thank you
What a remarkable piece of work
Transcendental criminal psychology
What makes it a great book is that you possess deep inside into what goes on in the mind of a serial killer
I especially liked your explanation of what motivated Heinz calls behavior in Chapter 3 of your book
Pages 262 to 294
I tend to agree with your supposition that the trauma he experienced during his childhood turned him into a sociopath
And then a criminal
Well then we think the same way I feel honored that you've read my book so thoroughly
My investigative methods also require me to get into the minds of these criminals
I try to predict what their actions will be by acting out what it is I think they'll do next
It sounds like you have a lot of experience
We should discuss your techniques when we have more time
I would have to agree that neither of us have much time I need to ask you something now
Lately
You've been driving a lot to Munich isn't that correct
That's right what of it
Please doctor have a seat for a minute
This won't take very long
You seen a psychologist named right fine three times this week
Why so often
Simple
He was one of my professors from University
Dusseldorf University
Correct
There was someone special in your class
This one fellow student of yours who went on to become a brilliant neurosurgeon
Where are you going with all this have you met up
With Dr Tenma
No what are you talking about
Allow me to refresh your memory
Let's talk about our memories of cheating
Rudy
You place that classified ad in every leading newspaper in the country from May 1st to the 22nd
Imagine my surprise
Shocking
I never thought brilliant people like you or Dr Tema ever had to cheat
Even as students it seems out of character for the two of you
It's interesting with best friends will do
Inspector I wouldn't say the doctor Tim and I were even friends when we attended dusseldor
Last man no deer park with your help the velbert police were able to surround Dr Tenma they were poised to take him
Into custody
But at the last second
He miraculously escaped well then you must also know that the wire I was wearing malfunctioned
It's still possible that you might have helped him to escape
Come on
I know the Tema is innocent
Really
Have an open mind and listen to me
The director of Isler Memorial Hospital and three other people that were murdered in Dusseldorf
The murder of a patient in a building under construction
And the murder and Heidelberg
The middle-aged couples that were murdered across the country
Those were the works of a Madman not tena
I reached this conclusion from interviewing Dr Tenma in person
As a criminal psychologist interesting
So
Where is he now
Who knows he's run off somewhere again
Why did he run away
Why would he run away if he were innocent he is innocent
You think so he needs friends like you to help him so why would he leave you in the dark
Well
I have proof that he isn't the murderer you think he is
Have a look at this inspector
I personally compiled this analysis of all the evidence in this case
You're very thorough
So tell me
Do you understand my conclusion yes
A strange death of foreign the boy who pretended to be shoe Volt's son
The seemingly accidental death of ex-police detective Richard Brown who was investigating this case
The questions and rumors surrounding shuvalt's illegitimate child
There's a young man who's at the center of this entire case
When timma was questioned by police he named this young man as the real murderer
Johan Liebert
Well he was still alive Richard Brown discovered a gravestone of a person with that same first and last name in
Call furthermore someone who admitted to being a Hitman tried to kill Dr reichfying after he picked up the investigation
From where Brown had left off
Oh I understand quite well
But you're wrong it's impossible to actually prove that all these separate events are connected
10 minutes has gone into hiding because he understands this more than anyone does
Am I wrong
I keep noticing that you tap your fingers
That's just a little habit I have
It helps me to remember important points in a case
As a psychologist it appears to me that your own anxiety is manifesting itself in the way you constantly do it
I do the same thing
I use my recorder instead of my hand however the sounds that are recorded on this device are Absol
Will be objective but in your case the information that you remember when you're drumming your fingers
Has already been tainted by your own preset opinions
That's probably how you've always done your job inspector for all these years right up until now
You believe that your memory is correct and that your judgment couldn't possibly be wrong do you have a wife or a
Family any hobbies outside your work you live for your job don't you ever
Made a mistake inside aren't you terribly afraid to make a mistake the way you think everything's black or
And if your judgment turned out to be wrong your whole world would fall apart
This is a recent photograph of Johan lemert
Can you prove all the deaths surrounding Johan is just coincidence
This young man
Where would I find him this very moment
He's a student at the University of mun
At the moment he shove out private secretary
So this is him
I'll need to hold on to this Photograph doctor
From this point on let's consider this a police matter
You know
Perhaps I made a terrible mistake
Where is Dr Tema right now
He should
Still being Munich
Yes this is Lungi
Put me through to the Munich police
I need an emergency deployment
Dr Tema is somewhere in the city of Munich
A sniper rifle
Oh look I don't got a clue what you're talking about
Wait so Mr hightmeyer didn't call you from his Mountain Villa in full sun
10,000 Deutsche marks in advance
Your order is a little complicated for me to fill
It'll take about a week to get it
In the meantime go get some sun you look pale
Listen you're getting yourself a good piece but it's a waste if you don't know how to use it
Just remember that
Next in the news
City officials attended a posh reception for the Munich electronics Industry trade show that's being hosted this weekend
By the state's Chamber of Commerce in association with local Business Leaders
Political and business figures from all over the world are attending
With the formation of the EU the various Industries are going to become the center of Europe media Network
This is the largest trade show Munich has ever hosted and the monetary impact on the local economy from this event is
Is in the
Noted industrialist Hans Georg who hasn't appeared in public for nearly 20 years
Was seen at the reception and received rousing Applause from the attend
Mr Shoe hold was in a wheelchair but he appeared healthy