Before the two of them arrived here they only had each other they were truly
Be alone in this world
They were found walking hand in hand near the border of Czechoslovakia
Just the two of them
Shivering all alone in the cold
I heard that the conditions and the orphanages in East Germany were pretty terrible not all orphanages were like 5
211 kinderheim
Inga deer the bathroom is the other way
Down the hall okay
It's all right it's all right there's nothing to be afraid of now you can go to the bathroom by
Self can't you
These poor children have never really felt the love of a parent in order
In order to develop as a person the only thing you need is love the orphanages of the East Side were truly
Horrible places for the children to grow up in everything was so impersonal even this place was only known by the number
You'd better believe we did everything we could do within our power so that we wouldn't be
Controlled by the government we weren't going to be another 511 kinderheim
It was a special orphanage controlled by the ministry of welfare and the ministry of the interior
Do you know what that means no the reality was it was the ministry of the
The interior's Pet Project East Germany was using that place for experimentation
On the children
Experimentation
They were running a project that would turn the children into perfect soldiers
Mental reconstruction
Twisting their minds for science
They made the children form factions to observe the aggression the fighting and the hate that resulted
It was an experiment to claw every last bit of compassion out of those children and see what
Remained can you imagine what kind of adults those children
Grow up to be
And now the problem is there's no way to prove that anything like that ever went on
Any type of data or secret records all those documents were burned before the wall fell
Everyone who had anything at all to do with the project fled the country
However
I've heard rumors of someone who remain
He managed to clean his records
He stayed even though he was the last person in the world who deserved a second chance
He was the man who was in charge of overseeing the Abomination that was 511 kinderheim
And even though he was actually a pediatric psychiatrist closely affiliated with the ministry of the interior
Your police
The man's real title was that of a district official with the ministry of welfare
A district official
With the ministry of welfare
Inga are you all done in the bathroom
Sweet dreams honey
All right
Good night
They were careful to cover everything up
Especially after that
Incident incident
Tell me
I need to know what exactly happened at 511 kinderheim
I've said too much already
Such horrible memories
But I have to know you must tell me what happened there please
Where's my soccer ball
Where is it do you know where my soccer ball went to
Here you go I have it right here
But you got to hold off on soccer until your wounds heal all right
Batman who brought you in earlier said he was going to pick you up soon
You just get some rest until then
I don't know what really happened there
No one
The East German government at the time placed a strict gag order on the event
It all began with the mysterious death of the director of 511 kinderheim
Soon after there was a power struggle among the instructors there as to who would succeed him
The place was thrown into Anarchy it was utter chaos
They couldn't even control the children it was every man for himself
It's a miracle Johan made it out of their alive then what what exactly happened at
One one kinderheim everybody there died what all of the instructors and
We last orphan except Johan those people massacred each other
The world's not a dark place that's a lie tomorrow
Will be a good day I promise
Excuse me Mr heart money but aren't we going to go
Go home now no we're taking a little detour
Back there
No no I don't want to go
Each other come on now be a good boy
What do you mean
I told you not to let her leave with anyone until I came back didn't I did was that person was the
Child's Foster father
And let me tell you he was very much a gentleman
Unlike you obviously
Look I'm sorry but that man I wouldn't worry
That boy seemed very happy to be going with him
Dana
I'm here
They're not back yet
Hartman's Library
These photos were taking a different
But they were all shot at the same location
So what am I looking at
Yoh
Who's the man in the photo next to
Yes that's it every single one of these photographs was taken at 511 kendrheim
And it looks like they were taken over 10 years ago all of the
Instructors and every last orphan except Johan
Those people massacred each other
Could he
Another
Just hold on Peter
I'm coming
This child is blind to what I show him
Hot mom
He can't see it
You can't even comprehend what Johan saw
He's not like him
It's no good it is failed again
This boy is no Johan
Every single one of them died here did you know that
10 years ago
The instructors and the orphans all 50 people died
Johann sat here just watching it
All happen you just sat here and watched everything
You didn't lift a finger you just watched
I had to know his secret so I ask
Johan what he done and this was how he answered he
The piece of oil soap cloth Into the Fire like this
Do you get it do you know what he meant by that
I simply added a bit of fuel to the hatred born when people come together
It was easy
That's what he told me
Only 10 years old and he said that
And he did it with almost no effort at all
He was able to make
50 people kill each other without even moving a finger
It was you
It was you and your damned experiments that Twisted Johann into what he is
So you think it was us
I'm sorry
It wasn't us at all
We didn't make him that way
It's true that 511 kinderheim was an experimental project
Specifically created to transform orphans into perfect soldiers
Thinking back on it now
It really was only a little experiment
As for joh
He's no Soldier
Not at all
He was better
He was a natural born leader of men someone who was meant to stand at the very top of the world
There's no way we could have ever created such a work of art
He was beyond human from the beginning
A veritable monster
Johann made a prediction
He predicted that mankind would end up hating itself into Oblivion
And what do you think Johan's goal was
Do you want to know what he told me
He said he wanted to be the last person left in this world
He did
My poor teacher
The future is dark you must try harder to become more like
It's a pity
Why are you such a failure
Why can't you be more like your house tell me why
Don't you lay a finger on him hurt man get out of here
This is our problem it's none of your business just leave Peter come down
Sorry Dr Tim that's right
What were you planning to do once you
When you find Johann are you going to try and kill him that will be impossible
Don't look so mad
I'm going to let you in on a little secret but in exchange once you hear it you must leave immediately
We never come back
You
Search out a general wolf he's the one who first discovered Johann and his abilities
I'm sure he's still alive somewhere
He's the one who brought Johan to us he should be able to tell you something now
Going
You can come with me or stay here
But you have to decide for yourself
There's nothing to worry about if heart Mount does anything to try and stop you
Shoot him
Listen to me the choices her own nobody else can make it for
Go ahead tell the doctor there's no way you leave me now would you you can't live without me
Because you're my child teacher
Now you see how it is Doctor Tenma
You can leave
Where are you going it's all right it's okay
That's good nice and slow
Come back here my dear little detail
You really think you can live without me no time
I love you so much Peter
The world is dark
The future is bleached the time
It's not true 10 minutes told me
Tomorrow will be a good day
He's wrong he Brave
Don't be afraid
Fly
Get on the bus here and take it to coonan Street
You got that
The orphanage is there by the bus stop
When you get there I want you to give this letter to Elna Tice
She runs the orphanage
I know she may look scary but she's a nice lady
Be a good boy okay
I can't stay in this town anymore
So I guess this is goodbye
The bus will be along in a few minutes
Take care de
Keep up the soccer practice
I'm sorry
You can't come with me
Here
Dieter
I'm telling you don't come with me
I'm serious okay
You can't come with me dear