And you haven't touched a drink since is that correct
Absolutely not even a drop
Well that's very good but you have to continue to stay away from booze to give yourself the chance to start over there's
Don't worry I'm going to drink as long as I report to you once a week I don't want to incur your Wrath
Hey I just the thought of it makes me afraid what are you talking about
I always conduct myself in a very calm professional manner I was kidding I don't have time to drink anyway
I got my first big case since becoming a private investigator
Well that's very good news
Dr rifine
How would you judge this fellow
What do you mean
But using your knowledge of physiotomy I thought maybe you could tell me what kind of young man appears in this Photograph I
Don't practice physiotomy
Richard I'm afraid you're mistaking me for some kind of quack fortune teller a weirdo psychic
But you have a well acknowledged reputation
You're able to predict someone's behavioral traits from just a single glance right
That's the result of many years of accumulating information from observing patients
Then can you use all of those years of acquired wisdom to tell me if this guy looks like a con man
Con man
That's not possible
A man with a face like his couldn't fool anyone
Even if you tried some kind of con he'd be easily found out
Ah
What are the odds that he commit suicide
Absolutely none at all
People with faces like his would never kill themselves
Well I must say doctor your observation seem to be pretty convincing
Then give me quite a lot to think about
And they're based on experience
So who hired you if you don't mind my asking Hans gay Yorkshire
You're working for shoe Vault I take it you know who he is am I right yes I'm quite familiar
You with him he's the wealthy vampire of Bavaria wow that immensely Rich gentleman is my client
And the young man in the photograph is Edmund fahren
And in person it who actually passed himself off as shoe Volt's son for a while you event
He gave himself away not really Mr Shoe volt bought every detail of his deception
It wasn't your typical run of the mill scam artist you know
I myself had a lot of trouble figuring out it was a complete fraud even though some pieces of the mystery
But I'm still remain how did foreign know so much about shoe Vault missing son where do you get the information and
The only way is to go straight to the source and demand that foreign tell you
Yep
Normally I would but the boy committed suicide
They say
Come on now Martin think of it as a
For an old friend at least let me take a look at the suicide note huh the handwriting's been analyzed
How to doubt the kid wrote it himself okay look you're an outsider now Richard I can't justify bending the rules
The two kids who found the body Carl Neumann and load of Frank
Didn't they work at the same part time job as I've been far
They were just friends that's all well maybe they weren't such good friends
So how you doing anyway is it the same old grind yeah you know how it is we never have enough personnel
In fact I've had no time to rest since I took over your position so thanks a bunch Richard
Slowpoke Martin has become one of the big shots now
You don't get to call me that anymore
When you have my boss anymore so I don't have to put up with your wisecracks oh come on Martin you just don't get it to you
You have no idea how much trouble you put us through
We spent countless hours hunting down that serial killer and had him in our sight
But you were drunk as hell and killed him
Believe me it was no picnic cleaning up your mess
Now if you'll excuse me I haven't got time to waste on simple suic
I'm a very busy investigator with important criminal cases
I want to check out the crime scene
I presume everything's been preserved right
I already gave the go ahead to have it cleared out since it's been determined that there was no crime
They'll be removing all of the deceased effects sometime today
Damn it when did Slowpoke Martin become so efficient
They're supposed to be arriving anytime now to take everything away don't worry I won't be more than a couple of minutes
Most of hung is real from this pipe in the ceiling
It appears that he wrote a suicide note of this desk
Here's a paper he was in the middle of writing
The birth of tragedy process and reality
World Views on psychology far for the course for a philosophy student
These must be the materials he was using for his paper
Caesar's gallic Wars now what was he doing with this book seems out of place
Spanish or it could be Latin I can't read a word of it
This is the only passage underlined in the book
That seems OD
Up here it is room 204
YouTube better go down and get a bunch of boxes
Okay
Start with the books
It's going to take a while don't work too hard guys hey what should we do with this desk
Let's just leave it there all right
Yeah
I'd like to ask you a few questions about your former neighbor
I have nothing more to say just leave me alone hold on I'm not with the local police I'm a private investigator I don't
Who you are Mister you're bothering me and I have a paper due tomorrow but I haven't been able to get it finished because of all the questioning and Comm
Ocean going on next door all right I'll be quick
Just one question then
Would you happen to know if these two were close friends of Edmond foreign
Couldn't say I'm too busy to hang out watching everybody around here but as far as I know that guy didn't seem to have
Any friends I ever saw really I've said enough go away hold on a second just one more little thing
Ah come on now what could you translate this passage for me the part that's underlined in red ink
This is just ridiculous it's going to be your fault if I flunked my class
Can't believe I'm doing this for you I appreciate it
It says I can no longer continue
To deceive
What was the last thing you said I don't know now if you don't mind I'm busy okay
So I can know
Longer continue to deceive
Where have I heard that before
You like coming here too
Hey
We met a few days ago Johan right why don't you come all the way up
You can get a much better view if you're standing up here at the very top
Right
Hey thanks for the hand
Oh man kind of scary up here huh
It's not scary at all
Johan come down from there
Come on stop it
I'm serious you're going to fall
Do you come up here a lot
Yeah
Around this time the lights start coming on and the neighborhood looks beautiful
Family members are returning home
And the delicious smells of dinner begin filling the air
It's something I've wanted for
A long time
Really
Yeah
I guess because I never really had anything like that when I was growing up
So tell me what's your family like
Got
Not something you want to talk about
Wish I could say the same
Being bounced from one foster home to another made it important if you don't mind
I'd like to hear your story
Tell me everything you remember
This is just sloppy police work
I can no longer continue to deceive and those words are supposed to be proof he was writing a suicide note
That wasn't a suicide note
Lauren was just working on translating a Latin phrase from this book
So anyway that's my story
I wish it worked so depressing but it's all true
It's very strange but I feel like I can talk to you about almost anything in the world tell
Tell me one with thing
That rich father of yours
Are you talking about shuvald
Those tears in your eyes are you
Crying for me
Listen
You've got to do something Carl
I'm there every day tending to housekeeping chores
And I see changes in him that really have me worried
Ever since Edmund committed suicide Mr shoebald hasn't been eating very much
If he continues to starve himself he's going to end up dying too
Carl why don't you try telling him that you're his real son what have you got to lose
I want him to get to know me first and then maybe shoot all will grow to like me
If I tell him the truth now he won't believe it because he just doesn't trust me yet
He could completely reject me and think that the only reason I'm coming forward is because I'm after his money
Seems like money means everything to him
That's all he knows
So how can he understand how I feel
Well we can't just do nothing your father is in a deep depression and we have to come up with a way to get him out of it
I see you're worried about him
But don't know what to do
I have an idea that I think might work
I can no longer continue to deceive
Edmund wrote these words but they weren't meant to be a suicide note
In his dorm room I found this Latin book
Caesar's gallic Wars and he was working on translating this underlined portion from it which means his death might
Might not have been a suicide
I don't have conclusive proof it's just my gut feeling based on many years of police detective work
Have you been listening to a word I said
Anything at all
No
Not really
Why
It doesn't matter now
Don't say that it does matter you have to believe me
If I'm right that Edmund didn't commit suicide there's a possibility that your life's in danger
That dear lad
He was my son and I can't bring him back nothing matters
I've already told you the facts everything about him including his birth was completely unrelated to you
He was a fake a con I'll Grant you he wasn't a very good con
Apparently he didn't make it a habit of fool people but
That's precisely what he did to you Mr shoeval he just saved you
I must ask you to leave now Mr schewold is tired and needs to rest
I'm not going to let this investigation end yet
And my decision has nothing to do with this being my first high profile Pi job
I can feel it there is a far greater evil lurking somewhere behind this case
Sometimes in life
Even if we want to
There are things we can't do over and we can't ever make right
They're gone can't you understand that yes
Yes I understand
Only too well
This isn't over yet
Good day to you sir
A children's rights treaty
Yes
I guess you could think of it as an international rights agreement to secure and protect the civil liberties of children in countries
All around the world
That's what I'm currently working on in my Law class anyway
But my volunteer job with the orphanage is completely unrelated to that project I do this because I know I can help make
Difference in their lives
Hey guys
Can we get back to what we were discussing earlier
You said you've all went bankrupt three times in the past
Yes
After each one of them
He would just disappear
And when he'd reappear he'd start from scratch
And work to regain his fortune
Mr scheuval told me during one of our Friday reading sessions how this experience re-energized him
Gave him new Strength
Well did you ask him where he went when he disappeared each time
Yes
I think I get it your plan is to take him there am I right
Everybody has a place to go where they can feel good
For you Carl it's the rooftop of the University building where you go to watch all the city lights
Mr Co
I think there's something wrong with the bathroom sink it could be clogged
Do you mind taking a look please
There might be water dripping out of those pipes see
Loca there's nothing wrong with the sink it's working
Open up come on open this door now
Stop playing around child
Open up the store now where are you going with Mr schumold open
Hey guys that's that mission accomplished let's go aren't you going to tell me where we're going
It's a surprise
Look lady
I'm well aware that you're not the real Margo Langer
I just want information on Edmund fahren the boy who died recently
He came to see you not long ago didn't he
Foreign remind me which one he was
Which one
Apparently I'm very popular
I had two pairs of visitors each said he was shoe volt kid
Was he the blonde one
Or was he the one with the black hair
The black hair
Yeah the black haired one came with a girl isn't that funny
I still can't believe it actually show up with a girl in a place like black hair you say
Did the girl have glasses
I got photographs of them somewhere
At least two
Yeah
That's who I saw
You're positive about this
He said that he was Hans gayorkshavald's son
Are you sure this is the right spot yeah I'm absolutely certain it should be right around here
Okay to tell me the name of the surprise
We brought you out to visit Ellenburg weather
We were hoping this place would cheer you up I'm sorry
Just let me out of the car
Can you see the lake from here
Leaves here always gets so beautiful in the fall
Yeah
Very much so
Way something
Is missing what happened to the wrens why don't I hear the chirping of the Reds
Yeah I know
I'm so sorry
This place has changed
They've turned it into a construction site you can't hear them Carl
If you listen very carefully you can make them out
Little birds delightfully chirping in the trees
Minneapolis have ripened and fall into the ground
And when you turn in this direction
He will see a spectacular sight
Autumn Leaves a blazing color in the afternoon sun reflected on the
Surface of the water
Like in a huge mirror
You must see it
Don't you sir
It's hard to believe such wonders exist
I see it I can see it
Back up a second
I just remembered something
You told me that you had two pairs of visitors
And you mentioned that the black haired boy brought a girl with him
So then
That means the blonde brought someone
Oh yeah that's right he did have somebody with him
That kid kept mumbling his words I could barely understand what he was talking about
The gorgeous boy you came along with him and ended up doing the talking he was the one giving me the lowdown and hey
Truth be told
If it's good looking pal would have turned around and claimed he was shoe vald Sun I wouldn't have had any trouble believing him
Who's the other guy tell me