Help me escape
I have to order so my baby will die too
I overheard them talking
Help me
Please help me
They're all going to die if I don't want him
Hey kid where the hell are you going
Come on give me a break
Leaving that rug in this town is a complete waste that guy doesn't know what it's worth
How many times do I got to tell you stop looking at me like that
Slime ball
Yes see if I care don't come crying to me when you're starving and I'm living like a king
And if you tell anybody about this you're going to pay for you got that
Who would want to be friends with a dirty Thief like him anyway
I don't need him
I'm so hungry right now
There there don't cry I'd be good boy
Mommy's coming back soon I promise what's wrong doesn't he have a mom of course he does
What about you what are you doing sitting here alone you should go home to your mom
Wait a sec you don't have a mom to go home too
Hey I'm sorry if what I said hurt your feelings kid
It's all right
I've got 10
Eat as much as you want it's nothing special but don't feel like you got to hold back
So you were just sitting on the steps waiting for that tender guy to come back and get you huh
That little guy is waiting too
Where's his mom why did she leave where'd she go
A bunch of bad guys came and took her away
We got a saver
It's just so dangerous out there
An Asian man I met said he was going to try and help her but then he got hit by a car right in front of me
An Asian man
Wait you said 10 Mile was Japanese didn't you
But there's no way it could be the same person could
Where are they I've got to help them
On the phone
I have to say that I'm going to burn the entire town tomorrow
Please you must help me
My baby
I don't want my baby to die
How crazy was telling me
Who is it
Professor guidlitz has asked me to bring you some fruit
Thank you very much
The professor also asked me to deliver a message
General wolf will be here shortly and would like to meet with you
You mean the man in the photograph with my brother
That's right
General wolf is the person who knows Johan better than anyone
Probably even more than you do even though you're his twin sister
That's what Professor Gillett said
No don't go dying on me just yet
General volts going to be here in a minute
And I want him to see what a wonderful job I've done of capturing you alive
Well if you say
That's General to you do you understand
You should search out a general wolf he's the one who first discovered joh
Disabilities
Receiving praise from General wolf is an absolute dream come true for anyone
Excuse me sir
We've assembled our members in the arson teams ready to set fire to the Turkish quarter
Shall we continue with the plan is scheduled
Yes proceed with the itinerary
I'm looking forward to dinner with a view of a beautiful creams in the sky
Be sure everything stays on schedule otherwise my perfect dinner will be ruined
And tell them that if anything goes wrong forgiveness will come at a very high price yes sir
He won't do it
Joan isn't going to lead you
You'll never be able to convince Johann to lead your organization are you out of your mind
Doesn't share your simple-minded views on racial Purity he's not just an ignorant bigot like all of you
He's different don't you see he looks down on all Humanity
Silence
Well well what do we have here
Hey get this gentleman a drink on me I'm thinking the usual
Right away
Damn well
Not bad for a little guy that kid's going to be serious trouble when he grows up
That was disgusting
How can they drink that stuff
This is 10 ms jacket
Where are you
Everything will be all right
Just calm down
I want to help you get out of here but
I can't really do anything right now
I'm going to sneak out of here
And I want everybody in your neighborhood
I promise you oh thank you tell me what's the name of the street
Calvin Street
And what's your name
I said I don't want you to worry about anything okay
I promise you your baby is going to be just fine
I'm going to save you too
Hang in there
I forgot to ask your name
Nina
And when this is over I hope we get to know each other better
I've had so many bad things happen to me since I came to Germany
I forgot to ask you what's your baby's name
Hey I say
Are you there
What's happening
Leave her alone
Tell me is the man sitting in that chair Dr temma
And I captured him with my very own hands
So where is General wolf
General wolf is waiting
Will be taking the doctor to
No wait what do you mean but I wanted to show General both my prize catch and then finish him off myself
So what do you want me to do with this kid
I found them walking around downstairs looking for Tenma it's a friend of yours
No of course not
Metro has nothing to do with this just let him go
You don't really expect me to take a filthy Street agent like this to General wolf do you
Dispose of him you heard me finish him off go ahead of
Already he bothers me yes sir
And
One of my men my
Apologies doctor please forgive us for the rude treatment you've received
It's very important to General wolf that you be treated as his guest
Poor I say
Please
Help me
I have to warn the other so my baby will die too
We are
Friends
Isn't that
Yes we are I say
We are friends
What happened here
Professor Keith let's
Everybody's dead
We should be arriving at General Volks Mansion momentarily after 10 month
Tell me is Nina going to be there yes you can rest assured she is all so considered to be a special
List of General wolf what about the Turkish lady the baby's mom I don't know we don't know anything at all
We simply follow orders and nothing else
Burn Tonight We got to go back we have to let them know where the lady who gave me dinner last night and the baby are going to die
They're all going to die be that as it may young man I can't let you go we must take
Thank you to General Volks mansion
Think you can make it to the Turkish quarter on your own I'll be there soon but right now it's important that I go with these men
But
You can do it I know you can if you go right now you'll be able to save everyone on Calvin Street go on hurry
From here you should be able to get to the city in 30 minutes
I apologize but I had to do that I had no choice
Now I know you trusted me enough to give me back my gun and I may have just broken that trust but it didn't seem like you
You were going to stop otherwise it's fine I'm sure General wolf will be pleased to know that you don't just
Area gun around for sure and that you're not afraid to use it when needed
If you would please follow me
Where's Nina I want to see her she is here isn't she
Patience before we do anything else we must see General wolf and Professor gilitz I just need to know for myself
But she's safe
Professor gate lets his dad
And it's not just gilets all of his men have
Call soap and kill
We've disposed of the bodies
Everything's been taken care of
What about Nina when we first arrived with General Volk we search the entire Mansion she was nowhere to be
Found
Your doctor tenmark corre
Wait do I know you
You wouldn't recognize me even if you saw my face
I don't recognize me but people call me for both
That means that you you don't look anything like the picture from 10 years ago
That's because
Fear has AG
Sir please hurry can't you go any faster you crazy
I'm pushing 200 here no reason
Make it in time
I think people's names are very interest
Mysterious
All the places I've been throughout my
Everybody has referred to me
On the other hand
Every time I encounter someone new I must tell them that my name is
I wonder
How can they really know that it's me
What's there to prove that I really am
You're the one who found Johan and his sister isn't that right
I did
It's happened 12 years ago
And that's when he was sent to 511 kinderheim they were going to tournament to a super soldier weren't they
But you had bigger plans for him
That's correct
He was supposed to become
Our country safer before it's down
And now you're trying to make sure it becomes the next Adolf Hitler so that he can lead the ultranationalist isn't that your plan
At the moment I'm only part of this organization because it benefits me
I did hear that the others are trying to make
I'm into another
I think it's a stupid idea
Imagine
If a man like Hitler was able to take things as far as he did Johan could do more
Yes
I was the one who gave him the name joh
We found the twins wondering near the check border
They had managed to evade the heavy security patrol somehow
They were dead on their feet
Malnourished to almost frozen to death
When we finally arrived the two of them simply coll
They both would have perished
If we hadn't found them when we
I too know what it's like to have saved johans
When he became Consciousness I asked him a simple question
How do you feel
And do you know what his reply was
He said
You will know very soon
I know there's no more proof I really
All the people who knew me have disappeared my wife
Children siblings relatives friends
Everybody from my life
Get all of them died one by one I have you'll have to thank for that
The money I brought with me back for me is Germany is the only proof I
Good morning name is Wolf
Because of your heart I am a stranger to all you will
Oh very soon
No I understand what he
Lonely
Take a look at this doctor
Come to the abandoned warehouse of hilden and Engels company in romb
Johann was here this morning
He came here to slaughter he let's send his men yet another
The person who knew me has been murdered
I imagine Nina must have seen this and gone there to
Please kill him
Back of you
Calm down kid what are you talking about
Calvin street is going to burn tonight we have to hurry and tell everyone I can't believe this
This is amazing it must be my lucky day this is great now I can grab that rug during the fire
What it's score
How can you think that way
Keep it down you little brat if you tell him you want about this I swear out hey let me go
Listen kid I'm not just talking about all those Turks okay if any of the right Wingers find out what we know
Dead what you didn't notice all the guys with the freaking SWAT the good tattoos around here
One more question
Was a Turkish woman being held hostage in there we found a dead woman on the third floor
Based on what we saw I don't think Johan killed her
Look like it was the work of Professor gilitzman
Well General wolf do you really think you'll be able to kill Johan
I don't know
However he still has time me maybe able to
What is this supposed to mean