Outstanding yes his skills are truly unmatched the aneurysm was in such a delicate
Location
Yet he clipped it off so effortless
IND
Another perfect operation by the Peerless doctor
I was finally able to observe the genius surgeon at work for myself
No I couldn't have done it without your help
Thank you all very much
It's not midday already
Well you know that surgery did go on for almost six straight hours
We don't have any more patience today
You should go rest
Mommy where's Daddy what happened to Daddy
Wake up sleepy head
It's time to wake up after 10 minutes
Looks like rolls have been rever
It should be a princess like me who's awoken with a gentle kiss
Well I guess you did forget about our date didn't you cancel
I didn't forget
Yesterday along with his family
Mr and Mrs leebert
Appeared to be in fine spirits
Along with their fraternal twins
The family will remain in dusseldor
For an unknown period of time
We'll be following this story
Great interest
Feel like I'm still so exhausted
Hey wake up
Look at the TV they're talking about you
But seems to be recovering well after undergoing surgery
Is holding a press conference now we take you there
Mr rosenbach's diagnosis showed a ruptured aneurysm in his cranial artery the operation went smoothly
Including the successful clipping
Of the patient cerebral hemorrhage
Yes well we will certainly do whatever is necessary for him to be able to sing again
Isn't that wonderful Kenzo
He wasn't even about me
It was all about your father
But it's only because you did such a wonderful job last night working as part of Father's team
I'm sure he appreciates all your hard work since you're the one responsible for raising the hospital's reputation
No I'm the one who should be grateful
I mean after all it is thanks to your father that I'm actually able to work here in Germany
Hang in there Kenzo
If you stick with Father your future is guaranteed
It won't be long before father becomes chairman of the board
Soon after that you'll become chief of surgery
And then Chief director
Which means I'll be the director's wife
You better make me happy Kenzo cuz hardship doesn't suit me
You still want to go out on that date
I said we
Blood pressure 128 over 64
Spatul
I will now scrape the pyramus
As usual you did a magnificent job doctor Tenma
Thank you very much
But it seems to me that your talents extend beyond the or
Well you're the head of neurosurgery it's such a young age
You've become the Golden Boy for both the director and the chief of surgery
And on top of that you've even captured the heart of the director's daughter
What exactly are you trying to say doctor sorry
I'm not suggesting you've done anything wrong here after all hospitals are ruled by politics
Come on
You do realize that you're being used by the director now don't you Doctor tema
I mean take that amazing surgery you performed on that Opera Sing
He acted like he performed himself
Even holding a televised press conf
Well
If he is using you then it must mean that you are gifted
When you do become successful don't forget about Good Old Becker
I'll buy you a drink next time
May
Help you
Are you Dr Tim
I am
Give me back my husband
Me back my husband tell me just tell me what can you operate on
Who are you my husband was dying and he was brought to this emergency room first
He came in long before that stupid opera singer was here
But you made him wait to be operated on everyone says you're supposed to be the best surgeon
In this entire Hospital
I remember now I was about to start surgery on a Turkish
The construction accident yes sir you shouldn't be here right now
Get over to or one immediately these are the directors orders doctor so please hurry
Why if you had operated on him he would have survived
Bring him back to me bring it back
And then my friend and I started fighting over that dress it was the only one they had in that size can you believe that but
Don't worry about it of course it was mine in the end
Hey are you listening
Is there something wrong
You seem distracted
I checked the records
And the surgeon who operated on the Turkish man was Dr Becker
Why are you still talking about that
If you look back over the charts they clearly show what happened
Becker took too long to treat that man
I don't know but I think if I had performed the surgery on him I might have been able to save his life
Do we have to talk about this at dinner
But what does she want from me anyway
I was just following orders from the director when I performed surgery on that opera singer
I'm not responsible
Well am I
Well of course not
After all people's lives aren't created equal
Is that the house
Yes
One of the neighbors called in
How many shots were fire
Five or six sir
Who lives in this house
Well it seems
It seems to be the residents of the Levert family who recently fled here from East Germany
This is going to turn into a big mess
I'll charge in there the count of three
Street
There appears to be one Survivor a girl
A man and a woman are dead a boy is in critical condition I repeat one boy is in critical
An emergency
A bullet to the head is that boy the only patient
Yes his parents were DOA it seems to have been a robbery all right then
I'm about 5 minutes out I should be there shortly
Oh Father
Evening Dr Heineman
I'm terribly sorry for keeping your precious daughter out so late
What are you talking about Tim
It's all right Ava is your fiance isn't she
Now
What are we all doing standing here come in have some tea
So tell me something have you notified your parents in Japan about your wedding date yet yes sir
But my father runs a small Hospital back home so I'm not sure if he'll be able to take the time and come all the way out here
To Germany well wouldn't it be a good opportunity for him to take some time off and enjoy a Leisure trip overseas
We're taking care of the expenses anyway
Thank you very much sir
I'm completely indebted to you for everything you've done for me
Did I ever tell you that when you first arrived here in Germany I thought you were a high school student
And now you're the best young doctor at Eisler Memorial Hospital
By the way Kenzo I want to talk to you about your current research on cerebral vascular spasm
And subarachnoid hemorrhages
Oh good I've been creating a model of a subarachnoid hemorrhage in a dog
I'm sorry but I'm going to have to cancel the project
But sir
I have been asked to speak at the next European Medical conv
And of course that means preparing a sharp presentation
That's why I want to have you compile my manuscript
Sorry my research is very close to being completed I'm almost finished by the way Eva did I tell you what happened
Later today
No father you didn't what happened
Not suspicious group of civilians forced their way into the hospital
They were protesting the operation We performed on the opera singer
They claimed we pushed back the case of a Turkish man who'd arrived at the ER first
They got the whole thing wrong that's not how it happened that Turkish man was operated on first there was
It's not a thing wrong with our procedures
Right Tenma
Yes
Apparently they think we're some kind of Charity or something
Our priority is to progress as medical Scholars before we save lives
Don't you agree
In any case I do want you to work on my manuscript
I have great expectations of you Doctor Tenma
I appreciate that sir
Where's the patience they just brought him in
How's he holding up blood pressure 72/50 his pulse
At 1:37 the bullet entered through his forehead we need x-rays immediately yes doctor
Oh doctor Tenma
Who's this she's the twin sister of the little boy we just brought in
Any injuries no but she seems to sustained a serious psychological shock
Yes what is it
The boys x-rays in CT scans are ready
I understand I'll be there shortly
It entered the front of the head
Then stopped deep in the center of the brain yes
This one is definitely going to be difficult
The bullet is touching the left side of the middle cerebral artery
Here
Will you look at that
Doctor Tenma is absolutely right
This one won't be easy
If you jostle the bullet even the slightest bit man they artery could rupture and cause a massive hemorrhage
Hey sorry I'm late Dr Becker you're supposed to be on duty I
Don't understand how you could be so late
Will do a full frontal craniotomy and remove the bone fragments and contaminated brain matter
Then we'll remove the bullet very carefully
And lastly repair the arterial wall
But with a little hard work and some luck I'm certain that we can pull it off
Blood pressure 120 over
Pulse 92
He's looking good
The anesthesia is taking effect
Oh there you are doctor yes
You shouldn't be here
You're needed in operating room 1 immediately
It's critically urgent mayor rudiger has suffered a cerebral blood clot
He's being transported here by helicopter
They're scheduled to arrive in 10 minutes then
I think the best thing is to contact Dr Boyer there's a chance his carotid artery is blocked
If that's the case we want you to operate on him
But sir I can't do that I was just about to begin surgery on that young boy yeah
It's an order from the director
Hello this is Tenma
Hello tema
Take care of the mayor will you
I've contacted Dr Eisen and Dr Boyer
It'll be good to have that extra
Support in case you need it
But Dr heinemann I was about to start another operation right now
Just let Dr Becker take over that one
With all due respect sir the patient I'm about to operate on has a bullet up against his left middle cerebral
Ordering it could turn into a very complex surgery
But I am confident I can save him director
So I'm going to let Dr boy or take care of
I'm expecting you to do everything in your power to save the mayor
You need to understand something very important in the next review of medical facilities the mayor has promised our
Spindle a very generous increase in funds
We can't have him die just yet
Do you understand
I'm expecting you will do this
I'm counting on you Doctor Tenma
Yes sir
The mayor has just arrived on the heliport doctor
After the CT scans are done do the angiogram
We need to confirm where the arteries blocked
About time to get ready Dr timma
Yeah we're all counting on those brilliant skills of yours
Apparently they think we're some kind of Charity or something
Our priority is to progress as medical Scholars before we save lives
10 my don't you agree but what does she want from me anyway I was just following orders from the
I'm not responsible
Well am I after all people's lives aren't created equal
Bring it back if you had operated on him you wouldn't Sur
Well
Is something the matter doctor Tenma
I have
I have a surgery to perform in the other room
Hey where are you going Dr tema
But this is an order from the director
Reading room on my way
Hang in there kid I'll save you
No matter what